<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4639</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dean Cain (yes, from the crappy Superman TV show) once held the single season interception record for 12 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard about this on a podcast, looked it up.  [Link](http://articles.orlandosentinel.com/2002-11-17/news/0211150589_1_superman-cain-interception) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creative ways to roll up long sleeve shirts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 16:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a friend of mine has [this shirt, which has dark brown lining under the cuffs](http://imgur.com/a/ntWkx).  We were trying to think of a way to roll the sleeves so that he could have the dark brown exposed when/if he rolls up his sleeves further up his arm, like up past the elbow. 

All we could really come up with is bunching up the shirt, but that looks pretty sloppy.  And all of the conventional ways to roll up a sleeve would end up hiding the dark brown part. 

So, any creative ways to keep the brown exposed while making a crisp/clean sleeve roll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Books' "Suggestions for you" is pretty bad. Anyone know of ways to improve it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded one damn comic book, and now ~60% of the suggestions are comics. I tried going through and gave high ratings to a lot of my favorite authors' books, but it only suggests other books by those authors instead of similar writers/novels/etc.  (Sadly, the comic suggestions I don't care about show a wider array of choices.)

Has anyone found a way to improve the suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She developed a habit of licking my fingertips. Eventually I realized she did that every time I had a smoke. I have created a monster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Upload   Update past rev carto maps on the wiki </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some carto uploads are missing.  Some don't have a link in the wiki.  pls to update generous mcp gods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I will now sell 5 copies of The Three EP's by the Beta Band" - Rob Gordon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 17:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Impostor! Trying to blend with the locals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 17:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to find an old Steve Aoki mix... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 22:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This mix would be roughly....6 years old? It was a lot of house/techno tracks. The second to last track in the mix (maybe third to last?) was a semi-remix of Kids by MGMT.

My hard-drive died recently and I lost the mix and I'm having no luck finding it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure this is the right place... trying to find a mix by Steve Aoki. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 22:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IPA, IPA, IPA, IPA, Stout, IPA, IPA, IPA...apparently this trend is taking over the nation. CAN I BUY A FUCKING NON-IPA BEER PLEASE?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be wary AFKing in Rose. You might end up with a hat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 04:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rose is down with the legalization movement. Check the "Tested by:" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 06:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See - "Tested by:" Rose City down with the edibles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 06:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Island names! Referring to them by direction is annoying/confusing. So come up with names! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 13:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the personal island location map [here](http://i.imgur.com/lzggjkT.png) - we have a number of islands.  They could use names that we refer to instead of "you know that NW island that's kind big bug not that big?"   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone gotten *any* essence of flight drops yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 01:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We set up a dark room grinder already to try to get essence of flight.  Not a single drop yet, with maybe close to ~1k mobs killed between the lot of us (plus generic killing in overworld, not just in the dark room).  

Does it only drop from a certain kind of mob like bats?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Strip mine beneath the main island is being converted to a dark room grinder for essence of flight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 10:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a heads up to anyone going down there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the early 2000s, I was part of a hiphop-ish jamband. Basically a dozen of us just kinda fucked around live. Here's a track, will share more if you want. (This was entirely live/improvised.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 05:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nostalgia moment - anyone remember who built this small town in Rev 13? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 05:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Image](http://i.imgur.com/htTOaFv.jpg)

It was made mostly of birch and mostly built into the hillsides.  So the SW in this screenshot is Faraway by katiewillis.  I just always loved this little town and was wondering if anyone remembered who made it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rev18 Plans! (Sorry for the late info) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Rosarians! Rev18 is coming, so here are some of the plans we've discussed.

**Biggest Changes**

1) We won't be requiring builds on the planning server first next rev, except for large-scale things like farms/townhall/etc.

2) Speaking of townhall - design for the townhall is open for anyone to give a go at. Whether you're new to Rose or an old hat, if you think you can make a nice townhall build, head on over to planning and give it a go! (Note: townhall should include both storage as well as room for rail stations.  Possibly incorporate a water elevator/ladder/something to get to sky limit for flying.) 

**Other Changes**

1) No terraforming.  We're building with the land again.  Edit: If you want to terraform your own plot you're welcome to.

2) The general theme is modern, eco-friendly. However, it's likely we'll have an "olde time" district for those who like building in that style.  

3) Similar to the past, the first few days of the rev will be **no personal builds** until we get the town center and some roads marked out.  Mayors will set up chests the first few days for storing your personal goodies. 

4) **Portals!** We will be hunting for a portal again.  This includes end portals, but preferably Nether portals.  We'll be striking South primarily at the start of rev.  If everything fails and we can't find a portal, then 0,1000 will be the location of Rose.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's commonly stated that Hitler's invasion of Russia was a big mistake leading to his undoing. Why aren't the German operations in Africa considered the bigger mistake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 04:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leavers because of quest fails? Form a truce to cut down trees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a game where, as a 5 stack, one in the other team DCed. Then 3 others did. So we negotiated a truce with the last player - stick around to the end, we won't push, just everyone cut trees. We all had a quelling/talon/Buffy and spent a long time killing trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocketeers who use the Steam Controller - do your bindings randomly change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rocket League on PC here, using a Steam Controller.  About 50% of the times I launch the game, my bindings are completely screwed up.  When I look at the options, all of the buttons look how they should.  But when I click, B for instance (which is what my boost should be), it instead brings up an option to leave the match/etc.  My right trigger, normally just "go forward" is instead boost.

And, again, if I go to the control settings in game, my controls appear there correctly.  But in game, they don't.  

Sometimes I have to restart Steam entirely just to get my settings to bind.  

But again about 50% of the time I launch the game, my controller bindings are for some reason completely off, even though in the options menu they all look correct.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fans of Neal Stephenson - what the hell was up with Seveneves? Why did it seem so off? (Spoilers I suppose?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished reading it for a second time.  I've read most of his novels multiple times, but this second read was more along the lines of, "maybe I missed something the first time...?"

But it was still mostly disappointing.  In past novels he tended to teach the reader something while doing so in a very entertaining way.  The action tended to be a slow build towards a big payoff, or possibly slow/big/slow/big.  

But Seveneves, when it came to the "teaching" elements, was just dry and boring.  Especially if you'd already read Anathem, the enormous amount of time spent explaining Delta Vee's was just tedious.  There were none of the humorous elements that might make them interesting.  

The "action" parts were just plain stale.  The build up to Cleft was kind of intense...in parts...when it didn't divulge into yet another science lecture about Delta Vee's that took up most of a chapter.  Edit: Also I can't recall a single other of his novels that made such a blatant, obvious plot point as "the gun was missing from the holster" and the former president using it to such terrible effect later.  When I first read the gun was missing from the holster I immediately thought, "Well that will come up again later to a shitty ending," and sure enough it did.  I don't recall any other examples of Stephenson doing such a shitty job of foreshadowing.

And the ending felt so very rushed.  Like his publisher put a page limit on the book so he had to hurry it.  The first time I read the book was as an eBook, and so it's a little harder to keep track of the page count/how far into the book you are.  "EPILOGUE" suddenly appeared on my screen and I was in shock.  I just could not believe that was really how that entire build up ended in a very short time.  

I have friends and family who also love Stephenson.  When they asked my opinion about Seveneves, all I could tell them was, "It was good, I guess.  But it wasn't a Neal Stephenson book."

Any theories about this, or explanations of why I didn't get it are appreciated.  Because I feel like maybe I'm missing something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 charges for 10 minutes of special river? Are you serious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 02:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little shocked there isn't a post calling out how bullshit this is yet.  Considering how high level you have to get for any of them, let alone the "best" of them - 100 fucking minutes?  That's all?  

When I saw it was 10 charges, at first I thought, "okay, I guess that's...fair? Ish?"  But each charge only lasts 10 minutes.

Fuck. This. Bullshit.  If there was at least a way to refresh the charges outside of the TIComp, fine.  But 2500 levels to get blood river for all of 100 minutes?  

You can only get [547 levels for free](https://www.reddit.com/r/DotA2/comments/4jr6hs/want_to_know_how_many_levels_you_can_get_for_free/) meaning you have to spend almost $900 just to get **100 minutes** of blood river?! $9 for 1 minute worth?! 

Fuck. You. Valve.  Fix this stupid shit.  Remove the counter, or remove the timer.  **At least!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazil to create a sex theme park. Attractions include theter with vibrating seats, bumper cars shaped like genetalia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AR players of /r/dota2/ - do you frequently random the same hero over and over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 05:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just randomed Elder Titan.  Again.  I checked my dotabuff stats.  Out of my 13 games playing Elder Titan, 7 are from All Random.  3 of the games are All Pick, and I am 100% certain that each of those 3 times were choosing random, because I fucking hate Elder Titan and would never choose him purposely. (The rest are Single Draft, where I probably picked him just because AR made me "familiar" with him.) 

That brings the total to 10/13 randoms.  

I have randomed Invoker once.  Earth Spirit twice.  TA twice.  Wyvern once.  Tusk twice.  (I'm going backwards from my least played heroes.)  Chen twice, Morph 4x, Lycan 3 times...

It's become something of a joke with the people I play with.  "Oh you played all random last night? So how did you like Elder Titan?"  

Anyway, just wondering if other frequent AR players have similar experiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for low-ish cost, low maintenance, to cover a pretty large area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 04:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I live in a duplex, with my friend living next door.  Rent is pretty low here, but part of the reason for that is we're supposed to keep the "yards" weed free.  So every late Spring/Summer, we have to go out and do a lot of work removing all the weeds.  

[Here are two pictures of the total area we need to cover](http://imgur.com/a/zwpgT)

So I'm wondering if there are attractive, low maintenance (there are no sprinklers, and the goal is to reduce the work needed) ways to fill in these areas to prevent future weed growth/removal.  

We're not against some amount of work setting it up, like doing some gravel areas or something.  But preferably it would be some sort of low, attractive ground cover plant.

Notes about conditions/weather - This is in Central Oregon.  It's a "high desert."  So it's pretty arid, with snows/freezing temperatures in the winter.  It's typically sunny, I think we average something like 300 days of sun per year.  And as you may or may not be able to tell from the pictures, shade is fairly minimal.  (More shade in the second picture, not so much in the first.)

Any suggestions would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mirana's Aghs upgrade needs a toggle. Running through the jungle is just pulling constant waves of neutrals behind you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 03:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right click starfall - passive is on/off.  Now you can time it properly without having the entire jungle rampage after you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> psyonix pls, y u no hef button to make car honkyhonk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 19:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beep s wanted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a friend working at my ISP generates interesting info. For instance, get an almost instant warning re: Silicon Valley, but no problem with The Leftovers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 05:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never thought I'd be saying this, let alone complain about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sky Map/Accelerometor is broken? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend lives next door, also has a 6p, just duplicated the problem on his phone too.

When looking at the sky map app, turning horizontally does nothing.  I can rotate 360 degrees and get the same image the entire time.  

Is this app borked? Or is my phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Log Cabin - Munchkins (Full album in link) - 20 years later, still one of my favorite hiphop albums all time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 03:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a very, very casual fan of the NBA/frequent listener of sports radio - WTF was this bullshit last night for Kobe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 07:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In my semi-drunken state, the fact that Kunkka has the only animation that indicates when a skill is off of cooldown seems kinda lame. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 06:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when DotA2 was first coming out, and there was a huge debate about, if you click an enemy, should you be able to see their mana pool or not.  Most people fell on the side of, tldr, "that too easily gives you too much information, no you shouldn't see that."

Maybe there's someone I'm not thinking of atm, but it seems like Kunkka is the *only* hero that has an obvious way to tell if a skill is off of cooldown or not.  And to me that seems similar to the manapool debate - it gives the enemy way too much information way too easily.  

There are a lot of abilities which have special animations *when they're active.*  But to me it seems like an animation of when it's active versus when it's off cooldown is a big difference.  I can think of a lot of skills where, if there was an obvious animation telling you if it's on cooldown or not, would change how you play. 

Imagine if Juggernaut had, say, glowing boots when his spin was available.  Wouldn't that change how you played against him?  

Edit: Jakiro and Bounty Hunter also apparently have these tells.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW another man asks me if I spell my name "Danny with a Y or with an I?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Safe with Nikki Glaser is the result of when guys constantly tell a hot girl "you're so funny" just because they want a blowjob. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 08:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not funny.  At all.  But it gets on TV because "hey here's a hot girl talking about sex." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK in Oregon (and possibly other states) there is a way to be reimbursed from the state for random crimes/damages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 03:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 10 years ago, a friend was letting me short-term borrow his car, as I had just moved back to the US.  Halloween came along and on November 1, I woke up to find that someone had thrown a pumpkin through the windshield of my/his car.  

This was obviously not a crime that had a chance of being solved.  My friend whose car it was?  He was a lawyer.  He told me, hey just go down to the courthouse, ask for these forms, they'll reimburse the cost of a new windshield.  

Lo and behold, it worked.  It took awhile, I think they wanted to give some window of time to attempt to catch the perpetrator?  But a few months later, I was compensated for the cost of replacing the windshield.  

[This is the Oregon-specific link](http://www.doj.state.or.us/victims/compensation.shtml) which mostly just lists *very* serious crimes.  But, at least in my one experience, they also support small-scale, non-violent crimes.  (And the way my friend so casually suggested I do that, it seems like he thought it wouldn't be a problem, so probably applies to other similar petty crimes.)

Edit: Oh a few other important points, possibly/probably also Oregon-specific : 

1) You had to have a police report.  I called the cops, they came and checked it out, I had a report.  You can't just fill out the forms for some theft that wasn't investigated.  

2) You had to file your claim within a certain amount of time, I believe 3 months was the window? So you couldn't fill out the forms, "yeah my bike was stolen last year..."

3) As hinted at but I didn't clearly state - you needed a receipt/some other form of proof of cost of reimbursement.  I paid out of pocket for the repair, included the receipt, was reimbursed.  So, unfortunately, if a particular object was a cheap item with high sentimental value, that won't come into play; just the cost to repair/replace. (note:this may vary depending on the seriousness of the crime; this was only my experience with such a cheap/petty crime.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is the proper time to add crushed red pepper to an oven baked pizza? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 05:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else had a lot of payment issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 07:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been signed up with Project Fi for 4 months, and already on two separate occasions I've had to have 1+ hour discussions with customer service to get them resolved

First time - I signed up with a certain debit card, which I also set as my auto-payment card.  Month 2 - Payment declined.  What?  After 45+ mins on the phone, finally figured out that for, whatever reason, they were using credit card details from 5+ years ago, from a card that's been inactive about since then.

Why? Why use a card that I didn't use to sign up, and a card I didn't set up for autopayment?

Tonight - two different 45 min calls.  Received notification my payment didn't go through.  I'd recently moved, updated my payment address - but, didn't go through.  45 mins on the phone, "sorry I can't help you, can you wait for a supervisor?" "can they call me back?" "sure!" ~10mins later receive a call back, I hear literally nothing but "boop boop (insert random computer noises here)" for 5 mins before hanging up.  

Now on the phone for another 30 mins.  Person just transferred me to yet another wait signal.

___

Finally got it resolved. Total call times (just tonight) - 49 mins, 47 mins, 44 mins, 14 mins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An easy fix to prevent Peruvians from playing on USW servers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 05:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are TV execs so out of tune with the on-demand/not 9-5 work hours generation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 07:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every 6 months or so I house-sit for my parents and take care of their dog while they go on vacation, and those are the only times I have to deal with cable tv. 

My job involves weird hours. I'm pretty sure I'm not the only one. During the day, nothing is on, ever. Price is Right is cool I guess, and then nada.  Then maybe at 6-7 PM something good comes on.  Sometimes. And after 9 PM, nothing again.

I'm currently watching Daredevil season 2 premiere because, at 11 pm on a Friday night, with ~600 channels, there is nothing at all worth watching. 

The current "let's cram everything into a 7-9 PM timeslot on certain weekdays" pretty much just encourages everyone to DVR those shows and save them for a more convenient time - allowing them to skip ads and reduce revenue. 

If there was something, **anything** on TV right now I'd be watching it, and its ads, and generating revenue. But there's nothing, and I'm watching Netflix instead. The number of times this comes up when I'm reduced to cable tv is ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I played Skyrim, but haven't played any other Bethesda games. After seeing all the hate, I wanted to enjoy this game. But I can't enjoy it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 06:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If pressure creates heat, why can I not stay warm in the winter by not paying my bills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 02:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 overdraft notices and I still have to wear thermals! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emergency!...maybe? Friend didn't pot a cactus properly. Over-saturated soil. Trying to save it's life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 04:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he placed a ~4" diameter cactus (looks like maybe a grusonia?) in a GIANT pot with no hole in the bottom for letting out water.  Then he moved away and left it behind.  It's been raining/snowing/shitty here for ~5 months.  The "soil" it was in before is basically 99% water at this point.  

I just repotted it, with some gravel at the bottom to help drainage, the pot has a proper hole in the bottom for excess water.  But, I was lacking decent new soil and had to re-use a lot of the original over-saturated soil.  

Is there a good way to dry out this soil?  I even put a lot of paper towels on top to try to dry it out.  And it's sitting by my heater.  

If I place it in the oven at the lowest setting (200 F) for awhile to help dry the soil, will that help? Maybe if I leave the oven door open and the cactus sitting on the door?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm pretty sure that reddit is hoping to encourage gold purchases in order to block subs like /r/SandersforPresident, /r/The_Donald, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 03:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's March and I still have a goddamn stupid Christmas song stuck in my head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 03:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March 19 Movie Night Nominations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 08:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We kinda tailed off at the end of last movie night and didn't come to a decision, so, another nomination thread! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rewatching Ep1, thought something was worth pointing out - The name of the Alliance Cruiser they run into is the I.A.V "Dortmunder" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 08:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why I think this is worth pointing out...

There is a long series of novels by Donald E Westlake, where the main character is named John Dortmunder. Why I think that *maybe* the name of this cruiser is related - 

1) Kinda a weird name to randomly choose.  Google "dortmunder" and mostly you get weird import/export businesses or foreign beer companies.  

2) But, if you've read the Dortmunder series, you might recognize the main character is very similar to Mal. He's a robber by trade, and frequently finds himself in a unique position to steal something valuable.  BUT, he is very much a "violence as a last resort" kind of person, and always basically kinda broke despite his last job.  And his plan often looks like it's failing, but works out in the end.  

If you read some of the Dortmunder novels, you'd probably see how my explanation doesn't do justice.  Mal is basically a futuristic-version of Dortmunder.  

I'm convinced that naming the ship "Dortmunder" wasn't an accident/random thing.  And these novels, while they're no War   Peace or whatever, are still entertaining "popcorn" novels - you don't need to think too much, they're page turners, but still keeps you interested.

If anyone here has read any of the Dortmunder novels...am I right in thinking this?  And for the people who have not read any of the Dortmunder novels, if you're looking for a quick/easy/entertaining read, check them out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of all the balances asked for by the community, haven't really seen this one. Shown stats for supports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 06:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supports get no love really.  Everyone likes to say in chat/comments how supports are great, but in-game, it's all about the carry.

When you look at the official stats of a user, it's gpm, xpm, last hits, aegis's, triple kills, etc...all stuff that favors the carry players. 

If we want support for our supports, why not show some other stats?  Wards per minute would be much higher valued than total wards placed, for instance.  (Since some people can play "support", buy all the wards possible in the last few minutes, and come out with a good "wards placed average.") Enemy wards destroyed, also good.  Tangoes/pots/clarities used on other people, also good. Total mana refreshed (through mana boots), total hp refreshed (through spells/mek), also good.

Why no public/visible stats for things like that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Literally unplayable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> heard.nu (EP) - music from the nerd.nu community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 06:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) I've been trying to keep this project hush-hush/surprise.  So the people in here are only the  people I've really seen talk about making music in chat.  Which is also probably why the track list isn't very big... :(

2) If you want to get added to this playlist, just message me with your own stuff!

_________________

And without further ado - 

[heard.nu](https://soundcloud.com/heard-nu/sets/heard-nu-1)

Track 1 - Groove90  (djdanlib)

Track 2 - The Listening Party - Low (downgrooving is a member)

Track 3 - Dan - Third Sun  (dnynumberone)

Track 4 - Everything Is Green - In Your Room (Weed_Pancakes)

Edit:

Track 5 - Odd One - Loose Yourself (Oddities) [Youtube Profile](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCbzNq-HeGcdf68BdUYb5lfw)

Track 6 - hexagonlux - Here and Now (Twoist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie Night - final choices up for vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 04:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like we've got all the suggestions for this week.  So I'm going to assume dictatorial control and say the following suggestions are the best choices.  

Vote for which of the following movies you prefer!

And viewing time will be Saturday night 6pm/7pm Eastern time.

______________

**The Shining** (1980) -- Drama, horror 8,4/10 -- http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0081505/?ref_=nm_knf_t2 (A classic! Can't watch too many times.)

**12 Angry Men** (Drama) 8.9/10 IMDB - http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0050083/?ref_=nv_sr_1

**Leon - The Professional** - Action/Drama/Foreign-but-not-foreign - 8.6/10 IMDB - Natalie Portman's first big role, Jean Reno being awesome. A mercenary/hitman befriends a young girl and takes her into his protection. I haven't seen this in a few years and could definitely watch it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rose City movie night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 06:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since pez is such a big lazy jerk and hasn't posted yet, I will!

We had our first Rose City movie night on Sunday, yay!  But it wasn't exactly advertised very well and was at a semi-inconvenient time, boo!

So this is the post for the second movie night.  What I suggest is the following - 

Make a comment below suggesting 3 movies - 

1) Give each movie a (say) 3 word description of it, and the IMDB rating.  Just naming random movies off the top of my head, something like - 

Cube - Scifi/Suspense/Indie [7.3]  
Saving Private Ryan - Action/Gritty/Big Budget [8.6]  
Brain Donors - Wacky/Comedy/Inane [7.1]  

And if there's a particular movie you feel strongly about, go ahead and say why you think it would be good!

2) *Maybe* stay away from big-budget popular movies since it's likely we've all watched them a lot/recently?  You know...no Jurassic Park or Jurassic World.  But then again, maybe we all watched Jurassic World when it first hit theaters and it might be worth watching again as a group?  So not set in stone.

3) Also, changing the movie night time to Saturday.  What time Saturday would be good to determine, since we have a lot of timezones to cover.  It seems like Zomise is the furthest-outlying timezone, so Zom what time would be best for starting a movie for you on a Saturday night? (My guess is, at the latest starting point, 6 pm eastern?  Which would be 1 am Helsinki time?)

Finally, this sub is part of the big mcpublic multi reddit thread thing, and other non-rose people might see this.  If you guys felt like joining in, feel free to do so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you want a series of novels (very) similar to the expanse - The Agent Cormac series by Neal Asher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was inspired by a reply in another thread.  [Here is Neal Asher's wikipedia with a list of the Agent Cormac novels](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neal_Asher)

The Agent Cormac series is **very** similar to The Expanse.  To the point where I thought James SA Corey was a pseudonym for Neal Asher. I finished the Agent Cormac series in 2008, so when I found The Expanse I immediately fell in love with it because I loved Cormac so much. 

They are very action/military oriented.  They're set a bit further in the future, where travelling between solar systems is a thing. And all the tech that implies.  

They aren't incredibly deep, I refer to this kind of writing as "popcorn novels" - something you don't have to think **too** much about, but definite page turners.  


____________

If you're curious about Neal Asher and want to know about his other series, I've also read the Spatterjay series which is also a pretty similar writing style to the Expanse. And I started on The Owner Trilogy but didn't get very far, because at that point I'd binged on like 6 books in a row and needed a break.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I'm muted for asking how I broke a rule that doesn't exist? (Sorry but, you know, since I'm muted apparently this is the only way I can ask?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 09:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I always have to click back twice after opening a youtube link? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 06:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With a bug report being the top post atm, thought I'd add my own. A keybinding triggers even though no keybinding exists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 18:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off - I use weird, non-standard keybindings. It was how I first set up DotA when I first started playing a decade ago, and it's way too late to change now. 

My keybindings for my item use are - space/w/e/r/t/y.  So column 1, row 2 is bound to R. 

In 3rd party voice clients (mumble, team speak, etc) I use V as my push to talk key. 

For some reason, pushing V (to push to talk in mumble) activates my R item. 

I've tried unbinding that key, changing the binding then changing it back, nothing seems to fix this issue. 

[Screenshots of my weird keybinding setup / proof that no V keybinding exists](http://imgur.com/a/BypUp)

It's been incredibly annoying that I constantly have to make sure a passive item remains in that item slot so I don't accidentally use it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I floated this idea before, it seems even more relevant than ever - let's release a Rose City Album. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 08:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I brought this idea up a few revs ago.  After a few private conversations with certain members...we apparently have a LOT of talent in Rose.  I don't want to doxx, so I'll just say the following - 

1 of us is about to release an album with the backing of a label.

1 of us has a band that is **very** well produced from what I've heard on soundcloud.

1 of us is forming a startup/web2.0 company specifically trying to find those kinds of people. 

1 of us has spent a lot of time producing music on their own.

Actually, check that, 2-3 (or 4 or 5 or 6) of us have done that?

I don't mean we have to take the time/effort to press CD's or whatever.  I'm really talking mostly about a nerd.nu effort.  

But hey why not? From all the private message conversations and whatnot, we seem to have a very talented group of folks here.  

Let's create a soundcloud group and "release an album" that way? Just seems like a fun diversion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you hide posts from a subreddit (x) number of times, posts from that sub become permanently hidden for you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tired of all the election crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit needs an "apolitical" mode during US presidential cycles to hide the spam that is now /r/all/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 07:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you tired of high lantern taxes? Long AFK times? A lack of fish? Rose Guardian Grinder is now open (and ugly) and 100% public. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 16:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still pretty WIP, but wanted it functional first. Follow the South Carbon road to 150, 1285 and [you'll find a wee derp island.](http://i.imgur.com/14Sz1mx.png)  [On the island is the entrance.](http://i.imgur.com/hD6hcFL.png)  And [follow the stairs down](http://i.imgur.com/lPWHVVU.png) and you'll find the collection point.  

There are two double chests for collection.  ATM it seems guardian grinders are in high demand, so if you're there at the same time as someone else, **please** just take from one of the chests and not both.  But if you're there alone, then have at it!

(Beautification efforts are in progress)

Oh also there's one small part where guardians might spawn outside the grinder, so if you wanted to help fix that, bring a lot of gravel.

Edit: Oh and thank yous go out to - pez, zomise, flumper, f0rtynuggets, nyxie, aghe, icedman, (insert name I may have potentially forgotten). And a **huge** thank you to kahbn for allowing us to park the elder guardian near him and lots of help with the construction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rose City has a Trello now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 17:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all still pretty new to this and getting used to it. But it seems like a very useful tool for organizing projects such as building Rose.

The trello is private so not anyone can join.  Which means if you want to join, you need an invite (at least, I think so?)

You do need a Trello user account, so head over to https://trello.com/ and create an account.  Once you have that, either leave a message here or contact a mayor in game with your trello username and we'll send the invite to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm pretty sure Quentin Tarantino just wants to get the world record for being the modern day white guy who can get away with saying/writing the N-word the most. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 08:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rev 17 Day 3 Info Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 16:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've found a lovely place to settle, huzzah!

So plans going forward - 

1) We have 3 (kinda 4) unique biomes. Spruce/taiga, extreme mountain, dark oak forest, and a wee bit of swamp. When we start developing the city, each of these biomes should have a semi-unique style and use the materials native to that region. Spruce taiga uses spruce, dark oak uses dark oak, swamp could use normal oak OR acacia.  The mountains are a bit tricky in this regard. It could be neat if people living there carved into the mountain and lived inside it, trying to leave as much of the natural mountain exterior intact as possible. (This of course leads to issues of how large an area in the mountain you can take up. We'll pretty much leave this to your discretion, just try not to claim the whole thing :P )  And adding fortress-like developments on top of the mountain works as well.

2) Town builds - We obviously need a lot of these things soon.  Proper veggie farms, animal storage, stables for horses.  If someone has a good understanding of how the new iron golem spawner system works and a good design, an iron farm would be good too. And of course all the other fun stuff like spleef, pvp arenas, etc. **Please work on these on the planning server first.  If you don't have planning server info, ask a mayor for the info, since they also have to whitelist you.**

3) We like a lot of the topography of this area and would like to keep as much intact as possible. Keep this in mind when planning any town builds. If you need help, a mayor (or other players) could help copy the terrain to planning so your build can work with the terrain better. We're not saying it has to be 100% kept natural, just keep a light touch. 

If you have further suggestions about, well, anything, leave a comment below :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rev17 - Last info post before the new rev. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 20:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) We aren't really going to be portal hunting. If we find one, neat. But we're looking primarily for biomes we like.  Specifically, we're kind of hoping to build on a border of 3 biomes. For instance [this spot on the current map which is a combination of plains, snow, and jungle](http://nerd.nu/maps/pve/live/?worldname=world mapname=flat zoom=4 x=-523 y=64 z=1783) - but probably/hopefully more like savannah/mesa/plains (mesa would be great for clay/sand needs early rev). 

2) I guess we're going South again? We haven't really discussed it that much. I'd be fine with going a different direction (North is already "claimed" by a few towns). But if we felt like going West or Southwest or something, I'm fine with that personally.

3) Planning server, people! If you have the server info, /mvtp plan17 to warp to rev17 planning. 

4) We are doing a combination of megabuild, while also having a more conventional city on the ground. The megabuild is going to be a very large spiral with central tower, with houses "hanging" off of the spiral.  On planning, you can see ideas at 2000,2000. 

The road designs on the ground are located at -50,50.

See you all later today hopefully! (Assuming I can get my computer working again...)

Edit: Some additional info - 

Examples of the megabuild.  [Here is the spiral in an 80% completed state](http://i.imgur.com/QAWwUv2.jpg)

An example of 1 type of house that can be built on it - [Embedded into the spiral and hanging out](http://i.imgur.com/KFlfEG3.jpg) - if doing this style it will be encouraged to develop the bottom of the spiral [in an organic kind of way like this](http://i.imgur.com/zXX137S.png).  
There is also the option to build a road to a [floating island](http://i.imgur.com/nPTpIgh.png) house, which you could also embellish with [more small floating islands nearby](http://i.imgur.com/ogizW3G.png).

Also part of why we want multiple biomes is so that the town on the ground can have multiple themes. So pretend we have mesa, plains, and mountains.  The plains part of the town might be where people who want to build in a Hobbit-y style can build, the mountains would be where people who want to build old medieval style can build, and the mesa can be modern style builds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [-1125,1950] Scorpii - Best Personal Build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 17:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering it was 100% built by just Scorpii, his build is pretty damn impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel about Zomise's PVP arena built for ghrey during nightoak. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 09:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, I would gladly pay for expansions/DLC/whatever for the Stick of Truth [Spoilers I guess] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 07:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I finished the game, I felt very...incomplete. I hadn't found all the kindergartners, I hadn't found all the chinpokomon, I hadn't made friends with everyone in town.  

When I play "semi-open" world games like this (Skyrim etc) I tend to basically do any quest that's nearby regardless of whether it follows the main quest or not. And I try to level up every single thing before completing.

I finished the game with still a lot of level ups remaining on my character, tons of money, etc etc. 

While I found the game entertaining one go around, it wasn't really fun enough to do multiple go-throughs. I could see most of it was predetermined regardless of how you leveled, what clan you joined, and so on.

Then I saw things like the crabpeople levels were removed, also vampire kids, also hippy fights.  

If the main storyline had a little more variation, if some of those missing levels were added, if it was a little harder to reach the end.  I would gladly pay again for those features, and play through the game again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the 10+ years of stadium fuckery, why hasn't this idea been pushed by public/media - convince the Spanos family to sell 50% of the team. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 08:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I can agree the notion seems silly on its face. Here's why I think it's a decent notion.

1) According to Forbes, the Spanos family is worth [$1.69 billion](http://www.forbes.com/profile/alexander-spanos/) of which [$1.525 billion](http://www.forbes.com/teams/san-diego-chargers/) is from the Chargers.  90% of their valuation is due to the Chargers alone.

2) Sell 50% of the team. Suddenly, the Spanos family has ~$750mil in liquid assets that they can invest in other things, that would potentially earn them much more money over the long term than a 100% ownership of a franchise. Hell, even throwing that in a basic money market fund would probably earn them more per year than having a 100% ownership of the Chargers returns. (Edit: I know this makes it sound like "well then why would someone buy half the team"; NFL ownership is an exclusive "club" and with a new stadium and decent marketing/concessions/etc, returns on investment could be much higher than at Quallcom.)

3) The NFL is an obvious "we want to get into that club" business.  Selling 50% of the team would likely attract a large variety of investors. 

4) The main reason the Spanos family can't personally fund a new stadium in SD is largely because 90% of their worth is tied to the Chargers. If they want to build a $1.5bn stadium, they'd have to sell 100% of the Chargers in order to build a stadium for the Chargers. That obviously doesn't work.

**Pros** - The Spanos family has liquidity to invest in other areas; they get a potential owner who could (primarily, with some city money) self-finance a stadium; the Chargers stay in San Diego.

**Cons** - They lose some control over operations; ego.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rose City Rev17 plans/ideas/etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 09:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mayors recently had a meeting, and we tossed around some ideas for next rev. There's nothing concrete yet, and of course we'd like your feedback! Below are the ideas that came up during that meeting. I'll post other ideas (my own or other mayors') that came up after that meeting as a comment(s) below.
___________
1) Going for a specific biome as opposed to portal hunting.  
1a) Ocean -  
Pros -  
* Variation in building (can build underwater, at surface, in the sky)  
*  More space (it's unlikely we'd have people building *right* at our border as usual), which also means we don't need to worry as much about initially claiming an area, and also room to expand later  
Cons  
* At least at the start, more difficult to build things (dirt towers from ocean floor to surface, or surface to sky, or building underwater)  
*  Early-rev travel difficulties (if no ocean portal) - boats are glitchy, swimming long distances, (early-mid) no horses until bridge(s) are made

1b) Dark forest was also brought up. 
_________________
2) Not pre-planning the build like we did for this rev, requiring massive teraforming to fit the build. Instead just coming up with the "ideas" for builds (roads etc) and going back to building with the terrain.
_____________
3) Early rev apartments. It seems like every rev we tell people not to build houses until we have good progress on the town layout. And every rev at least a few people set up a derp hut we have to later tear down/modreq away/etc.  So design/build apartments at the start, so people can have their personal space (and room for chests/furnaces/etc) and hopefully discourage people from derp huts.
___________

Other ideas that we didn't spend much time on, but maybe you have ideas and thoughts on them...

A) Helping to build server-wide infrastructure earlier on (such as CARBON)

B) a Rose mega-build - like a continuation of the townhomes in this rev, but where basically the whole city is a "single" build...somehow...
___________ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Match Thread: USA v China [Women's Friendly] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go USA Wambachs! 

I'll uh..try to fill this out more while the match goes on? Just...no one had made one yet so thought I would.


Edit 1 -  Starting 11s

USA |   | China | 
---|---|----|
Hope Solo (GK) |   | Lina Zhao (GK) | 
Kelley O'Hara (DF) |   | Xue Jiao (DF) | 
Julie Marryme Johnston (DF) |   | Rong Zhao (DF) |
Becky Sauerbrunn (DF) |   | Dongna Li (DF) |
Meghan Klingenberg (DF) |   | Shanshuan Liu (DF) | 
Heather O'Reilly (MF) |   | Jiahui Lei (MF) |
Carli Lloyd (MF) |   | (Sange and) Yasha Gu (MF) | 
Morgan Brian (MF) |    | Ruyin Tan (MF) |
Tobin Heath (MF) |    | Yang Man (MF and M/F) |
Abby Wambeast (FW) |   | Shuang Wang (FW) | 
Alex Morgan (FW) |   | Shanshan Wang (FW)  |

Edit 2 - Found a stream! As much as I loathe firstrowsports - [link 2 seems to work, not the greatest quality](http://ifirstrowus.eu/watch/396129/2/watch-usa-vs-china,-w.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need to make a Rose Gardens carnival event happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 05:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First - In order to make this happen, we could use a few more events/attractions/etc set up.  There are still open plots which could/should be filled.

Second - The event itself...basically we say "Rose Gardens events start at (time), with firework celebrations at the end."  I figure something like 3 hours between the start of the Rose Gardens opening and the fireworks? That would give people time to sample all of the events/rides/etc, and then firework finale.

The other thing is, we'd probably need a few more people to make some builds soon. Flumper could finish his dunk tank, etc...

Again, check planning, and confirm with tic/ice. If a plot is open on planning it's likely open on nerd.  So just confirm your build and make something awesome for ppl to go to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Double the turkey, double the death. Or maybe I was just interrupting a moment of intimacy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 22:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What happened to those weird signs/placards and weird formations from the Eagles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 03:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first season Chip came into the league -

First, there were a ton of weird signs from the sidelines; Will Smith etc... These supposedly were to say which formations to call.  I haven't seen anything about these formations/signs at all since.

Second, he did weird things like those 3 linemen formations/etc.  I've seen other teams run those formations.  I haven't seen the Eagles do that lately. 

Wondering wtf is going on in Philly? Where did the signs go? Where did the weird formations go? Etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub has become PC Principal where any criticism equals mass downvotes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see a post-episode (or related) thread, there is at least one person (usually many more) saying the current/past season aren't very funny.  And they're always downvoted into oblivion.

If you enjoy the current seasons, do you not see the irony? The majority of you act like PC Principal - you disagree with their view, and act extremely negatively towards it.  

If you don't want to be PC Principal, how about - if someone has a negative view; upvote them for sharing their thoughts? Accept that people have different senses of humor? Maybe, juuuuust maybe they're being critical because they love the show and it's going in a direction they don't like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US, most of Europe, Russia, China - All waging war on ISIS. Has there been a similar precedent of so many nations declaring war on a single entity [aside from WW2 I suppose]? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Items E, J, D. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 06:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggestion] For new users, an in-game msg/link that brings them to a "useful for beginners" post? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An on first-join msg that links to a post in this sub which is basically a "beginner's guide to PVE." Which includes a link to rules, a link to the livemap/carto, a link to basic commands (/dnymap show, /cmodify, /modreq water flow...)

Or maybe a command like /new which sends a link to that person for that sort of info? 

_______________________

Reasoning - 

There are a lot of signs with rules.  And signs are kinda...annoying. I'm guessing a lot of the people who will view/respond to this post are people who have played on this server a long time.

Putting yourself in the shoes of a first time player on this server, and seeing the chat from a lot of first time players on this server, the signs are mostly ignored. 

For instance, with new users, I frequently tell them "hey do /map and check the livemap link, and do /dynmap show to appear on that map" and I've seen lots of other people explain that same info.  Also lots of frequent questions/answers re:/cmodify, modreqs of various sorts, etc.  
 _____________

In summation - 

Maybe /new (or some command like that) could point users towards a very simplified version of common/helpful links/commands, with other helpful links included.

_____________

Example post of what /new would link to (a "permanent" post here) - 

_______________

Welcome to PVE! The following links are handy for new users to this server - 

1) Rules (no link on the sidebar apparently? But this should link to that theoretically.)

2) Livemap (link to info about the link for the livemap and how to appear/hide on it)

3) cmodify (link to info about common cmodify commands)

4) rg (link to info about region commands; how to add/remove owners/members, finding info about other towns, etc)

5) Clanchat (link to info about finding public clanchats, creating your own clanchat, etc)

6) Other (link to info about custom/etc mods like dopples, hgps, things of that nature.)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It seems like it may be time for a new UBER project. First post - brainstorming ideas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're not familiar with UBER - it's a large scale project that anyone/everyone can help out with.  It's not tied to a single town or group. 

Uber can be anything really - build a giant new town with a single theme, recreate all the famous monuments around the world in a single spot, giant monsters battling each other...whatever. 

So this first post is just brainstorming ideas. Throw out what you think might be a good giant project for people to work on. Next post (say in a week) will be maybe taking the top 3 ideas and fleshing out the details more, and seeing which of those ends up as the best/most popular idea for a giant collaboration. 

So let's see some ideas for what you think might be a good giant project! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primary concern - a small case that still handles decent gaming specs. ~$1,000 to start, with upgrades later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 00:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What will you be doing with this PC? Be as specific as possible, and include specific games or programs you will be using.**

So I'm looking for a pretty good gaming PC that I'll likely upgrade over the coming months. One of my primary considerations is a smaller sized case. 

I'm not a big gamer in that I don't play a lot of games/spend a lot on steam sales/rush to buy the big new releases. Over the past ~3 years I've played Dota2 and Minecraft and very little else. And my current (not very great) rig handles both of those fine. That's why case is higher on my list of wants than specs. However, I am usually running Netflix/streaming NFL games/etc on a second monitor, so there's some fighting for resources there which I'd like lessened.

I was very attracted to [this case](http://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16811139033) but if you have other suggestions I'm open to hearing them.

Second big consideration - as stated in title, I'll probably upgrade various parts. Certain things (RAM) are easier to upgrade later than other things (motherboard), so starting out with good/very good (don't really need "excellent") things like MB, power supply, are preferred. So for instance, I only need 8 gb of RAM to start, and it doesn't have to be super amazing RAM. A good/very good SSD to start would also be nice, as I already have a 3TB/7200 rpm drive which would become my second drive. So the SSD only needs to be 128 gb, maaaybe 250gb, for OS/program files.

**What is your maximum budget before rebates/shipping/taxes?** 

Let's say the maximum maximum is $1200, though I'd prefer to come in lower than that, again, because of upgrading later. $800-$1,000 would be preferable.

**When do you plan on building/buying the PC? Note: beyond a week or two from today means any build you receive will be out of date when you want to buy.** 

If I get a good list of parts at $800 I'd probably be buying the parts within the next week. If it's in the $1,000-$1,200 range, the purchases would likely be spread out between now and Christmas.

**What, exactly, do you need included in the budget? (Tower/OS/monitor/keyboard/mouse/etc)** 

Case, good+ motherboard, good+ cpu, average/good+ cooling system (fans, water cooled, or other), average/good power supply, (some) RAM, average/good SSD.

I would conder video card options, but at this point it's likely I'll keep my current card and buy one of the top of the line beauties a few months down the line.

**Which country (and state/province) will you be purchasing the parts in? If you're in US, do you have access to a Microcenter location?** 

Oregon, US. I do not believe there's a Microcenter in my town tho.

**If reusing any parts (including monitor(s)/keyboard/mouse/etc), what parts will you be reusing? Brands and models are appreciated.** 

I'll be keeping my current monitor, headset, keyboard, mouse, HDD (to be used as secondary HDD), probably video card (at work, will edit specific card when home).

**Will you be overclocking? If yes, are you interested in overclocking right away, or down the line? CPU and/or GPU?** 

I'm interested in overclocking the CPU if it's done easily/safely. If it involves me personally changing BIOS settings that are likely to void warranty, then I'd stay away from overclocking.

**Are there any specific features or items you want/need in the build? (ex: SSD, large amount of storage or a RAID setup, CUDA or OpenCL support, etc)**

Not particularly aside from, again, a small sized case that can fit all of this and not get too hot. 

**Do you have any specific case preferences (Size like ITX/microATX/mid-tower/full-tower, styles, colors, window or not, LED lighting, etc), or a particular color theme preference for the components?**

If there's a small-sized case that features cool paint job or LED lighting, I would definitely consider that if it's not exceeding, say, $150.

**Do you need a copy of Windows included in the budget? If you do need one included, do you have a preference?**

Most likely yes, and the standard Windows 10.

**Extra info or particulars:**

That's all, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 24 hours (1pm EST Sunday) Rose City will be hosting a Snowball PVP Grand Opening event! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 22:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Where** - NW Rose, -350,860

**When** - **4pm** EST Sunday, October 18 (sorry for title typo!)

**Format** 

There will be 2 phases to the event.  

**Phase 1** - *No armor or weapons.* Join one of the two sides, run around on the brick ledges, and knock people off the other side by throwing snowballs. 

When you fall to the ground, you can either run through a door, go back up, and continue firing snowballs, or, slapfight other fallen players to death.

Snow Golems are set up in each booth and shovels are provided (please return to the chest when done).

**Phase 2** - *No armor, using only weapons provided (stone swords, bows/arrows).*  This part's free for all.  

An unspecified number (currently 8) of **WITHERS!** will be released.  Stars will be dropping.  

**If you grab a star and you can exit the arena without other people killing you, you get to keep it!**

If you want to bring potions or end pearls for Phase 2, you're welcome to.  But please, again, **no armor, and using only the weapons provided.**  Want this bit to be as equal footing as possible.

So come to Rose tomorrow, throw some snowballs at pve'ers, and maybe go home with a star!

Special thanks to Zomise, Nyxie, StarMinion1, and m0rg4n4 for providing materials, helping to build, or helping to collect items.

Edit : and late thanks to ghrey/Solace for helping provide arrows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was curious about a B W episode last season. Mostly negative feedback. The start of tonight makes me happy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 06:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spleef in Rose in ~3 hours! 5pm EST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spleeeeeeeeef </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your embassy plot is an affront to our flattened state of affairs. There are not one, or two, or three changes of elevations, but four?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 08:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Rose will still build an embassy in your filthy pigtown, this obvious change of elevation serves no purpose other than to upset us proud southern flatteners. 

But proud Rose will rise up, above y68, and teach you infidels a lesson. Our glorious embassy shall shame you all. Rose City is most glorious exporter of ~~potassium~~ granite.  

Edit : also I used almost all of my food getting here, someone wanna toss me a few meats?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're using Rose Pack and experiencing problems with ingame chat... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 06:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, a few people have an issue with ingame chat with the latest update. 

For most of those people with that problem there are two solutions -

~~1) You can revert to the previous version of Rose Pack.  At the Technic launcher startup screen, click "mod options" in the upper right, and select use a specific version (0.6).~~ - sorry, I thought this was up, it isn't.

2) You can use the latest version with the following fix that mostly works - on pc, go to your /.technic/modpacks/rosepack/mods/ folder - make a new folder there /backup.  Move the file mod_watson_0.11.0_mc1.8.0.litemod into the backup folder.  Do this while minecraft is closed and try launching again. (edit: I don't know what the equivalent mac directories are, and the only other mac person I've seen with this problem, moving the watson file didn't work, so dunno about that.)

That **should** work, but if text still doesn't work - in the following suggested order, move the following mods 1 by 1 into the /backup folder and relaunch until things work right :P  -

InGameInfoXML  
TabbyChat-2.0.0-beta3.1  
MnM-Utils-0.3.1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A (not very) modest proposal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 11:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alter - our nether portal area design, main portal-spawn nether road, and all other nether roads of ours nearby, as well as every other surface nearby, by putting slabs on top of everything and preventing zigs from spawning.

I don't know if it's 1.8 or if something has gone awry with their moblimiter plugin or what. But the zigs are fucking crazy this rev, overworld near our portal is constantly being flooded with them, and their agro radius is insane. 

Zom and Pez remember the zigpocalypse from a week or so ago.  Well, same thing happened again last night, with Upvote and myself spending a good 20 minutes (at least) constantly running through spawn portals to despawn a never ending wave of angry zigs. It only really ended when we left to planning for 30+ mins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a zombie apocalypse, giving CPR would be the worst. You wouldn't know if they're gasping for air after being revived, or trying to bite you after dying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 01:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird stat of the day courtesy of /u/Upuser - in 9 seasons, Philip Rivers has never thrown a single pass in the final 2 minutes when having a lead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 17:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nether Spawn update - CARTS system now operational if you want to connect (just needs to be made pretty) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 08:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is an imgur album of where each line should connect](http://imgur.com/a/BmL8L)

All you have to do is link up a rail line to these parts. 

Also, you may or may not have noticed I've removed a lot of the slabs surrounding the nether spawn hub area.  This means yes, you can connect your walking paths now. 

I (think) I have enough blocks to finish making the CARTS section how it should look, and that will be done in the next day or two. (Sorry so much of it is over lava lakes, but that's where spawn was so *shrug*)

Edit : also if I have the wrong/missing town names for portal locations, sorry, and let me know here.  I've been using [this](http://bezkr.es/public/signs.php) as a guideline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I...I think this little hill is the last bit of flattening...West road then South between inner/outer walls. We're reaching the flattending! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 08:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rose Projects - some we need, some for the fun, suggest your own! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 01:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our town is filling out quite nicely! But there are still a lot of things that we haven't built yet of various importance.  The following are off the top of my head, some we should probably build soon, some that can wait awhile.

And remember, test your design on planning first when possible! Talk to a mayor and they can set up an area for you.  Also, on the planning server, if you /tp 0 50 0 - there is a board there set up with the following (and more) ideas. But you can also post ideas here as well!

1) Tree Farm - Soon(ish) - we don't have anywhere allocated for this yet.  We were thinking it might be nice to have an "open air" tree farm this rev, but if you had a building design in mind instead, we're open to hear your ideas! 

2) Dog/Cat adoption center - no particular rush, but you can design it now and build it later or w/e - people love dogs and cats. So an area with pens where it's easy to breed new ones for new town members would be great!

3) Villager trading - same as dog/cats, no particular rush, can design whenever and build whenever - right now Solace has a lot of great villagers (as they always do), so you can do a lot of good trading there. But it would be nice if at some point we had our own villagers as well to save us the journey.  If you have experience with villager breeding setups that's a huge plus!

These are just a few ideas, it's recommended checking out the board at 0 50 0 on planning. There are ideas there that aren't here; maybe you'll post an idea here that isn't there.

And finally if someone "claims" a project, but you're interested in it too, then just leave a comment here or chat them in game and see if you can collaborate on it! More than one person working on something generally helps it go faster and be less monotonous to build. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been scientifically proven that many hours spent on THE FLATTENING is deterimental to my brain-meats. So can you really blame me for this creation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 09:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labyrinth completed! Try it out for yourself and join the pez252 hate-train! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 03:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yay the end, finally!](http://imgur.com/a/7IuJh)

[A screenshot from Zomise with how many waypoints were added to keep track...and this was only the 2nd maze...](http://i.imgur.com/4xXcaL1.png)

[Even more waypoints!](http://i.imgur.com/kbfYmt1.png)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nether Spawn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 05:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain, engines are at full capacity! We need more power!

I'm trying to get Nether Spawn done as quickly as possible. But I'm also dividing time between Rose responsibilities (THE FLATTENING) and mining to make tools and get materials to finish Nether Spawn.

The reason I'm posting...pretty much every time I come back, I've found one form of grief or another.  (I haven't done any modreqs because it's mostly been minor, and I've left signs asking people to not do it again, /mail me, etc.)

So the reason I'm posting is to ask for patience, please. And also to get feedback.

1) The exit paths - (see footnote [1])

If you're two towns along a similar axis and want to share a path, I'm asking please let me know. But at the same time, for some distance through the slabs laid down, the paths will be separate.  If you want to combine paths after that point, please do it then. 

2) Chests being put down - so far these are mostly chests of gear from people who died there. No problem! But if you could leave a sign on the chest saying that's why (I'll go add a public chest of signs in a minute) and/or /cmodify @dnynumberone so I can remove the chest once their things are retrieved, that would be great.

3) If you want to help so it gets finished faster - coal blocks are the main lack so far.  I wasn't really around last rev and apparently with the new ore generations, well, I didn't expect coal to be such an issue. I also have a schematic available if you wanted to help build. 

**TL;DR - I'm working on it, please don't remove/alter parts of it (including the signs), I can try to accommodate towns sharing paths, I could use more coal.**

[1] - *puts on whiney baby face* I had an original design based on 8 portals since that was the most popular result of the poll on the forums.  Then the night before the new rev, they announced 4 portals.  I made a new design. Then this Zodiac stuff happened, and made a new 16 path version. I'm trying my best!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] John Elway, Philip Rivers, Joe Namath, Logan Mankins - all players who played without an ACL. Why is it a season ending injury for most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 13:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.complex.com/sports/2014/10/athletes-without-acls/

A lot of these people played their entire career without an ACL. What's the difference? Why not just have it removed outright if it's such an issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HAI GUIZ! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come back and play! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers All] Ep2/1.1 A (minor) example of...stuff...that I can't say without spoiling. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 03:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after last night I had to go start watching all the episodes again.

In Ep2 there was a minor moment that, in the discussion thread and a search of this sub, I can't find any mention of.

SPOILER REMINDER! DON'T READ MORE IF YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THIS EPISODE/ALL EPISODES SO FAR!

The episode ends with Elliot and Mr Robot sitting on the railing.  Mr Robot pushes Elliot off the railing. 

Just before this, as Elliot is first walking up, there are 9 kids sitting on benches hanging out, listening to hiphop. Right as Mr Robot pushes Elliot off the railing, there's a shot from far back which includes these 9 kids.  Mr Robot says something, taking just a few seconds, and gets off the rail.  There's then another shot from the same perspective, with all 9 kids gone and the benches empty.

There's no way this was an accident in the way it was directed; those kids were *meant* to be included in the first shot and not included in the second.  And given this, I don't think you can write it off by just saying "oh well the kids just happened to disperse in those few seconds."

One possible explanation I can come up with is these kids represented Elliot's childhood/innocence - topics that were brought up in his conversation with Mr Robot.  The song they're listening to is by Mos Def, and I'm pretty sure (not 100%) that this track is from the early 90s, or when Elliot would have been about the age of all the kids in that scene.  

So Mr Robot pushing him off the rails/the kids disappearing, it was Elliot basically trying to wake himself up, tell himself "you aren't a kid anymore," and that he won't be "normal" like all those other kids.

That's my theory at least.

**TL;DR - Mr Robot/The Men in Black aren't the only people that Elliot is imagining.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder: Jay Mohr Sports broadcasting from Chargers camp right now. Interviews with Rivers and Gates confirmed at some point. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 21:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have Fox Radio, you can listen on the Fox Sports Listen app or iHeartRadio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried for awhile to make a giant rose, finally got success (IMO). Notes in comments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For sports radio fans (and non-fans) - Jay Mohr Sports from Fox Radio will be broadcasting from Chargers Camp this coming Monday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 05:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First - I am not employed by the show or Fox radio in any capacity, so I'm not just trying to plug a show for any reason other than I like it and it's the Chargers.

Second - This is hands down, bar none, far and away my favorite radio show. When I'm at work and I don't have normal radio, this is the only show I will listen to on any of the Android apps.  (I used to listen to SvP Rusillo too, but since SvP left it's just not the same.)  If for some reason work causes me to miss the show, I will actually download the show when I get home just to listen to it.  That's how much I enjoy it.

I'm going to continue writing about how much I love this show down below after pointing out more meaningful info.

I'm pretty sure the SD affiliate only has the second/third hours of the show and not the first.  If you want to listen to the whole thing here are a few ways - 

Oh important note first - the show is live from Noon to 3pm Pacific time.

1) iheart.com - for normal browsers/PCs.  You can search either "fox sports radio" or "jay mohr sports" and it should pull up the link.

2) the "I heart radio" app.  Same steps as above.

3) The "Fox Sports Listen" app, which is what I use, because this is the only sports radio show I listen to with my phone. **Note:** his hours were switched, and apparently the app programmers were lazy, so if you do happen to tune in and use the "radio" function to listen live, it will say Steve Gorman sports is playing, but that's wrong.  

_______

About the show in general (more fanboy talk) - 

1) Most important - he combines comedy with his show as much as sports. Some of you are probably like, "Jay Mohr...isn't he an actor or something?"  Yeah, he's an actor/comedian.  And that's why I love it. There have been times where I've been driving while listening to the show and I've felt I should pull over and park because I'm laughing so hard it's probably not safe to drive.

2) Integrity - All this deflategate bullshit? He spent 1 day talking about it when it first broke, because he kinda had to.  He spent 1 day talking about it when it was going to go to court.  Other than that he has pretty much not brought it up at all, except to point out how stupid it is and how much he wishes he didn't have to talk about it.  

3) If you're new to the show, there are a lot of "in jokes" that might not make sense.  If you want an example of what is probably one of his best shows ever, using the Fox Sports Listen app, download the 05/07 show. I mean...I've re-listened to this episode like 5 times.  For a *radio show*.  How many radio shows are worth repeating even a second time? But holy shit is it hilarious.

Edit : found links for 05/07 show - (wrong links the first time correct this time)

[Hour 1](http://www.foxsportsradio.com/media/podcast-jay-mohr-sports-hours-Jay_Mohr_Sports_Hours/0507-jay-mohr-sports-hr-1-26033146/)

[Hour 2](http://www.foxsportsradio.com/media/podcast-jay-mohr-sports-hours-Jay_Mohr_Sports_Hours/0507-jay-mohr-sports-hr-2-26033413/)

[Hour 3](http://www.foxsportsradio.com/media/podcast-jay-mohr-sports-hours-Jay_Mohr_Sports_Hours/0507-jay-mohr-sports-hr-3-26033607/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 - semi-casual/first time watching TI, and very very few STR/Tanky heroes were picked. Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 06:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this just something with the current patch/meta? Have str gains been nerfed or something? Do they just completely lack the damage output in any/all phases?  Are the "squishies" at this level just too good that it doesn't matter how tanky you are, you'll get burst down quickly no matter what? 

Just wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching EG get interviewed after winning it all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 04:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Sports Radio fans - Jay Mohr Sports on Fox Radio is broadcasting from the Broncos camp today. (Currently on with Aqib Talib.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 21:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, Jay Mohr has become my number one favorite radio show. He combines comedy with the sports, it's the only show I listen to on my phone when I'm in the office, and if work takes me away from the office so I can't listen, I'll download the shows when I get home and listen to them then. 

On android there's the Fox Listen app (which they haven't updated, so if you go to the live/radio feed it'll say Dave Gorman sports).  On android there's also I Heart Radio app, and on your PC there's also iheart.com and you can search fox sports and listen there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys liked the "Meet the Villain" montage - here's another similar one (2 more in comments) - Warrior Concerto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 19:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought maybe you guys could help - has anyone else been experiencing weird audio compression/normalization/other issues since upgrading to Windows 10? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 03:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First - yes I've checked "enhancements" and none are enabled, I've configured my speaker layout so it's the right setup, I've gone through every other sound setting to make sure there are no weird options enabled. 

Second - I've found this issue occurs through any software I use, so it's not a software specific issue. Netflix, youtube, popcorn time, media player classic, they all have this issue.

The shortest way I can describe the issue is it seems like background/ambient noises in movies and shows are much more prevalent now. That's why I think it's maybe a compression/normalization issue. But maybe it could also be trying to force a "3d sound" effect, even though no effect is enabled? Maybe I'm imagining it but I don't think I am. It really does feel like anything I listen to there's a lot more "atmosphere" to it, and not in a good way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If time travel ever becomes a reality, then Hitler must have survived like a billion assassination attempts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 08:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having kinda weird sound issues since upgrading. Like it's trying to force 3d sound or something? Ambient/atmospheric/background noises in shows and movies seem a LOT louder now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 07:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't program-specific; I notice the effect in MPC, Popcorn Time, Netflix, etc.

I don't have any enhancements enabled in the playback/hardware settings.  I did the configure and chose all the right settings for my speaker setup.  

I searched "sound" in settings and went through every possible control panel. Couldn't find anything that fixed this problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the "Movies   TV" app constantly crashing for anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 07:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have yet to get a single movie file to open on this app without it crashing.  MKV, MP4, AVI, any movie file at all.  Opens in Movies   TV and immediately crashes.  

And to make it worse, I have Media Player Classic, but I can't seem to set this as a default app for those files?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to force my personal traffic to http only? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 05:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have roommates, and live in a semi-rural area with limited connectivity. The problem is 1-2 roommates basically do nothing but watch Netflix 10+ hours a day. 

My ISP (as I've recently found out) runs a "sandvine". Basically, torrents/Netflix/etc get capped. However a friend with the same ISP did the amazon firestick hack thing, and all his traffic goes through http and doesn't get restricted.

I've tried VPN s but all https traffic is throttled too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we ever develop true AI, it'll probably immediately learn from our movies/shows that we always try to kill any sentient robots. So we're basically training AI to want to wipe out humanity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 04:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone here signed up with Google's Project Fi yet? What have your results been if so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 03:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just received my invite.  Only $30 per month for a phone plan.  Sure, that's the 1gb plan, but I'm almost always on a wifi connection when I do any sort of data use, so I'm not worried about the 1 gb limit.  

My main concern is the coverage map.  I currently use Sprint, and man, Sprint's coverage in Bend is TERRIBLE. And Sprint's coverage map looks veeeeeery similar to the Project Fi coverage map.  

But then again, I find it hard to believe it could be even worse than Sprint.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another shooting incident...sometimes I don't get you, reddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 21:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else have Reborn get deleted with the latest update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 08:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I normally play with friends who don't like Reborn during the day, and then solo queue in reborn at night.  Last night, played several reborn matches no problem.  Tonight, kept trying to launch to reborn but kept launching to normal.  Then I noticed the reborn checkbox wasn't checked.  Checked it...and had to download all 7 gigs for the third or fourth time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After finding out Spiderman is being rebooted (again), I REALLY hope they don't have the same issue the #3 of the first, and #2 of the second had - TOO MUCH CRYING. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually went through and counted the number of times people were crying or had "teary eyes" in Spiderman 3 of the Tobey Maguire series.  24 times.  

I haven't bothered doing the same with #2 of the Amazing Spiderman series, but when watching it I recall a similar phenomenon.  

I'm in the theater to watch a superhero movie.  Not a bunch of fake/BS drama with people crying, on average, once every 6 minutes.

______________

Spiderman 3 Crying review - 

12:09 Sandman's Wife
16:05 Aunt May
44:40 Mary Jane
57:40 Mary Jane
1:00:00 Peter Parker
1:23:40 Peter   Mary Jane
1:25:00 Still Peter
1:30:20 Gwen
1:40:00 Mary Jane
1:42:09 Eddie Brock
1:48:32 Peter
1:52:33 Harry's Butler, Harry
2:06:10 Mary Jane
2:07:39 Peter
2:08:27 Sandman
2:09:40 Peter again
2:10:01 Mary too
2:10:19 And Harry too why not
2:10:41 Mary and Peter still at it, yep a full minute plus of crying here
2:11:31 Peter still crying, different scene though
2:13:18 Mary again and Peter again too why not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new favorite metal mining spot for early/mid game. 3-4 rich deposits, 5-8 medium deposits, TONS of stone for flint/sparkpowder, and not tall enough to attract Argentines/Sabers. (And apparently a cave nearby) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new favorite metal mining spot for early/mid game. 3-4 rich deposits, 5-8 medium deposits, TONS of stone for flint/sparkpowder, and not tall enough to attract Argentines/Sabers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S2E5] West Coast discussion thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Um...New Episode Discussion Thread for West Coast people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GT545 - With certain games, I hear the fan rev way up, then a few seconds later rev down. Then rev way up, then a few seconds later rev down. Is there any way to force the fan to just stay revved up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 01:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, it gets kind of annoying just hearing it do this over and over and over.  Playing Ark:Survival, which is an Alpha, and not very optimized.  And basically it's calm/normal for ~10s, then spends 3s revving way up, then it calms down.  Repeat.

Second, I just figure it would be better overall if the fan is using the higher rate while playing this game? If every 10s it needs to rev up, wouldn't it be best to just stay revved up?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I shoot a gun while riding a dino when the freaking LOADING SCREEN shows 2 humans holding weapons while riding freaking dinos?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 20:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to poach a freaking Rex from my freaking Ptero already! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 - with talk of collusion charges...how is the franchise tag not considered collusion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Post Match Thread] Panama 1 - 1 USA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.theguardian.com/football/live/2015/jul/13/gold-cup-2015-usa-v-panama-live

Important notes -

According to US fans, 90% of the US team is shit.

According to Panamanian fans, 90% of the US fouls weren't called.

According to both teams, Beckerman smells like licorice that's been left on the dash of a car for two weeks.

Edit : Oh crap didn't think this would become the "official" one.  Um...going to look for gif highlights now.

Edit 2 :

[Goal from Panama!](http://streamable.com/ptur) Good cross from Tejada to Perez via /u/Omar_Til_Death

[Equalizer from the US!](http://streamable.com/v3yf) Desperate stab from Dempsey hits his target Bedoya, with a cross to Bradley via /u/Omar_Til_Death

[Brooks with the beautifully timed 12 mile challenge](http://gfycat.com/DelectableAnnualBighorn) via /u/Fusir - Some say Brooks is still sliding to this day.

[The official game ball for the 2015 Gold Cup is brought to you by a robot throwing up after drinking too much orange gatorade.](http://ww1.hdnux.com/photos/37/52/04/8298760/5/628x471.jpg)

Edit 3 :  how has no one called me out for making a shitty post match thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The tip of my tongue is sore, and I just can't think of why that is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 21:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wasn't karmanaut once accused of the same things unidan was accused of, except like 10x worse? Why is karmanaut still an admin while unidan is a pariah? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 03:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers All] Out of curiosity, how many people here have read the Walk Dead source material? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 02:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask because I see a lot of comments that basically equal "Walking Dead is shit compared to this."  Especially after episode 8 of GoT.  

Since this a forum to discuss source material, I'm curious about the title.  

For instance, the comics themselves are very often focused on the "day to day" life of the people, the random drama, etc.  Basically, a lot of the things people complain about with TWD. 

And yes, I know TWD the show has a lot of faults.  Not saying it doesn't.  Just curious if people here and on r/gameofthrones/ are as familiar with TWD source material as they are here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most terrifying way you can describe a common everyday thing or event? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 18:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the scientific community, is 40 proof alcohol only half as credible as 80 proof? And if I indeed get drunk, have I given it another proof that it's alcohol? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 01:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers All) Two fan theories have me worried about the potential end of the series. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 10:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) R+L=J.  
2) Jon ends up with Daenerys.

This has me worried because if both are true, then we're back to Targaryens  inbreeding, and likely will end up with future mad kings with dragons in their control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Re-listening to the 05/07 episode - birth of "shut yo mouth before i give you these hands chump" and "obviously, and i mean no disrespect..." Holy crap this episode was so great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 06:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually listening to it for the like...4th or 5th time...

Still laughing my ass off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Come up with the longest sentence/paragraph you can, adding only one letter to either end of the previous word. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: A, an ant anti-antic.

"Rules" I've just now made up - 

You can add to either side. You can add punctuation that you remove for the next word (eg: can can't scant). 

And I guess you can use "any" English, for instance O, Oer, etc. as in Old English. And a single letter can be used if it's like a proper name.  "A" is the name of the ant in the above example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm trying to come up with the longest sentence I can by adding one letter a time to the previous ends of the previous words. Maybe you can come up with some better ones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sense8 - I've heard good things from some people, and "meh" from others. 4 episodes in, I'm leaning towards the latter. Change My View? (Spoilers?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 07:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the first two episodes 3 times.  Third and fourth episode twice.

I still have like...no idea what the fuck is going on?  

Like...start of episode one, Daryll Hannah shares a vision with these eight people.  Then the next 3.5 episodes, basically nothing comes of it except for they all sing a horrible song at the same time in E4?

Seems like, after an interesting premise, it's just become a character study since then?  

A friend, whose opinions I trust on such things, said I should really watch this show.  But holy crap, I keep watching episodes thinking I'm missing things or something but...no?  

If I didn't give much weight to episodes 2-4, would I have enjoyed this series more?

I just don't get why this show is so hyped, so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I leave a glass of alcohol (whiskey, vodka, etc., not rubbing/other kinds) out overnight, or for a day or two, does it become more potent from evaporation? Or does the alcohol content evaporate faster than the water content? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 05:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Valve, I think it would improve your sales if you implemented a rule that "Preview videos must contain at least 50% gameplay footage." Or something like that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 05:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mostly play DotA2. Every once in awhile, I feel like something different.  I browse my Friend's List to see what others are playing. I'll go to the game hub, then the store page (since there's no direct link, grumble grumble), and I'll watch the preview videos.

Basically my one and only question is - **what is the gameplay like?**  And so, so, so many times, the preview videos don't answer this question.  They're 99% cinematics.  

I really don't care what kinda fancy video you can create with a few months of time that has nothing to do with the gameplay.  

I'm pretty sure that, with gameplay video implemented, I would have purchased a LOT more games.  But, the game my friend is playing I just checked out to see if I might want to play it; 3 videos, all 3 cinematics only.  

So...fuck it, I'll keep playing DotA2. 

**TL;DR** - If Valve/Steam required that, say, 50% of their total video time required gameplay footage, I probably would have bought a lot more games.  Fuck cinematics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since we seem to be complaining about Netflix today - When I click "Back to browse" during credits... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 22:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there something like Kerbal Space Program/Google Sketch, where you can drag/drop simple items and connect them to make a machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 00:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this idea for a funky new machine, nothing too sophisticated.  Two wheels, some connecting parts, a gear train...but there are certain things I can't visualize in my head. 

So is there a program out there where you can basically drag/drop/connect pre-populated items to try to make some sort of new device?  Less complicated than KSP, because I'm talking modern day simple devices, not rocketships; but more complicated than Google Sketch where I want the pre-populated items to be able to connect/interact.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Kung Fury, some of you are looking for similar things. Heat Vision and Jack, a great parody of late 80s/early 90s tv shows like MacGuyver etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can everyone just chill the fuck out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean really now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What album has the best opening combo of tracks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to Tago Mago by Can for the first time in a long time.  And the first three songs just kick so much ass and work so well together.  After that it's just pretty good for the next few.

Wondering what your thoughts are on similar albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else experiencing a bug where every time you pick a challenge, the challenge changes after you pick it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The new waterpark thingy...I keep hearing ads on the radio about how they're $250k short...what will happen if they don't reach that goal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to the radio while driving a lot. I hear ads saying basically what the title says.  

What happens if they don't reach that goal?  Are they really just going to drop everything and say "fuck it, we're done", even when they've received 99% of their funding?  

Or..what?  I guess I just find it hard to believe they'd completely give up on the project when basically 99% done...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't firefox handle full screen viewing on a second monitor for flash streams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I follow soccer.  I don't have a TV, and even if I did, the majority of the matches aren't shown on TV.  So I use streams.

I have a second monitor.  Soccer match goes on #2, while I play DotA on #1.  

Except...I can't do that with Firefox.  With Netflix/Silverlight, it works fine.  But with sports streams (typically Flash-based), it doesn't work.  And no, it's not the stream.  I've opened the same links on Chrome, and it works fine using that.  

Is there maybe some plugin or something that fixes this issue?  Because otherwise, I have to keep using Chrome just to watch soccer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shouldn't we set up a bunch of Muhammed cartoon exhibits to work as terrorist traps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 10:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Test client download issues... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 06:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had test client before. HDD crashed. Didn't redownload until now BC 6.84. 

Tried once. Got to ~95%. My ISP died for 30s. Upon reconnecting, test client started downloading again, but only at the ~5% mark. Okay...wait a long time again...gets to ~95% again, my ISP *doesn't* die...the download just plain restarts to 5% again.

So I've basically downloaded 13.5 gigs today without a usable test client to show for it.

Anyone else have this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And Jesus said, "Give reddit a quote from a famous show, and ye shall be the highest comment. Give reddit a reason to quote every famous show ever, and ye shall reach the front page." - Memeisis 4:20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 01:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the release of the new Avengers movie...did you know Marvel and DC have made some pretty kick-ass animated movies? Here's a list! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 07:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] So um...one of the main rules for this sub is to not make "sexual" comments about a character. But this seems to only apply to female characters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So um...one of the main rules for this sub is to not make "sexual" comments about a character. But this seems to only apply to female characters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 04:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> lol...not so much a bug as a UI/design error...lost so many ground units in a battle, list went off the screen, couldn't get it to go away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/emxIwoy.jpg

I tried playing a few more turns but then another battle came up and I couldn't click any of those buttons.  Also couldn't click any of the upper left menus or anything.

Hoping the last auto save isn't *too* far in the past.

Also, thanks everyone for the tips you gave me the other day! Despite this screenshot I've just about finished conquering the galaxy. (Now to do it on not-easy mode)

edit: Okay, *this* kinda pisses me off though - http://i.imgur.com/5bSCKdo.jpg (couldn't click anything to make this go away)

edit2: okay, the famous leader rating system at the end is hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to this game and feel like I've hit a block. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 09:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a DotA friend playing this, he said he loved the first and the new one was awesome, so I thought I'd give it a try. Thing is, he lives in Sweden, I'm west coast US, so there aren't many times where I can pick his brain for answers.

1) Ship design - he told me I should always be upgrading and doing custom ships, and it's a lot of fun. But, for instance, I built a Human Stewart Class outfitted with mass drivers, and if I mouse over the lower left weapon info, it says "Seconds to Depletion: 400" (or something like that) and next to that for the powered weapons it says "Seconds to Depletion : Infinite." But then watching the battle, it looked like my rail gun ships only fired once, twice...maybe 3 or 4 times? Then I noticed clicking on the ship in-fight, they had 0 power after those few shots...

Is this a lack of power capacitors? Why does it say "Infinite" in the mouseover instead of like 2 seconds...

2) Money/Research. Another thing I was told is I should set up "farming planets" for generating income. So like, if a planet has a max pop of, say, 7, with good base food, should I basically have *only* farmers on that planet? And only do food upgrades there (like soil enrichment etc)?  And planets with small pops and 0 base food, *only* do production stuff there?  But then where does that leave researchers? Just sprinkle them throughout all the planets, 1 or 2 at most or something?

3) Also having trouble grasping when the right times to expand are. There's the research penalty for each colony, so I tend to go slow with colonies. But then I look at neighboring races taking up 1/2 of the galaxy and also with a ton more technologies than I do...(yeah yeah, AI cheats...) 

Tried googling and the wiki and whatnot but not having much luck. 

Any help is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't change default search engine. "Setting enforced by administrator." Obvious malware, nothing removes it, can only find old/outdated solutions. Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 05:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I'm now using Firefox because Chrome is dead to me.  I've used AVG, Malwarebytes, MS Windows Malicious Software removal, Avira...none turn up results, but still, my default search is locked onto this obvious malware search engine. 

I've searched and searched and searched.  I've found a lot of old (~2 years) posts related to this topic, but all the solutions are no longer relevant/point to registry paths that no longer exist/etc.

My default search is now http://www.google.lk/cse?hl=en source=hp q=hi cx=partner-pub-0659050299177733:qlji1xyvf02 and I am not able to remove it.  Where there is normally an X to remove, instead it's "This sietting is enforced by administrator."  I've tried a dozen different search terms going through my registry to try to find/remove this, with no results.

I would prefer using Chrome, but at this point I can't.  

(The old fix, going to registry and looking for the policies/google/chrome/etc fix doesn't work, since there is no google subdirectory in policies on my computer.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is AVG Free basically completely useless these days? Also an ELI5 question in post. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 04:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former tech support employee, but many years since I worked in that field. When I did, I always recommended people run a combination of AVG Free and Malwarebytes.  

For the ELI5 - This used to be a common issue, but it seemed like all the time when inspecting ole gramps virus-filled computer, AVGF would find, say 16 viruses.  Then MB would find 14 different viruses. Are they made to search for specific things, and each one searches for a different specific thing?

Anyway, back to title post - today Chrome wouldn't launch.  Just straight wouldn't launch at all. Naturally, alarms went off. Ran AVGF, 0 threats. Ran MB, 8 threats. 

I'm pretty good at web security typically - I use a custom hosts file, use ublock and flashblock, and AVGF is apparently running in the background.  But I also have a weakness for soccer, and have to resort to some pretty shady sites in order to watch certain matches. 

So apparently AVGF allowed this virus to be installed through my browser, then couldn't detect anything? 

I guess I'm switching to Avast to see how that goes.

TL;DR - Used to always recommend AVGFree, apparently it's basically useless now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the number that Chuck dialed using Jimmy's phone a complete fake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe...just maybe...how Jimmy responded to the big case was what determined Chuck's reaction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I can understand how this may be viewed as an idiotic theory.  I'm just playing Devil's Advocate here...

What if Chuck's call to Hamlin was something along the lines of, "Turn down Jimmy for a job here. If he declines the case out of spite, it shows he doesn't have the best interests of his clients in mind.  If he still gives you the case, even if he doesn't get a job at HHM out of it, it shows he has turned a corner and offer him a job after."

In other words, what if this was a test from Chuck? When Jimmy realized he wasn't getting a job at HHM, and decided basically, "fuck this case"...Jimmy was basically deciding at that point that his pride/honor was more important than, potentially, 350+ clients who were being ripped off.

So maybe, just maybe, Chuck/Hamlin decided, if he's going to throw away the well being of 350+ clients for his own pride, then he has shown he still isn't worthy for a position at that firm. 

If Jimmy, after realizing he wouldn't get a job at HHM, decided "fine, have the case anyway, it will do some good", would Chuck/Hamlin have reacted differently?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I be a naysayer for a moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 06:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First - This show has been beautifully written, directed, and acted so far.  Dialogue has been witty, the plot has made sense, it's great seeing backstories on some of my favorite BrBa characters.

Second - Despite what I'm about to say, I'm still very involved in this show and want to see more.

Buuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuut...

As we're approaching the season finale, I keep asking myself, "What has **actually happened** so far?"  And the basic answer is...nothing. 

We've gotten a bit of the Jimmy/Saul backstory.  We get a bit of Chuck.  Oh, hey, an episode explaining why Mike is why he is.  But can you actually say anything has **happened** so far?  

The first/second episode, we saw Jimmy conning some teens into a scheme, Tuco, a near-death sentence in the desert...and since then...?  

I mean, character development is cool and all, it's why I still watch each episode and enjoy them.  But at some point the characters have to actually *do* something.  And since basically the second episode, no one has actually done much at all.  

Bearing in mind that by this point, in BrBa (SPOILERS!)- 

Walt starts cooking, poisons/kills two people, a scare from the fire department (he/we thought was police), body melted in a bathtub, Tuco introduced, Tuco kills his friend, among other things.  

Not trying to be a dickhead.  And I'm not saying this show is terrible or anything.  Just that, for being wonderfully shot/written/directed/etc...nothing seems to have actually happened.

**Edit 1** - Episode 7 ends with a "cliffhanger" where Jimmy takes a call in his empty office...and, episode 8, had literally nothing to do with that phone call.  It was a "cliffhanger" ending that never, ever, resolved.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've often wondered how an episode shot in the "comic style" (black/white) would end up. Decided to edit a few scenes to try it out. [More links in comments, I guess I can't post an album here?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 05:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've often fantasized about an episode of the show being shot in Black/White to reference the comic. Decided to "comic-ize" a few of the shots of the past season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 05:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During the World Cup, I kept noticing a problem with the USMNT. Disturbingly, I saw this same issue several times in yesterday's match. [Warning, lots of text.] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 17:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer 1) Sorry for the potato quality images. Apparently the print screen key on my keyboard doesn't work, tried some Chrome extensions, etc.  Finally took pictures of my screen with my phone. Also I couldn't find proper replays and had to resort to a low quality semi-dodgy site.

Disclaimer 2) I've only done this analysis for the first WC match versus Ghana so far.  I'll be looking at Portugal, Germany, and Belgium when I get home from work tonight.

**TL;DR** Doing this at the start because likely a lot of text/pictures - our defensive back 4 is constantly out of position, regardless of whom is playing back there, and I think Bradley got waaaay too much blame from the WC for trying to help that.

**The Problem** - As you can (sort of) see from [this picture](http://i.imgur.com/BUF1KAG.jpg) - our formation is a 4-4-2 utilizing a Diamond midfield.  You could also call it a 4-1-2-1-2 I suppose.  The most important thing to notice about this - Bradley is the **forward midfielder**, whose nominal job is to help distribute the ball to the forwards.  

However, as I'm about to show, that is rarely the case.

**Evidence!** - It turns out I'm not crazy for thinking Bradley was in the backfield way too often.  In the game versus Ghana alone, I found 8(!) examples. And this was a match where we "parked the bus", meaning everyone should be playing strong-ass defense!  How is it that when we're supposed to be playing strong defense, our *forward midfielder* is constantly one of the rear-most defenders?  (And note: I had a cig or two while re-watching this match so I may have missed a few examples.)

[12 minutes in](http://i.imgur.com/o74Cel6.jpg) Bradley is the second closest person to the GK, and apparently one of our back 4 now?

[~18 minutes in](http://i.imgur.com/Z2B5Bos.jpg) Bradley is one of three rear defenders here.  

[~24 minutes in](http://i.imgur.com/yoKlOpO.jpg) Bradley is the closest player to the GK, with only 2 other defenders nearby.

[41 minutes](http://i.imgur.com/HuRW47v.jpg) Right after a dangerous chance form Ghana, Bradley is one of only 3 US players near the GK.  

[52 minutes](http://i.imgur.com/nJMDa3N.jpg) Bradley, just a bit below the guy with the ball, with only one other defender between him and Howard.

[58 minutes](http://i.imgur.com/qcfzUxd.jpg) Hey, there's our back 4! Oh wait, Bradley is one of them again.

[60 minutes](http://i.imgur.com/S7GmMiP.jpg) 3 defenders...Bradley being one of them...

[79 minutes](http://i.imgur.com/tgV7XWs.jpg) For a change of pace, hey look! We have an actual back 4!? Of course, Bradley is the rear-most midfielder in this shot even still.  

[83 minutes](http://i.imgur.com/1hzJ8GQ.jpg) 2 defenders, Bradley, but at least 3 others are at about the same distance.

**Who to blame?** As I said, I saw this problem happening again yesterday versus Denmark.  And that was with an entirely different back 4, and midfield too for that matter.  

*Is it Bradley's fault?*  I don't think so. For almost every one of the instances I pictured, he would soon after be quickly found at the top of the diamond, his actual position.  The dude was playing his ass off and, from my view, trying to shore up our defensive weaknesses.  And it's worth remembering this was during insane heat/humidity.  (Yes he had a few bad touches/passes here and there, but I'm giving him the benefit of the doubt and blaming exhaustion after considering all of this.)

*Is it the other players' faults?* At least somewhat?  Even if the defense needs help, which it obviously does, shouldn't that be the responsibilities of the rear and central midfield?  Not the *forward midfielder?*

*Is it Klinnsman's fault?* Considering the drastic roster changes between this match versus Ghana and the match against Denmark, I don't know if you can just chalk this up to players forgetting their assignments.  It really seems more like a team philosophy to have the two outside defenders constantly pushing up the pitch, and the "diamond" being more of a blob that just stands at the half-line (to congest the midfield, I suppose?) and makes Bradley do all the work.  

**Conclusions?** - We've seen how often Bradley is the key distributor on our goals, and theoretically that's why he's at the top of the diamond. But time and again we've seen him forced into defensive duties instead because of our team's questionable formations.  If our back 4 remained as an actual back 4 instead of the 2 outside backs pushing up, Bradley might have more freedom to wreak havoc up front. If JK wants Bradley to be up front, then he needs to stress more importance on the back 4 staying as, you know, a back 4.  If he wants the 2 outside backs to push up the field more, then stress that the rear and central midfielders stay that way.  Instead the team seems to be of the mindset of "All but two defenders push up the field, and Bradley, you run everywhere and do everything."

**Finally** - I have three more games to watch tonight after work, so I'll probably post again about those in the next day or two, and try to figure out a better screen capture solution in the meantime.

**Actual Final Note** - Holy crap re-watching this game was awesome.  Even knowing what was coming and when, the first goal, Altidore, the equalizer, the header for the win; knowing all of that was going to happen, it was still so sweet to watch.  When Brooks headed in the winner, my housemates probably thought I was crazy, hearing me screaming "Yeah! FUCK YEAH! YEAAAAAAAAAH!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This episode caused an overwhelming desire to watch the first episode again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 08:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of these points were brought up in talking dead, but I think a few were missed - 

1) The infidelity. Rick making a play on blondie reminiscent of discovering the Shane/Lori relationship.

2) Horse gets eaten.  Obvious enough.

3) Rick is a cop! Just like the start of the series.

4) Probably the biggest thing, we got to see them all in a "normal" life situation for the first time in basically forever.  Not since the first ~5 minutes of the show did we get to see any of these people acing "normally," until now.  

Edit 5) oh I forgot! And the song at the end! The first episode ends with a song that is frankly kind of "silly" with how it matches what's going on, and this episode was kind of similar in that regard.  It's been so long!

Went and rewatched the very first episode immediately after finishing this one. And it felt so good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Timm...please return to helping with animated movies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 09:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For awhile I would tell people, "DC animated movies right now are better than a lot of the movies you'll see in theaters."  I can no longer say that.  The last two DC ani-movies have been, frankly, *terrible*.  I say this after watching "Throne of Atlantis" and "
Under the Red Hood" back to back.  The former is entirely childish aside from token swear words to make it seem edgy, has basically no action at all until some generic scenes towards the end...whereas Under the Red Hood has a compelling story line, intricate (and frequent enough) action scenes...

A new DC movie used to be one of the highlights of my year.  I always eagerly awaited the newest release.  But "Throne of Atlantis" and "War" back to back have basically made me give up on this franchise.

Please Bruce Timm...return to making DC animated movies.  They were amazing and wonderful when you were a part of it.  Now they're just generic and boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck I love this game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 06:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it too soon to have an unofficial/official prediction thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 05:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A kinda different idea for keeping people more interested here - /r/mcpublic/ flair (or other flairs like that in game?) for various "achievements." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 03:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was very very active last rev.  And this rev, at the start, I was very very active.  And then I became very very inactive.  

Comparing my experiences last rev and this rev, last rev I had built houses in 5 towns, and did the uber-deux project, among other things.  This rev I was basically Rose Rose Rose and nothing but Rose, aside from spleef.

A lot of that was town-building projects.  And eventually I reached this point where logging onto nerd felt more like a chore than having fun.  

So off the top of my head was things like offering custom flairs to this subreddit.  "Pro Tourist rev 15" for building the most houses in the most towns.  "Pro Spleefer" for anyone participating in 3+ spleef tourneys.  "Active Trader" for being highly active in the trade chat.  

I dunno, I remember during the admin hunt in rev 13, hearing multiple people saying things along the lines of, "Wow I've seen so much of this map because of this event that I've never seen."  And I think encouraging exploring/trading/touring other towns, any way to help that, helps keep people interested/active in the server.

Note: I know there was a semi-recent post about how to "encourage keeping PVE active" stuff leading to a forum link.  I didn't post this there because first, it's a kinda old link so I don't think many people are reading it anymore, and second, the forums in general I think discourage a lot of response because people are like "meh, do I really want to set up some new account somewhere just to write a few sentences?"

Late Edit : I have no idea the possibility of this, but something like adding a + next to the user name for each flair they receive here? "I have 6 +'s woot!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] I guess a lot of people missed the other example of the "wolves not far" when driving to the small town. Sorry for potato quality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 21:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I had a nickel for every time (event) happened...what should the event be to get the most nickels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 23:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is the current strain of flu (and a few other recent ones) more dangerous to young adults instead of children/elderly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 02:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought most strains of the flu, or other epidemics, typically had the highest mortality rates amount children and the elderly.  But I've been hearing ads lately about how the current fly going around is more dangerous to college-aged individuals.  And I recall other illnesses in the past few years being similar in that regard.

What's different about these illnesses that makes the most harmful to what are (theoretically) the healthiest members of society? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The events in Paris suck...but the comic creator wasn't some great martyr or anything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 04:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please leave the footnote below the following line, but remember to delete this sentence by replacing it with the body of your post. Thank you!

_____
Almost none of his comics were actually relevant or topical in any way.  They were basically just shock-jock level of "oh hey look how insulting I can be, come at me bro."  If he hadn't just been killed by a terrorist, this was basically 4chan level of trolling. Not even that really. 

"I don't have a wife or children or credit" etc, sure that applies to him, but not the other people killed. And, frankly, his comics were awful, pure 100% trolling, but now they're "genius" because he's dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a bit of "desperation" I purchased Heiroglyph. After reading the prologue, I want a refund. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 07:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I recently posted this](http://www.reddit.com/r/scifi/comments/2qvu7m/is_there_a_dearth_of_good_standalone_scifi_novels/) -

The TL;DR - had a collection of Barnes   Noble gift cards from the holidays, went to try to use them, left utterly despondent because of their 3 shelves of "new" books in the scifi section, a) 70% were fantasy, b) of what were left, about half were zombie novels, and c) of what little was left after that, almost everything was part of a 5 to 7 to X#(where X is a large number) series.

I ended up picking up Heiroglyph.  I'd heard about it before, how it was this "call to arms" about trying to make a positive scifi impact in the greater world.  And it was very much a last resort option; I really don't like short story collections for various reasons.  But I was kinda feeling crap about the lack of any good "stand-alone" scifi novel options, and it was "optimistic", and so I bought it.  

I also love Neal Stephenson.  I don't think there's a single book of his I've read fewer than 3 times; Cryptonomicon was just finished for the ~ninth time.  

But his prologue was just...incredibly depressing.  And seemed completely counter to the spirit of the book.  His prologue basically just crushed what few hopes I had left about science/scifi progressing.  

Maybe it's just post-holiday blues.  Just...I picked up this book as a last resort, thinking, "at least it will be optimistic."  And the prologue by my favorite author is anything but.  He didn't even *try* to end on a positive note.  It was just, "things have gone to shit, and here's why, seeya." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a dearth of good stand-alone scifi novels atm, or was I just in the wrong place at the wrong time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 04:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TL;DR** - had a collection of Barnes   Noble gift cards from the holidays, went to try to use them, left utterly despondent because of their 3 shelves of "new" books, a) 70% were fantasy, b) of what were left, about half were zombie novels, and c) of what little was left after that, almost everything was part of a 5 to 7 to X#(where X is a large number) series.

First - I don't necessarily hate fantasy, I just wish the two sections were fucking separated. I was in the mood for a scifi novel.  "Oh that looks cool...oh fantasy...oh what about...fantasy...maybe that...fantasy..."

Second - I lost my tolerance long ago for any series that lasts longer than three books.  In my experience, anything that takes longer than three books to tell the story means a metric shitton of useless/shitty/boring descriptions of *everything.*  Pages of describing every single thing on sale at a market, or every single bit of food at a feast, etc.  Brevity is the soul of wit; 5-7+ books is just a cash grab usually; get to the fucking point...

Do stores like B+N basically only carry series at this point, because, being a series, they're a kinda "guaranteed" purchase?  Whereas a standalone book might be a risk for sales, so they don't bother?  

I just ended up leaving depressed and irritated.  All I wanted was one good book.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SD fan here, wondering - where have the unique/weird formations gone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 03:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for my once or twice a year check-in. (Sorry!) Thoughts on improving the sub, moderator applications, stuff like that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 11:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) In general - I've tried to be mostly hands-off with this sub.  I mean, it was only started as a sort of joke when I saw a comment in /r/shittyaskscience that asked if /r/shittyseduction existed.  It didn't, so I made this.  I didn't really know what to do after that, and thought I'd just kinda let the up/down vote system figure it out.

2) Quality - When this sub was a bit younger, the "hands-off" style seemed to work better. But I'm not so sure anymore.  Strike that, I'm pretty certain it doesn't work anymore.  Without calling anyone out, frankly, a lot of the posts aren't really shittyseduction but just, well, plain shitty.  

3) Mods - I had a second mod for awhile! But...then they deleted their account unexpectedly.  I've also started a new job semi-recently, and have some classes to be finished associated with that.  I'd like to spend time trying to "clean up" this sub a bit, but I can't.

If you think you'd be a good mod, send a PM.  The application is - send me your top 5 links from this sub all time, and If I basically agree, then you can join up and help out.  

I'll still try to help out around here a bit more either way.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 4] Speculation about one of Tyrion's lines from Episode 8. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 10:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exchange between Jaime and Tyrion in the prison - 

Tyrion: Matricide, patricide, infanticide, suicide. Theres no kind of killing that doesnt have its own word.  
Jaime: Cousins.  
Tyrion: Cousins! Youre right, there is no word for cousin-killing. Well done.  

I was binge-rewatching the season, so when it reached the final episode, and Tyrion shoots his father on the privy, it made me think for a second...

He just committed patricide.  He (technically) had previously committed matricide (his mother dying while giving birth to him).  

He didn't mention, say, regicide (killing a king), and he had no part in Joffrey's death.  He didn't mention homicide, and you could argue Shae was self defense (she grabbed a knife before he had done anything).  

Going back to what he did say, there's infanticide and suicide.  Infanticide?  According to the wiki, he and Tysha were together for two weeks, and secretly married, between first meeting and the rape by the guards that was ordered by his father.  And no one really knows what happened to Tysha after that.  

Was she pregnant with his child by that point? (They do specifically mention that Tyrion and Tysha had made love at least once, plus...the bad stuff could have caused a pregnancy as well.)  Tyrion was basically forced to rape her last.  Then he never sees her again, believing the story that she was a whore, when she was actually truly in love with him.  

Maybe, those awful events, and him leaving her, caused her to commit suicide.  And, in a way, at the same time infanticide.  

Meaning Tyrion was "responsible" for the four -cides that he names.  While the two prevalent -cides that are left off the list, he's either clearly not responsible for, or it can be argued it was self defense (or at most, manslaughter in modern-speak, acting in the heat of the moment/not pre-meditated).

Or, Speculation-B - those horrible events caused a miscarriage in Tysha, but she went on living.  Which would mean suicide would be the one last thing Tyrion hadn't been a part of, hinting at his future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fucking hell there wasn't a new episode tonight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 09:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on with Derrick Coleman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 06:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charger fan here, but I really liked his story and thought maybe he'd see some garbage time touches or something. Then I saw he doesn't have a single touch this season. Thought I'd read that he and Wilson had a good rapport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First World November Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 03:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are random mob-style killings (burying a body in the middle of a desert) going to, eventually, be the archaeological samples/fossils in a few hundred years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 06:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Huh...it seems like in the years 1800-2100, dying from a puncture wound in the back of the skull was the most likely/common cause of death?"

Edit: Deserts seem to store bodies so well, re:Egypt. Las Vegas, Mexico/US border, re-watching Breaking Bad and all the meth-head deaths.  Doesn't the dessert preserve boddies better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone here participate in the Arian Foster stock market/share-purchasing thing? Maybe not him but someone else in that? If so, what's your experience been like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 04:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when this first happened, and lots of opinions flying around both ways about how it might/might not work out.  

Did anyone here actually participate?  If so, what's it been like?  When he got injured did his "share price" drop, and if so did you buy up a lot of shares while it was low?  When he came back did the price rise?  

[The Arian Foster/Fantex/buying shares summation for those who don't know](http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/10/17/arian-foster-tracking-stock-investment-texans-fantex/2999201/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S04E04] If you're interested, the painting in the doctor's office and the possible influence on the episode. A wee bit of (maybe) relevant art history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The painting was 'Denial of St. Peter' by Caravaggio.  

To begin there is some direct relevance as, at the end of the episode, the doctor makes a reference to St. Peter, saying if Peter had said anything he'd have been crucified too.

[The painting in question](http://graphics8.nytimes.com/images/2012/06/08/arts/08FRAME_SPAN/08FRAME_SPAN-articleLarge-v3.jpg) features this exact confrontation - an angry Roman guard confronting Peter, while a maiden steps between them to intervene.  

Some quotes from a NYT article on the painting that seem to bear relevance on the episode - 

"In the best-known works darkness and light wage a battle" - I think we've seen a good bit of this throughout the series, but in the cinematography of the last few episodes, it seems especially relevant.  

"On the wall, the painting is even muddier than in reproductions  most of the light comes weakly over the guards right shoulder, falling on Peter, who makes a universal gesture of blamelessness, turning both hands toward his chest, as if protesting at that moment: Me? Im telling you, youve got the wrong fisherman." Again, referencing both the cinematography of the recent episodes, and the Doctor/Peter comparison.  

But possibly the most relevant bits of interest, relating to Beth - 

"But the longer I looked, the more it seemed to me that the saint  as the symbolic embodiment of the human frailty and faith that underpin Roman Catholic doctrine  was not the lead actor in the drama. It was the maid, whose eyes, catching the light with pinpoint reflections, somehow become the paintings center. "

and

"Her eyes seem to have come unfocused, and shes not looking at the guard she is facing but looking momentarily inward. Whatever precise Counter-Reformation doctrine the painting was once trying to expound, it is the maids hesitation and humanity in the moment of accusation that, to me, now remain as the paintings subject and its power." Which seems to resonate strongly with the final scene/episode in general.  

It just kinda jumped out to me; of all the paintings you could possibly include, why *that* one in particular? It must have some sort of relevance.  And if a Caravaggio, why not one of his more popular works? (There's a wee bit of art history class still bouncing around my head.)

**TL;DR** - On the left we have a Roman guard, and this was meant to be a scene right after Jesus's crucifixion, so he's clearly evil (Dawn/Slabtown people in general).  On the right is St. Peter, afraid of dying just as Jesus had and lying to prevent that outcome (The doctor, lying to save his own skin).  And in the middle is Beth, the maiden trying to save Peter by confirming his lie and allowing him to continue on.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The post for new Rose City members. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some useful links and stuff for people new to Rose - 

Are you familiar with the nerd.nu livemap of the server? Pez has done some amazing work to improve it.  [You can find how to improve it here](http://redd.it/2hq193)

Are you experienced with mods?  Maybe not, but always wondered how they helped?  Pez also put together a really awesome modpack that includes things like a minimap, horse stats, optifine, and more.  [Here is the link/instructions for that](http://redd.it/2fgsc0)

After you have that modpack installed, Zomise has many schematics (one of the mods) available for download via dropbox [if you go here](http://redd.it/2hfhuy)

If you're wondering how the town layout works, [this image should help](http://i.imgur.com/xmWrYbp.png).

And finally, within this sub, if you want username flair (so your MC name shows up on reddit posts here), just [go here](http://redd.it/2gijt0) to request it!

Edit: oh, and finally finally, we have a planning server.  If you're interested, message one of the mayors in game for details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
