<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject348</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah no worries man, each to their own. It's a pretty different sound to what we've been given by donald before, and i've got a lot of friends  who have been a bit put off by it. 

I think a lot of it just comes down to giving it a chance, but also accepting that sometimes its okay to have different tastes and preferences. just enjoy the music man! Whatever sound that may be for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zzlAvPZT2nA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While a significant part of the video, my focus isn't on the tackle, but rather the reaction of demonstrators after the fact. So while you raise a very interesting point (like i had no idea that he has aspergers, and i really appreciate the sharing of a source), i think i was sharing this with the understanding that political alignment had no relevance in the video

admittedly that's probably on me for mentioning their alignment in the title. But yeah i merely meant to share here because of its setting and the turn of events after the tackle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh god what have i done. i just thought the "shame" bit was funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Trump supporters chant "shame" as man is escorted through building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks Good Though </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [50/50] Bored School Boy narrowly misses violent car crash (SFW) | Bored School Boy killed by violent car crash (NSFW/L) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe Maybe Maybe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoying his stone collection in peace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 15:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for some reason 'Lost in the World' just didn't resonate with me at first but now its one of my all time favourite Kanye Songs. Weird how it works like that sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is soo soo good! and Just that laugh, like Donald knows something we don't and we're being taken on this crazy-experimental trip of which we really have no idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same too pretty please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
