<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9958</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot! And how long does it take for me to feel a difference in my body, if any? Not sure what to expect moving forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revenge mode needs to be removed? You cray cray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm nowhere near pro but from what I have seen and read raider is the weakest. LB has got sick combos and moves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't a revenge gain by attack. There's revenge mode attack which increases damage while in the revenge state. But no revenge gain by attacking, only revenge gain by injury and defense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What character do you use and have any clips of this? I'm yet to get revenge when I'm ranking in a 2v1 and the gain in a 1v1 is extremely slow. I'm a conqueror btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IF newbie here looking for tips and advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

So I started IF yesterday after a few weeks of reducing my meal portions and dieting. I'm eating my first meal at 12 and continue to eat until around 8-10 depending on when I go to the gym, so on average I fast between 9-12pm for a total of about 15 hours of fasting.

Basically I'm just looking for any tips and advice as I begin this lifestyle. What can I expect? What would you have done differently knowing what you know now?

Any help would be great! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand. But that's how you can win a 1v4. This discourages ganking and allows you to stop a gank and actually win. I like it as is, minus the 1v1 gain aspect of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it should be a thing. Winning 1vX is some of the most fun me and all my friends have. Removing revenge gain in a 1v1 is fine, but revenge works fine in 1v2+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many cases it is. Because of my gear as conqueror I can kill enemies who are critical whereas in a duel or mode with no gear stats I cannot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily, and this is in regard to your edit. But I'm consider myself casual and many times I feel the only reason I perform well is because of my gear. High skill players tend to move on to other characters more often since they play more often, and in those encounters I do well and even dominate at times due to the fact my gear is so much better than theirs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's it bugged? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind if they remove revenge gain from 1v1 but any other tweak is overkill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People need to realize gear stats aren't bad and either is Dominion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to start by saying that I see Dominion and gear stats get a lot of hate on this sub. Most of the complaints are about gear stats and balance and competitive play and feats and the list goes on. 

Now, I understand that most people on this sub play a lot and therefore are pretty good at the game. I also understand that by being good at the game you get annoyed when someone not as good as you are, but with far better gear, beats you solely because of their gear.

However, I draw the line when people CLAIM that gear stats are ruining the game. Let's take Overwatch as an example. Recently it underwent many changes that affected only the top their of players and did not affect anyone in bronze, gold, or platinum. Do you know how much of the player base falls under diamond??? 85%. That means that most players are casual and not highly skilled.

I feel the same goes for many games, and for honor is no exception. I'm not the best player around and I gladly accept that. My schedule and life only affords me an hour or two of game time, about every other day, and that's fine. When I sit down to play do you think I want a super balanced always competitive fight where multiple enemies mean certain death and a 1v1 against a really good player means I lose always?

No, if you're good at the game and are trying a new character, and I'm using my main with 108 gear, I WANT to be able to hang with you and beat you even if it's ONLY because of my gear. If the only way I can get an insane quad kill is by dropping a catapult on your team or if you are guarded a ladder so we can't climb up and I take you out with a heat seaking guided  arrow, so be it.

Gear stats are fine, they make the game fun and interesting for players of all skill levels, especially for casuals who make up most of the player base. Denying these players the ability to feel bad ass, win, and win consistently enough to warrant continued play means they will move on to the next fun to play game, leaving your beloved competitive game a Barron wasteland of inevitable death.


TL;DR gear stats are fine because they help casuals who make up most of the player base. Don't claim GS ruins the game when in fact it makes it enjoyable for all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salchichas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gear makes the game more fun but we all have our own opinions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this is a known bug in the game that has recently been patched. It was just patched today on console and it was patched a few weeks ago on PC. For the record, it was a very strong move but shouldn't have been there so I understand the salt but also just ZzZZ at all the the tears as well Q.Q moves like that should get he axe regardless of how useful they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your English is far better than most who speak it as a first language lol and a TL;Dr would be nice, no way I was gonna read all of that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm... Lawbringer and nobushi are quite strong... I'll give you raider though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may not be able to teach you how to get good-er. But, I may be able to teach you how not to become worse-erer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. It's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from an anime, Naruto. I might be a tin can but I'm a weeb at heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What platform do you play on? Maybe it's a platform thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ubi was talking about looking into conqueror for possible nerfs. So I guess they think otherwise which blows my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His shield bash is dodgeable. Mines gets dodged a lot. Why make it slower to the point it's not usable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're waiting for the game to become decent? Shit, I'm over here obsessing over how amazing the game is lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok ill say it. Conqueror needs a buff, not a nerf. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fact. He is fine as is, all he needs is a bit more damage to be able to take out opponents in critical health and he will be perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How sure are you of this? I've never had a side heavy get blocked. How can everyone I face be this stupid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love how wardens look end game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused? The bash is easily dodged and he has a guaranteed side heavy on GB. What am I missing lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warlord is definitely overall better than conqueror. Just saying in the hands of a good conqueror it's not just a one sided slaughter. I beat warlords consistently. But I do lose too. Just not as often as I win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have to avoid every head but. I just avoid most headbutts. Plus as I dodge and go into my shield bash I just bash then away. A couple repeats of that and they're stamina drained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about. This sub is really filled with great people lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dodge?  Lol the headbutt is dodgeable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a ton! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I have to play very turtly in order to win. If I am the aggressor then the warlord has the advantage. Smart warlords that know this results in a starefest where we fall asleep on each other and cuddle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider yourself lucky then. I have the exact same opinion about warlords but I'm a conqueror. I feel they are very one dimensional and I almost always beat them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much sums it all up. Basically what I would've said if I wasn't both too lazy to do so and also not wasting my life away playing this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm I guess you're just cheaper than I am then. I don't see movie tickets as rip off and 1 dollar per hour for a game is ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep 3 bucket head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why so? If you compare it to the price of a movie ticket let's say, 2 hours for 10 bucks. That means all you need to play to get your money worth from a 60 dollar game is 12 hours. Given the fact that you'll most likely go well above 12 hours you're getting better value than a night out in the movies by a long shot. Especially that I myself am already approaching the 100 hour mark. This game has infinite value and is well worth 60. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too enjoy skirmish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for your self. I dropped 60 on the game and another 60 on steel packs. All worth since I'm at about 70 hours played and counting. Definitely getting my money worth from this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/forfashion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But isn't that just a normal overhead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you're awesome with that LB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I like to post my conqueror right up on corpse of my enemy and emote spam for as long as I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kensei nerf video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys can someone link me a video of the move that is being nerfed, or fixed, for the kensei. I see people talk about it but am still confused as to what exactly is being changed. So, any video showing the move that will no longer work? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kensei ninja nerf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a video of the move that is being nerfed for kensei? I'm confused as to what it is exactly and was wondering someone had video so I can actually see it live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
