<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9951</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Within the past 1.5 months, i have already DE'd Neptulon, Malorne and FR4K.
But i used them to build up some really necessary legendaries. Got Sylvanas, Ragnaros and Dr. Boom. Never spent a dime of real money on buying packs.

I have nearly zero doubt these are the cards that will weather the meta and remain useful for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because they always have Steamwheedle Sniper out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 18:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit dumb, but you were **really** unlucky too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 15:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and Malygos and Nozdormu and Onyxia (and the whelps) and Deathwing and Faerie Dragon and Ysera's Green Drake and so on.

It'd be pretty decent, actually. Malygos still sees some play as does Onyxia from time to time. Hardly ever see Deathwing though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 15:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can never forget VanCleef, because of Unstable Portal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 02:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legendaries aside...

Ancient of Lore

Ancient of War

Force of Nature (Can you guess why i don't play Druid a lot? :D)

Any of the giants aside from one Sea Giant

Shadowflame (No handlock for me)

Lay on Hands

SI7 guy

Doomsayer

Ice Block

Doomguard (had to make them)

Lightning Storm (had to make it, still only have the one)

Same as you, Knife Juggler (had to make it, still only have the one)

Faceless Manipulator (this one's really been useful. For that, I DE'd a Leeroy i got shortly after the nerf, no regrets so far)

And of course, in this meta, BGH...

I guess i'm lucky i have most of the necessities for Control Warrior, it's been my main deck for a while now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 00:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing f2p for what i think is now a year. Still no Sylvanas yet. Just recently had to sacrifice Neptulon and Foe Reaper 4000 to finally get Dr. Boom!

Guess i'm not just jealous of his voice alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
