<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 10:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The collection was never meant to be a remaster, just a collection of ports. If you cant play a game without it looking HD I feel for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 10:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are indeed correct! Jet Force Gemini had widescreen and surround sound on N64! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 16:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a tutorial level? I didnt know that.

^^^^Dont ^^^^hurt ^^^^me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 16:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/trypophobia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 10:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, thats a good GWG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 10:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the longest time MGS has been closer to Playstation consoles to Xbox Consoles. Many of the people I know who have an Xbox One have only ever had Xboxes and never played a Metal Gear game so they're are not getting. I also know a ton of people put off by the amount of backstory.

Maybe that's the reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 10:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I've never heard that before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 10:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes an awful lot of sense. Yeah this was for TiP already 1--%d the first one.

Thanks bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 10:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks for letting me know. I am on/off playing this game at the moment and that will change the way I approach endgame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have more than one garden do what you've done on other gardens carry over? If I master romance a species does the other garden recognise that I've done that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 16:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically how I beat her. Be consistent during the race and right at the end go full on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make best use of my gardens space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 16:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved this game years ago and I'm playing through both again on Rare Replay however Leafos keeps telling me that my garden is too cluttered and there isnt enough room for anything else. I am at the biggest garden size and it doesnt look like anything that I want it to look like. Feels a bit restrictive here, you got any tips for use of space?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 12:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean it's not your thing? You have a thing against Trolls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 15:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now there isn't a way to change any controls in Conker. I got used to it though so it should be okay, if it really prohibits your enjoyment then don't worry because Rare have said they will change it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 19:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sonic PR guy is amazing 

http://i.imgur.com/cZKXhKb.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *looks at thumbnail*

So it begins... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 17:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GT- specialunitt

20/M/UK

Recently got Destiny and Halo MCC and totally willing to play either of those.

I have Rare Replay, Titanfall, GTA V and Minecraft also which all have multiplayer. If I'm playing single player I'm more than willing to talk in party chat! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 12:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I dont think that's necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion thread] Octodad Dadliest Catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 10:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this coy little website over at /r/internetisbeautiful. With sites like this, it surely is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 15:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 15:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I enjoyed was it was Jake Hurwitz. Other than that it was okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [m] ooooof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 13:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 12:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Any opportunity to bring this up!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tkPjS1CdbU4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 10:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no they cant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only just discovered this guy. Gemstones - Blind Elephant Album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 14:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [m] loving every mouthful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 14:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I being a bit reckless? [Christians Only] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 09:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really struggle with gluttony and eating and consuming. That also links to my struggle with money. Over the past week I have spent pretty much my entire wage on video games and food that hasnt been needed. As such I have decided that today I am going to fast food. I havent spoke to anyone about this but does this seem biblical? There seems to be many opinions online about repentance and fasting and I dont want to jump into something if it's not right and I definatley dont want to appear to be legalistic. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Rare didn't do that game. That was Krome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 11:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GT - specialUnitt

Self deprecating British 20 year old with mic. Have Rare Replay and play it a lot but play GTA, titanfall and battlefield 4 online  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 13:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 13:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth pointing out that Banjo Kazooie, Tooie and Perfect Dark are all the Xbox Live Arcade Remakes of the games that occured in 2011. There was a texture and control upgrade and widescreen. So naturally those games play very very well. However the other N64 games such as Conker and Blast Corps play very well to in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 15:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still want to get fatter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 14:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See who your real friends are... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 13:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relaxed [m] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 11:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasnt around then! But I'll play N B sometime, my GT is subject1260nitt :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 16:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely and I cant wait to get bigger and bigger.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 16:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 00:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can use the cannon?

Fuck, thanks! That's going to be easier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at the south of the map by GCPD. You have to hit the question marks when in the rings I'm just not fast enough to do this. Is there something I'm missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody got any hints for this riddle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 18:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The option is greyed out before broadcast and its on the recomended one apparently.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Streaming from Xbox one, app warns me of lag . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 14:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The app asks me to change my stream resolution but it won't let me! I've checked my internet speed and it's well above the minimum. What can I do to fix this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 14:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 year old / UK

obsessed with Rare Replay but would love to talk to people in party chat while playing I miss that.

Also have titanfall, gta and minecraft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting kicked from party chat [tech] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 13:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My connection is fine and fast enough but I keep randomly keep getting disconnected from parties without the notification coming up. Anyone got a fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a huge meal tonight... [m] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 00:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 10:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atic Atac doesnt get enough love. None of the Spectrum games do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [m] not big enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 19:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 14:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain your problems with the camera? i keep seeing complaints but for me it moves like B-K's and I'm having 0 problems.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 14:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gumtree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 14:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Rise of the Tomb Raider is going to be a 8 bit platformer on the 360 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 11:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only the 360 ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... should we start a Rare Replay multiplayer thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 10:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen alot of people asking about online multiplayer with the collection. Maybe we could start a thread where people try to play these games?

Some of these games are too old and not popular enough to find people in matchmaking.

What do you say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 16:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rare Replay.. for the rest of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 12:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, that looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything with Lego in the title :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banjo Tooie is 1-4 players but isnt co-op. Theres a multiplayer mode that unlocks Multiplayer versions of each of the Minigames once you play them in the main game :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority of the games have some sort of multiplayer, more games have local multiplayer than online. Any game that had local or online multiplayer on release has it intact for this collection.

I cant remember them all off the top of my head but there is alot of multiplayer options here.

Edit: [This handy dandy list may help you :)] (https://www.reddit.com/r/xboxone/comments/3b7609/will_rare_replay_have_multiplayer/csjhohq)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It;s because the controls arent bad with an N64 controller but just dont work with an Xbox One </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish it did though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think we will find many people matchmaking, I think for Rare Replay games we should make some lobbies and announced them here or else where. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 10:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 20:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Jet Force Gemini isn't an Xbox port is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 20:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly off topic is Bad fur day widescreen optimised like Jet force or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 20:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know if there's a way to make Conker wide screen like Jet force?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 17:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont like the redesigns of the character here. They look a bit too 'Minionish' if you get what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 15:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can turn that off.

What are the camera controls like on Conker? Does it try to replicate the feeling of the N64 C-Buttons or is it free flowing like the XBLA version of B-K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 15:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does the camera control in Conkers Bad Fur Day does it try to emulate the C-Buttons from the N64 days like DK64 for Wii U? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 14:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joining the preview program is one of the most dangerous things you could ever do. There's about a 60% chance that Phil Spencer himself will come out of your Xbox and eat your genitals.

Joking aside, there's always the risk something could happen but if you want to make Xbox better for everyone then go for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 12:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anybody down for playing some multiplayer on this in the next few days? Perfect Dark? NaB? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 11:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear some of the 360 games have slow down? Do Rare know about this and is it getting patched? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask, why does online multiplayer for a game matter so much to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesnt, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What he said was *kinda* right but not really. 

Viva Pinata is a garden simulator, you have to make your garden nice and approachable for Pinatas to come and then you look after the Pinatas.

It's like Pokemon as you collect these creatures but you dont fight them or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a reason that this collection exists. The price tag is worth it for the Banjo trilogy alone, they dont make platformers like that anymore. With creative writing and great worlds I highly reccomend this collection. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The collection also has Jetpac refuelled which I reccomend if you enjoyed the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 10:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's awesome. It's the Perfect Dark XBLA version which came with online play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is everything ok? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 13:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 13:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's devastating! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're gonna groove tonight We'll make you feel alright Simpsons Christmas Boogie! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 13:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I make the bible approachable and easy to read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 23:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many people who ask where to start reading the bible and which book to start on. That's not my problem, I know the basics of the word of God and know what I want to read but never actually read it. I want to get serious about this but I have an awful attention span and just don't know how to approach the bible. I'm inclined to read the bible as I would any other book, but I just don't remember any of it. And if I take notes and have a companion text with me I get bored easily and it feels too school like. How should I approach the bible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is Rare Replay allowing us to play backwards compatable games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 19:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering as Rare replay's 360 games are backwards compatibility, how do we play them if backwards compat isn't out yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 22:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely am! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 19:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this every month.

subject1260nitt

20 / UK

I have a few games like Minecraft, GTA . I want to make friends! Let me be friends with you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 22:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK here still playing up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 21:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems worldwide to me...

UK gamer reporting in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 21:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, all friends off and can't join parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 17:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the film didn't do anything different and I definitely didn't feel threatened by Ultron at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people love the elephant joke so much? [Season 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 12:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep seeing people on this sub say that their favourite joke was the elephant joke. It was awful, 'Lets talk about the elephant in the room' Oh look its an elephant and he's in the room. Thats not funny. How he reacted isnt funny either it would have been better if he did a slight perk up as he listened but to get completley irate about it isnt the subtle writing I expect for Bojack Horseman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buying yet another PS2 what are some unknown games I should check out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 10:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had two ps2's but sold both for some spare cash. Found a great deal on one the other day and was wondering what unknown games I should check out to keep me interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 10:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could I get an invite to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive loved it since it came out a year ago! True though a lot more people watching! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My game list is already way too long and that just seems super lazy to me

Can I ask why this is a problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banjo Kazooie and Tooie are my two favourite games of all time and I love Nut and Bolts, it's not a platformer no but it does have that Rare charm and wit that makes it completely worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cant get past the carrot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toy Story reference? Nah! Boy Cory severance! Cory is a flame we need to douse when he is in his Coy COy House! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Arnold Palmer

Nah! Anal farmer! Erect penis is my name, and raping teemasters is my game.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTFO? Nah Me The Cock Bout! A wrestling match for this sad sack makes me crackalack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead horse? Nah! Dead course! A round of golf for this teemaster makes sugar in your tea. Caster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad joke? Nah bad you! You coy smash bros dweebs need to learn how to take a joke... an up the butt poke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goku is coming to Smash Bros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wasn't that a great Itchy and Scratchy cartoon, kids? Well, we've got another one coming right up. But first! I've got a hankering' for some pork products! Mmmm... Look! Plump, succulent sausage. Honey-smoked bacon. And glistening, sizzling... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 11:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've lost my wallet... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 10:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've cancelled my cards but I am still rather annoyed about it. 2nd time this has happened! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want [m]y belly to get bigger and bigger. I want to be a gluttonous piggie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I replayed it recently. 

Differing opinions is good, I just like hearing why we have them

Thanks for answering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Absolutely new to Minecraft, never played the game before. If you want to play I'm down to clown but bare with me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamertag is subject1260nitt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject1260nitt is my GT. I'll add you now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your reasoning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 10:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject1260nitt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject1260nitt

20 year old UK. Trying to 100% Arkham Knight and complete all the indie platformers I bought or got for free.

However I do have GTA or Titanfall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuuuuuuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've shared the good review... it makes sense to share the not so good ones to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you see McDonalds as a career or are you hoping to take your managerial skills somewhere else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does there anyone who meet the same question with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 15:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'll sign. 

UK fan here to! Isnt the Blu Ray region free though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man I agree with you people should be careful but maybe you should unsub from here until you watch it? I can imagine that it will only be Season 2 talk around here for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shary Bobbins and I were engaged to be wed back in the old country. Then she got her eyesight back. Suddenly the ugliest man in Glasgow wasn't good enough for her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 14:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How're you guys watching Season 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 10:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you can? Binge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsthump is a spoof new website... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 12:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this discussion topic on Facebook, thought it'd be interesting to hear what you guys think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 08:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice guy on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> yeah we got you there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think that when Jake and Amir become famous and classless they will leave us on the floor assless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm serious dudes, when you hit the big time and take a slice of that big big pie you better give us back some of that sweet sweet cheese. You put in the hard work? We all had a good smirk! You owe us. Dweebs.

^^^Bury ^^^me ^^^in ^^^d-votes ^^^if ^^^y'all ^^^disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 10:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My deep hurt and apathy have screwed up my future job prospects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 10:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was told today by a friend that he was going to employ me for his charity when I left my apprenticeship but my boss didnt give me a favourable review. I'm apathatic and dont know why and dont know how I will change, I feel stuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your father traded all our tools for M M's again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [minor spoilers] only the Joker audio tapes have subtitles... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to the deacon or professor pyg tapes subtitles don't appear. It's really hard to hear what professor pyg is saying so what's the deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't believe the whole thing [m] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 15:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If somebody's in here, you're in for some serious ass forkin'! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats everyones favourite DVD/Blu ray menu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought out my old Shrek 2 dvd the other day for my neice and nephew and remembered the fun times I had on the menu alone back when DVD games were a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get up, mow the lawn! Move it on the double! 'Cause if you don't, you're in deep, deep trouble! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the purpose of fasting? [christians only] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 10:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen people say they have fasted for a period after repentance. Apparently this helped them, how what does it do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to have riddler trophies in buildings added to your map? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Places like Panessa studios dont have any informants inside the building or around. Do I have to find a map like the first Arkham game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to move rooms that you've already built or are they stuck where they are unless you demolish them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The old CITV logo.. [UK] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I dont like milk in my cereal and prefer it dry. Do you all hate me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 15:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING NEWS: JONTRON IS PLAYING ARIN HANSON IN JONTRON DE MOVIE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 11:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Racists... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Toy Story 2 video game commercial that played before the movie on the Toy Story 2 VHS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 12:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me when I logged onto Reddit this morning... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 12:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where in the actual fart is my complete blu ray set? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 11:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Mr and Mrs Blumenwitz! You know what I want? I want you to get off your jewish behinds and make me a complete blu ray set! Whats that? It's too much work? How about too much *twerk*. I've been a loyal fan for half a millennia and all I have is salmonellaia. You gave me hours of free content and what I want to do it give something back to you guys by you creating a blu ray set. ASS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Victoria, why has she been fired and why is everyone upset about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 10:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyti[m]e I touch my belly I get turned on so bad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cinematic History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making Dennis the Menace Chocolate Cupcakes all the time as a kid! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Christians Only] Christianity to me has become nothing more than something I know and is no longer something I am involved in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 11:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever a relationship with Jesus is, I wouldnt say I have one now. I'm looking away, I'm looking into the world and seeing I would be happier. I feel abandoned by God. I can no longer speak to him because He has disappointed me in the past. If he's all loving and He loves me, I cant feel it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marry her, yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A way to find whats coming out when? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 15:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the UK and right now I have to go on the websites to find individual comics and then see when the next one is out. Is there an easier way to see whats out and when? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im better than dirt. Well, most kinds of dirt, not that fancy store-bought dirt I cant compete with that stuff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like Harrison Ford Thunderbird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes](http://i.ytimg.com/vi/V4eiVvPWC8Y/hqdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because of this image, I had many nightmares </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 12:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started talking to a girl yesterday, I'm awful at keeping any sort of communication going for more than a day please help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 11:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I okily, dokily, schmokily do! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 16:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get started with DC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 22:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a suicide squad graphic novel the other day, but doing research people tend not to enjoy Adam Glass's, I got confused because I wasn't sure which suicide squad was the newest one. Anyway marvel have secret wars what does dc have to help get into it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What percentage does the campaign finish at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at 30% atm. Only doing side missions when the game tells me to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the lip animations awful in Arkham Knight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's new excuse after 4 years for audio not to match up to the lip movements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the percentage by the Continue Story a whole game percentage or just a story mission percentage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to go through the game too quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The water that comes out the tap is too cold so my teeth hurt when I drink it, as a result I have to buy bottled water instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 09:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me understand the continuity of secret wars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought Spider-Man renew your views #1 and I'm just curious is this happening during secret wars? Because Spider-Man takes place in the main secret wars? Is it after and what about the other amazing Spider-Man comics like #18 that come out a few weeks ago. Kinda new to comics so thanks for any help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [New to comics] What do I do if I miss a comic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my local comic book store no longer has a comic or a comic book run started months ago that I like the look of now? Is that it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just getting into Comics; got a few newer stories but now interested in looking into the older stuff. What are some easy to find good Silver Age comics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for some music [Minor Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 10:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know what the track is called that plays when you're in Ace Chemicals and its blowing up around you while talking to Alfred? That bit hit me quite emotionally and the backing music really set the tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else feel that Arkham Knights audio is a little bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primarily the voice acting, the lip synching is all over the place and the characters don't close their mouths half the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The identity of the Arkham Knight got spoiled for me on the day of release... [No Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 12:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Arkham Knights identity got spoiled for me on the day of release... [No Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 11:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those whose first Arkham game is Arkham knight... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 09:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made you delve into the game now? What didn't interest you in asylum and city and what won you over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox doesn't seem to be downloading when console is off and instant on is on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 07:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all last night I bought Arkham Knight from the Xbox store so that the game could install throughout the night and when I go to work today so I can just straight up play when I get home but checking on the progress this morning and there hasn't been any? The console is on instant on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the Season Pass cover preorder exclusive dlc in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'll be Gus, the lovable chimney-sweep. Clean as a whistle, sharp as a thistle, best in all Westminster. Yeah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curse you magic beans! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how the does xbober backwads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get my friends to give Titanfall a chance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 10:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My general policy is that playing with friends is always a ton more fun than playing alone, trouble is I only have 1 friend who has the game on Xbox and he is more of a PC gamer. I love the game and seeing as you can pretty much get it for free this month I want to convince of my other friends to get it. They say they don't like it because it's too simple, or "Battlefield lite", however I think under the surface is a shooter they all would enjoy. None of them have tried it and are basing opinions on what they've heard. How would I go about convincing them?

Edit: I'm an awful speller.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do people still play Titanfall? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 13:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All who were too late to preorder the collectors edition unite! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 10:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family holiday at Blackpool UK - any of you simpofiles ever played this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 12:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm on a family holiday to Blackpool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 01:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What episode of IIFY do The Master and The Master reveal there Snapchats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 09:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been away for a few months being especially coy and I feel like I'm missing out on the impending shit storm by not having these crude jews on Snappy C! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, I dont remember saying that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a clear, smelly penis leak. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 11:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man got off the train leaving his seat exposed, about 5 of us were in the immediate proximity to claim it but no body did in case someone else wanted it. As soon as I got the courage to ask, someone from the next stop sat on it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 11:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Stereo Headset as headphones for music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 21:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may seem like a stupid question but if I were to take my stereo headset away with me for a week and use them as headphones for podcasts etc how good would they be? And would they break easily from lots of use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legalized gambling is a bad idea. You can build a casino over my dead body. Blah blah blah blah blah. Blah blah blah, blah blah blah blah blah. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 11:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This community is dead, but I wanted to share the first part of a six part Pleasure Beach documentary from 1997. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 10:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SEX! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 09:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the Game Grumps GTA V crews? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 10:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got an Xbone with GTA V and was looking forward to joining the GG crew. Search the sub and cant seem to find them. :[ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats going on with Fifa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox One resolution worries.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Saw this article] (http://venturebeat.com/2015/03/30/the-witcher-3-producer-says-hed-rather-play-it-on-a-pc-at-minimum-settings-than-on-xbox-one/) confused by the whole matter.

Why doesnt the Xbox have as good resolution as the PS4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never played a Halo game and I want the most biased people on Reddit to convince me to buy the MCC to catch up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 11:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats right! I have never played a Halo game. I found the series a bit boring seeing as I dont really like FPS' or Sci Fi that much. I had a 360 for Party chat and now have a One because thats what my best friend has and we play GTA together. However the Xbox exclusives have never done anything for me and I feel like Im missing out. 4 games for 25 pounds is an awesome deal so please, I just need a little bit of a push. 

2 questions;

Is there online co op on each game?
Are all the games remasters of the originals or just the Orignal game, for example is Halo 2 remastered or is it just the Xbox game? Same for Halo 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Xbox Ones UI laggy for anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 00:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate inviting people to games and using the dashboard on the thing, it just lags. Also when returning to the game theres a black screen for 2 seconds or some stutter. Causing online deaths etc. For a console that's selling points is its multimedia and multitasking potential I cant say im not a little disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbone notifications question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 13:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing sunset overdrive and the Xbox notified me that a clip was recording, checking the clip it was from a piece of gameplay that occurred 5 minutes before the notification. I have this kinda problem with other notifications to ... Game invites, achievements etc. is this a normal problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I might have bought a stolen Xbox One which in turn may destroy my disabled teenagers heart. [Rant] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 09:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everybody, so for my sons 15th birthday I deicded to get him an Xbox One with live, a mic and a few games. Our family has hit a bit of financial difficulty so buying it new wasnt an option, I got it from Gumtree. I got to the place and brought the console. He had 1 xbox one and a few xbox 360's, he told me he was a merchant and just kept selling them on. Of course I thought nothing of it, and took the console home. We set everything up for him, but then it hit me. What if the console was stolen? My sons on Xbox Live at the moment and because of his difficulties wont understand the situation. Can they track a stolen console to our house if its connected to live? Half of me believes the man who sold it but the other skeptical side doesnt. If the consoles gone we probably wont be able to afford another one this year. So... thats my day.


Edit: without reading the situation, the title is hilarious.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> xbone game install times... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 11:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I bought an Xbone off someone on Gumtree. I put in Project Spark (the game it came with) and it took nigh on an hour to install + half hour to update. Is this normal or abnormal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting an Xbone tonight, is GTA V still played online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 15:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It seems that I have been doubting as a Christian with my head still being firmly within the faith. I have escalated to doubting as an agnostic who isnt really sure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres so many thoughts going through my mind as an ex christian. "Am I only doing this to justify my sin?" being the main one. The more I think of these issues the more I actually see how desensitised I have become to life. Working at a Christian chairty isnt helping either and neither is my volunteering at our Churches youth. Whatever happens, I am finally finding a happier me.

Sorry if this made no sense, my thoughts are everywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
