<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject16</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha Yeah he will rule against Obama, when Trump comes for them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch: Ill Have No Difficulty' Ruling Against the President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything that can be done to improve on Paul Ryan's terrible Health Care Bill? 

Or to make sure it does not pass the House? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Spencer really defended Flynn. (Who lied to Pence and was fired because of it).

Stone on the other hand he really tried to paint as a very distant person. 

So I guess there is something fishy about Stone. He paints himself as a trickster, so there may have been some rules he broke. This could reflect badly on our President if it comes to light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He made up an accusation that caused a diplomatic incident with Americas closest ally.

By accusing the British he most likely pissed of Rupert Murdoch who owns Fox News. 

There are limits of what Murdoch tolerates. He only supports Trump as long as it suits him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By accusing the British he most likely pissed of Rupert Murdoch. 

Remember that Fox News is controlled by this guy:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rupert_Murdoch#Activities_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is a good thing when partisan sites have articles that include paragraphs like this one:

It's understandable that the White House would want to distance itself from someone who has reportedly been investigated by the FBI for ties to Russia. But this is a bit much.

 When it comes from a source they otherwise trust it is much harder for Trump supporters to dismiss basic reality.  

I do not argue to support them in general. But whenever they report something like this I think it is way better to upvote for example Fox News and lead the clicks to them, than to click-bait factories like the Independent. 

Obviously not when they report on some reality-bending bullshit Hannity cooked up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just made up some shit, that caused a diplomatic incident. Even Fox News has it's limits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nur amateure habe keine alts. 
bin doch nicht auf der arbeit mit dem gleichen wie daheim eingeloggt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is a good idea to give clicks to shitty outlets whenever they report the truth. 

Reward them with clicks aka ad revenue so they have a financial incentive to show the truth. 

They will reach more Trump supporters than the liberal publications that just shout into the echo chamber.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spencer said Trump did not talk to him recently and it seemed like Trump does not want to appear close to him. 
 
I guess they know something is wrong with him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who doesn't? The government? Or the Russian?
Isn't polonium Putin's MO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> von einem auf den anderen tag komplett sein gesicht wandelt ist natrlich wenig beunruhigend

Das ist mit Verlaub gesagt Bullshit. Trump ist fr jeden der sich auch nur ein bisschen mit Politik ein einschneidendes Erlebnis gewesen und hat alles im negativen Sinne auf den Kopf gestellt. 

Er hat sich bewusst mit Ignoranz gebrstet und jede noch so simple politische Logik durch seine Gefhle ersetzt. 
Das fhrt halt einfach dazu, dass Leute die sich mit dem Thema beschftigen, dem gelinde gesagt kritisch gegenber stehen.

Die Debattenkultur seiner Anhnger hilft sicherlich auch nicht. The_Donald wird ja auch nur durch massivste Zensur   Votemanipulation zusammengehalten. Einfach mal vergleichen wie sich die Anzahl der gelschten Kommentare in politics und the_donald verhlt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweets were a bit low-energy. Most likely just a staffer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His staff probably organized it that way to keep him from making crazy tweets in response to what he sees on television. 

Bit of a shame really. Would have loved to have him dig himself in deeper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha crazy cherry picking from that hearing. 

And even with that this is the stuff they can find? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she does this:

She is, she explained, sympathetic to any woman who makes the decision to terminate a pregnancy. Do I know anybody who ever got an abortion? Well, of course I do. Ive driven them there. Ive helped pay.

But tries to overthrow Roe vs. Wade?

How will this go over with her pro-life followers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is, she explained, sympathetic to any woman who makes the decision to terminate a pregnancy. Do I know anybody who ever got an abortion? Well, of course I do. Ive driven them there. Ive helped pay.

That is kind of unexpected, isn't it? Is this real or fake news?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They lead the country. Errors like this one are unforgivable. National Security should be in the hand of people who give their best all the time. And do not lie to their superiors. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lied to Pence. So I think he does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real. Would be better then that drug-warrior Sessions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did they manage to come up with "resign".

She absolutely did not say that. 

This article is bullshit. Or more importantly the headline. 

Do not put words in people's mouth that they did not say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hier eine Studie in der die Namen variiert worden sind. Abhngige Variable in dem Fall aber Einschtzung eines Abstracts nach wissenschaftlicher Qualitt. Je nachdem ob ein Frauen oder Mnnername drber steht wird dessen Qualitt anders eingeschtzt (unterscheidet sich dann zustzlich noch nach Thema):

http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1075547012472684

Namen (Nachnamen wurden zufllig mit den Vornamen kombiniert):
Andrew Stone Brenda Collins
Douglas Burns Jennifer Peters
Craig Harrison Michelle Arnold
Jeffrey Crawford Patricia Warren
Stephen Murphy Melissa Jordan
Robert Phillips Amy Bell
Timothy Kelley Anne Cooper
Brian Stevens Janet Henry
Matthew Webb Lisa Sanders
James Nichols Elizabeth Hunter
Joseph Lewis Lori Ellis
David Hicks Christine Russell
Gary Sullivan Pamela Richardson
John Moore Susan Scott
Donald Elliott

Weiterhin bezglich der Mohammed Sachen gibt es teilweise auch Forschung. Hier wre ein Beispiel wo es um die Einschtzungen von Geschworenen geht:

[A perpetrator who assaulted an Arabic victim was blamed less than one who assaulted a Caucasian or African American victim, but juror race moderated this effect. This pattern of bias against victims with Arabic names was observed among Latin American jurors but not among Caucasian or African American jurors.](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/13218719.2012.736283)

Hier wre noch ein Beispiel in dem sich Schweden in konomischen Szenarien gegenber Leuten unterschiedlich verhalten, je nach Namen:

[The family name of the players was exposed to their co-players. Results for the trust game showed no significant discrimination against co-players with foreign backgrounds. On the other hand, the results for the dictator game showed a statistically significant discriminatory behaviour by men against co-players with non-European backgrounds. The discriminatory behaviour was solely a male phenomenon. In the second experiment, the dictator game was replicated to check the stability of the results in the first experiment. The second experiment also examined whether people with foreign backgrounds discriminate against other people with foreign backgrounds; that is, the purpose was to discover whether discrimination is systematic. The observations in the second experiment underlined the results found in the first experiment: foreign co-players are discriminated against by Swedish players. ]
(http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/00036840801964609)

Und um wieder zur Berufsauswahl zurckzukommen. In dieser sehr berhmten Studie wurden Bewerbungen rausgeschickt mit stereotypischen weien und schwarzen Namen (insgesamt 36 Namen). Die gleichen Bewerbungen mit "weien" Namen drauf bekamen 50% mehr Einladungen:

[We study race in the labor market by sending fictitious resumes to help-wanted ads in Boston and Chicago newspapers. To manipulate perceived race, resumes are randomly assigned African-American- or White-sounding names. White names receive 50 percent more callbacks for interviews. Callbacks are also more responsive to resume quality for White names than for African-American ones. The racial gap is uniform across occupation, industry, and employer size. We also find little evidence that employers are inferring social class from the names. Differential treatment by race still appears to still be prominent in the U. S. labor market.]
(http://www.ingentaconnect.com/content/aea/aer/2004/00000094/00000004/art00009)

Es scheint also schon ziemliche Unterschiede in allen mglichen Bereichen zu geben, wenn man alles auer dem Namen gleich hlt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> independent assessment and review of research

And again. You can have that without needing to have a private company profit of it. 

Exactly the same service as it is now could be provided by non-profits or by the funding bodies (e.g. foundations like the DFG or the NIH) itself.  The only difference would be that university libraries would not send millions to the bank accounts of the shareholders of Elsevier.

If those funding bodies wanted to censor something, they would not pay for it in the first place, so the argument about politization is completely without merit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, did not look that up.
I guess I still fail to see how Psilocin is relevant to the basic reasearch finding at hand?
It is nice if it helps some people, but honestly does not really relate to the idea that Serotonin is responsible for cognitive flexibility, does it?

This is pure speculation, but one could argue that the flooding of certain Serotonine receptors under certain drugs leads to too much cognitive flexibility. Which leads to the "great ideas" that some people have under the influence, which turn out to be a lot less genious when you are sober again. 

A counterpoint would be that under MDMA which floods the brain Serotonin you do not have extreme flexibility, but euphoria. People enjoy repetitive music (like house/techno) and sometimes engage in stereotypical behavior. 

So it is definitely not as easy as More Serotonin -- More flexibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the only research that will be published will be research that the government wants publicised.

This is a ridiculous statement, because all this research is already funded by the government. Under the curernt system private companies hide it behind a paywall from the people (taxpayers) who paid for it. 

You are arguing research that is created with government funding is somehow suppressed when a private company is not allowed to profit from it?

You can you possibly arrive at such a conclusion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those who have money can pay for it. As there are [some billionaires behind Breitbart](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/03/27/the-reclusive-hedge-fund-tycoon-behind-the-trump-presidency) who finance to push certain messages I really really doubt they will have a problem in a world without Net Neutrality.

Everyone without that powerful financial backing on the other hand... 

I guess that is what the conservative advocacy against net neutrality really about. Shape the internet in a way that only people with money can spread the messages they want. Then they (and every corporation that can afford it) can shape the information flow. Some fringe websites like InfoWars might suffer from that, but surely not Breitbart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is one driving point:

"Obamas attack  on the internet is another top down power grab. Net neutrality is the Fairness Doctrine. Will target conservative media."

https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/532608358508167168

I have absolutely no idea how to make sense of that. No idea why Net Neutrality should be bad for "conservative media". But hey. We decide policy based on feelings now. So there it is. 

Trump is against Net Neutrality, so a lot of people will be against purely based on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize there may be difference across fields, but in those fields that rely on peer-review they quality of the article depends on the kind of people who review papers. 

Which are again researchers that are in 95% of cases paid which taxpayers money doing the work of Elsevier without getting anything for it. And then their institution has to pay for access to the papers they reviewed. 

Apart from proof-reading what is the contribution of the publisher? Print it out and upload it to a webpage? This things can be done a lot cheaper, without having a private enterprise making a 40% profit for absolutely no reason.

All the intelectual work is done by scientists, who get nothing in return.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Submission Statement**

Given the recent problems of Uber, that resulted in its president stepping down, looking at alternatives for better business models may be useful. Here is an in-depth article about a start-up called Juno. Their main difference is that they focus on the drivers. This means that drivers get better payment and stock options in the company, so they can decide in which direction the company goes instead of faceless investors. Interesting concept, let's see how it pans out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juno Takes on Uber. A startups business model centers on getting drivers to defect from rival car services by treating them better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great Read.
Thank god there are still reporters who shine the light on these people in the shadows that wield enormous influence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
