<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I accept that I have changed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 07:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I accept that I have changed?

I have had depression for 6 years now and I keep going back to my past. I romanticize my past self and my past. Example of my inner dialog:

In the past I was strong, confident, I believed in myself, I had faith, I was always someone who took responsibility, never felt sorry for myself, and never played the blame game blah blah blah.

I am stuck in my past, but I am also stuck in the fact that I have changed. I am not the same person as I was 6 years, and I won't ever be the same person as I was 6 years ago. I can't go back.

Reasons why I go back is because I can't accept that I've changed, because I don't like these changes, and because I don't recognize myself anymore. I keep going back because there must be something in my past, with my past self that has sustained me, kept me going, and chose not to be depressed. I am trying to get back to me and help myself (whatever that means). But it's not working. What can I do?

By the way this isn't me accepting with my depressed self, but moving past my depressed self. aka deciding to be better. How can I integrate the new me with the old me without accepting my depressed self?  I don't even know if I am making sense. But again, How do I accept that I have changed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THIS IS AN UPDATE ON 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS IS AN UPDATE ON 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT.
I need to vent and continue my story from the previous reddit post I posted on August 25th 2016. I can't post the link but the exact title of that reddit post is: 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT.
This is not a progress report or some happy/miracle story. After the job interviews I felt good and proud of myself for being brave and overcoming my fears. However I reverted back to those feelings of insecurities, fear etc. Basically I am in the same place as I was when I wrote that reddit post. Though I NEED a job; I realize that first I don't want one, and second I am afraid to get one.
I didn't mentioned in my previous reddit post. But a week before that post I had a 7 hour/all day panic attack. I didn't realize this until I spoke to a friend who has had panic attacks before. This panic attack was scary to say the least because it was posing as a stomachache/nausea. I have emetophobia (fear of vomiting);so it was a trigger itself. But I pretty much spent the entire day with a stomachache/gagging. It was a panic attack because eventually I became exhausted, fell asleep, and woke up later on that day without any stomach aches (it was like it wasn't real at all/like the events hours before had never happened).
Pretty much since then I have been taking it easy. I really don't understand why or how it happened. But since then there were a couple of times I felt it coming (the panic attack) but I managed to relax/stop it.
I pretty much don't leave the house and I am not actively looking for a job (not that I want to). I am afraid it is going to happen again in an uncontrolled setting (like inside a train or in an office/if I got a job). That's my biggest fear right now. My body/mind/brain is attacking my physical body and that scares/scared me.
Efforts for me to get to the bottom of it (my panic attack) so far hasn't helped. I tried to journal/write for a while to get my feelings/emotions out but I realize that journaling/writing it all down is like a trigger/was triggering me. Journaling right now is not a good option because 1st it triggers me, second I am depressed and the way I write is from a depressed perspective/lenses and that my depression is shadowing/muddening/altering the truth. Pretty much me journaling is me punishing and abusing myself some more.
Overall I have to take care of myself but I don't know how. I don't have the proper support and I don't know what to do. I have been looking at self-help videos on YouTube. The School of Greatness podcast has been on repeat. Lisa Nichols has been so inspiring. These videos are helpful and it has allowed me shift focus away from the pain, and more towards seeing myself/life in a different, more positive, productive way.
I do know I have to change the way I am thinking (focus on positive thinking and gratitude). Positive thinking/gratitude is the hardest thing for me because my depression has trained my mind to believe all of the lies I have told myself over these past 6 YEARS. Like how do I unlearn, unbelieve the lies I've been telling myself for SIX YEARS. How? How do I regain control of my mind?
I do know that I have to have faith. I referring to faith as a synonym for confidence. I am not talking about faith in terms of religion/spirituality. I have to learn to develop faith (confidence of belief) in uncertainty and in myself. I have done it before during my depression so I know it's possible.
I do know eventually I have to act/ step into action. That is my weak point. I am dreamer, a planner, and an organizer but sadly not a doer. This was a natural trait even before my depression but since my depression it has really took off, took on a life of it's own.
Lastly I know I need to get a goal. Something to carry me through. For the longest time my goal was to go to college. This goal carried me through a fire/homelessness. But I did that a long time ago and that was pretty much my only real goal in life EVER. I feel my life is directionless and I feel lost. My working goal is to be financially and emotionally secure and independent. Even though I want this goal I don't fully believe/support in it yet. Which is strange because I want it.
I am venting/writing on here because it helps. It's strange and ironic but writing in my journal doesn't help but writing online to a bunch of strangers helps. Can someone explain that do me? Maybe it's the instant gratification or maybe it's because I can have conversations with people. Even when I am talking/communicating to my confidant I feel so much better. I guess a huge part of me wants to be understood. Random but talk therapy has helped a lot in my past, I am open to doing it again. I just can't now.
Anyway if you are reading thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly I agree. Before my depression I always felt in control of my life and destiny. I was always someone who took responsibility, never felt sorry for myself, and never played the blame game. Then something changed and now I am opposite and trying to regain control of my life. Even so I agree, it's time to join the transitioners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off don't tell yourself to "man up" That phrase has SHAME WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.  Shame as defined as Brene Brown: "I define shame as the intensely painful feeling or experience of believing that we are flawed and therefore unworthy of love and belonging  something weve experienced, done, or failed to do makes us unworthy of connection. I dont believe shame is helpful or productive. In fact, I think shame is much more likely to be the source of destructive, hurtful behavior than the solution or cure. I think the fear of disconnection can make us dangerous.- Brene Brown.

Don't let the stigma and shame of having depression destroy you. Telling yourself to man up is you shaming yourself. It is okay/acceptable for you to have these feelings. You are young, you don't have all the answers. So it is okay/normal to feel this way. Feel it, experience it. But don't bask in it.

By the way I am not enabling depression. I have had depression for 6 years and it isn't fun. I don't know at what stage of depression you are on (beginning, middle, etc.) but I would say running from depression, denying that you have it is NOT OK. "Manning up" pushing it down will cause you even more pain.

It is good that you are honest with yourself and honest with the negative effects that your depression has.   Even so, I would say change your perspective and find a way not let it get out of control. Monitor your thoughts, get to the bottom of it (why are you feeling this?) and do your best to transform your negative thoughts into more positive ones. Sit on your depression, don't let it sit on you.

I would encourage you talk to someone that will not shame you, alienate you or make you feel like a freak. Talk therapy is good btw. By the way this is a process, changing your perspective takes time. I am now starting to change my perspective and it's hard work. BUT IT CAN BE DONE. Anyway I love and believe in you man. You can do it. You have what you need. You are not a victim. You are not a drama queen, or a 14 year old girl. You are strong and brave. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
