<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4941</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 12:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? That just means they should be tagged along with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder is there anything to be said for an insta ban if you link this sub anywhere else on reddit like other subs do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with all the /r/worldnews comments lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya separate pill and we took it before we even went out I think so maybe an hour before I dropped the MDMA pill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Magnesium 

An absolute fucking miracle worker. I read so much about how well it worked and never believed it until I tried it myself and I was stunned, no jaw clenching whatsoever. 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When studies show strong evidence of neurotically in mice it's usually in outrageous doses, like the equivalent of an 80kg man taking about a gram and a half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A powerful beard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck were they hit with? You could put both hands through the hole in one of their heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam/Hinduism is almost entirely immigration though, stop that and the growth in numbers stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're renaming the Earth to Ireland after we conquer it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 12:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Generation_IV_reactor Thorium is one of many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 12:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Church attendances are dropping off a cliff. Ireland, one of the most religious countries in ~~Ireland~~ Europe is going to see priest numbers drop by about 60% by 2030, the number of people attending mass in Dublin is about 20% of the population and that's expected to drop by about a third by 2030 and these are the churches optimistic figures.

https://www.irishtimes.com/news/social-affairs/religion-and-beliefs/mass-attendance-in-dublin-to-drop-by-one-third-by-2030-1.2504351 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 11:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we to presume that this was the Telegraph being the tabloid that it is and making a mountain out of a mole hill for the sake of page views? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 11:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is it coincidence that are a boogeyman for the Democrats in the US presidential election?

Conspiracy theory.

U.S Politics should be banned unless it's directly related to the civil war anyway, like Hillary and a proposed no fly zone etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 10:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this related to the civil war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continue our downward spiral into a tax haven? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Very powerful and very dangerous](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BIql1ZpHovs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an eternity in the conditions they'll have to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communists? Are you retarded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the situation in Yemen, can Saudi Arabia really afford a war and afford an escalation in funding for groups in Syria for another full year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 11:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia has a lot more AA and anti missile tech in Syria than just the S300/400, lots of American planes would be blown out of the sky if a no fly zone was attempted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 01:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The debate between Clinton, Bush and Perot is such a breath of fresh air](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jg9qB_BIjWY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lordi party candidate can count on my vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be reading until Christmas if you want a full understanding of Northern Ireland's history and the groups involved from the Republic's independence to the Good Friday Agreement, just a word of warning :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get your point and I think everyone else does as well, but the IRA is one of the worst examples you could've picked. For starters there was more than 1 IRA and the main group the Provisional IRA (PIRA) laid down their arms after the Good Friday Agreement (GFA) so it was completely peaceful and overall amicable. The GFA covered many, many things but basically the main goal of the IRA, a unified Ireland, will be accomplished by political means not violent. There is essentially no IRA of any kind around today except for minor irrelevant groups that have IRA in their name but they're nothing more than gangs. 

Sinn Fin, was the political wing of the PIRA and is the party of unification in Ireland and Northern Ireland, they are a lot of things and right wing is not one of them. They're the most left wing major party in the Ireland so probably communists by American standards lol.

Edit: The National Socialist Underground is a far right German group if you want a right wing example, I'm not German so I don't how relevant they are today though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 17:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Some people are always going to break laws, we accept that we wont pander to some (child molesters, rapists, murders)

Do you really equate child rape to someone lighting a spliff or taking some MDMA? If you don't then you should delete the above part of your comment because it's ridiculous. Just because something is illegal doesn't make it morally wrong which is one of the main reason for legalisation. Everything you listed there is morally wrong no matter what way you look at it so they obviously shouldn't be legalised and no one is asking for them to be legalised anyway. 

Unless you want the government to start making these illegal drugs, that's just spending more money on these people

Very strange wording. "these people". . .what people? It's said in a way that would imply that the overwhelming majority of drug users are anything other than ordinary people in college or with jobs or whatever and yes I do think it should be up to the government to manufacture / grow the drugs. They can control exactly what goes into it and in what quantities. If I can go into a shop and buy a few grams of weed or MDMA and know exactly what I'm getting and for cheaper I'm not going to to some idiot hasn't the first clue what's in whatever he's selling. So the vast majority of any gangs income is now gone, never to come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I obviously can't check but I'm almost sure it worked sometimes. Like if you were on wifi and logged in then switched to mobile data it might work for a while, but log in on mobile data and it wouldn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Grozny was something else alright](https://www.google.ie/search?biw=1920 bih=905 noj=1 tbm=isch q=grozny+destruction sa=X ved=0ahUKEwix8LmU9M3PAhXDDcAKHYLbBDUQhyYIIg dpr=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're putting forth reasons to keep drugs illicit and then in same comment you're disproving them. This. . .

People who have no where else to do it. Young people who live at home, homeless people with no save place. Never mind the kids who will spend years walking past these places, do you not think that gives them a sense that this is ok?

. . .is mostly solved by this. . .

It would be enough to send a guard around to a lot of schools. Teach kids the dangers of drugs.

I don't know how up to do you are with the legalisation movement but education is one of the most important parts of it and to me is just as important as the act of legalisation itself. Why send a guard around to schools though? the only thing they can comment on with certainty is the after effects of drug abuse the way things are currently such as a heroin addiction quickly leading to a life of crime. Why not send a medical professional who is qualified to teach people about what exactly each of the most used drugs does to your body? They could explain what heroin does to a person, why it's so dangerous, why it's so addicting etc. If people know exactly the dangers are they won't do it.

The way things are is what you're advocating. At the minute the height of drug education is "Don't do it" and then the endless propaganda (yes it is propaganda) in newspapers but people are always going to do try one or some illegal drugs and when they do they've realised that they've been lied to all their lives. Weed doesn't give you brain damage, it doesn't damage your lungs as bad as cigarettes, MDMA isn't (physically) addicting, it doesn't put holes in your brain etc. So when 1 lie is discovered the whole thing collapses. The only thing that'll solve this is actual education from someone who doesn't espouse non-sense or has an agenda and we'll have to come to terms with the fact that people are always going to do drugs so why not let them do it in the safest way possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 13:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think the law stops a lot of people doing drugs. If the threat of the law was great enough, more people would avoid drugs to begin with.

This opinion is extremely common and extremely untrue. It can be demonstrated as untrue by looking to other countries and see how they handle the situation. Currently in the Philippines you can be killed on sight if you're suspected of being a drug dealer, 100s are already dead possibly thousands and even at that it still isn't going to completely eliminate drugs, is this a situation you'd like to see in Ireland where instead of the streets of Dublin being filled with needles it's filled with the blood of dealers?

Before you say the Philippines is a third world country or whatever, we'll look at the United States which literally declared war on drugs. Minor offenses like possession of an innocuous drug like weed can lead to years in prison. Cocaine, heroin etc can be a decade or longer, no knock raids are common on dealers houses, the Patriot act is used multitudes of times more for dealers than terrorists and there's still cities with epidemics that are stuff the nightmares for people in this country. Is this more a long the lines of what you'd like to see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 13:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  drug abuse will eventually kill them

This thread is about heroin but these comments seem to be about drugs in general so I don't know, are you saying heroin abuse will eventually kill them or are you saying other drugs (party drugs, for lack of a better word and because they're the most common illegal drugs) will also lead to abuse and death? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 13:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This encourages drug use.

This is a myth and nothing more. What extra people does this encourage to do heroin? Is it people already at risk that you think this will encourage, like people who are homeless, chronically unemployed, struggling with mental health issues etc etc because the people in these brackets that are already spending most of their time on the streets have obstruction to heroin because of it's availability.

Or do you think it's people that aren't currently at risk, people with steady jobs, a family or maybe younger people in college? 

The money would be better spent on policing.

How much should be spent on policing exactly?, because I find it hard to believe this is going to cost more than a few hundred thousand or maybe a couple of million. If that money was diverted to the police it wouldn't but a guard on every street corner and every alley way. It wouldn't be enough to bolster customs to such an extent that they catch all the heroin coming into the country because that it literally impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 12:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a rough time for me back then, i apologise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even bother reading the article? and you've pretty much spelled out why they should be brought in in your own comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently switched to Meteor, delighted. 30 top up and you get free any network calls, texts and 15GB of data. Never once had a problem with coverage in a city and I can not only get coverage to make a phone call in shopping centers now but I can even get 4g coverage with solid speeds. At least for me it's worth the extra money.

Edit: And there's no God fucking damned filter with Meteor either, yes you can actually use fucking tinder without have to go to a store with your ID. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First supervised drug injection centre set to open in Dublin this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 00:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First supervised drug injection centre set to open in Dublin this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 00:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 17:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A civil war inside a civil war. . .are xzibit memes banned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 12:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Obama took a piss on the constitution live on national TV and then announced he was running for a third term he'd probably still win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't get what your point is tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should go to the doctor and have a check for amnesia if you don't remember, ever hear of the PIIGS? One of the I's being Ireland in the off chance you don't remember and most did say we deserved what we got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more of a lack of sympathy (at least for me), you reap what you sow etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How efficiently money is spent is more important than how much is spent. For all the coalition has spent have they really got better results than Russia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start a nuclear war and cause a nuclear winter thereby preventing the apocalyptic events of global warming...if only everyone cared about the earth like the Russians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why hasn't Intel invested into the GPU side of things? It's no secret that Intel integrated graphics are, and have always been a joke.

The only joke is this statement. Nvidia and AMD have surrendered the lower end gpu market to Intel because of how good their iGPUs have gotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could say it about countries in a kingdom as well, a united kingdom even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 is a warm summer day in Ireland, and it's still ~~unbearable~~ raining

FTFY. Last summer was dreadful.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must be Scandinavian.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing was said [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=znxWfhJOP0E) on an English Political talk show he was, watch until the very end it's absolutely hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Stephan Hendry actually was a wizard, 7 and 8 in particular](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8VAtiOSB5cQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephen Hendry was more dominant though. Ronnie has been a lot better over the course of his entire career but in the 90s it was Hendry and no one else. Hendry still has more Masters, World Championships and UK Championships and ranking titles over all and any record that's broken these days is almost certain to be Hendry's like most centuries that Ronnie broke a year or 2 ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So corporations are benefiting from our nation's infrastructure and national stability

Apple does pay tax in the US, enormous amounts. What they're avoiding is this

The hard fact is that the US tax code incentivizes tax haven abuse by allowing companies to indefinitely defer **taxes on offshore profits** until they are repatriated.

For some reason the US government (the only government) thinks Apple should pay taxes on sales outside the US so when Apple sells an iPhone in Germany assembled in China with materials sourced from the four corners of the world with no connection to the US, the US government still thinks it deserves a piece of Apple's profit. There's obviously other ways these companies avoid paying taxes but Apple was singled out and this is a big reason why they have such huge offshore cash reserves.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title: "'Alien Megastructure' Star Keeps Getting Stranger"

Article: "though researchers have been keen to stress that this "alien megastructure" scenario is quite unlikely. "

Great work Author, stand up job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're white so we're not considered "dirty emmergrents" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An idiotic term for people too stupid to learn grown up words and phrases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why aren't altered headlines banned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thisismylifenow/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Never again let left wing activist human rights lawyers harass the bravest of the brave, the men and women of our armed forces" says the PM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 12:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you complain about the "far left" if they were trying to get a statue of General Franco torn down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 11:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hinkley C is bogged down in corruption which can happen to any project with idiots in government. There's dozens of reactors across the world and under construction (mainly Asia) that are being built without massive cost overruns and on time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intel seems to sponsor a lot of Rust talks, do they actually use it a lot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There goes my plan of going to bed early tonight... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit ironic how they're tearing it up after they basically created it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 00:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as a thread about gender is posted to /r/soccer the amount of upvotes or downvotes each person gets is a completely random number. Its like people don't even read the comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Governments Warn May Wont Get Early Brexit Talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about the same amount as the total world GDP per year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If we hit parity with the EU you can expect to see a big move of manufacturing to the UK 

Where do you think the materials to make things comes from? The lower the pound goes the more expensive it is to import those materials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This isn't consumer protection, it's the EU waving its dick around because they're mad their entire continent missed out on the tech boom growth." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switched to meteor as well and couldn't be happier. Not only can I get coverage *inside* buildings to make a phone call but I can also get 4g coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya definitely looks like he loves his yokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do Donegal accents not count because they're barely English? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 23:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which will also convince his idiot supporters to exercise their second amendment right and prevent a tyrannical dictator (Hillary) from taking power. It'll be lots of fun for all involved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Mind sees a mysterious man greet Hillary in the lead up to the debate and then notices him take her notes after the debate which leads to questions of debate rigging. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only site that doesn't give my laptop aids, sars and cancer when I allow scripts and I only have to allow 1 to watch the game. . .I salute you O7...and I also allow adds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The whole world put together would most likely loose to the U.S. in a war, what do you expect Iran to do by themselves?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 11:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi Aramco's value has been estimated at anywhere between US$1.25 **t**rillion and US$10 **t**rillion

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saudi_Aramco

They're not even the biggest modern day company there's plenty bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not an own goal? I couldn't see on any of the replays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **f**(x) = **f**unction of x, hardly random and when f is taken g is the letter next to it and for x and y here's an answer from quora...

The reason that x was first chosen to be the unknown variable in  algebraic equations is that the Arabic word for "thing" was translated  into the Spanish as "xei."  The first  algebra equations were written by Arabic speakers with the unknown being  labeled "thing" (much like some pre-algebra books today just use a  question mark).  After the Spanish adopted algebra the Arabic "thing"  was written "xei" and eventually shortened to just x.


Source: Michael Lamar's answer to Why are functions f(x) and not f(y)?

The primary underpinnings of modern algebra were born in Arabia during the Islamic civilization. In these times, the common word for a "thing" was "shei". This was used in books on calculations as part of equations. For instances, "four things equal 20", which is just 4x=20. "Shei" transferred to Greek as Xei, because it was tough to pronounce the "sh" sound, and thus it got replaced by 

which got shortened / changed to x.


Source: Himanish Ganjoo's answer to Mathematics: Why is the unknown parameter mostly taken as "x"? Does it possibly have any origins?
Lastly, do note that the letter y comes right after the letter x in (all?) alphabets derived from the Roman one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I read you're final paragraph I took you're 3rd example to mean every car has a factory associated with it, factory is a specific. . .trait. . .for each car. Which makes sense (I think). Bar being a specific trait of each Foo makes exactly no sense to me and worst of all has no memorability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 13:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason comments like the above person's are endemic on reddit. When someone says "if you do x, y will happen" someone will *always*, for some reason presume that they're condoning whatever y is like getting shot for mocking Islam in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 12:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  constantly changing

In what way? 1.11 code is compatible with 1.0.

very slow

Again in what way? It rivals C/C++ in most cases.

extraordinarily slow to compile

This is already changing, MIR was the first major piece in that puzzle.

unproven in the real world

It's only a year and a half so it can't be expected of it to be taking over the world, that'd be completely unrealistic but dropbox has already written 10s of thousands of lines of code in it and there's Rust code in Firefox now. So it mightn't be proven in the real world yet but it looks like it's on the way there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard Oklahoma be called OK city most likely, I knew about the bombing before but it still took a few seconds to register with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's 5 comments here and only one is sarcastic and already downvoted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't in the current circumstances which is what this post about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it is related to Syria it's still so full of shit that it shouldn't be posted here. The first paragraph...

'Madness is doing the same thing over and over again and expecting a different result', everyone knows the old clich but I doubt few expected it to so perfectly represent the Obama administration's policy approach to **the worst humanitarian crisis since World War II.**

Is this a joke? Has the writer never heard of the Cambodian killing fields, the Rwandan Genocide, the Iran-Iraq war, the Korean war, the Vietnam war, North Korea today or even the US's invasion of Iraq or the US's sanctions it had on Iraq for years before the invasion which caused untold misery to countless people. 

It's such an outrageous and ignorant statement that the rest of the piece isn't even worth reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're on a world of their own, they handed down a fine to an Irish team (Saint Pats?) for fans holding up a Palestinian banner and the original fine would've basically bankrupt them so they reduced it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's clearly a joke they even put in an edit for people that some how missed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Among a litany of other things, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just switched to meteor from the 3 and I couldn't be happier. For 30 a month (prepay) you get unlimited calls, texts and 15GB of data and best of all I can actually get coverage *inside* buildings now. They also send out a text on the 29th day as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not building prototypes they're building sub scale models, anything can be demonstrated like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's free advertising for himself, it'll never come to fruition (at least by Musk himself) but the media always has stories about the Hyperloop with Musk's name attached to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just looked it up and ya it was barely in any of Europe. I'm in Ireland and we've had it since 2012 same with the UK and Scandinavia I just presumed every where in Europe had it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It operated in nearly all European countries at the time I think, the problem is that the catalogue was (and to a large extent still is) utter shit when compared to America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird it was only on +10 when i made my comment and that was an hour after it was posted. . .its gone up fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A spot on analysis which unfortunately will be lost in the sea of memes and shit jokes.

I just don't get what's going on with him. At Madrid a lot of the players that played week in a week out like Ozil, Khedira, Modric et al were all bought by Mourinho specifically to fit his system and it worked beautifully like you said. Now it just seems like he's shoehorning superstars into the system and hoping for the best, the other possibility is that he doesn't have complete control over transfers which I find hard to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bigger chips have worse yields and even if they were the same yield you'd still get less chips per wafer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 13:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't get it. All you have to do is check in before the flight (which can be done 2/3 weeks in advance) and weigh your bag so it's not too heavy...maybe check in a suitcase. Like what the fuck is so difficult about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Transistors Will Look Like At 5nm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 12:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volkswagen Promises Its Next Electric Car Will Be as Revolutionary As the Beetle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 12:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 23:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same link but the the same story is covered here https://www.reddit.com/r/syriancivilwar/comments/5393ql/russia_convenes_urgent_unsc_meeting_after_us/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 14:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and a Masters would involve a heavy amount of theoretical physics and possibly chemistry so chip design and manufacturing *is not* limited to electrical or computer engineers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this quack like one of the best cardiovascular surgeons in the US at one time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [BBC article as well](http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-37355154) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First round of data released from the Gaia space telescope, each speck is a star; ~1,000,000,000 in total [15360 x 7831] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 11:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Connacht gold is nicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 00:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you think started the IRA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Critique of Rust's `std::collections` </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 13:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You should switch all your tea bags to green tea and get him back. 

Green tea won't kill him though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 19:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His penalties are pretty amazing as well, [against Leeds](https://youtu.be/YiyXdu03HNM?t=1m30s). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP but I'm in almost the exact same position. I've used Rust on and off for a few years now and I'm going to have to pick a project for my final year in college as well, the difference is I hardly even considered Rust. 

There is literally no advantage for me to use it. *If* I picked Rust (and I really would love to) the project would either be an embedded project (micro controller) or maybe a server type project running on a raspberry Pi. The documentation to do either would be poor to say the least and the ways of doing each in Rust seem to be still in a high state of flux. Not to mention none of my lecturers know Rust.

Also like OP now I'm thinking of doing a project in the .Net framework now. None of my lecturers know C# or have anything to do with .Net (it's either Java in eclipse or C), but I just finished a 6 month placement in a .Net house and Visual Studio + ReSharper Ultimate just makes everything so much easier and the benefits of the tooling far outweigh the negatives of none of my lecturers knowing .Net. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Part of this is the availability of tools, particularly for Windows. A debugger is very useful, and Visual Studio's debugger is pretty decent. I know gdb works with Rust, but that's more a Linux thing, and i don't have a linux machine right now.

Not sure if you forgot to leave it out or not but you didn't mention ReSharper. Visual Studio is frankly (and with no offence) out of sight of anything Rust has. . .Visual Studio + ReSharper Ultimate you'd need the Hubble telescope to see how far in front it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 12:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chips are completely different, like in every way. They don't even use the same instruction set. 

TL;DR They're incomparable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 12:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't report on it because no one cares about any of that stuff.

Sexual assaults are an epidemic in every music festival everywhere, why exactly would someone in Spain or Scotland or anywhere really care about one particular festival they've never heard of in Sweden? 

Why would some local schools changing their fucking dress code make international news over literally anything? Unless it was a direct order from the German minister for Education and not a unilateral decision from a few school principles then no one will care.

"as a true Guardian reader, and liberal leftie, I suppose I didn't want to raise that too hard. I think there was a culture of not wanting to rock the multicultural community boat if I may put it like that"

[http://www.telegraph.co.uk](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/uknews/crime/11059138/Rotherham-In-the-face-of-such-evil-who-is-the-racist-now.html). . .[https://www.theguardian.com](https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2014/aug/30/rotherham-girls-could-have-been-spared-ann-cryer), where's the cover up?

Not everyone wants to read about refugees and Muslims 24/7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an outstanding argument, brilliant logic, flawless in fact. Taking the comparison between being told to wash the dishes and being called a wanker and contrasting it with the comparison of being kicked in the shin to being shot. I would never have thought about it, thank you for showing me the light. The trauma caused from both incidents is most certainly comparable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're stretching it a bit, I think. It was a decision he didn't like and he couldn't call her a wanker (or whatever the default equivalent in Spanish is) because it'd make no sense so he defaulted to woman equivalent. There's nothing political here and nothing anymore sexist than calling a man a wanker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ. So telling someone to wash the dishes is invalidating an entire gender? Both are school yard insults and both are gendered insults. One would be classed as a swear word that's why I said, in my opinion, it's worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's a world record for number of straw-men put up in 1 hour because I think you might have just broken it.

Where did the other person say we shouldn't try? Why are you saying we should stop banning people for racism? What does racism even have to do with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that not mostly for monkey chants and the like though?. . .anyway I think the point is she's going to face this kind of thing (and worse) as referee, obviously she should be able to ref a game without being told to wash the dishes but if every game was stopped because the ref was called a wanker (which I'd rank worse, if there was a scale) then no game at pretty much any level or age group would be played the whole 90 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marketing more than anything, it's basically just the naming scheme for the different generations these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance of getting an unbiased article on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes about 5 - 7 years to build a large nuclear plant (~1600MWh) Ireland would be building one about half that size.

I don't know if I'm missing something but are you saying we currently have enough reservoirs currently in the country to output several hundred MWh of power if needed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So build a Gen IV reactor when they're ready? passively safe after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  by pumping water up an incline for example.

That definitely destroys a habitat though. . .and one of the main reasons people say we shouldn't build a nuclear plant is because there's a chance it might destroy a habitat (an almost negligible chance in this day and age)

Edit: Also this

 And the tech is getting better every year now that people are actually bothered about it.

We can't wait a few years and we can't afford to bet on the future the likes of Moneypoint should've been closed down by now if there's any chance of us meeting our green house gas reduction targets. And if we are going to bet on future technology why not bet on Gen IV nuclear reactors? Passively safe, massively reduced amount of waste and amount of long term dangerous waste, more efficient, broader range of fuels to choose from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you do when the wind doesn't blow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 13:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power [Synchronization](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Synchronization_(alternating_current) is much more difficult with wind (if it's even possible at all).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Transistors Will Look Like At 5nm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 12:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 11:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could replace High speed broadband with any number of things like water, electricity, garda coverage, ambulance coverage, fire brigade coverage but those services are still expected to cover rural areas.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Servo nightly not launching after running ./runservo.sh. . .not sure if it's worth making an issue on github </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So ya I downloaded the tar.gz from Servo.org about half an hour ago (09:15 : 7 - 9 - 2016), unpacked it and ran `./runservo.sh` and it came back with

`Failed to create window.: OsError("GL context creation failed") (thread main, at ../src/libcore/result.rs:783)`

After running `glxinfo | grep "OpenGL version"`

it came back with `OpenGL version string: 3.0 Mesa 10.1.3`. . .this version alright?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probe launched as garda is beaten unconscious in brawl at minor GAA game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were relegated for something literally everyone except Roma were doing, why wouldn't they feel victimized? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Science News Cycle](https://frontiersinblog.files.wordpress.com/2015/06/science-news-cycle.png?w=620) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.facebook.com/John-Traveller-Gossip-375739045968615/?fref=ts

This facebook page is run by travelers for travelers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well technically ya, but one is more a derivative of the other. It's like saying ethanol and methanol are from the same family but no one would use the names interchangeably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have to google it because I already know they're different. . .that's why I originally said they were different. Speed (Amphetamine basically) is the parent molecule of crystal meth (Methamphetamine) along with other drugs like MDMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....Or do I have to tell you?

Apparently yes you do, what is the difference between speed and crystal meth?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 15:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  speed (meth)

Speed and meth are very different things. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefighter attacked while attending fire in Co Sligo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know why there can't be a checklist posted to the contributing section of the Rust project, whenever I go through the process of making a pull request on the Rust compiler I always have to follow the Servo guide because it's laid out in such clear and concise way.

It's also extremely bizarre like the writer mentions that `make tidy` *must* pass before a pull request is accepted but the word tidy doesn't even appear *anywhere* in the contributing guide, why? The travis build failed for my first PR and I couldn't understand why until someone commented on the PR that I had to run `make tidy` and have it pass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 12:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why majority governments are over rated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intel has invested about 10 Billion here, and the Leixlip plant is 1 of only 3 plants that manufactures their latest 14nm chips. . .they couldn't leave even if they wanted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  could have happened only there and then.

A perfect example from Julius Caesar, no less.

[The Battle of Alesia (52 B.C.E.)
](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SU1Ej9Yqt68) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
