<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9409</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing? 

What do successful artists on Instagram post? What are their content themes? What hashtags do they use?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Showcasing the volunteers is a great idea. If you do a post with a picture and a little bio, tagging the volunteer, it'll be shared a lot - people want to support their friends. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! Social media for theatre is hard - there's so much out there! If you go the traditional route of pushing links, you are going to struggle. 

Getting publicity in local blogs (online) and local businesses (offline) will be really important for you. Via email, reach out to all the smaller outlets in your city with an offer for free tickets and great copy selling the show. In person, go from business to business hanging up posters. 

For Women, a Toronto Fringe mashup of Little Women and the TV show Girls, I created a Twitter account in the voices of the characters - this was a good hook for getting local blogs to cover the show. I would include a link to the Twitter account when emailing local outlets, and the tweets sold the show to them. (twitter.com/bethdiesto)

On both Facebook and Twitter, don't just push links. You should have content themes that don't just push users to the ticket buying page, but provide value up front. If you can include jokes or quotes from the play as your posts, you'll be providing value. These should be shareable, and will draw more people towards your play. On Facebook, we did quotes from Little Women with gifs from Girls. We also did cast bios - these were always shared by the cast. https://www.facebook.com/bethdiestoronto/

On all your social networks, remember not to be spammy. For the play, on a few days right before the show, we made the error of posting too much. Our engagement went down. Limit your posts to two per day - and make sure that one of those posts doesn't push links. 

Finally, it's important to look at your competitors and best in class brands. What are big theatres doing? What can you learn from them? You can use this to inform your content strategy, and to set goals. It's important to have hard goals for things like Likes and Followers before a show, as well as engagement rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of keeping it objective, I hope you believe in your own tool? I'm not sure why you would write a post telling users to use your competitors - do you believe that your competitors are better? 

Be very specific in these blog posts and write multiples. Instead of how to frame an entire room with our screwdriver, do how to loosen a screw with our screwdriver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really depends on the content of the posts. How tos that lead the user to a specific goal, using your product, will convert better than lifestyle pieces centered on the product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just click through on any of those fonts to get to the direct download page on Behance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 95 free fonts, from acclaimed designers (Tesla is my favourite from this collection) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it - I'd make the volume control much longer, and a bit less "blocky" looking. Kind of sticks out from the rest of the site.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 04:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're at a rally, so I'm sure that they do normally post political stuff. 

I think this was a good move by Hillary to get more social media groundswell - Trump has a lead in number of online fans there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a small agency, you can definitely be on the creative side - as a copywriter or art director - while also doing some of the analysis. You do have to specialize at some point, though. To get into the creative side of marketing and advertising you'll have to create a portfolio. You don't need any real clients, but you do need samples of work. 

If that doesn't sound good, you could go into machine learning at a larger agency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As someone who's built several online businesses that are almost entirely dependent on online marketing

You should do an AMA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a huge budget for a small company! There are a few different tools you can use to achieve your goal of more sales. The person you hire should know them well, and have proven success with them before. 

Targeted ads: on Facebook, these can be huge. Figure out your demographic (Google Analytics can help), aim for that demographic,  and go after it. A great way to do this is by using the pages that your target demographic would like - for example, what shows would your target demographic watch? On Facebook, you can target people by those details.

Social media / content marketing: Do you want to establish your brand on social media? It could be that for your business, social media doesn't convert customers. Since you're primarily visual, I think Pinterest would be huge for you. 

PR: Customers want social proof from influencers and media outlets. Profiles of your company on blogs - even small blogs - can help a ton.

Deals and partnerships: sites like Groupon can be a really good source of income for new businesses. You should also look to the businesses in your neighbour: what is a complimentary service? See if there's a store close to you that you could partner with (buy X from the other store, get a 50% discount on canvas prints; and vice versa).   

Social media and web analytics: You need to track this person's progress. When you hire a marketing specialist, they should provide goals based on the sales you want to reach. Good analytics tools will allow you to track their progress and see if they actually meet those goals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's a huge number! If I were you, I'd set up a forum on something like WordPress. Or a group on LinkedIn. 

There are other solutions like Yammer, which are crazy expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be really hard to go into a writing-driven area and not wring. Being an account manager might be more your speed - it's on the business side. Or, if you're into design and art, being an art director (less copywriting).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dwyane Wade vs Donald Trump: how an NBA player's personal tragedy turned into an election scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was interesting that a basketball star could be dragged into the national spotlight like this - downvote away if you don't like it. It was one of the few instances I could find where the election and national sports overlapped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump vs Dwyane Wade: how a player's personal tragedy became an election scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 19:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On my laptop, the images were too big to see the apps in full - I only got 3/4 of the phone stills at a time. 

Otherwise, looks really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will people be able to sue Facebook? If they were buying ads with video expecting XYZ number of impressions, but Facebook was lying about those impressions, surely that's fraud?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Using techniques from the book. Your username is so interesting. How did you think of it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lessons in social media marketing for startups from the DMZ incubator in Toronto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, what a great suggestion. How did you find that book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm biased, but I vote Reinventing Dell. It's a real history of a real company from someone who worked there for 10 years, from when it started to when it exploded to when it imploded. A really interesting history of how a startup transitioned into a massive global conglomerate, and where it went wrong. 

A company that disrupted an industry couldn't replicate its innovation, due to interesting hiring changes and the departure of its founder. Really cool read. Very different from business how-tos, which tend to do a shallow read on a bunch of case studies. This is very in-depth and well researched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be an interesting test. Make sure to also include them on your site!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have to say AR and VR. Snapchat and Facebook are investing heavily on both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need different content themes on your social channels, not just your blog posts. It can't just be bragging and spam.

However, that doesn't mean you have to go the lol cat route.

What does Google Analytics say about your demographics? What are their affinity categories? Find out their interests and go after those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Product looks great.

You need a full-width header on your site and a few brand colours. 

If possible, get a photographer friend (or do this yourself) to get photos of your products in action. What is the best possible use case for your product? With your exact demographic, at the exact right time? Go photograph it. Then do a full-width "hero" image or footer image at the bottom of the site. 

Social proof is key. Can your family and friends give testimonials? A picture of them with their first name and a review can help a lot. These can't be fake reviews - they actually have to use the product. 

Need more space between the site title and the top banner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that with the animated gif, you were trying to illustrate the problem. Before, you were using the common marketing tool stack. Now, with my product, you get... the solution isn't that obvious. I get that they're all together now, but I've just spent 30 seconds staring at an interface that isn't your product. At the end of the animation, can I see the interface of your product in colour in the same image? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try asking around at Viral Nation and hashtag paid - both are marketplaces / agencies for influencers.

You could also just try sending the influencers you're keen on free product. Micro-influencers will often do reviews for free (stuff).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome job! If you need a social media analytics suggestion, PM me. 

I'm sure the other entrepreneurs here want to know - how did you get the ball rolling on social? Getting those first 1,000 followers can be really tough. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 23:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More spacing between the menu items in the top nav bar. They kind of blend together. 

You don't have a clear statement of why you're the best or what benefits you offer. You should choose one, and then repeat it throughout the page (different wording). Why your company? 

Do you sell floor plans? Timber homes? Are you a contractor? I'm not sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Petite would be a good keyword for you. On Facebook, you can target people who Like to Pages similar to Short Girl Problems. https://www.facebook.com/shortgirlproblemsOG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowdbabble is great for Instagram analytics. More reasonable than Iconosquare, and you can add your other social accounts (Twitter, Facebook, etc).

Hootsuite is good for posting, but as with all Instagram posting tools, you can't schedule them in advance - you still have to click post after the notification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know of a free follower analysis tool, but prices for most are reasonable. You should check out BirdSong Analytics and Crowdbabble (https://www.crowdbabble.com/download-all-instagram-followers/).

Richer data is available per follower on Twitter - you can get 20 metrics per follower, including their influence and latest post. On Instagram, the data you get with each follower listed is more limited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What industry are you in? 

To avoid blogspam, I'd suggest going with bigger outlets. Harvard Business Review has great articles on social media marketing, as does Adweek. I'm a big fan of Douglas Holt at Harvard Business Review: https://hbr.org/2016/03/branding-in-the-age-of-social-media His most relevant social media articles are free. 

Avoid individuals who promise insights after you sign up for a newsletter - that's usually a sign that they're trying to get you into their sales funnel, which means their content is behind a paywall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to market yourself on social media as a wedding vendor, and use competitors to your advantage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social media is here to help you. To help your SEO, you need to be sharing your (watermarked) photos and linking back to your site. 

I did a case study of wedding vendors a few months ago: https://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/weddings-the-thunderdome-of-social-media/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I Just answered this in another thread! 

There are no standard times for posting. How could there be? Audiences are different. You want to hit your audience at the exact right time, not at standard times that might fit them. You can track when your followers are online using graphs like this: http://imgur.com/gallery/02gvJ

To do it manually, you can also just experiment by posting at different times per day and monitoring engagement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is important - you want to post when your fans and followers are the most active. There are no set times. It depends on your audience. 

In the second graph on this page, you can see peak fan activity: http://imgur.com/gallery/02gvJ Fans post the most at 4 PM, so that's a good indicator that they're online and active at that time. Page responses are pretty in sync, but there's room for improvement. There's also an Instagram graph there for you to check out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper cups are typically not recyclable, because of the plastic coating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That picture is from Crowdbabble, which allows you to add any Facebook Page to a Facebook competitive report with those visuals. It's not free, though. 

You can calculate your own engagement rates and make up your own comparative table if you'd like. Here's a full list of metrics Crowdbabble collects on Facebook - you can calculate some of them on your own: https://www.crowdbabble.com/facebook-metrics-glossary/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, but I am heavily biased because I work there. Crowdbabble is awesome and affordable. There are a ton of other options out there too and you should shop around to find one that fits you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Harley Quinn were on Snapchat [fan writing] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your process sounds incredibly painful. You're spending time with Excel that you don't have to. Why are you wasting time making your own visualizations? Use a social media analytics service to automate this for you - there are a bunch of affordable options for you. 

11,636 engaged users every single day could definitely lead to 1m+ impressions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A competitive analysis would help you a lot. Something like this: https://www.crowdbabble.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Competitor-Analytics1.png

You want to look at engagement rate, which measures how engaged Fans are in your content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audi's #PaidMyDues campaign, which bombed hard on social media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are ways to get ahead and write for a living - but be smart about it and do your research. Newspapers are laying off journalists who have Pulitzer Prizes, literally. Even if you did get a job, you don't want to work in an industry that's so oversaturated. 

Check out data journalism. Vox, Politico, 538 etc are all doing exciting new pushes in that area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New competitive analysis tool: download a list of Twitter followers + demographics for any account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 19:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do! I love providing UX help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it should be lower down and lighter. It just looks like it's not part of the written by/presented by graphic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Industry reports - all publishers and old media companies are laying off employees. They have been since the recession. Revenue is plummeting because digital ads do not pay as well as print ads. Conde Nast is also laying off workers. 

http://wwd.com/media-news/fashion-memopad/budget-cuts-at-hearst-magazine-industry-advertising-pullback-fall-10491044/

http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/conde-nast-layoffs-at-glamour-842302 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely use LinedIn in combination with Prospect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you need the big welcome, just more info closer to the headline of the site. It's what people are looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd remove the Welcome and social buttons - put your bio closer to your name, and the social buttons underneath that. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not mobile responsive and the header is very narrow. 

You should have two UX journeys up front: I'm a doctor and I'm an employer. Those should guide your site structure and content. Writing for both solutions means that you can't sell, the copy is too general. 

PM me if you'd like more in-depth feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great!

In terms of UX: the scroll arrows point directly to your resume - but your resume opens in a new tab. The placement makes it look like the two are connected, which they are not. 

Why is there a soundcloud link? No one wants to hear your music - this makes you seem really young.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the first one works - but the name of the college completely breaks the aesthetic. 

Do you have any reviews of the play from past performances (in other cities)? Those would be really helpful for selling tickets.

Also include a bit.ly link where people can make their purchases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks pretty cool!

The aesthetic on the homepage is so crisp and bold. When you actually show the items, that aesthetic kind of goes away - the fonts are more basic, the thumbnails are all stretched out. I'd at least increase the letter spacing on the headers so that it matches the font on the above the fold landing page, to start. 

Your view event button and time shouldn't have the same format - one is clickable, one isn't. 

How can I sort the events? What filters can I apply? My budget is Y and I like music X. Where should I go? Don't make me read them all. 

PM me if you want more detailed feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overall, looks great! 

Your menu items  are a little tiny for easy reading.

The slider doesn't make sense to me, with different versions of the same picture. Pick one - a stronger image, maybe, and choose text that doesn't need a shadow. The Welcome to Jetura Media slide isn't useful. You need to emphasize your value up front.

Paragraph font under Why Hire? is also pretty tiny. 

How do they actually hire you? You need a big Get Started Now button or some sort of form on the front end. 

If you'd like more detailed feedback, PM me. 

What industry are you aiming at? I'm not sure that the samples go together. Maybe categorizing them by industry would be better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [data viz] Sentiment analysis of iPhone 7 release on Twitter from /u/rya_moore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answer the questions below and you'll be well on your way.

Who is your audience? How old are they, what devices do they use, what networks are they on? -- picking social networks

What are your competitors doing? What about the best-in-class musicians?

How often are they posting? What are their content themes? What is their social "voice"? Who are the influencers for your demographics? -- content strategy

How much time can you realistically spend posting every month? When are your followers online?  -- content calendar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearst is haemorrhaging jobs. You should be very careful about the companies that you're aiming for - if they're firing dozens of people a month, they aren't hiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eek! I'm very excited about this new feature. Download all a list of all users who engage with your Twitter and Instagram posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brent Stirling, a startup advisor, has good advice here: http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/the-social-media-secrets-of-brent-stirling-crowdbabble-interviews-a-startup-guru/

Starting from 0 means that you have to share your milestones with followers and build a real, grassroots community. Give your first followers the insider info they need to feel like they're really part of your brand. 

I also wrote a case study about four small companies and how they built small, sincere followings in their first six months. http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/starting-at-0-social-media-for-new-businesses/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if it's free, but hashtagpaid.com allows you to search for influencers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it now -- intuitively for me, I view code/vectors/pixels as means to an end. I would use those tools to create a story or an idea.

I think what you're saying is that you make ideas into a reality. You might want to say that more concretely up front for people who are used to seeing the logic the other way around (like I used code to build this interactive story).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be better to use tools (cinematography, code) to create stories and ideas? You-- end product, rather than end product -- tools? I guess I'm not understanding how your skill set works. Or is it that you turn stories and ideas into working products?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how bold the landing page is above the fold. The white space, the line height, the font. 

That aesthetic goes away when you click to get a summary of each item. Try to maintain it - keep the white space, padding, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Instagram API does not allow you to schedule posts in advance and have them auto-post from those times. 

With Hootsuite, for example, you can compose your posts and store them. But you still have to go into the app to post. 

So you can have posts automatically created and stored, but you won't be able to post them directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks cool! Listening doesn't get a lot of love on Reddit, outside /r/dataisbeautiful. Check out /r/socialmediaanalytics for performance analysis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a really cool tool

Have you considered a partnership with ClarifAI? This would allow you to add keywords to the images automatically - making them way easier to search.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the minority here, but something that deals with storytelling and language. Most UX designers write their own copy. Studying literature and/or storytelling can help you create a clear and cohesive experience for users.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I'm struggling with a page for two new features: Download all Instagram followers and download all engaged users.

Do you guys think that the features should be more differentiated? I'm not sure if having the forms styled in the exact same way is clear. 

When you went to the page, could you understand how the features were different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with wording/UX for a new download all Instagram followers feature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SteadfastBeta provides legitimate test users - it's not free. 

What benefit are you offering in exchange for people testing your product? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter doesn't show you the usernames of everyone who likes your stuff, but the numbers should match. 

If you want the usernames of everyone who likes your content, you have to use a scraper or pay for an analytics service.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean that there's an inconsistency in numbers, between tweetdeck and Twitter? Or do you want a list of everyone that liked your content?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reinventing Dell, aka what not to do if you want to scale well. Or, how to build an incredible entrepreneurial spirit - then lose it to bad management. Really good rags to riches to rags story that shows how a small company became successful quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The politics of Pinterest: how Brexit and Trump triumphed on the most conservative social platform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you guys think of their strategies to concede or not concede? 

Are you surprised that Trump outpaced them on Facebook so quickly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your campaign fails: lessons in Facebook marketing from Jeb Bush, Ted Cruz, and John Kasich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Facebook, a good check is the location of the Likes. If they're all through locations that would probably want nothing to do with the page, then they're likely fake. For example, if you're a local restaurant in Texas and all your likes are from Bangladesh... bad sign. Crowdbabble does this for Facebook pages that you have admin access to.

Another good test is to use Facebook audience insights as /u/mjolnir630 suggests and look for activity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A year in marketing disasters on social media, from IBM's #hackahairdryer to Trump's Dwyane Wade tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 18:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for writing such a detailed analysis. The article had to be published on the Sunday after the scandal, hence the short analysis time. Looking at the numbers after that, Trump's follower growth was depressed for a week after the tweet while Hillary's stayed higher than normal. If I have only a short window, I usually check back a week after and if my conclusions are incorrect, I'll add a note with an update. 

You're right about the scaling on the graphs -- it adjusts to each candidate, so it's hard to compare them. That's why I included some competitive analysis graphs with the same scale. I thought it was interesting that Republicans have so many more social media fans on Facebook than the Democrats. 

Conservative outlets report that only around 10% of black Americans rate Donald Trump "very favourable". The Washington Post article from July said it was 6%. I checked those out numbers before writing the piece. I do think that the tweets after the scandal are a reflection of how black voters feel about Trump. "Die in a grease fire" covers it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graphs for Trump and Clinton used the Twitter API to access endpoints for follower growth and mentions. For the tweet screengrabs themselves, I just went in and manually searched the hashtag that blew up around the campaign crisis. I used Crowdbabble for the graphs, which I mentioned in the piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to use analytics to help you find what your audience wants.

What hashtags do they engage with the most? What filters do they engage with the most? What keywords? What time are they online?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audi. Their #paidmydues campaign was pretty bad.

IBM. Their vetting process is broken, because they allowed #hackahairdryer through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 22:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should work okay. Are you looking under Top Posts for the hashtag, or all posts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Export any influencer's Instagram analytics to Excel with one click </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Export your favourite celebrities' Instagram data to Excel with one click </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new crisis management example from social media: Donald Trump's "Dwayne" Wade tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lessons in what not to do on Twitter from Donald Trump's "Dwayne Wade" tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you including any social media metrics? Engagement rate, follower growth, organic/paid/viral breakdowns are usually helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really tough. Hootsuite is a great one for posting, but it sounds like you hate it. I work for Crowdbabble, and it's great for tracking your performance across platforms (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram). It's also really affordable, but no posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowdbabble has a Hootsuite plugin that tells you the best time to post on Instagram, based on your follower activity levels throughout the day. It's free. Crowdbabble's main app tells you the best time to post for Instagram, Twitter and Facebook - for Twitter, based on replies, favourites, and retweets, for Facebook, based on comments. It suggests best time to post, as well as best day to post, based on audience activity.

You can also do this manually by trying out different post times and recording your follower and fan engagement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at what your competitors are doing and check out Instagrams like Lisa Lost in Lit. Those will be a good place to start for inspiration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interesting, neat! I wonder if this is something that could be tracked with their API?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you selling them? It sounds like you're selling them the team, but these aren't investors. 

Does the team write the newsletter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough one. You basically want a google alert for a link, which can track social shares. I'll look into this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is your target audience?

What are your competitors doing on social? You might check out Hazlitt. 

If you're based in India, are Hindi translations necessary?

Your social links on the website don't go anywhere.

Some of your media has a cohesive look, like the stencil drawings, but it's kind of all over the place. You might look at this account to see how a strong brand looks: https://www.instagram.com/lisa_lostinlit/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty important, because it gages how your audience connects with your content.

For large pages, 3 to 5 percent is totally normal. Sounds low, but it's hard to get large audiences to all connect with the same content.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pinterest drives more traffic than Facebook and Twitter combined, so it's extremely valuable to marketers. 

You're a 'micro-influencer', so check out apps like #paid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exciting challenge! 

What are your competitors in the local area doing?

What local events does the store do that you can promote? 

Bookstores typically go the bookporn route on social media - or at least include that as one content theme. The challenge is connecting that to your local audience of people who will actually shop at the store. Example: https://www.instagram.com/typebooks/

Christmas is coming up. What are your goals? How much do you have to sell? What social audience will get you there? I'd say use the upcoming holidays for your timeline, and fill in the content by answering the questions above.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were these fake followers? Followers who would never purchase anything from the design firm? 

Did you go way off brand and grab a bunch of followers who will never buy anything from the firm?

Basically, a company is concerned with its sales funnel. If only designers ever make it down the sales funnel to make a purchase, then it doesn't matter how many followers you have. It's only about the quality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally depends on the audience. I guess my initial strategy would be:

 * See what competitors are doing in the same space 
 * Collect info on demographics and your audience
 * Find influencers in the industry for your audience

A lot of the research steps are the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleted tweets are usually not available from the Twitter API. Crowdbabble shows all tweets -- but not deleted ones. I don't think that's an endpoint you can get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter is more for engaging with people and participating in chats than just blasting out content. Find chats applicable to your industry and participate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did they post the article about the customer?

That's brutal. Did you lose the client? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, Hillary and Trump post the same amount. She focuses more on policies, while he typically does "hot takes" on current events (like the Dwyane Wade tweet) and talking about the campaign trail ("just visited Louisiana!). They both post roughly the same number of words every day on social.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take out everything about subscribe, and just write Get Invite. No one wants to be on a mailing list, but people want exclusive invites to apps that aren't out yet. 

Instead of Thank You, write Invite Sent or something similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marketers: What Are Your Favourite Social Media Fails/Crises That Went Down This Summer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite is Trump's tweet about Dwyane Wade, which he is currently getting a lot of heat for. 

What social media fails amused you this summer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning from Trump's shock-and-awe strategy on Twitter, after his "Dwayne" Wade tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's extreme strategy on Twitter might be backfiring, looking at his "Dwayne" Wade tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took a look at this social media crisis over the weekend, where Donald Trump tried to hijack a tragedy - where the grieving family's politics were opposite to his own. He also misspelt Dwyane when he did it. Pretty interesting! Wrote up a case study for the company blog, which I have pasted here (go to the blog to see the graphs).

Dwayne Wades cousin was just shot and killed while walking her baby in Chicago. Just what I have been saying. African-Americans will VOTE TRUMP!  Donald J. Trump (@realdonaldtrump)

Full article here: http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/donald-trump-dwayne-wade-and-the-outrage-machine/ 

When running a campaign, when is it a good idea to co-opt a personal tragedy for retweets and votes?

For brands, the answer is definitely never. For Presidential candidates, politicizing a persons death  especially when their politics are counter to your own  is usually a fire-starter. But Donald Trumps campaign runs out outrage. The Republicans baiting tweets often work for him, not against him.

Will the Dwyane Wade gaffe destroy Donald Trump on Twitter? Or is the mistake another key step in Trumps shock-and-awe strategy?

**Gun Control vs. Tough on Crime**

In the 2016 Presidential election, a key differentiation point between candidates is the second amendment. Hillary Clinton has positioned herself as the gun control candidate; even Bernie Sanders is against background checks. Hillary has succeeded in gathering support from minorities living in urban centres due to her voting record on gun control and emphasis on anti-violence policies in her campaign.

Donald Trump, as the Republican nominee, has taken on the partys values around the right to bear arms. According to Fox News, Donald Trump is running as the law-and-order candidate; he frequently uses #MakeAmericaSafeAgain on his Twitter account. Sometimes, it can be difficult to tell if his tweets are tough on crime or tough on minorities.

Trumps Dwayne tweet didnt come across as tough on crime to everyone. Throughout his campaign, Trump has been criticized for racism, including statements against the blacks. Appropriating a gun violence tragedy for his campaign, particularly one involving minorities he has sidelined, read as opportunistic on social media. Trumps political views couldnt be further from those of the grieving family, making the tragedy a poor fit for his campaign. Misspelling Dwyane the more conventional way added insult to injury.

Did the tweet impact Donald Trumps momentum on Twitter?

**Trump Falls Out**

Caught in the crossfire of a fight that had nothing to do with her, on August 26 Nykea Aldridge was shot while taking her daughter for a walk in her stroller. That night, Dwyane Wade tweeted about his cousins death, condemning gun violence. In replies to Wades tweet, Trump followers got to him before Trump did.

Donald Trump tweeted at 9:24 AM the next morning, on August 27. By that afternoon, the story had been picked up by most major news outlets and aggregators like Jezebel.

Dwayne Wades cousin was just shot and killed while walking her baby in Chicago. Just what I have been saying. African-Americans will VOTE TRUMP!  Donald J. Trump (@realdonaldtrump)

Response to Trump's tweet from Wade and other outraged Twitter users was swift and brutal. Donald Trump quickly deleted the original tweet and sent out a corrected version, with the right spelling of Dwyane  and the same message.

After retweeting Trump, comedian Don Cheadle asked the candidate to die in a grease fire.

Criticism of Trump from other outraged Twitter users quickly followed. Hashtag #dwyanewade took off.

With the misspelt tweet, Donald Trump thrust himself back into the spotlight. Trump, not the tragedy, was at the centre of the conversation around #dwyanewade on Twitter.

**Centre of Attention**

After Trumps tweet on August 27, mentions of the candidate were higher than average on Twitter.

His handle @realDonaldTrump received 5,978 mentions on August 27. His corrected tweet, not misspelling Dwyane, attracted 30,523 total likes and retweets. The tweet perceived so negatively received Trumps average per-tweet engagement, well ahead of his least-engaging tweet over the past two weeks, which received just 5,444 likes and retweets. Donald Trumps followers seem to be encouraged by outrage from the other side.
Outrage fuels engagement for Donald Trump on social media. By baiting the media with offensive statements, like his criticism of the Khan family or Mexican immigrants, Trump receives more attention and engagement. Since his tweet about the personal strategy of Dwayne, his reach on social media and in the news has only increased.

**Hillary Sweeps In**

Donald Trump goes out of his way to attract criticism from left-wing social media users because it reaffirms his outsider, conservative brand for his voting base. Pillorying the liberal elite ups his conservative cache for Republicans. The more opposition Trump can draw from them, the more authentic and powerful he seems.

Still, in solidifying his base, Trump might be alienating some Republicans. Even right-leaning publications like New York Daily News criticized the Dwayne tweet as insensitive and pompous. As shes done throughout her duel with Trump, Hillary has leveraged this crisis to her advantage. On Twitter, Hillary reminded followers about Trumps racist past business practices, like not renting to black tenants.

In the wake of Trumps mistake, Hillary has used these strategic reminders to undercut the purported sincerity and concern in Trumps tweet. On August 26, the day after the tragedy, her follower growth spiked.

**Will Outrage Put Trump or Clinton in the White House?**

From Elizabeth Warren to Dwyane Wayde, Trump draws liberals into Twitter battles that cannot be won on the terms of common sense or reason. Sensationalist messaging draws the spotlight back to his campaign and his policies, bringing with it higher engagement.

By encouraging outrage, Trump seems to win, no matter the outcome. But his divisive tweets come at a price to his reputation among more moderate voters.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Donald Trump's social media strategy driving away moderate Republicans? What his "Dwayne" Wade tweet is doing for Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just for fun: the favorite Instagram filters of Donald Trump, hillary Clinton, and Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "Dwayne" Wade tweet: Donald Trump's shock and awe marketing strategy derails on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 01:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Trump's Twitter strategy pushing moderate Republicans toward Hillary? Analyzing the fall out from his "Dwayne" Wade tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 23:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Donald Trump's Twitter strategy alienating moderate Republicans? Analyzing the fall out from his "Dwayne" Wade tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you didn't do it while running for office </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Twitter data this time, using the Twitter API and an analytics tool to make the simple bar graphs. I'm going to check in on the fall out later this week, to see if the "mistake" tweet by Trump had any impact on his engagement and follower growth over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calibri is my least favourite font. Its a comic sans version of Times New Roman. Am I alone in hating it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 17:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do it manually, by clicking through posts by the followers that have engaged with you to see what hashtags they use. 

You can also use a free app like Crowdbabble for Hootsuite to view the recent posts by your "most influential" new followers, so you can see what hashtags they use.

Who are your competitors? Another way would be to look at their posts  and hashtags, and borrow some of those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 03:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The United States is 3rd in the OECD for income inequality. 

http://www.businessinsider.com/ranked-income-inequality-around-the-world-2015-7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The equivalent of a $2,000/night suite in my city would be staying in the penthouse of the Trump Tower. Most people here consider tourists who do that to be tacky as hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 22:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more to do with showing off the wealth, like staying in very flashy hotels. Sort of tacky and unfortunate, given the US's level of income inequality. Flashy cars, flashy hotels, private drivers, etc - flaunting your wealth is very new money and sort of gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of Instagram and Tumblr posts with word definitions and inspiring quotes -- I suggested them because they tend to skew younger. It's a match for a younger audience, not necessarily your content. But since you're not going after kids, they won't fit as well. 

For parents and post-college graduates, Facebook, LinkedIn, and Instagram are your best bets I would say. 

You'd also probably want to hook into networking / job seeking meetups, perhaps offering your services at a discount.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 17:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally depends on your audience. Are you aiming directly at parents, or at students? Parents are on Facebook, but students might be on Tumblr, Instagram, and Vine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 16:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a whole bunch of apps that will charge you to do this. You can also do it manually.

Who is your audience? What hashtags do they use? Who are the most followed people using those hashtags? Focus on people who have real, organic followings, not people who follow 10,000 and have a following of 11,000. Check out their engagement rates: do their followers genuinely love their content (ie could they be swayed into buying something)? 

For example, this person is an influencer in the area of reading and book sales: instagram.com/lisa_lostinlit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show them best in class brands and your competitors. Social media has to be successful in driving traffic to your website, but it's the website that has to convert that traffic to sales. Trying to convert leads to sales directly on social media almost always comes across as spammy and will damage your brand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might look into social listening tools that use Pinterest. Tailwind seems to be a good option. https://www.tailwindapp.com/social-media-monitoring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Create brand guidelines for each one - including content themes, tone, brand personality, etc - to make it easier to choose your words and images.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What functionality do you need?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Analytics -- your web traffic

Social media analytics -- monitor your social media

FullStory -- track unique visitors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at his competitors. What are other famous photographers doing on social media?

For him, a good website where people can order prints and a solid Instagram presence will be key. To ensure no one 'steals' his work, he might consider watermarking them in the corner.

I'm not sure if a company would pay for employee portraits. He does not strike me as a B2B business model, but then again, he might be able to do commercial photography. 

You'd also have to do a full brand identity for him. Again, competitors can help you here. Edward Burtynsky is a famous photographer and his presence is pretty bare bones - which matches his aesthetic. http://www.edwardburtynsky.com/site_contents/Current/introCurrent.html His website also matches his books. 

Would Serbians buy a self-published book of his? Has he ever tried to get a coffee book deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Influencers. Some don't even need money - just send a free product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hootsuite. And if you could build a posting service for free, why don't you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally depends on your audience, and you need that data. I'd suggest loading up competitors going after the same audience using an analytics tool (like Crowdbabble), and seeing when peak follower comments are. Then you'll know when your desired followers are online, and you can try posting then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before and afters sounds like a winning combination. You can show the problem, the service you offer, and the finished result. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one is super elegant. That one stands out nicely to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social media is a great one. You should hop on location-based hashtags on Instagram, for example (if your product has products that can be communicated on Instagram, and if your audience is on Instagram).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are your customers? Where online do they hang out?

Targeted ads (like Facebook ads and PPC)

Social media - you have to have good looking photos and regular content if you go this route </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't do any unpaid internships. Unpaid internships are a sign that the company isn't doing well financially, or that you're in an oversaturated area. Companies that can't find minimum wage for their interns are not likely to hire you. 

Companies that replace entry-level workers with unpaid interns are not doing well. Seems pretty obvious, but some many people take on full-time, unpaid internships expecting them to lead to paid work, only realizing later that the company that couldn't afford to pay them can't afford to hire them either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I'd run analytics and get real data. Show the engagement rates, total fans, etc for best in class brands and for brands in competition. Crowdbabble does a really good Facebook page competitive report, where you can load up one brand vs its competitors. 

Real numbers will definitely help your case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One more case study about an advertising disaster: Audi's weird, off-brand #paidmydues campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
