<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go with feet. You can stand to be less nimble or strong... you can't adventure without feet. Unless you're a naga. Or a mermaid/merman. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rise of Mankind: A new dawn.

Not sure if it's a good fit for everybody, but it tickles my fancy of taking a Civ all the way from time immemorial to sci-fi-ey future tech.  
Also the sheer size of the maps. Which admittedly neither the AI, nor I are prepared to tackle. I'm approaching the modern era and there's still a whole massive continent that's full of nothing but barbarians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A New Dawn ftw. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not. Modded CivIV is my goto civ game forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if he were to be introduced to the modding scene of Civ4/5 :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's old as dirt.

The game has advanced since then. There are many many ways to do so before L13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 4D maze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or [GitP's play-by-post(PbP) forums](http://www.giantitp.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?3-Play-by-Post-Games). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... 72 points to distribute, but they get distributed randomly...

Probability favours all-12s. This is amusing for people with who just like to roll and are okay with the old-school method of dice-character. Mostly devoid of practical value.

What is infinitely more interesting is the interaction between rerolls, best-of-x and count-x-as-y.

Which you can explore to your heart's content at [anydice.com](http://anydice.com).

Edit:  
[4d6 best 3](http://anydice.com/program/2483)  
[3d6 reroll 1s](http://anydice.com/program/9e96)  
[3d6 count 1s as 2s](http://anydice.com/program/9e97)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid Positive Energy is an obscure material from an obscure, old, high-level adventure that has absolutely magnificent properties.

It is indestructible and breaks line of effect for all spells across ALL planes. Including the astral plane. Meaning you cannot use [Teleportation] spells to circumvent it. It allows the creation of a very specific concept I was looking to implement in my game. Also, shows that there's nothing new under the sun, if you're willing to book-dive enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that half my time is spent pouring over documentation rather than writing actual code, yes, very much so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equally as worse: Forgetting your mouse and being forced to use the touchpad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh... I pity all the poor artless folk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you as a DM start hogging the pretty pictures, then all I can say is "screw you".

Also, Manuel is not a monster, he's just differently abled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Sci-Fi.

Covers usually have nothing to do with those, but are generally pretty awesome arts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 12:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yify was like the Apple of the torrent scene. Polished turds with mass appeal. Glad he's gone TBH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 09:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you be persuaded to make a [deviantArt](http://www.deviantart.com) account and have all your arts properly named and attributed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's mostly the expressiveness they manage to coax out of animalistic faces.

But then again, that also makes many classic disney cartoonists furries as well. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll basically be running a similar campaign soon. How I handle it is:

1. Give players some free LA.
2. Start at a high enough level to allow high-LA races.
3. Allow automatic LA buy-off, based on how PF does it(we won't use XP since it makes things embarrassingly simpler).
4. Allow additional buy-off on top of what PF does, based on the amount of pure RHD.

There are additional option you can avail yourself of. Such as gestalt or PF's race builder system(though you have to be careful there).

It is a bad idea to start with players who are more than 2HD off each other. It is worse if these constitute half or more of the highest HD player.

Understanding the fundamental concepts of ECL, LA, RHD and Class levels is vital here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's 2 characters with 2 catchphrases:

1. Now it's MY turn!
2. I have an idea... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, you guys, I just had the greatest idea for a Rome 2: Total War mod ever... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er. Crusader? KISS enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope for the best, plan for the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roll20 man... the worst, I tell you, *the worst*.

Have had DMs tell me what to do, or think, DMs insisting on certain house-rules which I've warned them about, then kicked me out when I exploited, DMs who let the players walk completely all over them, DMs who insisted on taking turns when SPEAKING, DMs with horrific fumble charts that make you wonder how anyone who swings a sword in their world is still *alive*, etc. etc. Probably can't even remember some of them.

I am never playing D D on that site ever again. Not a single good experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... That is a very high-level spell, RP implications notwithstanding. No wonder you find it useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My major world, I started with the central mechanical and narrative premise, then built it up by osmosis from books, art and online RPG forums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her face already said that before the words ever left her lips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any adventurers in the world Erinea of look away on penalty of... well, mostly just spoiling yourself good moments in the game.
***
I called the size Kaiju, mostly because I couldn't think of any other word for "really big" starting with a letter that wasn't already taken.

They're smarter actually.

They're part of the ancient history of the setting, played a pivotal role in the creation mythos of my universe. They're the progenitors of the normal dragons and most of the hybrid races that exist(such as centaurs, nagas, dragonborn, dragonspawn, etc).

All but a few(Tiamat and Bahamut for example) currently slumber in great fortresses within the cores of stars, sustained by that energy, awaiting the return of magic to the universe, when they will be able to rise again and roam the skies.

I'm basically just copying Tolkien's mythology here, but adapted to D D. The whole "powerful ancient entities that have no place in the current universe" shtick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is precisely how it works for the lazy people. Which is the majority, hence Apple success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I wish someone would do the research on what exactly makes the tires jump further.

Like for example the F1 tire clearly has a lower moment of inertia than all the others... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... he's basically playing himself in Moana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

But I care about it only when it matters. Such as in survival situations or when it clearly exceeds the party's capabilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equally as valid:

Stop making people start at L1.

If they write a backstory like this, they obviously wanna play in that kind of game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Doom is one of my favourite.

Others I enjoy are blind love, the martyr, the disillusioned and the prince. Basically idealism taken to the extreme.

What I don't enjoy and go out of my way to avoid is revenge. It's just overplayed by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My inspiration is external, so basically everything I have created has been prompted to one degree or another by some piece of creativity by other people. Anything from books, pictures, comics, other DMs and players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have what are called "Primal dragons". They're bigger, badder, tougher and older than any normal dragon you could see. They currently slumber, waiting for the time when they will again be able to return to the universe.

P.S. By bigger I mean several size categories above the largest one in vanilla D D. I call their size "Kaiju+". Literally mountain-sized. Square-miles wingspans. You get the picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know...

I've always found these little lists missing that special something that makes them *actually* useful.

Like, why doesn't anybody ever post plot hooks that hint at the actual plot(which is what DMs are looking for) rather than the hooks(which is what gets presented to the players)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I present to you: [**The Voidstone Arsenal**](http://www.giantitp.com/forums/showthread.php?480986-The-Voidstone-Arsenal-For-when-you-really-want-stuff-gone) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I set up the expectation that there will be things, *a great many things*, especially at lower levels, that will simply be out of their league.  
Discretion is the better part of valour.

Some monsters are obviously way too strong. For those that are not, I leave hints, sometimes even subtle ones are enough. When all else fails a punch to the face that takes out half the character's HP tends to alleviate any misunderstandings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually build, but even then only in the most abstract sense. I see some mechanic or ability I like that inspires me and I create a character around that.

However you forgot the third option: Focus on art. Some characters come to be simply because I found a great piece of character art online and then I tailor the build and story to the depiction. It has the neat bonus of having a great piece of perfectly matching visual representation of the character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weiter hauen. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Errant HCF in the display driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Stereotypical Fantasy Campaign. NOT. Remove all restrictions for character creation. Have every single monster playable. Dispense with the meaningless prophecies. Or subvert them.

Begin the campaign with the players already being kings, generals, heroes. Bring them down. Then let them rise again and elevate themselves to legends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like "kicking puppies" evil.

Well-made evil characters have a ***purpose***.

What you're describing is a cardboard cut-out, even worse than the moustache-twirling cartoons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to know the rules well. Not by heart, word for word, but well enough to be functional in your job(which is arbitrating game situations).

To be a good DM however, requires a great deal of experience. Just like with any hobby you want to be good at.  
Contrary to popular opinion, being a DM is not exempt from reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The PF might be cheaper, but I can't say.

However, they are also available freely here: www.d20pfsrd.com  
In fact the entirely of the PF rules are under OGL and available for free. It is only the setting that you have to spend money on, which is moot if you decide to create your own world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me pitch in in favour of 3.5.

It isn't perfect, but I consider it an "upgrade" of 5e. It has more content, greater range of play and significantly more content. But not if you only get the base. Core 5e is better than core 3.5e, but all of 3.5e outweighs core 5e.  
Then there's Pathfinder which is released under the OGL and fixed a great many things in 3.5 while remaining almost completely compatible with it(only very minor changes are required to adapt content to and fro).  
In 5e, which I've played on occasion, I feel really constrained in the type of concept I can build. It only supports a very limited subset of generic fantasy tropes and if you want anything outside of that you're fresh out of luck. In contrast, with 3.P I can build playable monstrosities to my heart's content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5e I assume? PLEASE tag your thread.

If earlier edition, PF already has one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general your solution is tactics and more opponents.

If the BBEG meets them, make sure it's on his turf. Give him home-field advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modified Stormwind fallacy here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death's scythe is an artifact in my world.

It can transform from scythe to staff, is made from an exotic material and is vorpal in scythe form.  
Dealing lethal damage charges it up and it can use those charges for a few abilities.  
It is also intelligent and very moody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for linking to this video! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding me. Even then, they were only charged with manslaughter. The deaths were a tragedy, the spill was a disaster. Do laws even exist to prosecute something on that scale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea... I was like, "Wait, is that...? It totally is!".

That's so cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if our terms mean the same thing, but if you're veering into TO territory for your BBEG, I so totally wouldn't wanna be your players... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Escaping a grapple is a standard action, this is clearly specified [here](http://www.d20pfsrd.com/gamemastering/combat#Table-Actions-in-Combat). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. I'd make the fly more than 5 rounds though. A minute is fine.  
Never mentioned how many uses Dimension Door has(at that price, it isn't at will).  
The rest seems perfectly fine, thematically and mechanically.

I don't wanna bother checking the prices, but if you bothered to include book references, I'll just assume you know what you're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What weird CGI one?  
^^^^we ^^^^don't ^^^^talk ^^^^about ^^^^that, ^^^^it ^^^^does't ^^^^not ^^^^exist, ^^^^now ^^^^repeat ^^^^after ^^^^me  
Just think about how uncannily similar it is to a D D campaign. Everything from the party dynamic and levelling to the BBEG is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is highly useful.  
Man, there's so much quality content on YouTube these days and so little time. I've been wanting to get to the Crash Courses for ages.

But thank you for pointing that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a saying for DMing: How did Avatar do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woo. Exciting science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -2: Character creation and backstory(short 1-on-1 sessions).  
-1: Intro to the world and setting up the party.  
0: Intro quest(test drive of the party).  
1: Start of main campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The magnetic confinement one. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general, no.

But software becomes more complex and tends to incur higher overhead, thus making it seem like the hardware is getting slower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, perfected more like it:  
**Fusion** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More specifically, it'd be about the same height as a 27-inch 16:9 monitor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep a pen/tablet handy.

I get WB ideas at the most random times and places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, screw Beamdog.

BG have been and always will be Bioware games.  
IW(and PS:T) were Black Isle's games.

Erasing all the community content that's come out since then to play with slightly better graphics is retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually dive into the books and some mechanic or ability or bit of fluff catches my eye and I flesh it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a programmer's editor that can manage projects and many, MANY text files. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not the trait of a min-maxer, it's the trait of a murderhobo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks wretched. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real genesis of mine was actually just an accident. And it didn't even involve gods. They came after.

I can't actually stand the idea of an all powerful creator.

Of course, the universe has experienced different epochs since that beginning and different races have various creation myths that are based mostly on those epochs and a great deal of fiction.

So... basically, a lot like the real world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personalized intros.

As in work with the players to establish their place in the world prior to starting the campaign. Usually works best with a small party(3-4). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pun-pun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 08:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've toyed with the concept of Pelor, the Burning Hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 08:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So uh... am I the only one who feels that time travel twists are terribly overplayed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 04:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that starts with Sw*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mixing up fantasy and reality.

I am cursed, since this describes 99% of players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slapstick. (I think that's what it's called. It pervades sitcoms.)

I find it so cringe-worthy I actually cannot watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/unexpectedTFTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The culture shifted away from my flavour of gaming.

I don't doubt there's good games today, but for the life of me, I can't find the appeal in any of them. Doom's probably been the only cool blast from the past these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a world where his super-suit can be packed in a suitcase and self-assemble ON HIM on command, I don't see it as much of a stretch that it can assemble in such a way as to fit slightly different builds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could not, for the life of me, finish that movie. The cringe was that strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's is basically the same as this:  
https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5awz4s/til_of_canary_trapping_a_method_for_exposing_an/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I would.

Heck, I'd be more open to the DM coming and saying *"Listen guys, I can't handle you. What are you willing to give up?"* than him going full "that guy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, well... [Underdark](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Underdark_\(supplement\)).

Go figure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the trap options.

So much possibility to make something that's utter crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 06:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Open dev tools.
2. Find overlay.
3. Delete overlay.
4. Select any part of article.
5. Travel up tree till you find an overflow-y: hidden property.
6. Remove that.
7. Fuck the site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 06:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we make an exception for Mass Effect. Just that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 06:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's like your opinion."

No... fuck you. 2+2=4 is NOT an opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -1 for 3-4 sessions.

There are also other penalties that arise naturally - less of the loot fits(unless of course they make the same character or something) and RP-wise(the other PCs might not trust the new arrival yet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xavier, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give your other players a cool thing and move on to the next level of encounters.

What kind of game are you playing anyway? Straight up hp damage(a middling amount of it too, at L7) should be the absolute least of your worries. Do you have any idea the amount of hurt a well-built barbarian can output every round, WITHOUT having to flank or flat-foot people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, all the time?

No thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mechanically... nothing. Most are mindless, all are immune to mind-affecting, hence fear.

Otherwise, they hate their veggies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... soft lines, round shapes, warm colours. It's say that counts. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immediately knew it was Blaz. His style is pretty cutesy and unmistakable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The specific advantages are [these](http://anydice.com/program/b38).

You have a 50% chance to roll 15 or above and you'd roll 10 or lower only 25% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you cannot both regain spells and craft poisons at the same time. Crafting is taxing by default, therefore you lose the "restful" part of your calm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. 3.5
2. A lot.  
And not only would, but did. PF has some major good ideas. 3.5 has the content. Combine that, you get the ultimate D D experience.  
Heck by now, counting all house-rules I have written like my very own PHB. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... I regularly use the archives.

So much gold in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
