<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You continually fail to avoid the conversation and bait people by not conversing and acting childish.

Grow the fuck up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck that nominations track from washington post is crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter how many times you copy/paste, it doesn't make it relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  PS: a huge part of my campaign was funded by a country that actively oppresses Jews"

Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have my full support </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   He was the first president to be pro LGBT when entering office so I have faith in him

No he is not Pro LGBT. He just doesn't care so long as it doesn't impact him or his business.

Pro LGBT politician do not choose Pro-Gay conversion therapy people to be their vice-president. Plain and simple.

A select few quotes from: http://www.hrc.org/2016RepublicanFacts/donald-trump-opposes-nationwide-marriage-equality

--------------------------------------------

Trump Said He Would Strongly Consider Appointing Judges To Overturn Same-Sex Marriage Decision. Asked on Fox News Sunday WALLACE: But -- but just to button this up very quickly, sir, are you saying that if you become president, you might try to appoint justices to overrule the decision on same-sex marriage? TRUMP: I would strongly consider that, yes.

--------------------------------------------

Trump Compared Opposition To Same-Sex Marriage To Disliking Extra Long Putters In Golf. At one point, he compared his opposition to the legalization of same-sex marriage to his reluctance to use a new kind of putter. Its like in golf, he said. A lot of people  I dont want this to sound trivial  but a lot of people are switching to these really long putters, very unattractive, said Mr. Trump, a Republican. Its weird. You see these great players with these really long putters, because they cant sink three-footers anymore. And, I hate it. I am a traditionalist. I have so many fabulous friends who happen to be gay, but I am a traditionalist. [New York Times, 5/2/2011 ]

--------------------------------------------


Trump Said He Would Tell A Gay Grandchild Well, Its The Way It IsI Have Been Against [Same-Sex Marriage] From The Standpoint Of The Bible But He Would Still Love And Cherish Them. When asked by Bloomberg News how would he explain his stance against same-sex marriage to a gay grandchild, Trump responded, Well, it's the way it is, Trump said Wednesday during a Bloomberg interview with Mark Halperin and John Heilemann. I wouldnt speak to them at all about it other than they are who they are, and I want them to be happy and I will love them and I will cherish them..Ive gone to gay weddings. Ive been at gay weddings, said Trump. I have been against [same-sex marriage] from the standpoint of the Bible, from the standpoint of my teachings as growing up and going to Sunday school and going to church, and Ive been opposed to it, and well just see how it all comes out. But, you know, if I was ever in that position I'd just have to explain it. [Huffington Post, 8/27/2015 ; Bloomberg, 8/26/2015; VIDEO] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The centipedos

creative af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just report your comments for trolling because this is what you are doing. I don't particularly care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I take it you must not be a Democrat or Progressive. But instead somebody whose goal or just intention it is to parrot vitriolic sounding talking points to further divide politically left leaning people.

Because your clearly have no desire to do anything else beyond making such simple statements and snide remarks for seemingly no good reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? By wanting to know your stance on an issue beyond an Uber simple talking point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like we live in a Republic not a democracy right?

Obviously everybody is American but not everybody is morally American.

The litmus test is called the Constitution. When you fail to uphold the ideals in that you aren't "American." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "All Talk, No Action" McCain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alt-North Strategy* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  any of my fellow Progressives continue to insist that the Democratic party leadership didn't listen to them and wasn't willing to work together.

Because they weren't or aren't Progressives.

They were Bernie or Bust, plain and simple. Uncompromising, unwilling and unintelligent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is weird because the link doesn't go to Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured the best my vote could do is maybe get the Green vote closer to 5% to get federal funding. 

Shouldn't they earn they money, they vote. Not get a pity vote from people? That's my thinking.

I don't pity vote for candidates

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm just not supporting a guy who coordinated with the effort to push propaganda that Sanders, despite broad demographic appeal among young voters, was just the choice of white 'Bernie Bros' which was ultimately a needless attack, given Clinton's massive Southern advantage, and proved to be alienating to young voters, independents, and rural voters for the general, which cost the Democrats an otherwise-extremely-winnable election

FTFY:

I'm just not supporting a guy who coordinated a political campaign to defeat Bernie Sanders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing rude about doing things the right way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gild yourself.

Grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get wrecked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not NSA Chief. NSA Chief or rather NSA Director is job that is already filled.

NSC Advisor or National Security Adviser is how it should be referred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##**MILO HAS BEEN DISINVITED**

http://www.mediaite.com/online/breaking-milo-yiannapolous-disinvited-from-cpac/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ana Navarro is the kind of republican they should all aspire to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy across the street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Rush Limbaugh with the way it was set up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any relation to Hugo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So am I but there are some things where it shouldn't be America first it should be world first.

Such as climate change and the environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he wants him to succeed like any President. You might disagree but i would love for him to do good and prove everybody wrong. I think Baier is like that, at least publicly on his show, i think he gives healthy criticism and praise when due. But he doesn't suck his dick like Hannity.

I might go so far as to say he is a more level headed, journalistic O'Reilly. Whom i also feel wants the President to do good, regardless of party but will still heavily criticize and praise when the occasion or action calls for it.

I think Baier and Shep are going to be the future for Fox at least in the reporting journalistic area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would strongly consider voting for Mattis for President. Do i think it will ever happen, no. But if it did i would give strong consideration.

I don't know much about him and i hope to learn more but he seems like the defintion of "Speak softly and carry a big stick" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. Not at this point in his career, he was a reporter in the beginning but he's where he is for his opinions and interviewing style. He may considering himself a journalist which is is fine, makes no difference but he's not a reporter.

Journalist IMO is very broad, it doesn't take much to be a journalist.

Commentator, reporter, correspondent so on and so forth are more specific IMO and all fall under the catch-all-term of journalist.

Bill O'Reilly much like Sean Hannity don't break news. The react to it.

Shep, Wallace, Hemmer, Baier break  the news. Maybe not so much Wallace since Sunday magazine shows are different but regardless.

Whether or not this aspect of journalism or reporting is due in part to O'Reilly or Hannity's desires or success may be partly true. What is also partly true is doing taped news programs that air at what 8pm and 10pm respectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wallace and Shep are journalists first not pundits, not supporters of Trump necessarily.

Hannity, O'Reilly are pundits first. Hannity is a supporter. O'Reilly, i can't really says. But much of that comes from the prominence of Fox having a number of shows that are more opinion first, news second than the other way around.

Shep and Wallace are news first, opinion second. Same can be said IMO for Bill Hemmer who does the morning news program over there, i think Americas newsroom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah, conservative attack dog Judicial Watch finally does something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet you continually fail to defend yourself, explain yourself.

All you do is attack, attack, attack.

Don't waste my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you don't say the words "The definition of state-run media is" does not mean you are not distorting the definition or the phrase to make a point.

When you say this:
 
 Wallace claimed, "We don't have a state-run media in this country."
 
 What he fails to recognize though is that our mainstream media is anything but diverse and free.
 
 These 6 Corporations Control 90% Of The Media In America
 
 http://www.businessinsider.com/these-6-corporations-control-90-of-the-media-in-america-2012-6

You are strongly implying that Wallace claimed something and it is wrong because of this reason.

You are saying Wallace claimed we don't have state-run media and he is wrong because he failed to recognize that much of the mainstream media is owned by a handful of corporations.

Corporations that have a history of working with the government or lobby the government to their benefit rather than the benefit of the people who consume the news media from those division of the corporations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the author doesnt care about facts or context.

Why should the people of WV and ND vote against their best interests by voting for a candidate who doesn't support their way of life, their interests or values? Because some "liberal elite's" feelings were hurt by HRC losing?


 I dont care that West Virginia is a coal state and it is a specious argument for Joe Manchin to say that he didnt want to offend his coal industry folks.  Bernie Sanders, a hater of coal and a huge advocate for tough and immediate action to fight man-made climate change and a huge advocate for massive environmental protection won the Democratic Primary by 15.6 points and **might even have won the entire state in the General.**


 
 And I dont care that Donald Trump won North Dakota by almost 36 points.  Those people didnt, and many of them wouldnt vote for Scott Pruitt and Heidi Heitkamp shouldnt have either

That bolded bit, a huge fucking might. And is that might worth risking 1 if not 2 Senate seats on? Instead of risking it on a feeling, risk it on a fact and run with Manchin and get him to win, keeping his seat. Win else where, win Reps, win Senate seats where the risk does not outweigh the reward.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clearly a comment chain about people with the last name Wallace and you fucked it up.

Way to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wallace is a registered Democrat 

So he can vote in primaries in D.C. and stuff. Doesn't mean he's a raging liberal or anything. He's a registered Democrat solely b/c he lives in D.C.

He's an independent by his own words, having voted for both R's and D's for POTUS.

Just to be clear and mk sure everybody is on the same page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, i am not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are distorting the meaning of state-run media to make an irrelevant point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just not George Wallace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious if you bothered to read the article?



 This is the third such survey by the organisation, which began polling the panel of presidential experts in 2000
 
 The poll ranks each US president on various issues, including "crisis leadership", "moral authority", "international relations" and "pursuing equal justice for all".
 
 Obama scored particularly high on the "equal justice" scale, coming in third behind only Abraham Lincoln (1861-1865) and Lyndon Johnson (1963-1969). 
 
 But Obama ranked fifth from the bottom on "relations with Congress", and got a middling 24th best score on "international relations", the survey showed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they should be publicly discussing that until it's a foregone conclusion it will happen.

That's like discussing using nuclear weapons in a serious manner. Yeah it's there, everybody knows it an option but you just don't go talking about it all willy nilly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  de facto Democratic leaders Nancy Pelosi and Corey Booker

What. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disappointed. I wanted to watch it, oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So people need to not say words that could be mistaken for other words? That's dumb.

Also this person didn't say faggot.

https://twitter.com/KillianDain/status/833157753090752512

It's a non-issue and emotional knee-jerk reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 13:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it was on Tucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because they could go to journalists the tweets are unequivocally fake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If they're real, they can very easily go to journalists. 

Or they could just tweet anonymously and not have to worry about somebody else knowing their real identity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is how you further alienate conservatives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Mr. President be attending this rally as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Mitch McConnell told them to I think they would </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should people point out what you are? Because, and I'm mobile, but I was under the impression trolling was against the rules? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you have to answer to others why accept Keith Ellison? People shouldn't just wholly accept him in a leadership position for the whole reason is he is not stereotypically establishment.

Establishment is not bad. Poor leadership is bad. DWS was a bad leader, establishment or not. She failed at her job and replacing her with a progressive Democrat doesn't fix leadership problems if the replacement is a poor leader and somebody that can't organize to get others elected.

Tom Perez and Keith Ellison both seem like fine leaders regardless of politics. But this is about getting people elected, establishment or not. It's about getting Democrats elected, plain and simple.

Given the way Harry Reid lead the Nevada Democrats to fairly consistent winning against trends and who he endorsed that's who I think would best choice. But it's not me you have to explain, why people should accept Keith Ellison.

You should have a good reason to accept somebody or want somebody in a leadership position.

It's equally ignorant to dismiss or accept Tom Perez because you might say he is establishment as it is to dismiss or accept Keith Ellison solely because he's not. 

In my book for some people, let me be clear when I say I'm not saying you are, I've seen on here to use that as there only criteria, establishment or not as a means of choosing a politician is short sighted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   If they are unwilling to choose him in this lower-stakes leadership position it shows they are unwilling to change at all.

DNC Chair is by no means a lower-stakes leadership position.

Have you seen what a poor DNC Chair means for Democratic elections across the nation? 

The loss of hundreds of seats can be attributed to the poor leadership of a DNC chair by the name of Debbie Wasserman Schultz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking about Ellison. You make or made it seem like this Buckley guy has or had more endorsements than Perez. He didn't. Buckley isn't nor wasn't a front-runner.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perez has the Vice President and the former Attorney General amongst others.

I think those two, really the one VP Biden is far more than 2 senators and a few Reps.

There is a reason why Perez and Ellison are a front runner, not Ellison and Buckley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##**SHIT SHOW WON'T WAIT UNTIL THEN**

##**Trump will be addressing a joint session of Congress and  the nation on Feb 28th.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harward is also going to be on ABC This Week on sunday so expect more directly from him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is the one who will Shell access!

He'll also Exxon, Chevron, Lukoil and BP access! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or was that a transcription error from Time?

Politico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's a conservative pundit who wrote this piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you should read the article.

"The candidates will debate their visions and strategies for the 2018 midterm elections, how to rebuild the Democratic Party and the role of the DNC under the Trump administration." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 13:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he said we are going to win so much he meant we are going to win the race to the bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the pivot? The pivot to where Pence is President? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so? is that supposed to be a threat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer is going to spin it as Trump administration = White House

This wasnt a doing by the WH it was DHS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ''This is what it's like to be with Trump,'' Christie said on a New York sports talk radio show Thursday, the Boston Globe reported. ''He says, 'There's the menu, you guys order whatever you want.' And then he says, 'Chris, you and I are going to have the meatloaf.'''


I found this to be an interesting little insight into the Trump W.H. How he controls people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump dies as travel ban loses in court again

If only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But play him as the same little jewish boy from weekend update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ana Navarro is the kind of Republican they should strive to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see what you are saying. My point is using the abbreviation NSA for National Security Advisor is not usually done to avoid confusion with the agency of the same name. Informally you'd NSC Advisor or the official abbreviation of APNSA which stands for Assistant to the President for National Security Affairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does i just guess to get the audio in the press confernence, real quick they hooked up a mic for everybody to try and use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSC advisor is the proper way to call it.

NSA is nearly exclusive used when referring to the national security agency. The place Snowden worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we supposed to be surprised that Immigration is empowered to deport illegal immigrants? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  NSA job 

You should say NSC advisor.

NSA is nearly exclusively used to reference the National Security Agency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Shep, Bill Hemmer, Chris Wallace and Bret Baier are as close as it gets. In that order imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pool audio. So everybody else can pick up his audio clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wont fire their only openly gay male anchor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They are empowered to deport illegal immigrants for even minor offenses like running lights.

Source please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Didn't they attempt to impeach Bill Clinton for that same reason?

Under oath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about making a differenc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The leaks are real but the news is fake.

That is a real quote from Trump yeah. From the presser that is happening now or just happened, i stopped watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was already thinking about a QR code, good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Accosta cant even get Trump to explain wtf that means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##**NBC REPORTER JUST GOT TRUMP TO SAY "I FIRED HIM" IN REGARDS TO FLYNN** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to print these out and flyer them around NYC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reporters mic's aren't for the audio in the room, they are for their cameras so they go back to their respective networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Alexander from NBC just called POTUS out for lying about electoral college vote numbers.

Fucking balls of steel on Peter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NBD. I just don't wont confusion of people to think Flynn was heading up the National Security Agency, aka the thing Snowden worked for a leaked.

Flynn was merely an advisor to Trump with security clearance. But thats not something to shake a stick at too just not as "big a deal" imo as Dir of the NSA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't say NSA. 

You should say NSC advisor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about short notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody probably noticed. Look how get we got and are realizing the timing between the two. And that the ties to Russia are far more stronger to Trump now than months ago.

I didn't realize the timing. I work at a major media outlet and if I brought this up with coworkers I bet they didn't realize then or now.

Shit was just coming out it was a lot to process professionally and as a consumer of information personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Liam Neeson play him in a film entitled *Schindler's Twitter Feed* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they don't know where the bodies are buried they either find out or just bury bodies and "discover" them themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the accent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J Edgar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's also going leave the country tomorrow or this week and avoid Pruitt's EPA vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Oprah. Considering she provided the tape to the Senate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay and so? Thats past tense, what's he doing now?

He's not involved in the day to day editorial decisions, we know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popular isn't on my nav bar between FRONT and ALL.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well considering Bannon to Breitbart is different from Carlson/Daily Caller.

Bannon didn't found or own Breitbart. Carlson did and does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not involved in day-to-day editorial decisions. 

I can't really fault, if thats the right phrase, somebody when they don't oversee the day to day ops or are involved with daily editorial decisions. Im sure he wants his business to succeed like any other business-owner but if he's not operating it on a daily level any issues are with the current editorial staff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To study and learn more about them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tucker Carlson no longer works on the Daily Caller. He stepped down as editor in-chief in Nov </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A necessary evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were eye opening to anybody that has a simple view of the world, that thinks it works in black and white, that there is no grey.

Their failure is one of the primary reasons we're living with a Trump presidency.

No the reason we're living with a Trump presidency is because Hillary Clinton didn't campaign enough in the states that mattered when it came to white working class folks in the middle of the country.

We are living in a Trump presidency because HRC did not appeal to the needs of certain voters in the same way that Trump did.

The media is not a primary reason we have Donald Trump as president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the event of the 2016 primaries was all that it takes to make you lose faith in media outlets for investigative reporting then you never had any faith in them to begin with. Given all of their long histories, primarily the WaPo and NYT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its interesting he hasn't taken a question from Fox News. Only Fox Business, i think he's afraid of their correspondent, John Roberts as much as he his Jim Accosta or any other WH reporter from the main networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Accosts said on CNN:

In the last three news conferences, [CNN anchor] Wolf [Blitzer], Acosta stated. All of the questions to the American news media have been handled by conservative press, and I think, Wolf, theres no other way to describe it but **the fix is in** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean even if doesn't withdraw they say they dont have the votes so it doesn't matter really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wants to be Jackie Kennedy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was done explaining the correlation between Conway and OP.

It was you who went on to make the claim that we are all guilty of doing similar things as her and that must mean we are all Kellyanne Conway by my logic.

But if you want to play dumbass, thats your time to waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we are all guilty of doing this, i don't see why that's an issue.

 that means we're all Kellyanne Conway by your logic.

Sure if you want to claim that, i don't care. I can understand that not everybody who distorts facts and misleads people doesn't do it from the White House and impacts American politics on a national level but then again i am also able to see context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't say it's on the same level as Conway.

Distorting facts to fit your narrative is the same thing whether Conway does it or OP does it. Conway's just more impactful since she works for the WH.

Thats what happened here and thats what i said.

I'm done explaining this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distorting facts to fit your narrative is the same thing whether Conway does it or OP does it. Conway's just more impactful since she works for the WH

Thats what happened here and thats what i said.

I'm done explaining this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distorting facts to fit your narrative is the same thing whether Conway does it or OP does it. Conway's just more impactful since she works for the WH

Thats what happened here and thats what i said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Obama is, was and always will be the 44th President. This will never change.

Obama is the 44th President. He just isn't President now. Obama also was the 44th President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it's on the same level. I said it's the same distorting of facts Kellyanne Conway, as in it's the same type of misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing hyperbolic about this my comment. The only hyperbole is your title saying Whitehouse.gov stills lists are Obama as President and Biden as VP when it specially says otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesn't.

What it says is:

President Barack Obama is the 44th President of the United States

Joseph R. Biden is the 47th Vice President of the United States. 

When you go the administration page instead of just a bio of the executive brand it lists Trump and Pence.

This is the same distorting of facts that people criticized Kellyanne Conway for saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see whats so wrong about the monitors to allow media folks not near DC to get a question in. If anything it's the next logical step in bringing the White House into the 21st century at least in regard to their relationship with the media.

The only issue is having people who don't necessarily qualify as journalist and more just commentators or bloggers. I have to agree with the Trump administration on this point because i think it's a fine thing to allow people representing local news affiliates to ask questions thru this method. What i wouldn't agree with is allowing people who represent highly politicized blogs and sites that sound like Conservatard.com or GOPNews.net, i.e. sites that clearly distort the truth for an agenda rather than add their own commentary to the facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fuck that. If we are impeaching Trump, his whole admin goes and we put Ryan in.

The whole admin doesnt need to go for that to happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good thing the very definition of treason is in the Constitution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now we know Trump knew about the call for nearly two weeks prior and Pence didn't.

They are lying to each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When your director of national security is an agent of Russia,

Michael Flynn is not the Director of National Security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats going on here is simply to distract you from the fact that in 1998, The Undertaker threw Mankind off Hell In A Cell, and plummeted 16 ft through an announcer's table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the House leadership is having a press conference right now and they are all talking about Health care. Not a single mention of Trump so far but now here come the questions...

Yup the first question to Paul Ryan is about the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay off college for me, my brother and sister.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so do I but I don't act like the bastion of knowledge regarding such topics.

Did he or did he just share his opinion or view in such topics?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they know where good for them they will keep Keith Kellogg, the acting national security advisor in the role.

But they clearly don't know what's good for them so I doubt this will happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I checked people weren't going to George Carlin for this science knowledge.

They go for good social and political commentary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will they have Colin Powell show up at the U.N. with a little vial of Bernie Sanders to illustrate Russia's WMLs.

Weapons of Mass Leftism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they won't.

They won't fire him, he won't quit. Where have you been in the last 2 years? Trump doesn't give a shit about if something looks illegal, is illegal or corrupt.

They only give a shit if the person it's attached to has a (D) and Clinton in their name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
