<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject251</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there any reason to deposit any other way than via Bitcoin?  It makes no sense why anyone would do otherwise imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald? Is that you, Mr. Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this close? I live in central CT and have plenty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, maybe next time. Cheers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better list would be cool. Was thinking mixed 4 pack of Tree/Trill so something to that value  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hops, stouts, sours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you have to offer? No idea what you have locally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still looking? I have tree house and Trillium to work with (located in CT) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would help if you posted what you got BT for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casinos surely cant be allowing this... Guess its incognito? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent PM still no response.  Maybe he realized ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/cringeworthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of my sources have confirmed that...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea the windows thing is a myth... just like the background color of the On Tap page.  The only true way to know is to wait for the announcement.  Lately for the whales like KJ and JM they announced really late in the day like 3pm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girlfriend of the Year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to tree house yesterday, copped 20 cans of bright.  Most are already accounted for, but I feel like a big release is coming tomorrow.... Good Morning possibly?  Either way, I need to get some mules up there for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole hand is a disaster... 

1.  Raise to 100 is way too small
2.  Flop bet is WAY too small
3.  Turn bet is WAY too small </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do that there literally is no "variance" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to sound harsh, but maybe they should do a better job of marketing themselves?  Some places obv gain popularity vi word of mouth and develop a cult following (ie. Tree House, Alchemist, etc) but you have to put some of that burden on the brewers themselves.  If people don't know about it, they aren't going to seek it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall of text, but worth the read IMO.  It felt good to write this all down and I'm kinda laughing about it now.

During college I came home for Thanksgiving (class of 2010 for reference).  The night before Thanksgiving everyone generally goes out and gets wasted at the bars.  This particular night, I went out to Hibachi style dinner with some friends for a girls birthday, we have drinks, dinner, etc then head to a bar downtown.  They have 22oz drafts of anything on tap for $1, so I proceed to have quite a few.  Finally, I feel that rumble... I go to stand in line for the bathroom, there are 3 urinals, and 2 toilets behind these weird western saloon style swing doors facing each other.  It gets to be my turn and I know this is going to be ugly but it has to be done, so I say "sorry guys but im going to shit my pants if I don't take a shit now... enter at your own risk."  I proceed to have the most explosive mud bomb explosion in which I must have been airborne for a slight period of time.  People start clapping and jeering as I walk out of the bathroom.  That is part one....


A few mins later, this girl starts chatting me up.  She's petit, pretty cute, and I've somewhat seen her around as she was from my town but we ran in different circles.  We're hanging out and some dude walks by and says "yooo youre the dude who took a shit in the bathroom!" and offers me a high five.  I sort of chuckle it off and she is visibly disgusted and walks away.  Fine, whatever.  I few hours later I end up at an afterparty.  She is there, we are really drunk by now and she says "well are you going to bring me home or what?"  So, we walk about 3/4 of a mile to my house.  My dad is basically an insomniac, I can see him in the living room on the computer. We sneak in, and I lead her to the basement stairs (where I normally sleep).  My dad asks how my night was from the other room and I just say "great, going to bed see you tomorrow."  We screw each others brains out that night, it was pretty unreal.  I wake up in the morning to the sounds of my parents walking around upstairs, clueless that I have a completely naked girl in my bed in the basement.  Then, I hear my father open the door to the basement and start to make his way down.  I cover up the chick as best I can and pretend to be asleep.  He says "hey time to get up, we have to go to the football game" and I say ok and I would be up in a minute.  Now the panic sets in as I have no way to get this girl out of the house.  Her mom calls her and asks where the hell she is, she says she stayed with a friend and would be home after work.  After hanging up she looks at me and says "so can you give me a ride to work?"  Well, no, no I cant - I have no car here and I have to go to a game with my dad. Mind you, her work is about 40 minutes away from where I live.  Finally, it dawns on me that when I was in highschool I would sneak through the crawlspace window and out the neighbors yard at night.  I look over to the girl, tell her the game plan, and was briskly greeted with "Youre fucking kidding right?" I say nope, and boost her up to the window to make her escape.  I tell her if she walks a couple blocks south there is a pretty main strip of road where she can likely find a cab.

The football game was pretty fun.

**TL;DR:** took a mean dump at a bar and was berated for it, took a chick home to my parents house and made her crawl out the basement window and figure out how to get to work 40 mins away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, looks completely fine to me, maybe slightly bigger on turn I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate it multiway but prob less than optimal.  If we feel like we have any type of edge post its meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The math is strong with this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line moves incredibly fast, way more efficient than any other big release brewery imo.  A 2.5 hour line at Trillium Fort Point would be like 45 mins tops at Tree House.  They really have their shit together and its overall just a really well managed establishment.  I really don't have a single bad thing to say other than sometimes the field smells like shit from the septic system lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm I'm part of all the groups, never seen that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, is this with the spread or straight?  If with spread, what line do you like?  FWIW, im in CT and have treehouse, trillium, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious, how big or small are you looking to go for these types of things?  Like couple cans, or couple whale stouts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see something like this.  I was literally thinking about it again today on my way to work about making a release history spreadsheet for Tree House's past releases.  It would come in handy for trending data and predicting release dates!

I plan to do some asking around in some of the Tree House circle jerks that I am a part of, but if it doesn't exist I'll probably take it upon myself to create something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might have a problem when... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to PM you Sat if this doesn't close first.  Will have DI, NA, and some Tree House on Saturday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll shoot you a PM tomorrow.  I will have 16 Never and Again from Trillium and tomorrows Tree House allotment, also have some Julius etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is 6 Julius + 6 Green  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man but not going to make it there today after all. Not worth the risk as they only had 160 cases left as of 2:00. They sold 50 cases in the previous half hour. I'll be going tomorrow like 95% and will get growlers and can allotments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But spread limit... right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa that looks like a really nice room judging solely by the table and chips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wishes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I forgot about pisco  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As other users have stated, the amount of force exherted (or absorbed) over a period of driving time is significantly higher with braking than it is with shock absorbtion.  These systems also weigh a lot.  Some manufacturers for hydraulic regen braking systems make the giant accumulators out of wrapped carbon fiber to save on weight - but its a double edged sword as that accumulator is then extremely expensive.  

Source: I was previously employed as a hydraulic systems engineer and worked on regen systems targeted toward city buses and garbage trucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't sorry. Usually shared w friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any known craft beer in Santiago, Chile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heading there for work next month and would like to bring back some local goodies. I have no clue what their beer scene is like, but I enjoy IPAs, Stouts, and Sours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If posted this in detail before, but cliffnotes

-Played in a big club game

-Won ton of money

-Was walking back to car about 1/2 a block away and man grabs me in a choke from behind and points something into my back with "I know where you're coming from, just give me the cash and I wont hurt you"

-Bye bye 5 figure cash sum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 15:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little gem that no one has mentioned - Missouri.  STL and KC both always have a ton of action from huge PLO to normal 1/2.  When I still lived there we had a 5/5 PLO game that had a mandatory 10 on the button and SOMETIMES even 30/100 dark from the SB and BB.  It was nuts. I've seen big 50/100 Mixed games running recently in KC too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they release this everywhere in the states or just in the Midwest? I just moved OUT of KC unfortunately... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think driving drunk is a fairly unanimous answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> prob also going Wednesday man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 13:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2008 to 2010 or so I was staked mostly for $26 freezeouts on FTP, obviously I played a ton of miniFTOPS and some of the actual FTOPS events.  We did pretty well, I shipped the 35k for like 9k once and a couple other 4 figure scores.  I was in college so my volume wasn't insane but I had a pretty damn good ROI with a medium'ish volume.  One day, my backer just fell off the face of the earth - to this day I have no idea what happened but I think he prob just went busto.  Occasionally I would catch him playing PLO up to 25/50 and just getting hosed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 13:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> daaaaamn shots fired 
popcorn.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 13:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you flying or driving?  Either way I don't foresee this being an issue.  Cash will be fine, 5k can easily fit in a pocket or two (or sock if youre really that worried about being shaken down lol). 

I would just say be safe leaving the home game.  Make sure no one follows you out, make sure you have safe travel back to your final destination.  I was robbed once leaving a club game and it was not such a great memory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't knocking your evaluation, just didn't know! 12x Tree House = a whale  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy cow is that what Miami Madness is pulling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 Lights On + 2 Julius + 1 JM for 1 NG Raspberry Tart + 1 Bruery Oude Tard?

Im on the Tree House side, so hard for me to gage value on non IPAs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> results?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha fair enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta ask, why did you want 18 Broncos cans that badly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No...
Also, $600 is only 2-3 full buyins.  He could lose that in an hour, realistically.  Just tell him to save up until he has a roll of his own.  Or tell him he has a gambling problem and should seek help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me guess, you think Bush did 9/11 and Hillary Clinton is part of the Illuminati too, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/poker post of the year for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try not to divulge what side I'm on to reduce any bias, but thanks for the answer. I'm on the TH side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oude Quetsche Tilquin a L'Ancienne for variety of Tree House.  How many TH is fair assuming 1 whale like a JM or IP? Guessing somewhere between secondary value and $4$? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 17:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems completely fine.  1/2 NL games usually rake more once you consider drop for BBJ and what not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Content blocked from Olympic committee :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 00:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not right downtown, ameristar and Hollywood generally have the most action. Check the bravo app for live listings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Monkish you have available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your turn sizing is pretty horrible... I honestly don't hate leading the turn but why are you betting 1/4 pot?

AP, river is a pretty easy fold as this is Ax 99.9% of the time. That sizing looks like a sure valuebet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 300 kg is like 661 lbs... So that would be about 6 tusks total...

am I missing something here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't we just drone Hillary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: Fold

2: Shove </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically, yes.  My senior design team shut down the idea and we made some surgical stapler type of thing instead.  Years later I saw this on an infomercial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had an idea in college for a container that had a screw bottom to push the contents to the top.  Imagine for salsa, peanut butter, etc. to avoid breaking chips, awkward butter knife maneuvers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3b pre to 40, rest of the hand plays itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 12:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed 
Source: CT Tree House trader :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I inline from my phone without linking to imgur? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 23:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good point. I'll rearrange  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea had some first meal, pulp, and walk of shame from a trade. Pulp and 1st meal were pretty solid. Walk of shame was a blonde but had strong coffee notes - really strange but I actually enjoyed it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just moved into my new house. Fridge is still a little empty for my gf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP cold calls a 3b pre. 

OP bets 800 into over 6k. 

OP calls villain a fish. 

Online poker is unbeatable folks.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where you located? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> saw a man at the Borgata in Atlantic City walk up and put a $1K chip on number 29 black on a roulette table.  It hits, he waits to be dulled out his $35k, then walks away - literally emotionless.  Can only imagine he does this a lot and doesn't always have the same luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish there were more of this type of news instead of the typical "x bombs y: z people dead" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You in CA? I'm in CT and would prefer not to ship all the way across country but may consider.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok this is fucking incredible. Imagine real money games w this software.  I have the strangest boner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DFS is a game of skill though, remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly who I thought of.  Guess ill go catch up on his blog now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BA Oro Negro + Cerise Morte for x2 JM + x2 Julius + x1 In Perpetuity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Todd The Axe Man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM coming your way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty hilarious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TTAM is very good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yea... wasn't going to spell that out but yup. Used to live/play there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 05:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you in Missouri by any chance? Saw this on a poker buddies facebook page  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice call. I think you see Ax there a lot but a good reg knows that as well. GL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which alpaca magi, there are several variants... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 13:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's why it struck me as weird haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also your username is my dads name... same spelling. Weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All true. Also need to consider that all the kids went back to college and vacation season is virtually over. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have IP, JM, Julius, and other random TH.  PM me w ratios if interested - Located in CT but can ship. Also going to Trill tomorrow and can pick up what is offered at Fort Point location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
