<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol going after work...I'll update as I am disappointing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am close as well, can someone give me a guide to best stats of a Magikarp to upgrade so I don't have regrets for another 4 months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's like xmas in .8 km ! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those seats are not ideal but they do 1/3 of the show at the back stage where you will have a great view of the performance. I guarantee she will have a great time. Honestly, its not too hard to just go on to the floor, wrap a colorful band around your wrist (bring a few colors) and run in when there is a lot of colors flashing, security won't notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the water pump...I guess I bough a cheap knock off so the fins broke off the spindle...Lesson Learned - don't ever buy cheap parts! my front brakes were EBC Yellow - great stopping power but they wear out quick. Mobil1 is oil change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 14:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> e46 M54 engines have timing Chains - no need to replace till about 300k miles or 480k KM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 14:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Below is a list of all my repairs and maintenance items for my 2002 BMW CiC I bought with 89k miles. I hope this gives you an idea of repairs to come. You will save a lot if you can do most of these yourself. Let me know if you have any questions
http://imgur.com/a/QrLxz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 14:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Below is a list of all my repairs and maintenance items for my 2002 BMW CiC I bought with 89k miles. I hope this gives you an idea of repairs to come. You will save a lot if you can do most of these yourself. Let me know if you have any questions
http://imgur.com/a/QrLxz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! I never did figure out if that actually happens. I got a stiff eibach front swaybar and beilsteins PSS - so it may actually lift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious how the auto pilot would do on Boston streets. The street quality rivals any 3rd world nation and the road patterns are over 250 years old: rarely a straight road, many intersections are 6 way stops and in many places there are no double yellow lines separating the road....but I see many testas on the roads here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 13:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the roofrack look! If my wasn't a vert, I would have one as well even if I had nothing to carry up there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Action shot of me mid-slide from a BMW Auto Cross event. Has anyone else enjoyed AutoX as much as I have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 13:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 15:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would help having a sign 'THIS IS A HAND DRYER' with an arrow pointing down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case anyone doesn't get it, this is a reference to an opening sequence of The Office (US) tv show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly it was insanely over budget and they probably will take another 10 years to build one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this show incredibly engaging, the character development was something rarely seen in a mini-series. loved it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, but you are missing the point of my question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Can you slowly descend from space (maybe use of a jetpack?) and not burn up in the atmosphere on re-entry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We always see the colossal heat generated on re-entry of a capsule but lets say a spacewalk goes wrong and the astronaut needs to get back to earth without a capsule, and lets say he had enough fuel to reduce his entry speed to, lets say 100 miles an hour and then deploy a parachute when atmosphere is thick enough...would he survive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This belong in /oddlysatisfying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I am ever in a situation where I need to answer the question: How Many Chemical Elements share their symbol with a US State acronym? - I have the answer! = 15   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 20:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping someone would answer it - the show is called Better Things - female version of Louis CK  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing John Lennon performance of the song called Mother - You may recognize it from a new TV Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 15:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Lennon - Mother [Acoustic / Rock] 1972 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 15:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> net </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> addedit to watch later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of my GF - She gets pissed when I quote her insults back to her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just about that age when I randomly found a hard copy of 'Da Vinci Code' in an unlocked locker. This was early 2000's and I hear all the hype about the book. That evening I opened the book and didn't put it down till early morning hours the next day. I finished the book by next evening and was mind-blown by my ability to read a book (considering I have not read a book since I was in grade school) Thank you Dan Brown for teaching me how to read again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6_n4cp_jedo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Touch me I'm Karen Taylor

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6_n4cp_jedo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you need to adjust the surface area for the fact that its a goose egg (stated the video description (see URL to youtube video below)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just made the mistake of googling his name and viewing the images........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 15:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was literately his only goal in this election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boston here - never seen Mr. Mimes or Farfetchd but a ton of Tauros </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with your thoughts on Viceland, they go out into the real world and report on life as it is, applying high value production and just short enough to keep the attention span of an average consumer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  is it me or does it look fake?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that is all the sleep your body needs - then you have that much more time to spend on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work, catch a plane, etc. - waking up naturally has really helped my overall well-being </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When watching movies, i think about when they would need to poop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being able to wake up without the use of an alarm clock feels like a major life accomplishment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am drowning in drowsie's here in boston, easily 5 an hour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I am more disturbed when I see voice-over actors performing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 12:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly...half the fun of the game is managing your pokemon collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 13:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great representation of what the future potentially may look like! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unrelated news, OP's home is surrounded by mysterious holes in the dirt, new ones popping up each morning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not understand how it works...it just gets it wet...so a wipe must still occur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what Kanye thinks of Kanye deconstructed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 13:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't understand what these happy berries are a reference to
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
