<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the USA is #1 at making war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'He's lying to you': MEP Seb Dance mocks Nigel Farage during Trump speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon me, do you have any Grey Poupon?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delawares Governor and Lt. Governor Declare Feb. 12 Charles Darwin Day Throughout the State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people approved of the "final" solution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solution: buy electric cars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will they outlaw news organizations not considered "friendly" to the Republican cause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under A New System, Clinton Could Have Won The Popular Vote By 5 Points And Still Lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, god made man from dirt and cloned another from a rib.  It makes perfect sense, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SF sues over Trumps executive order targeting sanctuary cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the "final" solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, dear.  That might not be good for business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will they ban publications not considered "friendly" to the Republican cause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this before, there is research to back this up. They call it "Time Resisted Feeding". It is like IF, but they found that during the feeding window, even if a person eats LFHC, they get the same results. Basically, a person eats in a 12 hour window, they will maintain their weight. If they shorten the window to 8-10 hours, a person will lose weight and be lean. If a person is eating and lifting, they get muscle gains. Further, I think it is easier for a fat burner to do this because they will not be hungry. More details from the researchers in this [ video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-R-eqJDQ2nU).

There is a neat little app available called "Zero" that a person can use to track their fasting time.  It is made by Kevin Rose of Digg fame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person can test insulin response in a lab environment.  Unfortunately, this is not available at home.  A blood glucose monitor is a close approximation.  They can test eating fat, eating protein, and eating carbs and sugar.  Carbs, and sugar spike insulin the most and then it takes the body 4 hours to get back to normal insulin level.  Insulin causes energy to be stored as fat, and it blocks fat cells from releasing energy.  Over time, a person just gets fatter and fatter.  Later, insulin resistance will develop then diabetes. For 90% of people, insulin is the key to losing weight, and reversing diabetes.  IF and fasting is the best method to get a person's insulin level to drop the most.  This literally resets a person's body back to normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Keto got a lot of body fat off, but fasting get me very lean.  I can see muscle definition in my whole body.  I am not puffy like the carb eaters.  It is awesome!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy likes the keto bars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YfS8MO0Sh_s) from Low Carb USA last weekend, Jimmy is really big.  When I started keto, IF, and fasting 3 years ago, I was 40% body fat.  Today, I am 10-12% body fat.  In that time, Jimmy has not gotten much smaller.  Don't know why.  All I can say is that it works very good for me.  On LFHC, I just got fatter and fatter every year (high insulin), and if I didn't change, today I would be diabetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That didn't take long...8 days.  WTF!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least he didn't attack the Sikh temple thinking they were Muslims.  I hate that when that happens.  Stupid is what stupid does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all fairness, just because he is registered to vote in many states doesn't mean he voted multiple times.  Someone should investigate to see if he did vote many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atheists Ask Michigan Town to Remove Veterans Monument Honoring Only Christian Soldiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Origins of Totalitarianism, Hannah Arendts defining work on tyranny, is out of stock on Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American, Delta and United promise full refunds to those hit by travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Origins of Totalitarianism, Hannah Arendts definitive guide to how tyranny begins, has sold out on Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fate of a Leg of a Statue of Saddam Hussein - "Kai Kobold, a German antiques dealer, recently sold what he believes to be the left leg of a statue of Saddam Hussein famously toppled by U.S. troops in April, 2003." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then tomorrow, Trump will complain about the air in Beijing.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're an atheist in southern USA, people will do the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: "You're eyes are lying to you!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change orders are expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps they can build a Wall of Ignorance around the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I would be worried that Trump and his people in the White House are f*cking idiots.  Prove me wrong.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Survey Shows Far Too Many Americans Believe God Influences Sports and Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, the sun doesn't rise or set.  It is an illusion caused by the Earth spin around.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save money, live better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read up on autophagy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is research to back this up.  They call it "Time Resisted Feeding".  It is like IF, but they found that during the feeding window, even if a person eats LFHC, they get the same results.  Basically, a person eats in a 12 hour window, they will maintain their weight.  If they shorten the window to 8-10 hours, a person will lose weight and be lean.  If a person is eating and lifting, they get muscle gains.  Further, I think it is easier for a fat burner to do this because they will not be hungry.  More details from the researchers in [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-R-eqJDQ2nU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Koch brothers are good fellows. They are said to occasionally wave as they pass by in their chauffeur driven limousines. "The common man is revolting" is their favorite saying.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason given in the petition to deny the state visit is that it would embarrass the Queen.  Funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be poor because he doesn't have his own airplane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Truth be told](https://i.imgur.com/bmRRcuN.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low Carb USA - West Palm Beach 2017 - Keto Panel Q A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YfS8MO0Sh_s

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Researcher's Guide to the Resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conway: Trump's immigration order not a Muslim ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giuliani: Trump asked me how we can build extermination camps "legally" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Venezuela, we couldnt stop Chvez. Dont make the same mistakes we did. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 of the 19 9/11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia and their leader was at a safe house in Pakistan.  What does the USA do, invade Iraq and Afghanistan.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Venezuela, we couldnt stop Chvez. Dont make the same mistakes we did. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump resistance is beating him on his own turf: Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 of the 19 9/11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia.  The others were from Egypt, and UAE.  None of these countries are on the banned list.  WTF!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem: $15 billion dollar wall

Solution: $50 ladder
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the President doesn't pay taxes, why should we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People with money can fly to another country to get an abortion.  So really, the Republicans are just punishing the poor in forcing them to have a baby they don't really want.  WTF!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Donald Trumps call with Vladimir Putin is scheduled to take place amid widespread speculation that the White House is considering lifting sanctions against Russia. For the sake of Americas national security and that of our allies, I hope President Trump will put an end to this speculation and reject such a reckless course. If he does not, I will work with my colleagues to codify sanctions against Russia into law." - McCain
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem: $15 billion dollar wall

Solution: $50 ladder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glenn Beck and David Barton Want To Build a History Museum (Like Things Werent Bad Enough Already) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Orwell's 1940 review of Mein Kampf is kind of chilling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Search for Billions to Pay for Border Wall Confronts Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The leaks coming out of the Trump White House cast the president as a clueless child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post-inauguration Street Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Koreas Masikryong Ski Resort Is Kept Open by Work Gangs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is.  A government can't keep people in jail with no charges for an unlimited amount of time.  It is unconstitutional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detaining people who have not committed a crime and who are not charged with any crime for an unlimited amount of time is against the constitution.  This is what the federal government wants the cities to do.  They want cities to house people who aren't charged with any crime until they pick them up.  It is against the US Constitution to do something like that.  In the state I live in, they can only hold people in jail for 2 days without any charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's Folly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the president isn't paying taxes, why should the rest of us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the fact there is already a wall along most of the border, it seems fixing gaps is a good idea.  Can't blame the chief for leaving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking city governments to do things that are not constitutional is not a good thing, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can be the most presidential person ever, other than the great Abe Lincoln" - Donald J. Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking fights with the smartest people in the USA is not going to work out very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not good for business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scathing audit faults Wisconsin Transportation Dept. after nearly $1B budget shortfall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryan Says President Trumps Border Wall Would Cost Up to $15 Billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ICP not the brightest](https://i.imgur.com/aYEX8gP.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My IQ is one of the highest  and you all know it! Please don't feel so stupid or insecure; it's not your fault." - Donald J. Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump, Aping Fox News, Calls Chelsea Manning Ungrateful Traitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two dead after light plane crashes into the Swan River in front of shocked Australia Day crowd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First train in over four years travels through Aleppo - "Hundreds of Syrians returned to everyday life on Wednesday by taking the first train ride through the ravaged city in five years." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Much of the Cuisine We Now Know, and Think of as Ours, Came to Us by War - "The long and winding road that brought "local" dishes to our plates" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person doesn't lose muscle mass on a fast unless they are less than 4% body fat.  What would happen during a famine?  People would be just a ball of fat, no?  HGH levels are high during a fast.  This protects the muscles and protein.  I lift the heaviest weights after 4 days of fasting.

https://intensivedietarymanagement.com/fasting-and-growth-hormone-physiology-part-3/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 9/11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia. Why is Saudi Arabia not on the list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 9/11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia. Why is Saudi Arabia not on the list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans say they are all about freedom and such.  Obviously, this is an alternative fact.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The USA already has a border wall, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Obamacare, but I like ACA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the USA already have a border wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 9/11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia. Why is Saudi Arabia always let off the hook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we do need to save the world from the next ice age. Last ice age, my hometown was under a glacier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The stupid...](https://i.imgur.com/ISwvWW1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Is a Strange Way to Show Me You Love Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: I'll Order Probe Into Voter Fraud, Voting By 'Those Who Are Illegal' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 9/11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia.  Why is Saudi Arabia not on the list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As President, Trump should launch an investigation into this issue immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it odd they want to build a wall when there is already one there.  Then Trump complains about Boeing wasting money on a new Air Force One.  WTF!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cold weather keeps the bad people away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we do need to save the world from the next ice age.  Last ice age, my hometown was under a glacier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To all the people who said Dayton was drunk or on drugs last night, FU!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Trump's claim is true, he should launch an investigation, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like wanting to drink clean water, and breath clean air is a bad thing.  WTF!  Can't wait until Trump starts complaining about the air in Beijing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Mark Dayton has prostate cancer, says he can do the job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gov. Mark Dayton, who fainted Monday night during his State of the State speech, revealed Tuesday that he was diagnosed with prostate cancer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Mark Dayton has prostate cancer, says he can do the job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not just one data point.  It is easy to test.  My wife and I mess with them. Telescopes, trips to England, and laptop computer.  It is very creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gasoline powered cars will soon go the way of horse and buggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is true, why doesn't Trump call for an investigation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking to my wife at home the other day about buying a pizza oven.  Next day, pizza oven ads popped up on my FB feed.  A-holes are listening to my phone.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump kills TPP, giving China its first big win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Romaphobia Became the Last 'Acceptable' Form of Racism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. judge finds that Aetna misled the public about its reasons for quitting Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much money did they give to Israel?  $38 billion over 10 years.

http://www.cnn.com/2016/09/13/politics/us-israel-military-aid-package-mou/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is making George W Bush look good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 11:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British cops used a Taser on a black man they thought was a robber. He was their race-relations adviser. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Europe, the football (soccer) teams own their stadiums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Welcome to America](https://i.imgur.com/nEVpegJ.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny thing about facts, they are true whether you believe them or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The resistance is strong.  You can't defeat Trump with with just one blow.  He will fall in death by a thousand paper cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your eyes are lying to you!" - Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your eyes are lying to you!" - Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This had to have been one of the biggest protests in USA history. Good for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This had to have been one of the biggest protests in USA history.  Good for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your eyes are lying to you!"  WTF!  They need to go full China and censor the Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your eyes are lying to you!" - WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your eyes are lying to you!" Donald Trump is such a phony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting to the Womens March: Metro reports packed trains; MARC adds more trains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Resistance Plan: Step One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Resistance Plan: Step One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is such a phony! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon me, Do you have any grey poupon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When is the Muslim Kenyan President Barack Obama gonna take away my guns?  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I for one am looking forward to gondola rides in the streets of Miami. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow!  Fox News is now fake news.  Oh, dear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Anna-Senpai, the Mirai Worm Author? - "Mirai, a malware strain that enslaves poorly secured Internet of Things (IoT) devices like wireless routers and security cameras into a botnet for use in large cyberattacks." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon and Jupiter in the early morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, Donald Trump Isnt the First President to Celebrate His Inauguration at the Lincoln Memorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbus didn't discover anything.  There were already people living in America when he arrived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really understood Columbus Day.  People say Columbus discovered America, but there were already people living here when he arrived.  He didn't discover anything.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Plan to Replace Obamacare Does Not Exist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FFRF, parent sue to end 75 years of bible classes in Mercer County, W.Va. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Pascal's Wager, you know, proved that it was rational to believe in God if there was the slightest chance it would annoy Sam Harris." - Slavoj iek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/yIkkxzk.png

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Amazon, a person can get a used older edition for around $10 or so.  In many cases, the older editions are not much different than the new edition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im not an extrovert  and that makes it harder to find love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Times Trump Spread Fake News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen pictures of a person who did a 30 day water fast.  The person's liver was noticeably smaller at the end of the fast.  However, once the person started to refeed, the size came back.  Apparently, stem cells get activated in the fast.  A switch gets turned on.  When a person refeeds, new cells are generated.  It this case, the person ended up with many new cells in his liver and other organs.  A 30 day water fast is very long.  Most people would not do a fast like that unless there is a medical reason to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA to explore asteroid made of $10,000 quadrillion worth of metal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA to explore asteroid made of $10,000 quadrillion worth of metal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biden calls Russia biggest threat to international order - "Under President Putin, Russia is working with every tool available to them to whittle away at the edges of the European project, test the fault lines of western nations and return to a politics defined by spheres of influence," Biden said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama approval hits 60% as end of term approaches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FL Atheist Offers Invocation to City Commission, Urging Them to Use Hard Data in Decision-Making </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topless FEMEN activist squeezes Trump waxworks groin while shouting grab patriarchy by the balls during unveiling ceremony in Spain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topless FEMEN activist squeezes Trump waxworks groin while shouting grab patriarchy by the balls during unveiling ceremony in Spain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't Pres Obama who is pissing on Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is cold outside.  I will stay home and watch Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Laws Repeal Could Raise Costs and Number of Uninsured, New Report Says - "...would cost 18 million people their insurance in the first year and could increase the number of uninsured Americans by 32 million in 10 years, while causing insurance premiums to double over that time." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republican healthcare plan kinda sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump said polls are fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which god?  [Godchecker.com](http://www.godchecker.com/) lists over 4,000 gods.  Which one exists in reality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a cry baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antiscience legislation in South Dakota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like people who aren't pissed on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Dakota Republicans Propose Legislation to Weaken the Teaching of Evolution in Schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Brexit Speech, Theresa May Outlines a Clean Break for U.K. - "Mrs. May emphasized Britains determination to regain control of migration from the European Union and rejected the supremacy of the European Court of Justice" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Brexit Speech, Theresa May Outlines a Clean Break for U.K. - "Mrs. May emphasized Britains determination to regain control of migration from the European Union and rejected the supremacy of the European Court of Justice" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Further, they can let them sink or swim on their own.  I predict they would fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the top leaders in the Communist party in China have advanced degrees in science.  The top leaders in Washington are lawyers and fucking idiots.  I don't think this is going to work out well for the USA at this point in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The alt-right eats its own: Neo-Nazi podcaster Mike Enoch quits after doxxers reveal his wife is Jewish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The alt-right eats its own: Neo-Nazi podcaster Mike Enoch quits after doxxers reveal his wife is Jewish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Road to Pseudoscientific Thinking - "How to prevent the most salient feature from being the least informative" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of Prayer Warriors Descend on Washington to Provide Prayer Shield for Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't NATO protecting the interests of capitalist countries?  If NATO falls, American corporations will lose money.  Oh, dear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is just making things up as he goes along.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German beer is very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confucius say, it is better to be pissed off than pissed on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is so full of shit, his arse is going to explode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confucius say, it is better to be pissed off than pissed on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korean prosecutors seek to arrest Samsung heir - "The move against Samsung Electronics Vice Chairman Lee Jae-yong on Monday is part of an investigation into a massive political corruption scandal that has shaken South Korea's political and business elites." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 11:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 04:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confucius say, it is better to be pissed off than pissed on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you dont finish then youre just busy, not productive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jennifer Holliday backs out of Trump inauguration gig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video shows police tackling and beating a black man suspected of stealing a car. It was his. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confucius say, it is better to be pissed off than pissed on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minnesotan cut 2,700 Christmas tree tops in national forest, charges say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commercialization of the sport really cheapens it.  I hate having to sit and wait for several mind-numbing minutes of commercials to see play begin.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * If something takes less than 2 minutes to do, do it and move on.
* Eating fat makes a person thin and doesn't kill a person...opposite of what the government says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Takata agrees to pay $1B over faulty air bags - "Three Japanese citizens were indicted by a grand jury in the U.S. District Court of Eastern District of Michigans Southern Division on six counts of charges related to wire fraud in a document that was unveiled on Friday." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryan faces (and flunks) health care test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview: The Spy Who Wrote the Trump-Russia Memos: It Was "Hair-Raising" Stuff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WhatsApp backdoor allows snooping on encrypted messages - "Privacy campaigners criticise WhatsApp vulnerability as a huge threat to freedom of speech and warn it could be exploited by government agencies" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an oddity about humans that gets lost in modern society, but humans need salt.  In the past, many cities were built near salt.  Salt was one of the first goods traded between civilizations.  The word salary is derived from the Roman word for salt and means money that the government gave soldiers to buy salt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Carbohydrates are how the body makes energy if you read what's scientifically proven.' - perhaps this is why the Neanderthals died off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Welcome to Trump's America](https://i.imgur.com/H1j0ep2.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran: Two Young Girls Were Arrested for Riding Motorcycle - Colonel Ali Elhami commander of Dezful police force said "this is the utmost denunciation of religious norms and has caused enormous tormenting among city officials." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran: Two Young Girls Were Arrested for Riding Motorcycle - Colonel Ali Elhami commander of Dezful police force said "this is the utmost denunciation of religious norms and has caused enormous tormenting among city officials." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
