<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first book of this universe that I've read but I'll definitely look into the others. You got me hyped for a sequel coming out in a few days! I should be able to finish the book by the time it comes out so this is perfect! Way to make my Monday feel like less of a Monday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braid

The ending to that game was really well done and even crazier when you understood what the game was portraying. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Six of Crows, by Leigh Bardugo**

Seems to be a great read so far!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for informative tutorials/books relative to game development programming for beginners! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just getting into some game development programming and looking for some of the best recommendations from all of you for a programmer that is just starting out in game development. Languages I'm familiar with are Ruby, C#, Java, HTML   CSS. I've browsed around on this subreddit and found a few videos that I plan on looking into in the upcoming weeks but I was looking to see if you have any recommendations that are a must read/watch for a beginner. Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little late on this one but there are definitely some games that have been missed that deserve some credit although I will repeat some good ones 

Braid - my most listened to soundtrack

Fez

Ori and the Blind Forest

Animal Crossing

I am Setsuna - Incredible solo piano soundtrack 

Kingdom Hearts (obviously)

Final Fantasy

Dustforce 

Super Mario Galaxy

Child of Light  

I left out a few others but those are some of my favorites. If you'd like links to any of them, let me know! I have a few favorite tracks from each.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nature is also probably one of the best tracks from that soundtrack! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
