<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6524</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so incredibly much. Your hard work is never unnoticed or unappreciated!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish *I* had a buffet in my kitchen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't. You just can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to read TIFU by being rude to a fellow bus passenger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you are saying the gross was "impressive". That gross is not impressive at all when weighed against its 125 million dollar budget. It also doesnt make me  a horrible person because of the comment I made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I wasnt banned from there for making a relevant anti-trump comment on an entirely different sub not related to r/the_donald, I also would try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say I would be against it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't fit into even ONE of your stereotypes. Don't you see how that makes your entire thought process and world view a failure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife passed last fall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is what I said so horrible exactly? Are you trying to say video game movies haven't been terrible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to refer to this as digital darwinism and I think we should just let it play out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are doing God's work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [http://i.imgur.com/y9I8672.gifv](http://i.imgur.com/y9I8672.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to smoke weed, eat pizza, and constantly switch back and forth between 10 different games, never settling on a single one!

edit: please stop upvoting this

edit: I dont deserve this, I dont deserve any of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the NFL is trying its best to expand internationally, so it makes zero sense from a marketing perspective to *not* do it, especially considering it doesn't have any adverse effects, other than, for some reason, triggering random people on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I thought *I* was asking a lot!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smoke spliffs. And on further thought, its probably more like 2-3g a day, which I acknowledge is still a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know what you would really do with those tissues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. =(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted you for the honest question that you framed with respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For like an entire *decade* I aimed to grab Gore as my #2 fantasy RB. 

Even counting all the amazing RBs of the past, most of whom all had way better single seasons, or 5 amazing seasons better than Gores best 5....I think he has been the most *consistent* RB I have ever seen over so many years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id say its just about on the line of the maximum someone with a lot of money would buy for themselves. 

I wouldnt want to hassle with buying weed every week or two if I didnt have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never seen a real person who is as big of a pathological liar as this guy. AND HE IS THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES. 

FUCK OUR LIVES!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will have no problem constantly bringing up the ridiculousness of the deflategate penalties in comparison to every single punishment going forward in the NFL for the rest of my natural born life. 

Maybe one day after Goodell is gone and enough time has gone by,  they will be able to admit some of their mistakes and we can stop. 

Fat chance of that happening though, so, oh well.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, hollywood exec, this will continue until you put him in your movies again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god your SO is training to be a firefighter. You are going to need his skill at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont ask questions you know people dont have the answers for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to but I'm gonna wait for xenoblade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like saying u have the 8th best tasting dog shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet you have no problem playing Kingdom Hearts 2.8. Pretty funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have pc and ps4 and couldn't live without either. There are a retarded amount of ps4 exclusives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14 year Olds are so annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been married </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my wife passed last fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish someone would deliver me hotdogs 3 days a week. Id prefer them not in my lawn, but I guess I'd take it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way this isnt happening now. Please also make it bend/break space time and allow its use in the 4th dimension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I would </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you know I have the body of Danny devito?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think www.mail.com may not have been a good choice years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I check my spam for important emails more than I check my regular inbox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want you to know I didn't expect to read that whole comment, but I did, and I learned a lot. I hope one day there might be just one person I can pass this stuff onto as well. Fuck this drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoy how casually people call him the goat now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Highlight of junior high, and one of the most depressing moments of my life when my car finished in dead last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things like this are the reason it stinks living in Maine...lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its just on Reddit no big deal....but I was just imagining someone in real life who constantly tries to take dissenting sides of things just for the sake of it and how  annoying that would be to suffer through constantly. But yeah, I should relax you are right about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's no way to predict based on such a vague comment.

But I didnt base everything off the comment, that was just one part of this, along with their promise that they would have much more to show us in the winter, and also their recent history in terms of length of production.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen way worst shitposting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm usually full of unpopular opinions

You should probably take a deep look into a mirror and really think critically about this line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its almost like we dont want to pay 400 dollars for books we only use for a couple months that we can get for free online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else worried that SE has spent over a year on FF7 and they may only have only finished the first hour of the original game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the long wait for FFXV and the ridiculousness that is the KH3 wait, I am officially concerned. 

When they announced the game and already had all that footage, and then when they showed combat just a few short months later, I felt like FINALLY Square had a solid plan and was working hard and fast on it. 

What brought me to make this post was the devs saying (just a few days ago) they are in the process of cleaning up the "Bombing run".

While it is possible that they have done much more of the game that takes places *after* the first couple hours of the original, we have no reason to believe that to be the case. 

It has been over a year, I believe, since we got the combat trailer. I get that they may not want to show much because it could still change, but having them not show a *thing* to us other than 2 still pictures, in over a year, especially when we were *told* we would get a lot more on it this winter....is bogus, and alarming. 

I have been worried about this game ever since it was announced that it would be done in episodes. 

If it takes them 3-4 years to make the opening Midgar section of the game, I will be dead by the time the game is on its last episode. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still love him. As long as he keeps his crazy beliefs to himself and doesnt try to push them publicly I will continue to love him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you call yourself a Patriots fan? Honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUI at was a bad example. Please insert a more apt lesser crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   "very attractive otherwise"

This just means you are very attractive, btw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me feel like maybe I have a chance. I have some idiosyncrasies and I would love to find someone who has them too. How did you two meet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what constitutes a criminal record? Someone who got a DUI when they were 18 count?

edit: yeah not the best example, I'm retarded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish u had the experience I did. I also hadn't liked a game since vesperia, but I adore berseria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tales is my favorite series ever.....I'm 33....played them all multiple times. Berseria might be my favorite. I still am in disbelief about that. Ps, when u do new game plus, try English voices. They are much improved, especially the main character. The actress who played velvet was incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first day here. Will somebody love me too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show gets better and better. Amazing work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So fucking disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just paid 40 for 3.5 of shit. I'd gladly have given u 40 for that nug. Goddd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this isnt copypasta, it is now. Finally some circumcision pasta!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be my favorite couch ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The professional is an all time underrated, under appreciated movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> =( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ, which time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playoffs is a diff story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My imaginary friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Its why I both love and hate these videos =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the goat of gifs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand jobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, BB stresses conditioning probably more than any coach in the league. Which is weird, because you would think it would be such a main focus of many NFL programs. 

BB makes his players run like crazy in practices, especially in camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ol' McNabb 101  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats that? An excuse to link this? [just saiyan](https://gfycat.com/UnhappyPastKodiakbear) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the only place I can masturbate while shopping for a new washing machine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone looks up uncircumcised penises on the interwebs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he goes backwards though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugh Jackman Loses It Over Sir Patrick Stewarts Ridiculous Circumcision Story - Graham Norton Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in case you post the story again, its "canoe" by the way =)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you just make that story funnier.....lmfao. I wish this wasnt a shitpost so people could read this story ahahahahaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  later that day some mad man in a canoo came out of nowhere catching the same wave I got

Oh my god, this is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 12, I used to go to my extended family's beach house. I went in the water, about 30-40 meters out. I noticed a ton of birds above me. Then, I started feeling things moving around my waste. I had waded into a school of little fish. The birds started dive bombing all around me for them. 

Then, as I was freaking out about that, I started feeling BIGGER fish around my feet. I screamed and started swimming as fast as I could to get to shore. Once I finally made it, in my panic, I didnt watch my footing and stepped directly on top of a jellyfish. 

It was then that I peed on my own foot while crying in front of dozens of people. 

Havent been in the ocean since, and its been 20+ years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the scariest experience you have ever had in the ocean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Making a more expensive phone than everyone else that requires more, and more expensive accessories was a bad long term business plan? Weird! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you dive in the open ocean, it's not uncommon for lost divers to never be found. People freak out at a gear malfunction and drown, get separated and disoriented and drown, run out of air and drown, or get separated and surface and can't find their buddies and just drift away.

I swear to god reading this just made me *feel* every single one of those horrifyingly terrible deaths. Fuck the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this guy just hurry up and get assassinated already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's much less excusable to be someone who uses the constitution or bible as the core of their political beliefs without reading it.

Yeah, fair enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am def a lot older than u, been to stadiums all over the country, and Gillette more than any others....am the biggest pats fan u will ever meet......but you are wrong about the fans in our stadium. We have arguably the worst home crowd in the nfl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is petty much it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude what? Come on. We got great fans in general but the stadium crowds are shit. I'm there all the time, before you try to tell me I've never been.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was good. But really he has had only one *really* good year. I just think people overrate him the same way we do Blount.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree with your sentiment, I gotta wonder just how many of your average Americans have actually read the constitution. I mean that from both parties. Not many, yet everyone loves talking about how important it is. 

I think there needs to be a class in high school that is nothing but reading and learning about the constitution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you'd prefer the worse player? If Lacy is in 13-14 shape (caveat of this thread) you're choosing a less talented, less versatile player.

In your opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. For me personally, I understand why contempt of court is there, and I am OK with it. Even if it "violates" my rights. 

Until I see it being used or taken advantage of, I will continue to feel that way. I havent seen too many stories of people being charged with it who didnt deserve it, though I am sure a few exist. 

But yeah, if it ever starts being abused I would take issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look man, I dont know how many times I gotta say it, Im not a lawyer, Im not even taking a side, just trying to answer your questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A sneeze is an involuntary reflex....laughing at someone recounting their loved one dying is a choice. 

As far as violating their rights, read [this](https://www.quora.com/Why-are-contempt-of-court-jailings-not-considered-violations-of-the-Constitutional-right-to-due-process) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I am questioning is whether or not that woman posed a significant distraction to merit anything other than her removal from the room

That is entirely up to the judge. Again I am not a lawyer, but I believe that the law puts it at their discretion. Also it doesnt matter if the distraction was "significant". A distraction is a distraction, and they wont be tolerated, because when you start allowing one small one, it opens the floodgates. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like english may not be your first language, which is OK. 

Are you saying that misbehaving and creating a distraction during criminal proceedings should not be punished? 

Like I said, it was a night or two in a cell, by herself. Not prison. She was safe and fine. 

Are you angry she had to do that instead of pay a large fine? Or do you think you should be allowed to do whatever you want inside a court room no questions asked? 

By the way, a large number of people would choose to spend a night or two in a cell by themselves rather than pay a few thousand dollars in fines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you fucking talking about? Are you seriously comparing slavery to contempt of court?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a lawyer, I won't pretend to be one. But contempt of court is criminal. She was only using her voice, but it was a distraction to the court, therefor against the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont know what I do or how much money I have. Not that it should matter. The mere fact that you have resorted to taking pictures of your diploma and your checks to post onto reddit says everything I need to  know about you, which is everything I already knew before you did it. 

You are Trump loving scum, a stain on humanity, and a terrible human being.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A courtroom is not the same "public space" as the park or a street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol linking me your student loan reimbursements now? lmfao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master of Arts. Who is the liberal here? lol. Congrats on your recent graduation, young buck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont think someone laughing at someone who is recounting the tragic death of their loved one in a court of law should be punished with a night or two in jail? Please dont respond with the "but it was 93 days" because it wasnt, and never was going to be, unless she wasn't remorseful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
