<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She missed that moment of running? That terrified me, it anchored me back to seeing It Follows at the cinema and kind of ramped it up by having the guy sprinting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! So glad you liked it. Who's side were you on by the end? I agree with Casey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes thats it! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not, Robert Hare is a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this, a more epic edgar wright style finale. The plot did feel like a Worlds End type plot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you spell "role" as "roll" intentionally? If not, thats a pretty funny slip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could go on your own? I did and loved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Invitation, The Parallex View. There was an interesting one a couple of years ago with the guy who played the "...and then I fucked her!" guy from Seven, I cant remember what it was called </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, you just haven't watched it enough times to figure it out. A man becomes paranoid his wife is cheating on him and enters a psychogenic fugue. The dream logic works in a similar way to the first half of Mulholland Drive. Sound plays an important part in tying together certain scenes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone in UK, Odeon are doing a mystery preview of this tonight at 815 for 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shes my sister AND my father! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, its a great film. It was also nice seeing William H Macy and Joan Allen as a couple again after Pleasantville, even though they were separated. Sort of like a sequel to that film.  

*Just thought I'd reverse the usual "oh hai Mark" switch when Room is mentioned.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. There are apparently quite a few making the rounds second-hand, leading to all sorts of problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just add The Man Who Wasn't there, Max Mad Black and Chrome and The Mist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its about this guy who tattoos himself, keeps post-it notes, goes on holiday to Mars, starred Christopher Plummer as an ex POW with dementia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they recall all of the products? Was it total?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been much better if the bad guy jumped through Robert's window, and Robert suddenly pulled a shot gun and blew his head off, shouting "NOW WHERE'S THE TARGET HUH YOU SERIAL KILLER BASTARD YOU" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't really anything to do with the guy in the basement, and everything to do with how Robert was perceiving it. Its about his paranoia and confirmation bias at that stage in the film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a great film I caught on Amazon Prime in US called Citizen X, true story about a hunt for a serial killer in Russia in the 80s. It has Donald Sutherland and Stephan Rea. Was an excellent, detailed film that really got into the trajectories of the main characters, like Zodiac.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gone Baby Gone, The Town, Mystic River, The Departed, Changeling, all very good solid films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, Walken, gotta be, so comPELLing, talkin' about, that watch, a WATCH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Le GO**, a revisioning of Doug Liman's debut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Jack and the other weird guy that sits in on the interview switch sides, and the rolling trolley of suitcases changes direction. It wasn't a mistake though, or an imperfection in any way. Because anything that may *look* that way, was actually *Stanley creating a sense of subliminal unease, to stir your unconscious into feeling a sense of foreboding anxiety, so that you can feel how he felt after successfully staging the moon landings in Elstree for NASA and the American government in 1969*. OK? GOT THAT?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about February 3rd? Our records show you weren't regretting it that day. Where *were* you that day? Returning videotapes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised and impressed with it on first watch. After the first act, it moves at a breakneck pace and really keeps you gripped. When I rewatched a few years later though, it wasn't the film I remembered it being - it seemed more rushed, sketchy, and nowhere near as great as it could have been with the strong premise. I do love the final shot though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pain and Gain. Its full of inaccuracies, but makes such a great satire of the american dream out of the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to Rewatchability which sounds like the exsct same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I'd like it but it felt really silly and comic book like to me. So many implausible cliches and "huh? But..." moments distracted me from any intensity. Like how that pit floods so quickly from *rain*, and why the woman and child don't just inhale and float rather than making out like theyre tied to the ground and about to drown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bridge scene... How that was ever made, wow. I felt like having a hot bath and a cup of soup after that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a lovely story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His performance in Demolition is fantastic too. The film massively exceeded my expectations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen Alien three times at the cinema, and every single time it was a claustrophobic, amazing cinema experience where the whole cinema was engaged in the shared experience. Even though we'd all no doubt seen it a bunch of times. I can't think of another film that even approaches it in that regard. Two of the showings were double bills with Aliens, and whilst Aliens is a great film it felt more TV-ish and less engaging than Alien when seen straight afterwards.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think though, that shooting efficiency is a variable which changes depending on the approach to production. When film was used and budget was much more of a concern, producers would meticulously plan each shot beforehand so as not to waste any. Shooting hours of footage would then be more an issue of choosing which takes to use. Take Primer for example, as complex as that film is, Carruth knew exactly what he wanted to the extent that the ratio of what was shot to what was used was something like 4:3 (i.e. very efficient).  

I can understand that editing is a ton of work, but if whole scenes and characters are being shuffled or deleted, then it would just suggest that the script wasn't perfect/ready to begin with. Not a bad thing, this was exactly the case with Die Hard, but its not always the case with a film shoot. I heard the Coens are ruthlessly efficient with their writing and planning too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean. You think you have a favorite, then rewatch Fargo for the twentieth time and think "actually..." or No Country where it opens up in a way you haven't quite realized before, or even Hudsucker where you forgot what a ridiculously well written film it was. Its like their films are alive, they seem to grow and change with each viewing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw In The Heat Of The Night last year too and it was the best film I saw all year. The picture quality, direction, characters, freshness of it and power of the story were so satisfying to watch. I massively recommend it to anyone who hasnt seen it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Blood Simple, I cant get over how well structured, directed and understated it is for a debut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the Predator conversion was great, and really gave a new lease of life to the movie, so I'll look forward to this. I think of Camerons work, Aliens and The Abyss would be well suited for 3D. The corridors and submersible scenes would be great in 3d, especially the end of Abyss with the alien landscape stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that Timothy Dalton did a terrific job in remolding Bond in a way that was ballsy and ahead of its time. He showed Bond thinking, being unsure, doubtful, frustrated, angry, and with a complexity between the lines. The Living Daylights is by far my favourite Bond film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats interesting. Why would they have to delete the watch stuff to accommodate the ambulance scene though? Also, "I was in junior high, dickhead"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive listened to the soundtrack more than any other, its a brilliant masterpiece. As much as I love Inception, Interstellar osts, I think this is Zimmers best work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea, I really miss the forums. r/movies is *terrible* for discussing older films. The thing about IMDB was that you would only be discussing with other people who had sought out that film so it was an immediate like-minded community discussing the same thing. Here, anyone passing by will throw in their irrelevant, self-conscious comment, sarcastic ones will get upvoted by anyone else who doesn't care for the movie, etc. There simply isn't a substitute, the lame little wannabe forums get nowhere near the traffic to make it work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I predict John Wick 2 will have a similar pattern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the better movie Mashups (Neeson calls Ed Rooney) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steve Jobs movie by Danny Boyle is like that, very fast paced and witty with a kind of between the lines ongoing tension </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to live in West Yorks and loved it. A little chillier but it felt more real-lifey, reasonable prices, roads through sparse countryside, people who seemed more grounded, and little fetes where you could see falconry and buy pork and apple baps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 400 for a 1 bed flat, all inclusive? Where the hell are you living? In most places you'd be incredibly lucky to find a tiny, dank attic bedsit with sloping ceilings and no communal areas for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find a lot of companies don't know their own rules. For important stuff, its always worth ringing up twice and getting a second "opinion", you'll often find it completely different to the first, even its something that should be standardised. Sad but true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It felt like a season of American Horror Story edited down to a feature length, and missing important bits that would help things make sense. Or a Black Mirror episode that doesnt reach its turning point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Split? That was pretty effective as a suspense/horror too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is useful to compare to. Thanks also for understanding what Im saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about you stop being stupid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You haven't read the post properly, but thanks anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the earlier post that said "Many would disagree with you, let's leave it at that"? I'd like to believe that you like how I deleted it, but is there any evidence that you like it? If not, how can I be sure?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the large letter size though, the issue is this. Say you have a very light jiffy bag, it bulges slightly half way. You could easily squash it to well within 2.5cm, but it slowly bulges out again. Because its so light, when its dropped through, it gets caught on the slot. A gentle push will easily push it through. Putting slightly more weight in the envelope would push it through due to gravity. But some postmasters let it get caught, then charge a small package, whilst others are more than happy to offer the *slightest* effort to push it through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is obvious, unless you're a naive fucking idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fairness to OP, your lack of "evidence" also doesn't suggest it *isn't* happening, so doesn't form a logical argument for its absence. It quite obviously *is* happening, most people accept that IMDB contains shill reviews, the plentiful one-review accounts are *very* suggestive of that. The anonymity (lack of evidence) is exactly why its such an easy way for people to help influence perception of a film. You'd have to be pretty biased yourself not to at least acknowledge that, regardless of JW2. I'm not a fan of the film either, but am astonished that this thread has gone the way it has.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have thought so too, but [this guy](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/5wuk6c/john_wick_2_convinced_me_this_sub_and_imdb_is/) is getting crucified for suggesting so on the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not about disagreeing with the wave of popular opinion, its about how much of an imbalance there is between the later reviews, and the early ones. I agree entirely with OP in that the early reviews were suspiciously overhyped, compared to the overall disappointment on the official discussion board. Manchester By The Sea has had a fairly consistent pattern (mostly positive, occasional disappointments, exactly like La La Land and Moonlight).  

I think its massively unfair and odd to call OP a "little shit" for stating what seems to me a well formed argument that is more about the pattern than his/her individual taste. You hating on the OP is far worse to me than what you're accusing OP of, and completely contrary to "You won't find anyone more willing to discuss the quality and the reception of a movie than me" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually agree, the early reviews were overhyped and the later ones are far more balanced. I also found the film a massive disappointment - but you're writing in the wrong place. You won't find many here even capable of understanding the point you're making let alone willing to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree. I think this film has been shill reviewed like crazy. In a few years it will be seem for the total piece of shit that it is, along the lines of Taken 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt the lobby scene in Matrix do this? Or The Raid films? I found JW2 hugely repetitive and tedious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are complete genre tropes by now. The invulnerable hero is Hollywood stupidity, influenced by superhero stories and thinking audiences will find it "cool". But actually its just disengaging and unrelatable, which is why the die hard films steadily got shitter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I thought the exact same thing. It was repetitive as fuck, the script was almost satirical in how minimal and shit it was, and it had no soul or finesse whatsoever. It was genuinely the most boring film Ive ever seen in theatres. Im convinced the hype was due to studio shills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some great looking shots in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved it, is it because I think I should? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feldman was [sexually abused](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-3611046/I-molested-passed-Corey-Feldman-details-horrors-Hollywood-pedophile-ring-reveals-Corey-Haim-just-11-raped-leading-life-drugs.html) though, so I think his situation was a little different, also I think a child actor's subsequent career isn't comparable with a hugely popular and very talented band.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People hanging up without forewarning and not saying bye. Not a huge red flag, but I'd think "what's up with that?" and maybe call back to say "did you get cut off?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I often wonder what would have become of Nirvana's trajectory had he not killed himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "As the narrator invites us to explore the horrors of an insane mind, a young woman wakes from a nightmare in a cheap hotel room. We follow her through the skid-row night and encounters with an abusive husband; a wino; a pimp and the rich man he panders for; a flashback to her traumatic childhood; violence; pursuit through dark streets; dementia. Filmed in film-noir style throughout; only the narrator speaks."  

Looks pretty progressive for 1955!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But your Mona Lisa implies direct copy/duplication, I wasn't implying that. I was just saying that the two films are alike, but yes, thinking about it I'm sure Nolan is very influenced by Cameron. But I really don't think its something worth nitpicking.  

Personally I feel there are strong thematic, character and structural ties between Abyss and Interstellar that are more than just genre staples, templates or common tropes.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If two things are alike, are they both not like each other? I obviously wasnt implying intention. I'd struggle to find as much synchrony between Event Horizon and Interstellar, except for maybe thr pencil/paper/wormhole moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 11:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is an underrated gem, although I preferred the original (Moon, 1983).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 11:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think any film whose surface level story revolves around a metaphor of some aspect of the human condition will split audiences - those who appreciate the metaphor (even if on an unconscious level) and those who don't. I would add "The Babadook"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss those intelligently silly films like Austin Powers. They don't need to necessarily spoof things (attracting the "quick to become dated" argument). I guess The Lego Movies are quite close to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its worth seeing if you find the Apple story interesting, if only to reflect on the writing/structure etc. But no, its not on the level of Steve Jobs. As someone else mentioned, Social Network is a must see, as its the same writer and similarly brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ashton Kutchner version is worth seeing, called Jobs. More garage stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it was *adapted* from the stage play, but what we're talking about here is the film, not the stage play, and not all stage plays sound like Mamet's style of writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do like Glengary Glen Ross, although less so now than I used to. I find Mamet's writing a bit too self-conscious and scripty, which becomes distracting sometimes with all the half-finished sentences and over-talking. Jack Lemmon's monologues really grate too. Pacino though is terrific, and his whole performance around the situation with Pryce is by far the best bit of the film for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it. Its absolutely a solid genre piece, a bit like Kurt Russell's Breakdown. *So what* if it slides into Silence of the Lambs cliche towards the end, I enjoy it regardless. Its not trying to be anything gimmicky or notable, its just a solid thriller that works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel really conflicted about Split. Part of me wishes it had gone down the chilling suspense/horror road rather than self-conscious comic-book style film. In the hands of someone like Jeremy Saulnier (Green Room/Blue Ruin) the concept of it could have made for an insanely gritty and terrifying film, especially if a few different personalities all developed completely different relationships with the captives. if for example one was a sadist/rapist, the other a kind helper, the suspense of the kind helper helping a girl through a precarious vent or something and not knowing if he was suddenly about to turn into the sadist would be really effective.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets not forget Wild At Heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Ferris and her character's kid are hilarious in 3, and its great fun seeing Charlie Sheen do his dead-pan Hot Shots thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great idea, but to prevent it becoming a stuffy, exclusive kind of thing, perhaps make it OK for people to make threads about any rare/obscure film that they want to? It doesn't need to just be about the film of the week? For example, I'd like to talk about Bob Balaban's film "Parents" (1989).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the OP says about taking two days to take in ID, getting sacked etc, and you use that to "paint a picture". Which is ambiguous, and doesn't really mean anything. But, there's a clear implication, which I call out as unfair. You then get uppity about words being "put in your mouth" because you couldn't be clear to begin with. You then explain that you think the OP is *lying outright about everything*, an assumption which is somehow tied to the picture you painted because they took two days to take in ID, got sacked, and whatever else it was. That makes no real sense to me. You make a leap from trying to paint a picture of someone who is leaving things out as being unreliable, to outright lying about everything.   

My point is that it doesn't matter what the OP left out, because no context is appropriate for a security guard to grab someones neck like that and threaten their life. If you're doubting that happened because the OP left things out, then you're just a doubting kind of person, which is a shame because some people are genuinely in need of some compassion.   

I'm not getting mardy about anything, I was trying to understand what the fuck your point was. DON'T PUT WORDS INTO MY MOUTH. For the fifth time. Jesus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Willis really disappoints me. Even in interviews he's sort of checked out and not quite there. He leans on his fame and recognition far too much, especially in his cameos like Planet Terror/Expendables/recent film (which I won't spoil as its still in theaters) where he literally just tilts his head and implies "hey audience, look its me, Bruce Willis". He needs to make a kick-ass revenge thriller like everyone else (there can never be enough) and become likable again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which part of this didn't you understand, and please point out the bit where I put words in your mouth.  

 Ok then what was the point of your comment, if not to imply that they somehow caused or are otherwise responsible for the outcome? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not putting words in your mouth, I'm calling you out on your implications. If no implication was meant, then its completely arbitrary to point out what the OP *didn't* write. You're accusing me of putting words in your mouth, yet you're "painting pictures" of the OP and then claiming that you aren't implying anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok then what was the point of your comment, if not to imply that they somehow caused or are otherwise responsible for the outcome? In writing a post like that there would naturally be a difficult balance to strike in giving the relevant information, without giving endless detail and justifications for every little thing. Especially if those things would just give the "no smoke without fire" crowd more cause to be contrary.    

Its irrelevant that OP took 2 days to take back ID. Its irrelevant that they were unemployed for a year. Its irrelevant they were sacked. Whatever picture you want to build of them, is also irrelevant. It has absolutely nothing to do with DWPs actions or how they handled the situation, which is what the post is about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A picture of what? Someone who deserves that kind of treatment? You're exceptionally ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Serafinowicz's Sassy Trump series on Youtube has completely affected how I hear Trump whenever he talks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a great film, directed by Richard Attenborough too I think? Another cool eerie movie that I don't hear enough of is Seance on a Wet Afternoon, where a wannabe-psychic convinces her reluctant husband (Richard Attenborough) to kidnap a posh school girl, so she can hide her in a forest, tell the police where she is (as a psychic) and get publicity. It all goes tits up of course, but is brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad they didn't, it would have been a bit too gimmicky and distracting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite a film about a girl obsessed with sex, but Jack Ketchum's The Girl Next Door sounds a lot like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting. In the US version of the film, Kubrick has a scene where Hallorran passes an upturned red Beetle, which was apparently a subtle attack on King also (as of course he swapped the original red Beetle at the start of the novel for a yellow one).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! The only others I can think of are Minority Report, The Prestige and The Shining (I know that last one is contentious but I found the book too rambly and cliched whilst the film is a thing of meticulous beauty).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for the part of "Jimmy" in Pulp Fiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gravity is the same as acceleration, so you can simply accelerate something to create artificial gravity. Likewise, you can use gravity to experience acceleration. For example, in simulator rides (where the screens are fixed to seats), when the seats momentarily tip backwards the mind experiences the feeling of gravity momentarily pushing from the front rather than above as a sense of acceleration. That's my bit, I'll leave others to talk about space stations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite foreign film is The Lives Of Others. Have you seen it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure sure, I do realise all that, but its still lucky that those specific, brilliant actors were even available, that the script even came their way. Say for example it ended up with Eric Stoltz as Mr Pink, Michael Ironside as Mr White, and James LeGros as Mr Orange. Put another way, for every Reservoir Dogs there are probably quite a few very talented debuts that for whatever reason just don't come together quite as well and fall off the radar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I half agree with you, but I enjoy it regardless. Its just "that kind of war film". A bit like all the flaws and saccharine elements in Titanic, but if you watch it as an old-fashioned genre picture, its still enjoyable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, now I need to watch Fight Club *again* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its amazing that as excitable, poorly directed, gimmicky and sweary the short version is, the actual feature turned out as restrained and focused as it did. I think Tarantino was immensely lucky to get Buscemi, Keitel and Roth on board, and wise to limit his own role as much as he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Jackson's "Dead Alive" (Braindead) is a trove of inventive special effects, they really went to town on that film. I miss practical effects, there's something so much more alluring and fascinating about them, even if they look a little odd (e.g. the latex skin in the Hellraiser tearing scene). My brain just instantly filters out CGI, it has no impact at all, whether its CGI blood sprays, heads exploding or whatever, it has no more effect than if it cut to a title card reading "head explodes".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Looks Could Kill (Teen Agent in UK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK: Alexa pronounces "nice" as "niece", and it sounds weird when I thank her (she says "niece chatting with you") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell, Alexa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 13:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes absolutely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be a tumor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zommie, Zommie, Zommie - ie - ie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had a small part in the Dirty Harry movie "The Dead Pool" which was terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
