<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7030</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the surface temperature of the sun is 5,504C, it would practically freeze the card.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Veganuary have a program for re-posting the same image on 4 different sub reddits? You're a point whore cancer that brings nothing creative or unique to reddit. If you're going to repost shit at least use the higher resolution version. https://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/4bw5wl/lap_bull_calf/ 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karma Whore alert.

Repost: https://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/4bw5wl/lap_bull_calf/

User poster same image on /awe and /pics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.tushy.me/collections/bidet-attachments $94 Heated bidet attachment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is why I installed a garbage disposal in my toilet. I can flush anything! Hell last week I flushed an old t-shirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also check out this one. http://iradukai.com/making/597/00.html Amazing work done in PS. He shows all his original sketches of the scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I linked the original...Google translate is not particularly good. He said he uses photos for reference and traces his line drawing sketch (done with a mechanical pencil) in Sai (kinda like Photoshop).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sure the artist was painting over photos...I could not have been more wrong. Found a tutorial he did for another one of his paintings similar in style to this one: http://iradukai.com/making/566/hyoushi.html   Truly amazing light work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, what a dolt to think that was serious. Ahh too funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 23:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's about the dumbest thing I have ever heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am part of a Mensa only ARK group. If you are interested PM me your MENSA ID, IQ-I 2.2 spectrum via MENSA, and NACElink Network Scores if available. Part of our rigorous recruitment progress includes a detailed gaming history with references for our recruiters to interview. If you have what it takes, Join us, the Mensa MLG Elite. Regards, subject7030 IQ198, Kendo 7th Dan Shichidan . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have bet the Shire and everything in it that Mithril would make the cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it wrong to be attracted to a disabled girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem atrophied legz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should change the title to "The Repost"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think God gave you twins so that they could decide in Vitro if they'd rather strangle each other with their umbilical cords than have you as a mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're sterile is that it? Naw that's too convenient of an excuse, the truth is nobody ever wanted to have babies with you isn't that it? always the mom's maid and never the mom, must be hard on you, knowing that the years are ticking away, you're friends all getting married and all the while you're uterus slowly shriveling away, drying up, becoming totally worthless.](http://southparkstudios.mtvnimages.com/images/shows/south-park/clip-thumbnails/season-10/1007/south-park-s10e07c02-cartman-vs-nanny-911-16x9.jpg?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you'll someday make a Klingon a very hansom wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing my clinical psychology doctoral on something I am calling the "She's all that" phenomenon. It's the study of a delusional metamorphosis where the subject let's down their hair and takes off their glasses and honestly believes they have become attractive. Would you be available as a test subject? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd roast you, but I'm afraid the only ovens big enough were decommissioned in Poland in '45. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you wax your asshole cause with that lack of a bulge going pro bottom is about the only thing I see in your future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry scro. there's lots of tards out there living really kick ass lives. My ex wife is tarded. She's a pilot now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buys RC sub...buys shark fin...attaches shark fin to RC sub...let the hilarity roll out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The old age before computers. The L looked like a 1 back then on typewriters. There was no number 1 key. Image is of such an old typewriter.](http://machinesoflovinggrace.com/large/RemScout32keys.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explains how it works, it does not explain why there are two distinct sounds from this motion (tick and tock). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that makes it even funnier. I didn't take it serious for a second. With an author that writes such satirical novels like this seemed like an elaborate joke to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Greek as fuck. That is basically a photo of my foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First rule of underground basement cooking club is you don't talk about the underground basement cooking club. Second rule...see rule one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 13:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the PC version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Approved.

Oh boy. Thank you for approving it massa. Bless you massa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NoMansSky the Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hello games has finally broken their silence. They will begin filming their epic biopic in Jan 2017. Speaking from the set in Toronto, the film's style is heavily influenced by the 1979 Gore Vidal hit film Caligula. A spicy, candid view into the realm of game making.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an ICE 3 high-speed train...come on not cool to graffiti that. Stick to the subway trains, local shit box ones...these things are 200MPH wonders of engineering. Not cool at all, and I like graffiti. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goth's walk into home-depot "We're here to buy all your paint." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does my pleasingly proportioned subcutaneous adipose tissue stimulate  a release of endorphin's to an adequate amount to lead to increased vascular dilation and heart rate baby? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I wash my ass like a man
This is what we do
Gotta get them traces of poo
From the top of the ass crack all the way to the ball sack
Huh!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tnzoF61hlRs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, I can't wait for Schindler's List 2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assure you, my mother had me tested. Which now that I think of it...it's taking quite a long time to get the results. Been almost 20 years in fact. I think I need to make a call. That doctor definitely is ripping us off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be glad it is, or we'd hear news like this: "On today's evening news, a troll from Yorkshire is being held responsible for the declaration of war by the Garrtakiki Aliens of Planet Garrtakiki IV. According to sources the fleet of Garrtakki ships will arrive next week. The Garrtakiki are quoted as saying "We are coming for the one called "AssClownChowder69". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You people think so 2 dimensional. You need to think in 4d like Trump. He's not building "a" wall, he is building two. Two walls to contain the largest military base in the world. You're probably thinking "You can't build a military base that big that is ridiculous." And you would be correct. But on paper you can. No why would you need a paper base thousands of miles wide along the boarder? Think Trump. What is the greatest patriot of all. He never sleeps, he never hungers, he is perpetually vigilant and on guard. Willing to give his live at a moment's notice to protect our great nation. The humble landmine. But wait! Geneva convention! Ohhhh paper military base...it's not a minefield, it's a ordnance disposal yard. Now your thinking Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'll stick to Horseshoe crab blood at $60K per gallon. A lot safer than those, and a hell of a lot easier to actually sell/get at meaningful quantities.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow is this before the nuclear accident thing? Is she still alive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 07:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the flight the panda had plastic surgery eh? Pandas have triangular noses not circles... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol consoles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 11:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a mod for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, but fake. Look at the source of the poop emanation. And remember that a dogs anus is at the base of the tail and not well below the hip. The angle of the poop shot is all wrong based on the body position of the dog. The sputtering effect of the fluid is indicative of pneumatic pressure drop of a non-compressible fluid. AKA there is a pipe filled with chocolate pudding behind and slightly underneath the dog. A person blew into the other end of the pipe to shoot the stream out. The reaction of the dog helps to confirm this. First he looks to the rear at the source of the sound, than he turns directly forward toward the location where I am guessing the "pipe blower" is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NASA has a couple spare Hubble telescopes laying around...gifts from the CIA. Link = Proof](http://www.space.com/16000-spy-satellites-space-telescopes-nasa.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
