<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4830</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80? If we get a double event, and with lucky eggs, I'm sitting on 200,000XP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 07:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ironic that play is "A Christmas Carol". Dickens was an early fighter in the War on Christmas. He was accused of taking the Christ out of Christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The history of the War on Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 07:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eastbound 580 closed in Oakland after double shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun owner pleads guilty to killing 3 in Pasadena shooting rampage, facing 181 years to life in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> School play captures nation's religious Christmas divide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing that can stop them is the voters at the midterms, or if they get enough calls before the vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the GOP will control every come Jan 20th, but can they seriously get away with repealing Obamacare, and privatizing social security and Medicare? They talk a good game, but how would their base go along with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NY Times has a [good debunking and explaination](http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/12/10/business/media/pizzagate.html) of the whole pizzagate story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jewish family leaves town in fear following conservative news story coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like that. Merry Christmas to you and enjoy your break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Natural Law

I have read some about Natural Law and it being the basis for the Church's views on same-sex relationships, birth control, and more. With same-sex couples and children, there are other methods: adoption, and in the case of women, one of them being the biological mother. Is it really in the best interest of humanity and our fragile planet that everyone who wants to be in a sexual relationship, get married to someone of the opposite sex and try to have lots of children? It's just cruel to tell people who feel otherwise, "no sex for you" when there are all sorts of benefits to human sexuality beyond keeping our species going.

 Kalam Cosmological Argument

I don't know where all the matter and energy in the Universe came from, but I do think it is a fascinating question. The idea that all of it had to come from somewhere and someone had to light the proverbial match to start the Big Bang, I just am not satisfied with "God did that". That leads to "where did God come from". If God is immortal, then why isn't all the matter and energy immortal?

I don't have a good answer for all this. I have spent a long time thinking about it, reading about it, and talking about it with others. I love books on Cosmology and trying to wrap my brain around topics like String Theory, Supersymmetry, and the Multiverse. It is pretty amazing that we little humans can ponder such big questions and come up with so many possible answers.

I am glad all the matter and energy are here. I try to feel a general sense of gratitude, though not directed towards any particular being. It's more of a gratitude that all these billions of years of time has led to people like you and me being here, pondering such questions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early on as an ex-Catholic, I did want to be excommunicated but had no idea how. I saw it as a clean break. I never did figure out how. That process does seem to be selective on the Church's part. They seem to reserve excommunication for public figures, perhaps to make an example. The hassle to get excommunicated was just going to require me giving more time to a church I had already left. I found therapy to be far more helpful in resolving issues I still had.

I also gave up on the idea when I thought about some Church official sending a letter to the parish I grew up in, asking them to take me off the books, and how upset my mother would be. I had my fill of that grief when I told her I was no longer going to Mass.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We don't teach to be jerks to LGBTQ people

"Jerks" was a poor choice of word on my part. It does bother me that the Church has taken a stand against same-sex marriage, and generally same-sex relationships. I have lots of LGBTQ friends and know 5 married couples. I know the Church has its theological reasons. I just think they are coming down on the wrong side of history.

 abortion is a huge fight for us as we value the life of everyone

I don't want to make this a thread about abortion since the Church's views on abortion had nothing to do with my decision to leave the Church.

 I'm curious why you think science and the faith are incompatible. Many theologians and scientists of the Catholic faith are highly regarded in fields like astronomy, biology, and evolution.

I don't think science and faith are inherently incompatible. For example, I appreciate the Catholic Church's acceptance of [evolution and the big bang](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2014/10/28/pope-francis-evolution-big-bang/18053509/). I am grateful I didn't learn Creationism in CCD class and I could enjoy science classes in high school and college without wondering about 'young Earth' issues. It wasn't until my mid-20s that I met people who took Creationism seriously, and they weren't Catholic.

My story, of leaving the Church, began later than this article describes. I was in my 20s when I left. I could point to a moment or two of doubt in my early teens but still went to Mass and thought of myself as a Catholic until my early 20s. It was a gradual process over several years. I did have a crisis of faith around science and religion. The Universe being 13.8 billions years old, human evolution going back 2 millions years, modern humans 100,000 years, and the Bible stories all taking place in the past few thousand years. Looking back, I did have a literal interpretation of the Biblical stories and events. It bothered me how human-centric everything was. At the time these stories were written down, the understanding of our place in the Universe was quite different.

I came to understand that the Universe had been humming along and doing its thing for those many billions of years. At first, I was a little sad once I stopped believing we were Gods chosen species. It was even a little scary to see the Universe as a place not controlled by a divine being who could intervene on our behalf.

Over time I came to appreciate all of it in a different way. I love being a small piece of such a grand story going back billions of years. All the little random moments of evolution and all my ancestors going back to the earliest forms of life, each making another generation. I prefer the Universe where there is not a prime mover or clock maker. Where I can look up in the night sky, seeing the stars and light from stars billions of miles away, and knowing that I am connected to it all. That's the stuff that fills me with awe and wonder.

In terms of values and behaving kindly to other people, I think I am now in the secular humanist camp. I prefer living in a world where we try to treat each other with kindness and respect. Not because someone else is telling us to, or out of fear of punishment after death, but just because it makes this a better world to live in.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again the [Make America Kittens Again](http://www.tomroyal.com/blog/2016/12/18/make-america-kittens-again/) browser plugin brings me a smile, replacing the Trump map with a picture of two kittens. I would gladly visit TrumpLand if it were filled with kittens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, dude. I hate the Trump family and all, but I wouldn't go that...

Nah, it's okay, fuck 'em.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope a cell phone video surfaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Ivanka needs to get a life of her own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Passenger who confronted Ivanka Trump gets kicked off Jet Blue flight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I did it! I finally caught an Aerodactyl! NA Gen 1 complete!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's only if you want to link your account. I didn't do that, it's a violation of the PoGo Terms of Service. It's a bit tedious, but I have been manually entering the details for my key fighters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an IV calculator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything on day 1? Trump is sure going to be busy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 08:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I've found 5, ranging from 75% to 26%. So far I've kept all of them and evolved the first one I found. If I find a few more, I'll start trading in the weakest ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "as soon as possible" is this before or after he builds the wall, bans all Muslims, repeals Obamacare, or destroys ISIS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student arrested for making death threats to shoot up the school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Folks Say This Is The Most Controversial Nativity Scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the photographer case, would the KKK have any legal grounds to sue the photographer for refusing service, even if the photographer said, "I won't work with you because I think the KKK is a bunch of racist assholes." I would expect that court case wouldn't go very far.

Another example: let's say a heterosexual couple wants to get married in their local Catholic Church. The couple isn't Catholic and has no interest in becoming Catholic. Let's say they like the pretty stained glass and think it would be a nice place for a wedding. I think it's reasonable for a Priest to say no. No to performing the service, and no to using the Church, on religious grounds.

The reason I mention Civil Rights issues about (whites only signs, etc), is those are cases where the Court ruled against the business owners, on grounds of what has become known as "protected status". On the federal level, protected status does not include sexual orientation, though it is included in a number of states. The Supreme Court should weigh on if sexual orientation is protected status in all 50 states. If this law passes and is challenged, it could be the right opportunity for the court to weigh in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I see your point, but that's not what this law is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about this:

 FADA would prohibit the federal government from taking "discriminatory action" against any business or person that discriminates against LGBTQ people. The act distinctly aims to protect the right of all entities to refuse service to LGBTQ people based on two sets of beliefs: "(1) marriage is or should be recognized as the union of one man and one woman, or (2) sexual relations are properly reserved to such a marriage."

It's not just having the right to say you don't like same sex couples, it protects the actions they take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does not serving someone breakfast because of the color of their skin differ from not making a wedding cake for a same sex couple? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about equal protection? No separate but equal water fountains, seats on the bus, tables in restaurants, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will need to raise it, and keep on raising it. If Trump goes through with his plans to cut taxes and increase spending the magic money that will be needed to fund the federal government will come from more debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will only go down once he was sworn in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next level War on Christmas behavior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just another reason to be ex-Catholic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That joke will be on you once Trump gets sworn in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Solstice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help me Rhonda! How can this nonsense stand up to a Supreme Court challenge? When did religious freedom include being an asshole to people you don't like and having legal protection to do so?

I look forward to walking into my local bakery and filling out an extensive form on my religious views and relationship history, just to get a cookie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope that his supporters actually get pissed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key for Trump will be his approval rating. If it stays low, it will provide cover for Republicans to take a stand against him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps apparent disregard for nations laws raises fears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more Pokestops the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping for a repeat of the Halloween event with the bonuses and shorter walk distances. More ice Pokmon during the event. Hopefully more Gen 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hatched a Dratini yesterday. I've hatched 1 Snorlas and 2 Lapras. Hopefully I'm close on the Aerodactyl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Conservatives most likely to be offended by holiday greetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be willing to pay a reasonable chunk of change to have 9 infinite incubators. Then I wouldn't need to spend any more money. That's probably why it won't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author is articulate, but doesn't offer any reasons why voting for Trump would help address his problems and that of his fellow coal miners.

 Corporate greed, mechanization and the rise of fracking have forced people in Dickenson County into lower-paying, less stable work.

This is a good summary. The Democrats really dropped the ball this election cycle. Democrats are the ones who fight against fracking. Democrats are the ones who fight for raising the minimum wage. Democrats are the ones who see more value in Unions.

Why would anyone think a rich guy like Trump and all his rich friends he is bringing into his administration would also fight for the little guy?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump vs. Obama in the alleged war on Christmas: Ugliness in a season of joy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this data is helpful. So far, I've hatched a Magby, the easiest one to get in the stats. Hopefully, I'm getting close on some others, I've hatched a lot of eggs recently.

What are the odds of hatching an Aerodactyl? I'm still trying to get one of those. So far I've hatched a total of 587 eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing meth or bath salts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man accused of Ithaca homicide: 'I shot and killed Donald Trump purposely, intentionally and very proudly' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most anti-Catholic people I know are people who went to Catholic school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech companies 'profit from ISIS,' allege families of Orlando shooting victims in federal lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is the sheet old, before the update?

That might be it.

This is working better: https://www.pgnexus.gg/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my trainer level (30) set at the top of the spreadsheet, and double checked the data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IV calc in Google spreadsheet - why so many "No combinations found" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best web based IV calculator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 07:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a surprisingly frank assessment of the situation. I took a similar path out the door, the struggle between faith and science. Science won. I didn't have anyone who was a devote Catholic who I also felt comfortable talking about my doubts with. Those conversations always felt like "it's just a little phase. There, there. You will come back to the Church."
If I could give the Church, and the writer of this article, some advice, it would be to focus less on faith and more on good works. Put aside the miracles and the super natural. Is it any surprise that kids these days are a skeptical of stories of Jesus walking on water, or feeding the masses.
For the good works part, just look at all the young people Bernie Sanders got excited with his progressive platform. A lot of that is in line with Catholic teachings, it's just that pesky abortion stuff that gets in the way, or being a jerk towards LGBTQ people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a surprisingly frank assessment of the situation. I took a similar path out the door, the struggle between faith and science. Science won. I didn't have anyone who was a devote Catholic who I also felt comfortable talking about my doubts with. Those conversations always felt like "it's just a little phase. There, there. You will come back to the Church."

If I could give the Church, and the writer of this article, some advice, it would be to focus less on faith and more on good works. Put aside the miracles and the super natural. Is it any surprise that kids these days are a skeptical of stories of Jesus walking on water, or feeding the masses.

For the good works part, just look at all the young people Bernie Sanders got excited with his progressive platform. A lot of that is in line with Catholic teachings, it's just that pesky abortion stuff that gets in the way, or being a jerk towards LGBTQ people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it hard to imagine Donald Trump as consoler in chief after some sort of national tragedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would require Trump to attend his daily intelligence briefings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is going to be a depressing President if this is how he looks at problems in the world.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuff like this isn't helping me take the Alt-Right seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I will stop saying "Trump makes me long for the days of W". The joke is officially over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to lookup [Antinomianism](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antinomianism). 

 The distinction between antinomian and other Christian views on moral law is that antinomians believe that obedience to the law is motivated by an internal principle flowing from belief rather than from any external compulsion.

That almost sounds like Unitarian Universalism or even Secular Humanism.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it wasn't some Russian Arch Duke's Nephew, otherwise I would be hiding under my desk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hatched a Snorlax during the first event when double candy was happening and got 60. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy, 3, out shopping with grandma dies in road rage shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I caught this guy outside the local weed dispensary, obviously. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to say, didn't I read earlier today it was canceled?

I'm glad it's still in the works. I was holding off on buying an Apple Watch until the Pokemon Go app was available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 22:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any campaign promises Trump plans to keep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Jesus was a Middle Eastern refugee' post goes viral </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California adult store employees ward off armed robber by throwing sex toys at him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 08:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 Alameda County deputies fired over Mission District beating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the full truth comes out. There's got to be some crazy shit going on between Trump and Putin to have the Trump organization saying so many crazy stupid things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is going to need to work on his empathy if he has any hope of being a successful President.

I will miss President Obama. He comes across as authenticate, and as a person who thinks before he talks. I appreciate that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was a highlight for me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all well and good if the Democrats control the House, Senate, and White House. It's a lot harder the way President Obama had it, at least for the past 6 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump would have called the sick reporter a loser and made fun of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the problem is, what don't know what the extent of the Russian influence was on the election. If it's true that they didn't influence the election enough to be responsible for Trump's election, then President Obama's reaction is appropriate. A lot of people are thinking otherwise, that Russia's influence was key to Trump's victory.  Maybe those folks are venturing into conspiracy theory territory. I really don't know. There's just not enough info being released to make a good judgement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this one has been a disappointment. The President is phoning in some of his answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun owner apologizes to man he robbed at gunpoint 3 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent... excellent...

President Obama is about to have a press conference. This should be fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all fun and games on Twitter until the shooting starts.

Isn't "threatening stupid actions that might cause WW3" a condition that violates Twitters terms of service? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess Trump doesn't see visiting veterans as a good PR opportunity, or a group he can be exploit for personal gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY

~~some~~ all leaks came from Russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting the giant fan to play a starring role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing (almost) every day since July. Still looking for the Areodactyl and now the new little ones. If I ever find them all, I might scale back, but as long as I'm still having fun I'll keep at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 106 MPH tornado-force wind gust recorded in Sierra Nevada Thursday morning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Trump will do so many other horrible things that people will remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago's murder rate keeps rising and the gangs can't be stopped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dylann Roof Found Guilty in Charleston Church Massacre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see how funny voters thought it was in 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Draining the swamp must cost a lot of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: He was naked, unarmed and tripping on LSD. Police ordered their K-9 to attack him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting theory about the electric biome. I have caught two Porygon. The first was near some high voltage power lines, so that fits. The second one I caught was in the middle of a Whole Foods supermarket. I don't think there is anything particularly electric near there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but I'm wondering, why draw the line here, with bullets and background checks? Don't other gun laws (background checks, waiting periods, magazine capacity) also inconvience law abiding citizens? You could also argue that laws restricting access to automatic weapons are unfair, since some criminals find a way to get their hands on them.

There is evidence that gun laws work:

* [More Guns, More Crime](http://www.nber.org/papers/w7967)
* [The Relationship Between Gun Ownership and Firearm Homicide Rates in the United States, 19812010](http://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/abs/10.2105/AJPH.2013.301409?journalCode=ajph ) - "Gun ownership was a significant predictor of firearm homicide rates (incidence rate ratio=1.009; 95% confidence interval=1.004, 1.014). This model indicated that for each percentage point increase in gun ownership, the firearm homicide rate increased by 0.9%."
* [More guns, more crime: New research debunks a central thesis of the gun rights movement](http://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonkblog/wp/2014/11/14/more-guns-more-crime-new-research-debunks-a-central-thesis-of-the-gun-rights-movement/)
* [The Accessibility of Firearms and Risk for Suicide and Homicide Victimization Among Household Members: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis]
(http://annals.org/article.aspx?articleid=1814426) - "Conclusion: Access to firearms is associated with risk for completed suicide and being the victim of homicide."
* [Long List of Research](https://www.reddit.com/r/GunsAreCool/wiki/academic_sources)
* [New Study Is Latest to Find That Higher Rates of Gun Ownership Lead to Higher Rates of Violent Crime](http://www.thetrace.org/2015/06/new-study-is-latest-to-find-that-higher-rates-of-gun-ownership-lead-to-higher-rates-of-violent-crime/) - Data shows that states with the top rates of gun possession have nearly three times the rate of gun murders compared to states with the fewest guns.
* [Guns Don't Deter Crime, Study Finds](http://www.livescience.com/51446-guns-do-not-deter-crime.html)
* [States With Tighter Gun Control Laws Have Fewer Gun Deaths](http://www.slate.com/blogs/the_slatest/2015/10/02/gun_control_by_state_tougher_laws_mean_fewer_deaths.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a good idea to get rid of all gun laws. Since criminals breaks laws, we should get rid of every law and tear up the Constitution while we are at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War on Charlie Brown Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal judges rule Californias restrictions on guns are reasonable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 06:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have storage for 350. I keep the high IV mons that are good fighters, and then one of each in the most evolved state.

For the ones that can evolve into gen 2, I keep a few and have enough candy for all but the Porygon.

For the ones with gen 2 babies, I had been holding onto as many as I could find, thinking they would randomly be assigned genders and then breed the little ones. Now that it's random based on eggs, I'm going to trim those groups down.

What I used to do with th common ones lik Pidgey is, I would transfer them as soon as I found them, until I had enough to evolve one, then evolve right away for XP. Recently I switched to holding on to enough to evolve with the candy I have. I was waiting to evolve all the gen 1 mons that have a gen 2 version. I want to us a Lucky Egg and then evolve everything for max XP. I'm still holding out for that, of if they have a Christmas event with double XP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War with Russia is highly unlikely. With whatever is going on with Russia poking around in our election, and with Trump picking people for his administration who are friendly with Russia, if anything, relations with Russia should improve. There could be the risk of a crisis with NATO if Russia sees an opportunity to grab more land, thinking Trump will not push back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there really nothing changing from day to day? Just the situation in Syria should be enough to provide him with new details each day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost 10lbs but gained some back since Thanksgiving. All the extra walking to hatch more eggs should help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Newtown, mourning parents enter into the lonely quiet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump hotels in every National Park! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of stuff is only a problem with Democrats are the ones doing it. Plus, I thought Trump was going to appoint Putin as his National Security Advisor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A nativity scene without Jews, Arabs, Africans or refugees." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why Trump is skipping these briefings. What's the upside for him? Just tweet less and spend some time each day listening to the smart people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting a gun in your mouth and pretending to commit suicide. That shit ain't right too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can confirm that. I've hatched around 15 new eggs, nothing new or particularly rare. I did find one Santa Hat Pikachu in the wild, so I've got that going for me, which is nice.

**Edit:** Go me, this morning I hatched a Magby from a 10k egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or drive on my slow commute with lots of stop and go traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Their dinner party was being streamed on Facebook Live. Then, tragedy struck as drunk guy playing with gun accidentally shoots and kills his friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was probably trying to sell Trump fireworks for the inauguration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is un fair how Republicans were so kind to Hillary. They could have at least made an effort to have eight or so Congressional hearings on Bengahzi in an effort to tarnish her reputation but yet find nothing in the end. They could have blown the whole email server issue out of proportion. If they had done the she might have lost the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really need to learn how to write a Reddit bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on [reddit so it must be true](http://www.snopes.com/trump-did-not-donate-to-nambla/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NAMBLA allegations? Tell me more. I know about Trump being accused of raping a girl, has he also been accused of man/boy love too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York man arrested bringing knives, fireworks into Trump Tower, police say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, those are worth looking into too, but since neither of those people is President-Elect, it's less important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't thought of it that way. Yes, we should make this another Benghazi. We need to get to the bottom of Trump's relationship with Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 07:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witch was pretty twisted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing says Presidential like acting like a toddler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it a conflict of interest to cancel a press conference on conflict of interests?

Also, why does Trump have a spokes person? Who can possibly speak for Trump as well as Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dispute in SFs North Beach leads to drive-by shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As Trump's popularity sinks it will be easier for Republicans to stand against him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can confirm this. Hatched the 9 pre-announcement 5k eggs I had. All had pre-announcement Pokemon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 01:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have gone with Toddler, but your version works too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have 10k rates increased? I found three in the last hour! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 01:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late, I've got 9 5k eggs cooking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DRINK YOUR OVALTINE

Son of a bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Pokedex looks the same as before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm expecting an announcement about an upcoming announcement where they make another vague announcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 07:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  i also liked how Rosita seemed super upset about it once she realized what her actions caused.

It looked like she understood Eugene's warning at the bullet factory. There was going to be a fallout from her actions. Even if she killed Negan, people would die and not just Rosita. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was glad to see Eugene step up and own his part. I am glad he is still alive, probably being forced to make more bullets every waking hour of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best moments of the episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington is in line for a huge shipment of political theater </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has wanted to get away for some quality alone time. Who knows what revelation might come from that, or if she gets overrun by walkers. I hope she returns to the group at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 08:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you found a church that's been good for you and helped you through tough times, that's great. I've had plenty of stuff to say in criticism of the Church, but it's not like they are wrong 100% of the time.

As far as being pro-choice or pro-same sex marriage while also being Catholic, I don't think you are in as small of a minority as it might appear. I don't think I've ever met a Catholic, even the hard core ones, who could honestly say the agreed with the Church 100% and tried to live up to it. For people who stay in the Church, they find their ways of making peace with their differences. The unlucky ones get stuck with a lot of guilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 07:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the outrage? The author and I must have different friends on Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 07:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See points 8   9

 On Dec. 4, Edgar M. Welch, a 28-year-old from North Carolina, arrived at Comet with a military-style rifle and a handgun. The police said he fired the rifle inside the pizzeria, hurting no one, and surrendered after finding no evidence to support claims of child slaves being held there.

 The shooting did not put the theory to rest. Purveyors of the theory and fake news pointed to the mainstream media as conspirators of a coverup to protect what they said was a crime ring.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Clara police officer arrested on suspicion of domestic violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We can't let this type of un-American activity go unchecked. Before you know it, out leaders will be in chains, our women will be learning how to shot-put. And all we vital American males will be forced fed borscht along with generous helpings of Das Kapital." -- Cliff Clavin, Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and Russia gets another Cabinet position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the rest of the country, just the fly over states, and the south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Resistance to Trump is rooted in the Bay Area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give Trump 8 months before he gets impeached.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling Trump a terrorist sounds like the right reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College instructor tells students that Trumps election was an act of terrorism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A look inside the trial of Dylann Roof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please revoke all of Trump's social media access and get him to behave like a real President and speak to the Press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissecting the #PizzaGate Conspiracy Theories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 09:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would suck for reading poetry.

Let's do a little math. I've always wanted to read War and Peace, but didn't want to invest the time. There are [587,287](https://indefeasible.wordpress.com/2008/05/03/great-novels-and-word-count/) words in War and Peace.

* @300 wpm: 1957.62 minutes or 32.62 hours.
* @500 wpm: 1174.57 minutes or 19.57 hours.

That assumes no blinking or bathroom breaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't you seen those memes: why do women not report sexual assaults or wait a long time to do so? Because a dozen women reported it and Trump still got elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on the assumption that at least some of these accusations are true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need Trump's accusers and these new accusers to press charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps war on women: 3 key team members have been accused of physical or sexual violence against women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My oldest is a Tangela, caught on July 11. I started playing on July 8. I've only seen 3 and caught 3. The first one is still my best Tangela. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We finally have a term for the right-wing version of political correctness: [patriotic correctness](https://www.washingtonpost.com/posteverything/wp/2016/12/07/the-right-has-its-own-version-of-political-correctness-its-just-as-stifling/?utm_term=.06d56b40887e). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at how the M makes horn shapes over Trump's head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since being the President is an entry level job to Trump, he will have plenty of free time to pursue his side projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we are lucky we got Trump. Hillary also [kills cats](http://m.motherjones.com/politics/2008/01/did-clintons-try-whack-cat). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time: No, we didn't give Trump 'devil horns' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick, Carl, and Carol finally make it to the Grand Canyon and find it filled with walkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! I'm an exCatholic turned Unitarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY:

 America ~~is losing~~ has lost its mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm ready for all but Slowpoke and Porygon candy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I mostly get 5k eggs. Occasional 2k eggs, and even less 10k eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, downloaded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida Woman Is Charged With Threatening Sandy Hook Parent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evangelicals, your attacks on 'the media' are getting dangerous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, that was good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a simpler solution: if you are too stupid to look up the laws, then you are too stupid to own a firearm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be sweet. I'm ready to evolve all the Gen1 to Gen2 versions, except for the Porygon 2 (only 7 Porygon candy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad would have eaten all my Doritos. Not cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only missing one is the Aerodactyl too. I am working on powering up my best fighters to max, but if it's a long wait for Gen 2, I'll probably take a break or at least scale back, until then. I am optimistic for Gen 2 before the year is out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summer? That's a long time to find the Aerodactyl I need to finish my NA 143. They would risk losing even more daily players as people complete their Pokedex and even make it to Level 40. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I put a dent in my head then [my hair just ain't gonna look right](https://youtu.be/c9G1VWo_yyU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn it, I missed out with on /r/pizzagate.  That would have been fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess: they will add Pokestops or Gyms to all Sprint retail locations. Have a new Pokmon that's only available at the spots, maybe for a limited time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that term. I first heard it in the past year, with all the shit stirring Trump has done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Snorlax showed up today on the Tracker. I headed there as quickly as I could, but it took off before I could get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, earlier today. $50 billion will buy a nearly limitless supply of coins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the very least, I hope we get some details on when Gen 2 Pokemon will be out and about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from his age, I don't see why so many people are dismissing Biden's chances. When Hillary lost, there were plenty of "what if" people who thought if Biden had run, he would have won.

I do think we need some new players in the Democratic Party, but unless we can find someone who is up to the job, I wouldn't have a problem voting for Joe, especially if we could keep those "creepy Joe Biden" memes going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how much Trump himself knew about the backstory here. Did someone tell Trump: "If you take this call, China will be really pissed, but fuck it, take the call anyway".

This is clearly part of a much larger goal by Taiwan that flies in the face of China. Pass the popcorn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This conspiracy theory is so hard to follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Age of Donald Trump, Pizzagate, and Stupid People With Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got it a week or so ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the big deal? I rarely go to Starbucks, but if I pass by a few more Pokestops in my daily travels, that's a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invest in index funds. Reinvest dividends. Steadily add to investment to dollar cost average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tried both approaches, not going can be very ackward, but at the time it was important to me not to go. More recently I have made my once a year visit to Mass at Christmas. For me, what it came down to was: not going seemed to be causing more problems than it was worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would add Daryl to the list of people plotting to kill Negan. His plan is less clear, more of a waiting for the right opportunity plan.

I'm also wondering what Spencer is planning. If he is to kill someone with the bow he found, his likely target is Rick. Would he try to kill Negan if the opportunity presented itself?

Michonne's plan of going to see Negan with just a sword and a pistol seems rather crazy. It's not likely she could just walk up to him and chop his head off.

Carl is another person looking for another opportunity. Especially now that Negan is playing with Little Ass Kicker.

If Rick comes home to find Negan holding his child, that could push him over the edge too.

All this plot setting up looks to mean at least one of these stories will lead to an attempt on Negan's life next week. I expect Negan to survive and then kill someone in revenge.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering about that too. It looks like Jesus got off the truck and is still at Negan's compound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is yet another example of how the people who own guns are the ones who should be least allowed to own them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez, who on this show doesn't want to kill Negan? Little Ass Kicker, but I can't think of anyone else. If these folks can get their shit together, next week should be great. Negan will likely survive, but I expect he will take out a few people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 06:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I think I would be fun to make up a new bullshit conspiracy theory, then create a bunch of fake accounts on conspiratard sites and see if I could get people to believe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
