<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8653</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 05:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.orangelodge.org/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 05:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orange_Order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first time to visit Prince Hall. The 3rd D ceremony was 5hrs long and packed with amazing details. The reception was very warm and the food was phenomenal! They share lodge with another "secret" society. This is the first thing that will catch your attention as soon as you step in the building. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 01:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fo'sho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fraternal embrace from Doric 316! We performed a 3rd degree there back in 2012. I did the PM charge. Awesome lodge room! Good acoustics! And your JW back then was a chef so great food!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 01:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a few here and around the greater Toronto area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this car and this street sign while driving around Toronto East. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 01:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 21:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the ref. The POTUS and Zucherberg are inviting him over for a visit. Cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 20:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reference please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 16:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in my day (insert statement here ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 06:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we can laugh at ourselves too. :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 05:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. sharing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toronto Ontario - Moth with curly mohawk. What is this thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 23:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 20:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you all the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 11:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. I got your PM and responded to it. If you have further questions, post it right here so others may chime in as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 10:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toronto / North York here. DVP and Lawrence East to be precise. What's up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one but I would prefer 'Gridiron and Turducken' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 03:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget about old religions and philosophical beliefs from the ancient past- I was totally drawn to booze and other vices when I was in my stupid younger self. Had no idea what Freemasonry was even after joining DeMolay. I just wanted to belong to a cool fraternity that was all. Proof here - http://i.imgur.com/kOqZuoE.jpg that's me with the spiked hair (third from left) drinking with the rest of my DeMolay Bros and a sister from Rainbow Girls back in '97 somewhere in the Philippines. I wonder if this fact makes me a 10 percenter and more uniquer than most. LOL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 02:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's time to change my username. Also, Streisand effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 22:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/1AuwM.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 10:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I was initiated, passed, and raised here in Canada but I was a DeMolay in the Philippines first. Don't wear it in the Philippines if you're not a member. There's a DeMolay in every corner and it is really frowned upon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 00:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art is my ally. I was born in it. Molded by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 15:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for taking your time to explain this to me. Very much appreciated. I'll drop you an email when it slows down here in my household- it's Sunday and all my kids are here- 14yr old, 5 yr old, and 20 month old twins! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 15:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For science, here's the link to my website www.fraternalties.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 14:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the good feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 14:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't make money because of my behaviour and personality quirks, not because I don't have anything on my website at the moment (with the exception of this 416 illustration, my collections sell out fast).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 07:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to say this- thank you for the kind words. I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 07:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LoL. I know bro. I get it. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not from your own life experience, it's not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessir, please excuse my ignorance. If you have the time, I am very willing to learn. Or at least direct me to a good resource. No sarcasm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're talking to anysize but I just would like to make a comment.

My kids have no other home country but Canada. They are firmly rooted here. My kids are my future, and for that I consider myself a Strong and Free Canadian at heart. But you have to understand that sometimes certain life circumstances can be a hindrance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to but I can't be separated from the existing brand that I have. I took me 6 long years to bring it to this point (and it's not even far!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, once again, my bad. I am an artist and not a scholarly researcher. I am a slave to my emotions sometimes (that's what makes me an effective artist sometimes) and I can tell you that from where I stand and look, it definitely feels like there's been a tremendous increase year after year after year... Must be fatherhood that's doing this to me... :-| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come your name is not here? https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canadian_Forces_Chief_Warrant_Officer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True this. And we don't mean it as disrespect. 3 of my 4 kids are born here and I am proud to say that I am a proud father of 3 Canadian kids! :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will. But I have to Google you first. LOL
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want me to tell my life story on a public forum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do have an existing shop (online) but my products are exclusively for members of a certain organization (with the exception of the teespring campaign for the poster in question here). I'll PM you the link to my website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  as long as the message is focused on illegal guns

I guess this is where I failed design-wise. In my head, I'm thinking that the random arrangement and positioning of the guns in the artwork will imply a state of disorder and that those guns are illegal. I suppose it will not be readily grasped and requires a little bit of explanation to get. Thanks for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. I know. It's funny when you look at it that way. But why not, I'm not exactly anti-guns. I actually dream of having a vintage Colt one day. I'm just anti-gun violence and anti-irresponsible gun ownership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admit, I am no researcher, I should have entered a little disclaimer next to that statement of mine. I made that "stat" up from this report http://www.680news.com/2015/07/16/gun-violence-on-the-rise-in-toronto-report/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd tell you my story if you're inclined to listen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 05:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter. I don't really have anything to sell right now anyways besides this 416 No More Gun poster. And I'm thinking of unpublishing it as well... Thanks for the interest though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 05:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a non-native, I'm not sure if there's a Canadian joke buried in there somewhere but thank you for your comment! To answer it, nope... Unless there's enough demand that is. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made an illustration in support of Toronto Crime Stopper's #NoMoreGuns #StopTheViolence and got in trouble with my own followers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 04:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit of background: I'm a Toronto based artist/entrepreneur and father of 4. I make money by merchandising my art. My Facebook page have a decent amount of active following. Roughly 90% of my customers and page followers are in the United States. My niche is very narrow and specific. There's really not much money in it (because I suck at business mostly) but I really enjoy what I do. 

I'm an immigrant. I landed here on November 2004. I have chosen this city because it is diverse and peaceful (and everyone is so polite!) I thought to myself that Toronto is the best place to build a nest. 

I am now a 34 year old with four kids in tow and can't help but be sensitive to the bad things that are happening in our streets beginning on Boxing Day 2005 (I used to work at the Bell Trinity Square and I was there in the area when it happened). The gun violence rate just kept on climbing year after year since that. We used to live near the Science Centre and it's not exactly a peaceful place- there's police presence all the time, on the day we moved out, someone got shot in the head and died where my daughter used to wait for her schoolbus. 

We are in a different location now but there is juvenile delinquency in the area where we live- we had to call the police on a few occasions because of this. We have been harassed, stolen from, family van vandalized on a freezing 2014 Christmas week... At least there's no gun involved... yet... As much as I would like to move my family away from this particular neighborhood, I can't because I don't have a steady job that could afford us a more secure place (thanks to my anxiety and PTSD).

I thought to myself, if I can't afford to move my family to a safer place, what can I do to influence a change even on a minute scale. That's when the idea for the poster hit me. I imagine the red maple leaf in the Canadian Flag, the maple leaf shape was formed by gun silhouettes arranged in no particular order- the guns were arranged as such to symbolize disorderliness and illegal activities; and the red color that used to cover the entirety of the Maple Leaf shape is slowly draining away because of gun violence brought upon us by disorderliness and irresponsible gun ownership. I began working on it last night and finalized it today this afternoon and I was very happy with the result. I published it on my Facebook page and, following my usual modus operandi, made a Teespring campaign out of it as well (I do this to get some grocery money and to protect the copyright of the artwork). 

After just a few minutes I found out right away that my followers do not appreciate my latest creation. Now I am feeling torn, part of me thinks that I should protect my business and the sensibilities of my mostly American followers by unpublishing the "offending artwork", but at the same time I also feel strongly about the gun violence that is rising in this city that I now call my home... What should I do? Is the artwork sending the wrong message? Your thoughts will be appreciated. Here's the link to the poster: http://i.imgur.com/T4VNKgm.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 07:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I summon http://i.imgur.com/e5yijUo.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 16:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been there once. Great lodge, great food! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 16:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I was about 14 years old when I joined the International Order of DeMolay sponsored by Mindoro Lodge No. 157 F AM in the Philippines. I moved to Canada when I was 24 and became a Freemason not too long after. I joined because I felt that it was a natural progression for me, being a DeMolay and all. I wasn't really thinking much about philosophy and spiritual growth when I first joined- I just wanted to belong. I'm 34 now, been through a lot of dark times, and have a completely different mindset- stronger and better thanks to Freemasonry. Our officers are mostly in their 20's-30's. We're a young lodge and don't have a lot of PM's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 03:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toronto here. Doric 316 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 08:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, totoo ito. Na meet ko sya nung dumalaw sya sa music bar ng kaibigan ko dito sa Toronto (Minerva Studio). Nag bigay sya ng Hebrew prayer before and after performance. Proof pic: http://i.imgur.com/d78RpVO.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 04:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toronto, Canada here. Proof http://i.imgur.com/VPEzXU5.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 06:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to The Working Tools? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 05:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that Bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 05:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too long ago I removed my S C car decal because I realized that I still get angry behind the wheel from time to time. Hardly a master of my own emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 05:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few designs that I'm working on but not yet ready for production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sublime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 21:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 19:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all due respect, I don't need any of you here to check my page or buy my products because you are simply not my target customers. My page is one of the most active in my industry and I honestly have troubles keeping up with the demand already that I have to slow down by taking some of my products off the shelf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millennial Freemasons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 07:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 20:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be a protocol. Page admins must be required to identify themselves and provide proof of their membership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 18:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he's a Mason. I sent him a message telling him that sharing and personal use is ok but selling it is not acceptable. He responded by blocking me and by getting more aggressive with his paid and organic advertisements. I don't think any Mason would do that to a Brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 14:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, caught one stealing my work. http://i.imgur.com/eSrPGCR.jpg

Since he advertises to, he managed to sell more shirts than I ever had. You can tell I was really butt hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 07:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Millennial graphic designer here (born in 1981). Here's a few of my creations - http://imgur.com/a/aQDZg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 00:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a small compilation a while back. Check it out http://imgur.com/a/ZT00c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 07:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've known Bro. Trevor since 2013. We're in the same business industry (Masonic apparel). I'm based in Toronto and he's in Vancouver I think. I haven't met him in person though but we have exchanged emails in the past and have mutual support and respect for each others products. I regularly post selfies of myself wearing Grip or Token hat on my own business page.

I don't know if he have a business partner who can help out with the administration but I think he's doing this by himself. I certainly can't speak on his behalf but as a small time business owner myself, responding back in time can be a real challenge sometimes especially when personal life gets in the way. I know I still have unread emails from years ago. Have you tried messaging him in FB?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 04:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm saying though is that we have refreshment, and the particular time for this activity must be high twelve, because we are simply following natural law and we emulate it in our ritual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 04:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If I were to desire to see the metaphorical darkness that all religions have as an adversary to the true God of that faith then I can do so and by doing so learn as star wars says, The Dark Side. Ultimately leading me to a God of darkness... God creating all from the void and being one with the void is an entity of nothingness, and if darkness is just an absence of light the true home of God is darkness.

Like you, I am also born and raised a Catholic. We have nuns and priests in the family, an uncle of mine, a psychologist and SVD missionary priest, is currently one of the regular TV mass hosts in the Philippines- the country with the largest Christian population in Asia (5th in the world). I don't mean to brag, I just want to quickly paint you a portrait of my Catholic background so you would know where I am coming from.

I am sad to say that despite that kind of Catholic upbringing, my human mental faculties is not sufficient enough to dissect and have a meaningful conversation with you about the true nature of God and, as a Freemason, I am not inclined to talk about anything that I personally know nothing much about mainly because Freemasons are typically well read and well informed and I don't want to sound like an idiot- so I'd just share with you this quote from Ghandi "If you do not see God in the next person you see, you need look no further."

If your quest for Light is just leading you to a dark place, then perhaps Freemasonry is not for you at this point in time.

S F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 03:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For this particular topic, is it really important to cite another source if the answer you seek is observable, immutable, and contained within the ritual itself? Savannah animals, field workers, farmers, and operative masons all have one thing in common- they must take a break when the sun is at its meridian- it's a biological thing to go from labour to refreshment when the sun is at its highest peak- it's all about energy conservation. This point in time is known to boost the power of the brother who sits in the south by over 9000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 08:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's the only degree that deals with the present, the 'now'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spirit that guides us is are older, more primitive, more essential than national and cultic worship in Egypt.

I agree 100%. Hence the word "affinity" and not "origin".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 21:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first learned in the 1st Degree about this "near affinity" to Ancient Egyptian philosophy, thoughts of a guy with a funny hairdo and aliens was the farthest thing from my mind. Are you familiar with the Feather of Maat? http://imgur.com/ApmXduI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating is a necessity but cooking is an art. ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 20:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Yes I'm very much aware that it's mirrored. I just like the image.
2. I'm not trying to add my own speculations... Have we forgotten that the title is actually a quote from the JW's lecture?
3. See #2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2nd Degree Refreshment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot of Fellowcrafts. FC is my favourite degree. Just want to share this. 

Hiram's Kitchen album - http://imgur.com/a/DLHrD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "An affinity with those of the Ancient Egyptians" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 05:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prove your horizontals- check it out http://teespring.com/level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my youth I was a diehard Christian, and then I was a stupid atheist, and then a quasi mystic who tried to answer my life's questions by dabbling with drugs and by paying attention to false prophets. I was lost, confused, and angry. I lived my life just drifting along not really knowing where I was from or where I was going.

I joined Freemasonry in 2008 because I felt like it was a natural progression for me as a DeMolay- I didn't expect to gain much in terms of self-improvement or self-knowledge. All I had in my head when I joined was the romantic notions about the connection of Freemasonry to the Knights Templars and ancient mystery schools. 

I began to notice changes in me about a couple of years after I joined when I sponsored two of my friends. To impress them, I memorized the 1st Degree Past Master's / Final Charge and volunteered to deliver it on their Initiation. I was the Junior Deacon at the time. The many compliments that I received encouraged me to memorize all 3 Final Charges as well as other parts of the ritual. 

As I became more adept with my knowledge of the Work, delivering the lectures became second nature. I no longer worry about forgetting my lines. Because I no longer worry about the next word, my mind was free to explore my true self and relate the contents of the charges / lectures to my own experiences. It was at this point when I realized that our ritual holds the key to releasing my full potential as a human being. 

Being a Freemason helped me figure out the many mental complex that used to bog me down. The lessons that I have learned helped me keep my sanity when we went through a series of tragedy which involved 5 deaths in our family and other misfortunes. I am now more confident with myself, my faith firm, more accepting of things that cannot be controlled, and in many ways more focused and more certain of what the future holds. 

TL;DR
Freemasonry illuminated my path.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pyc2ZFPc1s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget the name, it's the familiar fez and 3 question rule. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 08:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be able to help. I have the existing business and I have contacts to craftsmen from USA and beyond. A number of them Brothers or related to one. I don't know how this works exactly though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 02:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll pm you bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really happy to know that you like, Brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that Brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you referring to the solid bronze Sprig of Acacia cufflinks and lapel pin? http://i.imgur.com/BvtLGAb.jpg

We're making a small handcarved wooden box that would house the pins. I want to use acacia but present conditions dictates that only Sheesham wood and mango wood can be used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't, but will try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely correct Brother. The design was based on an old artwork of mine that I originally designed to be woven as Persian rug - http://imgur.com/DrjgPQt

The S C emerging from the iris of the Eye of the Providence, the triangle, and the rays are too much details and carving gets problematic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's another look http://i.imgur.com/3MWzPBW.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No final calculations yet but depending on how many will be produced, it would be anywhere between $20-$35.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming soon. You may pm if you need more info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't yet. These are just samples. We're making more samples so there will be a lot to choose from. From these 4, I'm keeping the 2 All Seeing Eye and will give away the other two because I don't like them at all. PM me Bro if you would like to know more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to share what Albert Pike said about commenting on the motives of others.

"Those who are invested with the power of judgment should judge the causes of all persons uprightly and impartially, without any personal consideration of the power of the mighty, or the bribe of the rich, or the needs of the poor. That is the cardinal rule, which no one will dispute; though many fail to observe it. But they must do more. They must divest themselves of prejudice and preconception. They must hear patiently, remember accurately, and weigh carefully the facts and the arguments offered before them. They must not leap hastily to conclusions, nor form opinions before they have heard all. They must not presume crime or fraud. They must neither be ruled by stubborn pride of opinion, nor be too facile and yielding to the views and arguments of others. In deducing the motive from the proven act, they must not assign to the act either the best or the worst motives, but those which they would think it just and fair for the world to assign to it, if they themselves had done if; nor must they endeavor to make many little circumstances, that weigh nothing separately, weigh much together, to prove their own acuteness and sagacity. These are sound rules for every juror, also, to observe." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peculiar wooden boxes for your peculiar lapel pins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 01:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peculiar. I love that word. http://i.imgur.com/sUXyuoc.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great looking website!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 21:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Thanks for sharing this. Like the hashtag, I can also use this as new material for my did-jah-kno series http://imgur.com/a/Bndv6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A father willing to sacrifice good name and career to better his son, I bet not many will not have the courage to resist and to decline what would have been a very lucrative opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
