<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1236</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magnus and Ciderwhalk colors are so similar that I cant tell which item Santorin has. I think its Magus but im not sure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 00:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really think that Magus or Cidherwhalk should be in a different color. Yes, I can see the sunfire effect. But what if i open the stream, watch builds at first and dont see santorin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Militaaris on kirjas et too mingisugune vaatetorn mis see tundubki olevat, kuid lukus. Vibolla murrangi lahti :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ma mtlesin et lheks kangiga kohale, tmbaks ukse lahti ja vaataks mis seal sees on :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See on pmst mingi 1 diameetriga ovaal kus leval on vike rdu. Ei kujuta ette mis too on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant find MSI B75A-G41 (MS-7758) Chipsets anywhere. Feeling I will buy a complete new hard drive and motherboard since nothing else has worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited and removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM'd you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi Dyrus! I need to make some kind of a interview for school and I thought I will do it about sports, specifically e-sports. Could you answer these questions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are the questions I would like  you to answer!
* When did you start playing League?  
* How did you get to League?  
* Did you play any other physical sports before you quit and started playing LoL?  
* If you answered **yes** to the question** before**. Then why did you quit?  
* How did you pro teams start to notice you?  
* How did they approach you to ask and join their team?  
* What does your family think of you playing videogames to earn and make a living out of it?  
* What do you think of older generation people who think that videogames are for children or a childish activity?  
* What do you think of TSM as an organisation itself and the team?  

Thank you for answering :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh AP Lee Song  mains 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather learn myself that watch 1000 tutorials to play better. Played 800 games S4 and climbed from B2 to Gold 4 which I am proud enough. Didnt watch tutorials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peeter 1 peidupunker kakumel. Kas keegi oskab selle kohta midagi rohkemat elda? Googlest leides andis tulemusi, et seal olevat mingit sorti veesidukid. Hetkel vesi sees ning polnud lampi ning sisse ei linud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/DQB4I1G   
http://i.imgur.com/Ihu2TLM.jpg

Vgagi huvitav leid minujaoks kakume poolsaare otsas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 16:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna try to PM them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any pro player up for a interview that I need for school? 6-10 questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screen is frozen for a second is what i meant by **stutters**. Mouse and keyboard dont work for 3 seconds or forever until a restard. I had Windows 7 Home Premium at first but when the problem occured i put on Windows 7 Ultimate hoping it was a windows fault. Mouse and keyboard are both wired by USB. *This is how I wire them up in the motherboard:* http://i.imgur.com/E7CnaGj.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse, keyboard and windows stutters for either 3 seconds, or mouse and keyboard wont work until a restart, windows wont sutter. Power Options: High Performance, HDDscan shows that there are no bad sectors. What is wrong with my machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mouse, keyboard and windows stutters for either 3 seconds, or mouse and keyboard wont work until a restart, windows wont sutter. Power Options: High Performance, HDDscan shows that there are no bad sectors. What is wrong with my machine? 0 bad sectors. My only guess is that the power supply unit is too weak or something like that? Thank you if you take time to invest into my big problem ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 21:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do it as fast as i can
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slooshi did the same that Locodoco did aswell on stream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuke
Name: nght (nuke grenede help tactic)[just stomped keyboard)
How to: All buy 2 flashes, go to door room. Open door and throw 10 flashes and plant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 07:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estonian is my native lang. I learned cause school makes me and videogames taught me it. My favorite part of the culture is that sauna is so popular here and our Summer Song Contest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love half cooked steak and all fruits. I dont give damn, as long as i have my euros its fine. Whats an integral? Non native speaker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will answer this with a simple ,,k." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I improve just by playing, fuq guides a d tutorials </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Placed firstly to silver 4, went to b2 and climbed to S1. I lack concertration, i laugh most of the time. I just gotta proxy bettet and play more Nasus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun ofcourse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz i play cs more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi I am Silver player who plays League. Ask me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. I play nasus singed and vlad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have some kind of tactic of winning a game? When I play Dominion I just derp around and capture flags and kill bitches :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 18:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punched my keyboard since I nicklamed other famous pro 1.6 players allthe time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think that Proxy Singed could lead my way up to Gold V from Silver 3? Or shall I stack myself up to Gold V? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 00:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To start things off, I'm a lover of disrespect, fun and cool mechanical champs. I am a Nasus lover and also Singed lover. With Nasus I usually stomp lane no matter what, even when I get babysitted a ton or im against a counterpick that silvers believe is teemo. I have 400 stacks at 20 like 90% of times which I consider great. I usually farm up to 700-800 stacks and then start serious grouping. 
With Singed however, I can be 1/10 or something similar but I still manage to win most of the times because I proxy. Today, I litereally gave my team 3 dragons straight cause I was laughing and proxy farming in their base and my team also pushed bot and got inhib free there while I was having fun with 2 enemies at top which at the end of the day didnt kill me. What do you think would be the better way for me to rank up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brand? What ya mean by that. I myself have chosen the hardware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 16:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soo, what do i have to do? Diagnostics? What is that and how do i d it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Glock so weak compared to CT default handguns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 15:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. You litereally need to shoot about 6 times to body if  you dont HS to kill a person with glock. WIth USP and P2000 it is 3-4 shots, headshots are 1 bullet. While with glock you need to shoot twice to head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 12:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ye I wanted to write cannabeard at first but got confused. Eestlane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ,,Kannahabe ja niaktt'' (Translation from Estonian: Witchman and kannalbeard) and ,,Sure, koer" (Die, pig/jerk/fucker/dawg. Dont really know how to translate that word. Straight translation is dog) by Edward von Lngus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 01:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/RX3pSqb.jpg

Basically police arresting a marijuana bearded man. The marijuana bearded man is actually a well know fiction charachter who had moss growing as a beard. It has a political message behind it cause in Estonia, you actually get more prison time by owning marijuana than lets say punching your wife to injuries (not always tho, if the injuries are very hard that the wife is now on wheelchair forever)

http://i.imgur.com/pIaMEV7.jpg

Famous Pulp Fiction scene with faces replaced with very well known film characters Joosep Toots and Arno Tali from film Kevade (1969) There isn't a Estonain who doesn't know what Kevade is. Either way he knows the original book from 19th century or the film made in the 20th century.


He has sold some of his stencils and work for over 600 (for collectors, not other artists, ofcourse)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/E7CnaGj.png Does this explain that? I can send you a picture of the things tomorrow aswell, but right now cant do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will draw you a picture how my USB things are made since i cant explain that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zilean Splash art and his Voice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, splash doesnt seem to fit with the voice very well. When I click on zilean i  hear the old, tried voice of Zileans; i know you would do that. But the splash art seems like he is so evil and has all the energy and stuff but in the old splash he was just goofing in the air and smiling like he was high on crack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cant understand this, can somebody explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse and keyboard suddenly stop working for 3 seconds or forever until a restart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been having this problem in past month or so that both of my mouse and keyboard suddenly stop working and i hear the plug out voice in windowows. I doubt its a mouse or keyboard problem cause they both stop working at the same time, it ain't windows fault too cause i just reinstalled windows. I think its either dust problem or USB ports are simply broken and i have to buy a new motherboard which means 100 gone. All drivers are the newest. Keyboard is Logitech K200 and mouse is SteelSeries Kinzu (v1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 20:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indeed it is.. but.. league of legends, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unpopular opinions in LoL (idea stolen from /r/globaloffensive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 20:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **mine**  
* -arcade hecarim is a pile of shit, worst hecarim skin.  
* -akali cant be countered  
* -katarina cant be countered  
* -leona is the most op support ever  
* -ship(ht/th)ur is a god  
* -ap nunu is op  
* -janna blows ass aka she is useless  
* -shaco is the best jungler in the game  
* -old summoners rift was better  
* -texture rebalances suck ass  
* -new splash arts are the worst ever  
* -nidalee isnt op  
* -ip prices are ok  
**post your opinions**

- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse and keyboard suddenly stop working for 3 seconds or forever until a restart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 20:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been having this problem in past month or so that both of my mouse and keyboard suddenly stop working and i hear the plug out voice in windowows. I doubt its a mouse or keyboard problem cause they both stop working at the same time, it ain't windows fault too cause i just reinstalled windows. I think its either dust problem or USB ports are simply broken and i have to buy a new motherboard which means 100 gone. All drivers are the newest. Keyboard is Logitech K200 and mouse is SteelSeries Kinzu (v1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 19:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, did you prefer the old pre-rework nidalee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 19:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you main Nidalee cause of her* strip dance? What is your favorite Nidalee skin?
And also, answer in russian/ukrainian please


EDIT: HER NOT HIS OMGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Configs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 16:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I load my config why is the crosshair defaltpile of shit? I just took my config and loaded to my new PC with fresh windows etc, put it on and 0 fucking settings came over. All are default </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legit. I have used it to bu skins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Valve will rework Train again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faker fucking ryu right in the face in PornHub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 22:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is that Bill Gates fell out of HARVARD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I was hovering my Screenshots folder to see how I built Heimer by Mobafire guides when i was lvl 15. I found a picture also how toxic I was a year ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 21:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/UA0GLmv.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I was hovering my Screenshots folder to see how I built Heimer by Mobafire guides when i was lvl 15. I found a picture also how toxic I was a year ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summit stream is talking about TSM not being all american and all kind of nationality stuff, this one made me gringe so hard for no reason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 13:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant even downvote in cSGO reddit, no button for it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 13:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've loced a tricast or quad-cast like LoL does in big event finals. Poor Deman, haters got him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 12:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you ult you are invunerable for 0.5 secs, so yes you can dodge spells with  him but timing is key. I myself have mastered the technique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 18:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ye i know that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 18:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ye i saw the NV game, when they were 14-12 i was like ez money but then they seemed to troll kinda. Sad to see them go already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Titan already fall off? I mean the tournament is over for them now right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favorite Siv video of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it is either AP Xin Zhao song or shaco guide. I love his guide music choicces, the comical sound to it and ap xin zhao foam swords 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 20:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tbh i loved how siv punched his monitors with his foam swordes in the rythm, it really made me laugh so hard :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seemed like a time where a person can decide and a make up his thoughts about the game. I personally played the game for 7 years but I think that in 1.5 years most of players got to do the 5on5 with other teams and gather late in ventrilo in 1.6 not play public servers anymore etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, write reasons why you prefer your choice. I prefer 1.6 cause wallbanging, simplicity and memories it brung every game. Ofcourse, I understand that GO is a new generation game and it cant be with potato graphics but it is my opinion. I play GO and it is a good game aswell, but as I said I like 1.6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-made cause one comment made me think that some of community hasn't even played 1.6 and then vote go since they think 1.6 is a shit game cause of graphics etc and GO is better because skins etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you prefer CS:GO or CS 1.6? Please answer people who have played 1.6 for atleast 1.5 years and play CS:GO actively </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read today that CS is still the most played game on Steam, no idea if it is true or false. I think that atleast 65% of reddit csgo has played it, but it is just a assumption but it seems that todays kids prefer CoD's etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually dont spill sauce to my games. If you meant source then I dont see people arguing with that game a lot :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made to see what reddit thinks, seen people arguing about which is better from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> naah cause i cant play it anymore, all people quit it. I prefer 1.6 over GO but GO is a good placeholder for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of them, all because league RANKED made me rage while cs:go comp doesnt make me rage. I still from time to time play normals aga casual games with friends but I dont play it very serious anymore. I just started to like CS again like I did 2 years ago and a lot of streamers play CS:GO between high-elo(division) queue times. Somestimes queues are 15 minutes so they play like a viewer game or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 18:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kinda sad tbh, grew up playing that with my 6 year older friends.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 15:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can use pocket pussy/fleshlight to fap tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 15:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10+ if you win every game by 5 rounds atleast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 19:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, spear hit Flag which is coded as a part of jarvan itself probably so when it gets hit by something that deals damage, Jarvan recieves dmg?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Christian from Season 5 opened his own food truck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 18:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if he actually did that :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope SivHD will do some charity event this year in summer aswell! May it be 20 hours, I will watch it all :=) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best pun in your opinon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal best is Phreaks one to Aphro on dlift against xdg zuna/sheep bot lane: ,,so you got  sheep on one side, moo on the other, bit of a farm lane - how to..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What skin do you see every game or 99% of your games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 22:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see AK Blue Laminate absolutely every single game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 00:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you estonian? EST League of Legends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 12:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you mean overslept? He didnt play cause he was sleeping when the game was on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant understand the bug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I asked Steam Support aswell but i read that they answer like it two weeks. I really cant understand howbuggy Steam is. Errors here and there but eventhough a great program </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unexpected Error </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I tried about 10 times to get 10 to my steam acc but doesnt work. Always said unexpected error. I'm paying from my paypal account that is unverified but it worked before everytime. What shall I do? By the way, will I have to wait like a week again to buy from Community Market if I added funs from unverified paypal account again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unexpected Error. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 21:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!
I tried about 10 times to get 10 to my steam acc but doesnt work. Always said unexpected error. I'm paying from my paypal account that is unverified but it worked before everytime. What shall I do?
By the way, will I have to wait like a week again to buy from Community Market if I added funs from unverified paypal account again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nautilius get nerfed and Nidalee buffed what the fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 16:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 in a row yes, played with a friend who was smurfing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you need to do to rank up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 16:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win 60 games in a row being the top fragger or what? Won 15 in a row being a fragger in top 3 in my team and 0 rank up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 14:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is he saying at the beginning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are these Vans Slip-Ons still sold on any e-shop in Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 19:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does RP players mean? :D ELI5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 18:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AKALI PERFECTLY BALANCED WHAT THE FUCK ?!??!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 22:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *juggler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 22:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anybody help me switch back to all old splashes? I  installed a few but i only see it in champ select but not ingame and loading screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help repairing the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 20:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Installed a costum skin, some kind of file got corrupted pak01_dir, deleted it so steam can restore, since it differs from comp. servers, not got a 7 day ban for abandoning since cant fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 22:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have like 200 hours in a silver 4 scrub but honestly, i dont give a shit i just play the game :D My flair is wrong since i want to seem better :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dyrus lost weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 02:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse not working in-game shop and tab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 15:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked yesterday, now doesnt. cant buy items by mouse and cant report etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 22:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seda kinni ei pandud v :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 18:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See kuradi mt, et patsidega inimesed haisevad :D Stereotbid.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 16:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rastasid tuleb pesta iga 5 peva tagant, kuid enne rastade tegemist tulebki lihtsalt harjuda nii et iga 5 peva tagant pesed  juukseid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 12:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tsi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 22:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ma ei disrespekti sellega kultuuri, sest osaliselt usun isegi rastafarianismi ja selle puhul ei mtle ma nalja. Tean millega patsid seotud on, aga mulle ka lihtsalt meeldivad nad. Endaarust olen jrele melnud :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 21:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absoluutselt ei huvita mind et need moes pole, mulle need meeldivad :) kopp ees tavalistest noorukite pea-karvkattest. Krvalt lhikesed, pealt pikemad ning anum geeli phe topitud :) Aegunud teave oli 2013 ning enamus neist enam ei tta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rastapatsid Eestis (hind, koht jne) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 21:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keegi teab mingit salongi Eestis kus rastapatse tehakse? Asukoht pole oluline, kohale lhen niikuinii. Sooviks salongi, eraisikuid siiski ei taha :D Google ei andnud tulemust, enamus teabest seal aegunud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i love in estonia where they dont sell these kind of things in shop ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems to be haunted, thats why i posted here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PayPal and steam wallet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 16:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wallet and PayPal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 15:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Is it possible for me to give 5 to my steam wallet? I have them sitting around there, HOWEVER i dont have a debit/credit card linked. Cant i transport money from paypal to steam wallet without card linked to paypal? If that, then that is hilariously stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> neXtPlease needs to learn how to motherfucking rusj, not wiat until 10 fucking seconds.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can somebody photoshop this boys face to this dog? Like beautifully like the dogs face is actuallty him :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 20:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy: https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/412644706216972288/tBWwxSXN.jpeg
Dog: http://pngimg.com/upload/dog_PNG2453.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 20:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for the Windows Phone one. 2030 the hype?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me or topcatti :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 21:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What ya mean bad troll? Yea textures were better aswell, now we have futuristic shit, but on a serious note: Old train was such a balanced map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valve Train rework </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 21:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why did they rework Train? I mean the old version aka from 1.6 was one of the most balanced maps ever compared to the new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wallpapers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 19:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fellow summoners!  
I just wanted to ask if anybody actually uses all the league of legends wallpapers that are posted here a dozen every day? Like for me, seems kinda wierd to use a LoL wallpaper but thats my opinion. I dont want to offend the artists since some of them are really great work but do people actually use them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] FT Five Seven Case Hardened, FT Glock Candy Apple, FT M4A1-S Dark Water, BS M4A1-S Basilisk, FT USP-S StatTrak Blood Tigger [W] FT AWP Corticera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> b/o FT **AWP** Corticera </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalista Hurricane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 00:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] FT Five Seven Case Hardened, FT Glock Candy Apple, FT M4A1-S Dark Water, BS M4A1-S Basilisk, FT USP-S StatTrak Blood Tigger [W] FT AWP Corticera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] 5-7 Case Hardened FT, Glock Cand Ap. FT, M4A1-S Dark Water FT, M4A1-S Basilisk BS, USP-S StatT Blood Tiger FT [W] AWP Corticera FT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 23:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 22:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tean neid videod, sealt tuligi ksimus pooleldi :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 varbalised ltlased/leedukad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 21:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erinevates foorumites, aastast 2009 nen et kui baltimaade vahel mingi simlus kigul, siis eestlased simavad teisiest rahvusest balitikalisi 6 varbalisteks, 6 *toed*. Kus selline asi tuleb ja mis ajast juba? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) I will just buy a montiro with DVI-D hole :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 VGA Connected montiors doesnt work imo, tried it coudlnt do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 3 VGA ports and 2 DVI-D versions. I guess i need a new montitor with DVI-D hole?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I buy like a DVI-D-VGA cable? My 2nd monitor is from 2006 or something and it doesnt have a DVI or DVID hole so i would preferrably put VGA to the 2006 monitor and DVI-D to my PC. Is that possible? The one without the 4 extra pins is DVI-D by the wy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Seems like i will be hitting my local electoring store tomorrow and buy a DVI-D cable then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sjokz dinner and movie fined  
Nick, the "fine" pick-up lines are never going to.. [work (possibly?)]  
East Coast Servers are ready.. just kidding what's for lunch  
Daily picture of my beard to Joe Miller and Deman.. we left riot dude stop sending the pictures  
**BEST IMO** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DVI adapter question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! So I recently bought a DVi-VGA adapter so i could connect my 2nd monitor. Comes out that my DVI adapter in the DVI hole has 4 extra parts: http://imgur.com/EaLjeLQ  
This is what my DVI connectors look in my PC: http://imgur.com/8ZhYHq6  
I wonder if the adapter will work when i punch these 4 extra parts in or basically break them or it wont. Dumb as hell question problably you thinking right now, but im just a dumbass and dont know if they are needed. By the way, Yes I know that PC is dusty as hell, going to the store tomorrow to buy some air in bottle-shaped thing :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 22:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spooky fiddle doesnt look spooky anymore :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A useful thing for me and maybe for some small amount of player for Deathmatch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 21:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im on of these guys who play USP without Silencer. I practice awp on DM and when i feel like i need to take out my secondary and realise its silenced and i hate it, taking it off takes time. Sometimes I die during taking off the silence right when i respawned even. Maybe if i get it unsilenced once it could stay what way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 22:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counter Strike (1.6)
Revolutionary game, best FPS ever made </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 19:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> akali is uncounterable. CC or pinks it wont give  a shit, he will lifesteal and spellvamp the life back in seconds or QSS out of the CC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rip Goldking gangplank :(( captain gold  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lee, Akali aka the most unbalanced fucktard champion in league of legends and ofcourse, Katfuckingrina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just implement TwitchChatTV to SR somewhere, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually there is couple of tips to climb elo: Play akali. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sound comes from earbuds, headsets are to block other sounds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 22:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I litereally learned English all from photoshop and sony vegas tutorials when i was like 8. Most of my english comes from the net, estimated around 85%. I can outspeak every classmate of mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 22:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started playing LoL at EUW server since my friends were there, now can speak fluent french and spanish tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 12:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mafia graves ones are very awesome indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zilean has some pretty horrible ones and also Karthus. I really like Lucian ones since they are so instant and Graves's are good aswell! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 02:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gotten fatter significaly* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
