<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1459</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The methodology is a little questionable here. The example of "positive coverage" is saying things like "leading" and "gaining ground," while "negative coverage" is "trailing" and "losing ground." These aren't opinions, but just facts about the race - those aren't the type of phrases where people inject bias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gary's call was electrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're missing my point in the context of this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coincidentally, I did mention Kanye West as another example.

In regards to Trump, I can personally see it both ways. I think he truly says what's on his mind and he's taken a lot of criticism for it that he hasn't backed down from. That to me takes a tremendous amount of balls. I know if I was him and I was receiving the amount of media hate, I'd probably kill myself. It's like a teenager suffering from online bullying x 1000.

Sure, he fights back, which could be seen as "caring a lot what people think" but I also see it as another example of not being willing to take shit lying down. So I'll just have to agree to disagree with you on this one - but I totally see where you're coming from.

I knew the example of "Trump" would be divisive though. But then again so would Kanye West, who plenty of people hate as well. I think the "not caring what people think" attitude *always* creates both lovers and haters. It comes with the territory. 

Thanks for the comment. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Do you have any studies supporting that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are completely valid concerns, but I think you're being overly critical.

Even just practicing your presentation out-loud in an empty room can help you become more comfortable with presenting the material and seeing how it flows. While we should be mindful of bias among friends/family, they can still provide useful feedback as well (especially if you actively encourage it - ask "What do you think I need to work on the most?").

I'm not sure what the alternative would be, rounding up a bunch of strangers? I test out jokes/stories all of the time among friends, even if it's just a casual setting like sitting at the bar or talking on the phone. I personally find it helps me perfect my story-telling ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 16:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the article isn't actually about becoming a stand-up comedian. And in that section it mentions how stand-up comedians practice new material in small clubs or open mic nights, which is pretty standard advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she just say "goysplaining?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the support! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking for more, you might also be interested in: [Small Talk vs. Big Questions: How to Build a Deep Connection With Anyone](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/small-talk-vs-big-questions-how-to-build-a-deep-connection-with-anyone/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely some truth to this. 

Democracy only works when choosing priorities among shared values. It doesnt work when there is an inherent conflict of values. If I start a book club, it makes perfect sense that we can vote each week on what book to read next. But if movie fanatics who dont read books start joining the club, out-numbering us, and then voting for movies instead of books - you have fundamentally changed the nature of the club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Statement about the video:**

I find Haidt to be one of the few social scientists who can look at current politics from a broader perspective. His work on moral psychology is key toward understanding differences in belief systems. This latest video provides more insights on what is dividing our country at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally agree, I think it helps to focus on both similarities and differences if you want a "complete picture" of yourself. That being said, while the idea of "we're all individuals" is certainly nothing new, I found the 3 principles mentioned in the article to be a useful way of framing these individual differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a fairly [popular quote](https://www.google.com/#q=This+is+your+life+and+you%27re+writing+your+story.+Don%27t+ever+let+someone+else+hold+the+pen.), though it's hard to find what the original source is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you find this somewhere or have you actually read all of these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 15:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good tip. I think any type of stretching and getting the blood flowing is a good way to keep you alert and attentive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 15:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're talking about the Reinhold study - it's just one study that didn't replicate. Cuddy has done dozens of studies and you can see her response to this study [here](http://faculty.haas.berkeley.edu/dana_carney/pdf_Summary_Expansiveness.pdf):

In this review we list the 33 published experiments based on 2,521 participants demonstrating the embodied effects of expansive versus contractive nonverbal postures. We discuss a new addition to this list that found an embodied effect of nonverbal expansiveness on self-reported feelings of power but no effect on risk-taking, cortisol, or testosterone. **Taken together, the body of work demonstrates support for the embodied effects of expansive nonverbal postures.** However, multiple experiments have found that the postural effects appear to be bounded by social context, culture, and participants awareness of the hypothesis. Fruitful avenues for future research are suggested. 

Also, considering the [facial feedback hypothesis](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Facial_feedback_hypothesis) is already a well-documented effect in psychology, I think it logically follows that a "body feedback hypothesis" would likely hold weight as well.

Of course, it's reasonable that only a single 2 minute "power pose" session would have a small (if any) effect, but an interesting future study would be to see how multiple sessions spread over an extended period of time (a couple months) would work. 

You wouldn't expect one dose of a medication to cure depression, so why would we expect one single power pose session to have a massive effect? I've been practicing power posing for several months now and I definitely feel a significant change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 04:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the power poses are meant to be practiced around people. They are just a way to prep yourself and pump yourself up *before* a meeting, or interview, or date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.

On the flip side, audio books will be better for my pronunciation. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That article only mentions one study that didn't replicate. Cuddy has done dozens of studies and you can see her response to this study [here](http://faculty.haas.berkeley.edu/dana_carney/pdf_Summary_Expansiveness.pdf):

In this review we list the 33 published experiments based on 2,521 participants demonstrating the embodied effects of expansive versus contractive nonverbal postures. We discuss a new addition to this list that found an embodied effect of nonverbal expansiveness on self-reported feelings of power but no effect on risk-taking, cortisol, or testosterone. **Taken together, the body of work demonstrates support for the embodied effects of expansive nonverbal postures.** However, multiple experiments have found that the postural effects appear to be bounded by social context, culture, and participants awareness of the hypothesis. Fruitful avenues for future research are suggested. 

Also, considering the [facial feedback hypothesis](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Facial_feedback_hypothesis) is already a well-documented effect in psychology, I think it logically follows that a "body feedback hypothesis" would likely hold weight as well.

Of course, it's reasonable that only a single 2 minute "power pose" session would have a small (if any) effect, but an interesting future study would be to see how multiple sessions spread over an extended period of time (a couple months) would work. 

You wouldn't expect one dose of a medication to cure depression, so why would we expect one single power pose session to have a massive effect? I've been practicing power posing for several months now and I definitely feel a significant change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really interesting but if I showed this to any of my friends they would think this is another example of white privilege and the negative effects of colonialism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always conflicting studies in psychology, I never know what to believe. They make me feel good, so I'll just stick with that. Could be placebo, but that's still a psychological change.

I wonder if there are any studies on frequent "power posing" over the course of a month or more. It's reasonable that only one 2 minute session would only have a tiny effect, but I wonder if that effect can build up over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm certainly not against being positive.

But I'm not against being negative either.

I think all emotions serve a purpose in the right context. This view is mostly aligned with other research in psychology and emotional intelligence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you feel negative that is what you will attract.

This isn't always true from my experience.

Sometimes when I let myself be negative and let myself digest negative feelings, they serve their purpose and I can more easily move on.

I can't imagine how depressed and trapped I'd be if I felt I had to fight every negative feeling I had.

Giving myself permission to feel negative sometimes was one of the most freeing things I've ever done.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a short on how did I attract child abuse: https://youtu.be/C1f6jOxUYS8

That was a very underwhelming explanation to me.

"You were offering a vibration but you didn't realize it."

Really? The child was offering a negative vibration that led to them being abused? 

What about: sometimes bad things happen to good people that they don't deserve. The end.

Also, to the extent that "free will" exists, I think it's obvious that a child definitely has less choice than an adult does.

"We cannot say you're the creator of your reality sometimes and sometimes you're not."

Sure we can. In fact, the whole basis of the philosophy of stoicism is that *some* things are in your control and *some* things are not. Your power over your life doesn't have to be "black" or "white" (you are in complete control or you have no control). There are actually grey areas in life.

**To be clear: I do think some things in life ARE a "self-fulfilling prophecy" (and that idea can be very helpful). But the law of attraction definitely takes this belief to an extreme.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this even remotely bad?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't affect "everything in the universe." That's the fatal flaw of the Law of Attraction. That's what inevitably leads to undeserved blame and guilt.

The simple truth is: there are limitations to what is in your control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article doesn't say it's the only cause of social anxiety. Just that it's a factor that contributes to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a common saying among hypnotists that "All hypnosis is self-hypnosis."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 01:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, Donald is going to have enough gold for decades after this AMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the best you can do is have a diverse range of news sources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a final note I'd make here, in terms of the studies they've passed over, they have passed over a surprising number of studies written by economists of great repute -- for example, they skipped a positive pointing study by Giovanni Peri.

Yes, that study finds a correlation between ethnic diversity and economic growth in metropolitan areas - but it could very well be that growing economic areas attract ethnic diversity, and there's no causal relation at all.

Do you have any other studies that may have been missed in the podcast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Functionally-speaking, why and how exactly should we suppose that these are different?

You can easily tease apart different intellectual backgrounds (biology, mathematics, psychology, engineering) vs. different ethnic backgrounds.

Here in Europe, "ethnic diversity" usually also has a strong linguistic component to it. Most of our ethnic minorities are also linguistic minorities. If nothing else, this implies that a more diverse work staff will be able to work in a broader range of languages (a skill which european employers put a very large premium on)!

Sure, but that's a problem that only arises in diverse populations in the first place. In a more homogeneous population, that extra demand for a diverse working staff wouldn't even exist. 

AFAIK, Groupthink is something that can be undermined and chipped away at by ALL kinds of diversity. 

According to the evidence presented here so far, that doesn't appear to be the case.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read his book, it's not mentioned at all. And for the sake of fairness, the last chapter of the book is actually pro-immigration (and his colleague Bryan Caplan is a huge "open borders" advocate). I don't think these findings on the "costs of ethnic diversity" are politically driven, believe it or not - I think he's genuinely interested in a well-rounded discussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The podcast is very explicit that forms of intellectual diversity and gender diversity have shown to have positive effects - it specifically focuses on ethnic diversity though. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is doing AMA during WI rally? But how?

I guess right before he goes on he'll be answering a few questions.

EDIT: Got it, I'm stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 01:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagreed with the removal. There are many citations here and the podcast is with a professional economist. There's no valid reason for this to be removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if it's culturally biased (toward Westerners), why do East Asians always perform very highly?

The [Ravens Progressive Matrices](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raven%27s_Progressive_Matrices) is an IQ test that is generally considered the least amount of cultural bias because it's just recognizing visual patterns. 

You should try asking your question in /r/AskScience. I can't promise better answers, but I know anthropologists almost always underestimate biological factors and overestimate cultural factors. And the top comment here ("IQ has been thoroughly debunked") is flat-out wrong.

You might also be interested in checking out the book [Hive Mind: How Your Nations IQ Matters So Much More Than Your Own ](http://amzn.to/2aoAosS). It's a great breakdown of various IQ research. It doesn't focus on "ethnicity" at all, but it does show differences between nations and how this can have influence on economics, governments, and other social institutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend asking this question on /r/askscience, considering the top rated comment here saying "IQ has been thoroughly discredited in psychology" is laughably wrong. Anthropologists tend to put more bias on culture over biology. /r/askscience might be a bit more well-rounded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got wrongly removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm going to have to pass on comedy specials for the next few years - there's only so much "OMG Trump is stupid, am i rite?" that I can take.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 05:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **H.I.G.H. E.N.E.R.G.Y.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thought, but I don't follow the logic that wealth makes us lose social connection.

The logic is that wealth makes people more self-sufficient and less dependent, therefore there is less of a need for group cohesion.

One of the reasons there is now low social trust in the U.S. is ethnic diversity...

Yes, that's definitely one factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think these are weak expressions of tribalism, but they are definitely a byproduct of those instincts. Like Junger says, I think the big question is "Who are you willing to die for?" Most people are probably not willing to die for the things you mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 02:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he waited for such an opportune time to "reveal the truth." I call bullshit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love that book myself. It's influenced by Ayn Rand/Objectivism so it's very individualistic oriented. I've actually become a little less individualistic in the past few years, but there are pros and cons of both perspectives. "Balance" is often key here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our identities become more static. We end up stuck in similar patterns that we picked up throughout our childhood/teen/young adult years and begin to think "this is just who I am." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except it's a lot faster and without all the cucking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Willie Robertson, surprisingly good and well-written speech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is this barbarianism?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 21:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for serious response.

In regards to animal migration, the video says that temperatures have decreased in South pole and increased in North pole, is that true and would that explain the animal migration rather than rising temperatures overall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence contradicts Trump on many positions, so lets frame this as: "You see? Trump is willing to work with people he disagrees with." That's not a hard spin - it actually works in Trump's favor, as he is usually seen as someone who isn't willing to compromise with anyone.

He also has less name recognition/unfavorability than Gingrich and Christie. So I think this pick won't hurt Trump at all. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 13:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone says something good about a book? Must be advertising! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 01:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.

It's almost like...telling people to stop killing people doesn't stop people from killing people. Can we stop acting like we're 5 and realize that bad people actually exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rasmussen had him +2 in an earlier poll, so it would be a +5 change. Rasmussen is also known for heavily leaning Republican. 

Personally, I'm more excited about the tie in the NY Times poll. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, according to the article, those with autism *are* 5x more likely to have alexithymia, which is a difficulty of understanding one's own emotions. So it's not completely inaccurate. 

That being said, it's always worth noting the nuances of mental disorders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention an aspirational slogan: "Make America Great Again!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He called Clinton a "wonderful public servant," and called Trump a "racist." 

He's basically a milquetoast liberal at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been very vocally against it throughout his entire campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I found the book, I read it, and I really liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Borders are analogous to property lines. Both are arbitrary social constructs which exist only by convention. Both nevertheless exist because Darwin rewards people who practice their use. (And punishes those who do not.)

Property lines exist when individuals claim territory and succeed in defending it.

Borders exist when groups claim territory and succeed in defending it.

If property lines are the boundaries between property holdings, borders can be thought of as the boundaries between property regimes.

In practice, you have the property and property rights that the people around you are willing to concede that you have. One man cannot stand alone against the world.

But a few in confederation can hold the looting hoards at bay indefinitely.

Property and property rights are obtained in exchange. You recognize and uphold mine and I'll do the same for yours.

But to this basic condition, others can be added to protect the long term viability of the confederation which gives it force.

And first among these must be "don't let the looters in."

One condition people may demand for recognizing and upholding your private property is help in upholding shared borders.

You don't have to assent to that condition, but if not, you might find your position very lonely." 

Eli Harman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but Gene Callahan is also a well-known libertarian, so it's relevant here too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, now I get it. I thought it was just referring to his performance with creating jobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused, isn't that only "job approval" rating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but it's still not a majority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what the article says. 43% show strong support or somewhat support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 14:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no real "mastering" or "applying" the rule. It's just keep practicing, keep practicing, keep practicing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 13:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, so basically the same advantages and disadvantages of any heuristic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Cernovich for the most part. The book is kinda "beginner"-oriented as far as self improvement goes, but it covers all the key stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 14:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course this is assuming presidents have a direct and relatively immediate impact on the economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting how this statistic hasn't been mentioned at all since Trump's original comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 04:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be able to x out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 14:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the interesting thing about this book is that if focuses on the effects of IQ at a national level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 14:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I messed up. Apparently the result I thought was mine was just an "example."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very true, but I didn't want to get downvoted into oblivion for pointing that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an advanced report that costs money, but the first page after you complete the exam should show your score. At least, I got to see mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes sense to me. America is a very divided place, it's hard to extend your pride from Texas to New York, or vice versa, when those places reflect very different types of people with different values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For this reason, I like to draw a distinction between "country" and "government."

I think you can be proud of your country while still being upset at your government, especially when that government doesn't accurately reflect the will of the people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Do you think it's possible for those feelings to extend to your nation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 14:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about gay pride? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 14:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should people be proud of their families? It's just something you were born into, it's not like you had a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 14:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the chart, that doesn't seem to be the main catalyst. 

The real fall starts around 2004. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 13:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cheerleader effect, also known as the group attractiveness effect, is the cognitive bias which causes people to think individuals are more attractive when they are in a group.

That's not what the article is about at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 04:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's less than a standard deviation but sure, 2 points could be significant - we have a very large and diverse population. On average, however, we're certainly not the epitome of "stupid."

You can see countries ranked by IQ here: https://iq-research.info/en/page/average-iq-by-country

The site also offers a version of the Raven's Progressive Matrices here: https://iq-research.info/en

(It's considered one of the more "culturally fair" IQ tests since it's completely based on pattern recognition and no language/verbal questions.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 04:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take a version of the Raven's Progressive Matrices IQ test here: https://iq-research.info/en/

It's considered one of the more "culturally fair" IQ tests.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 23:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America is around 98 average IQ (2 points below average, UK is 100 and Denmark is also 98 for comparison). There are countries that are far, far lower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're just being cute - but the whole point of saying it's a "temporary solution" is that it is NOT a "cure" for social anxiety. It's the solution that is "temporary," not the dog. Although maybe a better word would be "supplemental."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dog isn't supposed to be temporary, the solution is temporary - by this the articles means it's not a "be all, end all" cure for social anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 13:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, not even close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 19:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chatango is down, yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 15:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what the article is saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 02:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was going to vote for Hillary?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had never seen it before yesterday, but yes, I did cross-post it from /r/getmotivated. Others seem to enjoy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you guys need a refresher:

[Why is /r/ZenHabits not just about "Zen?"](http://www.reddit.com/r/ZenHabits/comments/zo9n8/why_is_rzenhabits_not_just_about_zen/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump paid less money per vote in the primaries than any other candidate.](https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://img.washingtonpost.com/blogs/the-fix/files/2016/04/Money_NoOutsidev2.jpg w=1484) 

Seems like a good use of money to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 14:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are we supposed to find out the results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 13:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're taking the analogy a little too literally.

The first two clarify outside observation. The other clarifies inner observation. That's what the comparison is based on.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 03:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the grand scheme of things, is *anything* on /r/The_Donald going to change the election? Probably not. But we should play our part as best we can - because that attitude *will* be necessary to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 03:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised by how a simple step like providing a direct link at the top would improve conversions compared to telling people to Google it.

The less hoops, the better - especially from a marketing perspective. This is why Amazon has a "One Click Purchase" button. Even the "Donate" link on the sidebar is buried and hard to find.

It'll make a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep donating guys. Seriously, I don't want this election to even be close. Let's win, win, win.

Can we sticky a donate link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you *need* hatred, it's just a natural consequence when something you love is being threatened. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a planned/written speech (like his address to AIPAC), not a rally speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 

Ive been thinking about this a lot lately, so let me try to share my perspective as best as possible.

I find people who believe love is the solution to all of our problems show a sign of emotional immaturity. Its the same as thinking we should only experience happiness and never sadness. 

Ultimately, this is rooted in a fear of negative emotions.

Hate can be a productive emotion though. It means you know where your values are and you know when something stands against your values. Its the flip-side to love. You cant have one without the other.

And honestly, whenever I see people who say love is the solution to all of our problems they end up, upon closer inspection, to hate plenty of things.

I think the anti-Trump movement is one of the biggest current examples of this. Many of my friends say if only we loved everyone, but they also deep-down want to see Trump die. I certainly dont see them extending any of that love toward Trump. And thats fine, if youre being honest about your values and that not everyone shares them.

However, I would try to draw a distinction between hating people vs. hating ideas/behaviors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, I think being aware of it is the primary step to take. But the article could've probably elaborated a little more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it was Republican rhetoric. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll agree to this. The problem isn't necessarily the causes people are saying, but the causes people are ignoring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely! I really relate to the concept of having an "imaginary audience."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 03:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I literally just finished Ryan Holiday's book "Ego is The Enemy" and it mentions this idea of an [imaginary audience](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/destroy-your-ego-before-it-destroys-you-and-how-we-make-bad-situations-even-worse). Check out the third section of my article:

As the psychologist David Elkind has famously researched, adolescence is marked by a phenomenon known now as imaginary audience. Consider a thirteen-year-old so embarrassed that he misses a week of class, positive that the entire school is thinking and murmuring about some tiny incident that in truth hardly anyone noticed. Or a teenage girl who spends three hours in front of the mirror each morning, as if shes about to go on stage. They do this because theyre convinced that their every move is being watched with rapt attention by the rest of the world. Even as adults, were susceptible to this fantasy during a harmless walk down the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 23:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorguts
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 20:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want a name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 14:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a well-written article with countless studies mentioned. Why can't we focus on the actual content?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 13:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible for science to find racial differences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm here to learn. I'm looking for substantial criticisms of the article - not "Haha, racists using facts to justify their beliefs." I'm sure *you* have no ego, assumptions, or intellectual baggage at all...you are just a straight line to the truth.

That being said, I do appreciate your *actual* response, even if you are being an asshole about it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of these studies did control for socio-economic status.

Childhood poverty and mental health are variables that may not have been accounted for though. Good point.

I'm only here to talk about the facts. No one "nailed me, bub." Thanks for the actual response, even if it came with some snark.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your only substantial criticism of the content is that there might be confounding factors that haven't been accounted for. Any ideas what those might be? Stereotype threat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a problem with any of the findings in the article? Or do you just think these are things that shouldn't be talked about?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the facts, please. 

/r/skeptic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 13:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you point out the grammatical mistakes? I'd like to fix them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 03:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably used the tag wrong, I meant there was no spoilers in the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 03:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Slander a man in his own home, you might find yourself crossing swords with him."

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 03:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One sales manager for Trump University, Ronald Schnackenberg, recounted how he was reprimanded for not pushing a financially struggling couple hard enough to **sign up for a $35,000 real estate class, despite his conclusion that it would endanger their economic future**. He watched with disgust, he said, as a fellow Trump University salesman persuaded the couple to purchase the class anyway.

So...Trump U. is like every other college and university? Damn, it really is a scam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crucial Conversations is fantastic. 

If you want to know more about it, I have an article about it [here](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/how-to-defuse-heated-arguments-before-they-spiral-out-of-control). The diagram in the middle is a very good breakdown of the philosophy in the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeling Good + Six Pillars of Self-Esteem are probably the best ones for people on /r/Confidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. It's Weaver Wordpress theme if you're interested. You can customize it a lot, I basically just turned it into an empty page though (hide page titles, categories, other Wordpress stuff). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really loved The Righteous Mind (one of the most illuminating books I've read on politics and morality - it cleared up so much confusion for me on why people don't see eye-to-eye on everything), so yeah, I really should check out The Happiness Hypothesis too.

Thanks for reminding me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 13:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with it by title, I really should check it out! Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been studying and practicing CBT for over 7 years now. It's not a quick-fix solution, but the tools can definitely be applied and re-applied over time. If you're thinking of just doing the exercises once and forgetting about them though, the effects won't last long. These are tools you need to keep in your back-pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What book would you recommend instead? As someone with a pretty decent familiarity with body language, I thought the book was very practical and realistic. He explicitly mentions the ambiguity of reading body language and that you can't necessarily tell if someone is lying based on nonverbal signs (though you can tell if they are generally comfortable vs. uncomfortable). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 22:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, what were the 3 duds you read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 20:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes, this reddit is dedicated to self improvement, not just Zen.](http://www.reddit.com/r/ZenHabits/comments/zo9n8/why_is_rzenhabits_not_just_about_zen/)

Also, I would know, because I'm the moderator. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 20:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reddit is supposed to be about positive vibes. It probably won't hurt us to loosen up a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 18:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you end up being better than others, don't say I didn't warn ya. :-P

EDIT: I was *clearly* poking fun guys, wow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 18:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He definitely doesn't attribute all of his success to affirmations, though he does believe they played a role (as well as other skills he picked up as a trained hypnotist).

Can't comment about the women comments, there's nothing about that in the recommended book.

I personally think Scott Adams is a really smart guy. His blog posts on Trump's persuasion tactics have been incredibly fascinating to me. He had a recent appearance on Real Time with Bill Maher that's worth checking out [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2pX1SkJMCrI). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like

Bernie's movement is not cult like


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 14:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best advertising *is* lowest common denominator. That's how you cast the biggest net. Coming up with cutesy nicknames that stick is certainly very simple and base, but that's also what makes it so effective and contagious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 14:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't fall for 3rd grade persuasion skills."

"Check out my 'Make Donald Drumpf Again' shirt!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big portion of them did for Ron Paul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 16:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Interesting quote:

Since 1920, the vast increase in welfare beneficiaries and the extension of the franchise to women  two constituencies that are notoriously tough for libertarians  have rendered the notion of capitalist democracy into an oxymoron. - Peter Thiel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 02:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #BELIEVE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why it specifies that these are insights from those with social anxiety. It's not meant to be representative of the average population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely.

Some of the best public speakers I know are in-fact very introverted. But when they step on stage, they can "flip a switch" and go right into performer mode. Then, they'll go right back into super introvert mode once they get home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 00:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - ["That's fine. Blacks and Hispanics can vote for the Democrat party en masse and stay broke."](http://i.imgur.com/DUvRzi2.png)

- ["Hilary Clinton is a racist, war mongering murderous butch queen. The Clintons decimated black communities in the 90s."](http://i.imgur.com/GCelRGk.png)

- ["Trump just wants the U.S. to be lavish...for all of us. I can fuck with that."](http://i.imgur.com/w5vv7Mz.png)

Yeah, she's been going hard on Twitter the past 24 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 20:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, I'm lightfiend, moderator of this reddit. 

It's likely you guys are already familiar with me as a moderator of /r/ZenHabits, /r/Psychology, and /r/Mindfulness. I also frequently share content from my website [The Emotion Machine](http://www.theemotionmachine.com), which nowadays is mostly reviews of various books in psychology and self improvement.

As far as my story, I'm a 27 year old male currently in New York (though I'm moving somewhere else soon). I worked at a music and arts venue in Brooklyn for a couple years, but mostly since college I've just been focusing on my own goals and eventually becoming self-employed. It's a long process, but I know it'll be worth it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 02:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was it? Thinking about checking it out tonight. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is no such thing as "Zen philosophy".

Then there's nothing to correct. Carry on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're really good at analogies, I'm still waiting for you to address what the article is misguided about (though I'm guessing you never planned on adding anything of substance anyway). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The elitism on this reddit is hysterical. You must think you're really above all us peasants, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give one example?

Maybe you're too attached to only one way of thinking about Zen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like to clarify? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's Camille Paglia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is based on the book, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 01:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if there is any relationship between Bullshit Receptivity and Open-Mindedness on the Big 5 Personality Scale. 

High levels of open-mindedness tend to increase suggestibility ([Study](https://www.researchgate.net/publication/256933656_Hypnotic_responding_and_the_Five_Factor_Personality_Model_Hypnotic_analgesia_and_Openness_to_Experience)).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, you *can* be mindful while watching TV or movies. But usually when we watch TV we get very absorbed in the characters and storyline, getting sucked up in the dialogue and emotions, and not exactly being "mindful" of what we're doing (sitting on a couch, watching TV, laughing at a joke). Instead, you think you're on a plane with snakes, or whatever - living in your imagination and not in the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He throws his primary base under the bus, knowing that they won't vote for Clinton regardless, and turns this election from a left-right conflict to a populist-establishment one.

He's already been making this pitch for a long time now. 

He calls himself a "commonsense conservative" (which I'm sure he'll drop in the general election), but he's made it clear he doesn't really care about the GOP or conservatism in general. He's already started positioning himself to the left of Hillary when it comes to war and foreign policy, and he's already taken a more "tolerant" stance on LGBT, planned parenthood, and other social issues compared to other conservatives who can't let that stuff go.

The "establishment" vs. "the people" theme has been with Trump's campaign since the onset. He's only played the card more as the GOP and media have treated him worse and worse. He even says nice things about Sanders getting screwed by the establishment.

In the primaries, he's already attracted a lot of moderates, independents, and Blue Dog Democrats. I imagine he will only double-down on those demographics once we hit the general election.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 16:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I appreciate the "correlation isn't causation" sentiment. Some things to consider:

It could tell us that being psychopathic leads to being more creative, it could also mean that being more creative leads to greater psychopathy.

Of these two choices, which do you think is most likely?

It could also mean that both variables are caused by a range of other variables.

Sure. But do you have any in mind? 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think any experience of loss can elicit grief, even if you never knew the person in real life. Hell, I sometimes get sad after finishing a really great TV show because I'll miss all the characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 15:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, wasn't aware of this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think "pathological altruism" may be an extreme form of "feel good altruism." Not being able to be satisfied with yourself unless you give, give, and give. 

The paradox is by never drawing boundaries or taking care of yourself, you often end up hurting both yourself and the very people (or animals) you're trying to help.

Animal hoarders are a common example of "pathological altruists." They can't say "no" to a wounded animal, so they end up taking in way more than they are capable of taking care of. As a result, it ends up creating an unhealthy and destructive environment for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 17:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair. I think "doing good" is going to make you "feel good" no matter what. The important difference is to not let the "feel good" be the only guiding factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 17:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [GiveWell](http://www.givewell.org/) is the recommended source for most effective altruists.

Though they have very limited options - only about 5-7 charities listed. However, according to them, these charities do significantly more "good per buck" than your average charity.

I'm most interested to donate to GiveDirectly, because I think the potential economic and psychological impact could have a good multiplier effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 14:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Caveman TV," I like that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 19:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long did Melt Banana play for? And I heard they only have 2 members with them, no drummer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump doesn't drink though, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 14:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on the bottom of the sidebar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most IQ tests these days measure for culturally biased questions and remove them. It's not as big of an issue these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of that has anything to do with IQ tests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 23:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't look like it'll fit anywhere near the expected 10k. Are there people crowding into other rooms in the facility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certain gestures and common greetings can be culture-based. 

For example, Navarro talks about how in many Central/South American countries (he's from Cuba), males hug each other as a formal greeting (an "abrazo"), which is typically seen as odd by Americans. 

He recommended a book on this called, "Gestures: The Do's and Taboos of Body Language Around the World." I haven't checked it out yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How early you heading over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very close to me, I really want to go. What's a good time to head over? Anyone want to meet up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, some cross-cultural differences are mentioned in the book, couldn't get into them here though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there are a good amount of pictures showing what he talks about, but it's not meant to be a strict rule-book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely necessary to create models and equations to try to explain complex phenomenon. I don't fault econometrics for that. But I do think economists can sometimes fall into the trap of trying to boost their pet equations more than actually trying to raise standards of living.

Not a reason to throw out the field, but a caveat worth noting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter, we pregame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 22:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Me right now](http://33.media.tumblr.com/e384f1addc096cddc5cf5db224480b80/tumblr_n7d5xyZgJd1qhhh7ko1_400.gif). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the plans they've modeled has ever been implemented AFAIK

They can't apply their models to plans that are already in place?

Say they projected a 1% increase in growth but growth increased by only .5%, that doesn't necessarily mean they were wrong, because there could have been other factors that produced a .5% drag.

If there are other factors that influence the outcome you're trying to predict, then that's a weakness of your model.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine it's really hard to predict economic growth, especially on a tax plan alone. But out of curiosity, how accurate have The Tax Foundation's predictions on economic growth been in the past? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily. Lowering tax percentages doesn't always lead to less government revenue if it spurs enough economic growth.

See: [Laffer curve](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laffer_curve). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 17:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It moved a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 21:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this video not up anymore? Doesn't seem to be loading for me. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's ever too late to build a small group of friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 20:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Levittown, NY here. Represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 20:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Levittown represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 23:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a really great interview. Trump hit on a lot of key points and letting it happen on his own plane was just beautiful. Surprised he talked that much before a town hall - he *really* likes talking - but he was probably aching to get some of those things off his chest after his weekend break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 22:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nothing is presidential but victory."

#CUCKSTOTHELEFT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 17:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article doesn't say anything about strict family determinism. The whole point of being aware of these patterns is so that, hopefully, you can do your best to avoid repeating them.

Family is an influence, but it's not destiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 17:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family isn't destiny, it's just an influence you need to be mindful of. Be aware of the patterns and try your best to avoid falling into them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very low energy of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 03:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, Savage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 15:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Keep my bases loaded like the New York Mets."

RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 03:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are coming at us from every angle, the poor bastards, they can't escape now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBT includes both behavior therapy (gradually exposing yourself to anxiety-inducing situations) and cognitive therapy (questioning your thought patterns and beliefs). So it sounds like your talk therapy might've included some CBT elements (most of them do these days). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 14:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The research does include other European countries, like Germany, Italy, and some others. From what I remember, Southern and Central Europeans differed from Northern Europeans, and we're more moderate in their "Western" perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 00:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I basically agree with all of that. But the first step toward re-training your responses is to admit that your emotions don't always serve you. That's all I'm saying in regards to "empathy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 23:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hypersensitivity" might be a good term too.

But why is it not possible to be too attuned to others? If you are swept away in every person's emotions, that could cloud your judgment and become maladaptive. 

For example, it could mean you have trouble saying "no" to people, because you don't want to disappoint them or hurt them. Or it could mean you're compelled to help every single person you come across, which can lead to burnout and emotional fatigue. 

That's not empathy in the sense of just "understanding" people, but allowing everyone's emotional burden to become your emotional burden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
