<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 05:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One serious problem/consequence with senate reform would be that in the absence of a separate executive branch of government (i.e. we have a symbolic governor general), reforming the red chamber would significantly diminish (if not usurp) the authority of the Prime Minister as the de facto head of state for Canada.  Therefore, it may harm the bargaining power of the Canadian government in international trade relations if the commons cannot as easily enact negotiated terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 16:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's lack of bravery.  I would think historically the problem has been communicating new stances to the electorate in a way that it can become an issue of debate. 

Maybe it's easier today to disseminate and discuss policy alternatives. Not to blow our own horns, but /r/CanadaPolitics is an excellent example of new social infrastructure. I had interest in Canadian politics before joining, but little understanding of the issues, and more importantly, no one to argue with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 02:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Higher revenues, while potentially paying less overhead (i.e. hosting fees, bandwidth, etc.) makes it actually a extra-lucrative change of pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 01:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I received a mailer the other day informing me about a new tax-credit for charitable donations.  I know tax-credits have been popular in the [latest federal budget](http://www.budget.gc.ca/2013/doc/bb/brief-bref-eng.html).  

In some ways, I like this idea, because it lets individuals choose where they would like to direct their funds.  I think it would be interesting if there was a system, almost like Kickstarter, where Canadian citizens could elect to fund certain programs over others.  Like a policy market-place.  There could still be general revenue to fund regular activities, but there would be an additional system to fund things like science, research, the arts, infrastructure, bike-lanes, etc.  Provide some ownership, such that citizens feel like they're paying for the services they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 01:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are tried and true methods of taking up revenue, for sure.  However, as economies become more globalized I worry more about these revenue generating methods, because Canada is forced to compete with other countries to attract investment.  

Raise corporate income taxes, and companies just move elsewhere.  Raise personal income taxes, people just hide their funds in offshore tax-havens.

Plus, these forms of taxation are politically unpopular, like you've mentioned, which can lead to irresponsible government policy and populism leading to deficit increases attempting to make the electorate happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government Revenue: What are some revenue sources that government should be exploiting that they're currently not? On the flip-side, what are some current revenues-sources that should be curtailed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 00:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With growing demand for overhaul of transportation infrastructure in various municipalities and ongoing concerns of deficit-reduction, I'm curious to a hear opinions from our community on taxes and revenues.

Some topical examples that have come under fire:

* Changes in the federal budget regarding [tariffs](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/report-on-business/economy/economy-lab/canadian-consumers-will-feel-the-pain-of-ottawas-tariff-hikes/article10753547/)
* [Fees](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/story/2013/05/27/toronto-ontario-metrolinx-revenue-tools-gtha.html) proposed by Metrolinx for the GTA, which include tolls and PST increases
* [Carbon taxes and Cap and Trade](http://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2012/09/18/reality-check-all-carbon_n_1894400.html), which might see more play during the next election

As citizens and consumers we all pay taxes.  I believe everyone understands that for governments to function and provide services, they require revenues; the size of government and the scope of those services notwithstanding.  So, I thought it would be fun to try some out-of-the-box thinking on how they could go about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 05:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good example of this would be the [videos of bait cars](http://youtu.be/lx43pW94RDI) the Vancouver police put up. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 04:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be pretty funny to see someone try it tomorrow and crash and burn horribly, but really, think about all the kids born post-Facebook.  Of that cohort, the ones that end up in politics are going to grow up in a hyper-documenting culture of people photographing, video-recording, and micro-blogging just about every innocuous event of their lives, *voluntarily*.  72 hours of video already gets uploaded to YouTube [*every minute*](http://www.youtube.com/yt/press/statistics.html).  

The average person's privacy is trending downwards rapidly as we head somewhat organically into a complete surveillance culture.  Extrapolate 20 years and think about how politicians are going to be behaving...

It's that whole 'Little Brother' thing (rather than extreme surveillance by the state, i.e. 'Big Brother', there is extreme surveillance in aggregate by everyone's individual recording devices and our hyper-documenting behaviour).  Someday, to be a public person will be true in every sense of the word, IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 01:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, I completely misread your earlier comment, nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 00:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a fair ambition; however, perhaps instead of a whole other party you can seek to affect policy within one of the existing parties.  I think some of the problems you're noting are really just symptomatic of the limitation on the independence of individual MPs within parliament to voice their own opinions and form factions.  

Many CPC representatives probably agree with you, but their hands are tied and they're getting whipped...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 00:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it would be overkill if it was an enforced scenario, but with the amount of self-documentation people already perform just as part of growing social media, I don't think it's out of the realm of possibility to start seeing politicians record and distribute all their official activities voluntarily. 

Especially with the convenience of wearable computing devices coming out like google-glass, I feel like politicians might be driven to such self-documentation as a means to control how they are perceived by the electorate and the media.  

That's one of the strengths of politicians like Naheed Nenshi.  Since he actively and consistently communicates by twitter, facebook, etc., directly to the Calgary electorate, in many ways he influences his own public perception more than if he just relied on conventional media reviewing his tenure as mayor.

Also, wow, I'm getting a ton of downvotes lately, I wonder who I pissed off... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $53B federal infrastructure promise doesn't sway mayors - Federation of Canadian Municipalities meets in Vancouver for annual convention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 22:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 19:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a major reason this is coming about now, isn't so much a culture shift as it is that the threshold for the technology has finally been passed, such that it could actually work.  

A device like this can be reasonably small, light-weight, with a powerful camera, and enough storage capacity to last through a person's shift.  The long-term storage of the data may also be a manageable cost.

Also based on some other threads in this conversation, devices like this could have applications for other professions where liability is a concern:

* Elected officials
* Doctors performing medical examinations
* Armed forces in combat zones
* Personnel working in prisons (such as with the recent [Ashley Smith](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/story/2013/05/28/nb-smith-inquest-incident-reports.html) case) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 19:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking it in a different direction, what would you think about something like this for elected officials?  

Looking at Naheed Nenshi in Calgary, he's already embraced social media very successfully and that's sort of how I see it.  Imagine being able to Ustream any MP or senator when they're acting in an official capacity at events, meetings, campaigning, etc...  That would be pretty interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 19:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's been some experimenting with this for the sake of strategic advantage as well, for example someone commanding a small group of people can bring up their separate video feeds to get a more complete perspective of a combat situation.

I wouldn't be surprised to see a militarized version of google-glass in the foreseeable future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 18:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you think about applying the same technology to members of the armed forces in combat zones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The union says in other jurisdictions where police officers are equipped with  point-of-view cameras, the use of force by officers and assaults on officers drops by as much as 60%.

I'm likewise impressed to see them embracing this.  Those are impressive statistics.

The experiment ongoing with the Edmonton Police also mentioned in the article apparently [began in October 2012](http://www.edmontonpolice.ca/News/BWV.aspx).  It will be interesting to see what the results are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops with cameras: the good and the bad [Montreal Policemen's Brotherhood is proposing that officers be equipped with uniform-mounted cameras] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 18:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 01:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I'd like to see an older next Doctor too.  I was actually thinking of Rik Mayall could be a cool Doctor.  Bring back the funny arrogant side of the Doctor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 00:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how many positions Harper personally added.  The wikipedia article lists the precedence of each position, but the [last 10 or so](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cabinet_of_Canada#Current_Cabinet) have no date associated with them.  However, looks like it's on par with what Paul Martin had:

 ...the size and structure of the Canadian Cabinet is relatively malleable, the slate of Cabinet positions tending to be substantially restructured periodically, the last major period of realignment occurring between 1993 and 1996. Throughout the 20th century, Cabinets had been expanding in size until the Cabinet chaired by Brian Mulroney, with a population of 40 ministers. Mulroney's successor, Kim Campbell, reduced this number, and Jean Chrtien eliminated approximately 10 members of the ministry from the Cabinet, so that by 1994 there were a total of 23 persons in Cabinet. Under the chairmanship of Paul Martin, the number increased again to 39, in the vicinity of which it has remained; the Cabinet proper currently comprises 31 ministers, with another 7 members of the ministry who are not of the cabinet.

[Coyne](http://www2.macleans.ca/2011/01/07/how-to-make-a-cabinet/) made some good points on the subject a while back: 

 As far as I have been able to tell, Canada has the largest cabinet of any government in the democratic world: possibly even the undemocratic world. It is 50 per cent larger than Britains, 73 per cent larger than Italys, and more than twice as large as that of the United States of America. It is also more than twice as large as the cabinet Mackenzie King employed to cope with the Great Depression and fight a world war...(Macleans, Jan 2011) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 22:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, Rona Ambrose is the Minister of Public Works and Government Services.  [Full list](http://www.parl.gc.ca/MembersOfParliament/MainCabinetCompleteList.aspx?TimePeriod=Current).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 01:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came across this conservative action group after hearing about it on the This American Life podcast (also listed on the front page for the link).  

They make some really interesting points beyond those you've listed for why conservatives have thus far rejected climate-related issues.  The major one seemed to be that acknowledging climate-change was seen in some ways as a betrayal of "the American dream", because it suggested people should have to give up the privileges inherent to developed western nations.  That they should 'feel bad' for wanting to hold on to the way of life we enjoy.

I can see something similar in Canada when people suggest that the answer to climate change is to completely forego exploiting natural petroleum reserves such as the oil sands, which has been a major national income and overall economic boon.

Personally, I think if Canada pioneered a position where personal and corporate income taxes were nullified in place of taxes on environmental impact, I think it could:

* a) Spur some really interesting engineering innovation to lower emissions
* b) Attract a lot of new business, since corporate income taxes would be much lower than other countries

The only problem would be that as such innovations occurred, national revenue would gradually decrease, and there would be a structural deficit driven by green-innovations...

Also, finding ways to balance the new tax code such that existing operations weren't suddenly swamped in new environmental taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy and Enterprise Initiative - Putting Free Enterprise to Work on Energy and Climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 00:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 22:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under this hypothetical situation, I believe Alberta is still subject to federal laws and any attempts at their contravention with provincial legislation would be cast down as unconstituational by the courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 20:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right to worry about losing the broader picture; however, I think you need to consider that it's the regulators that see this every day have the expertise, more so than the federal bodies. 

I worry more about situations like Fracking, where most of the analysis and field-testing has been done in Alberta, but shale-deposits in other parts of the country might not benefit from the regulatory know-how that's developed in Alberta.  Another good example is acid-gas injection for sequestering CO2 and H2S under ground.  Nearly all of these wells are in Alberta, but if carbon-capture became a federally mandated scenario, you would see it in other parts of the country quite rapidly.

Rather than having approvals go through the province and the federal government, it makes more sense to share information and research between provincial regulators and have the feds set the bar for what the provinces should be looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 20:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe *in situ* EOR is across too many provinces. However, I do totally agree that holding the same meter-stick to these projects across provinces is essential. However, I think that can be achieved by a federal body mandating that onto provincial bodies, rather than doing double or triple submissions to multiple regulators.

Furthermore, some provincial bodies have greater expertise in particular areas, such as Alberta Environment and the ERCB for *in situ* EOR. Ideally, they would help draft guidelines that Environment Canada could approve and apply to other provincial bodies.

So I guess what I mean, is that I'd prefer more information sharing and stream-lining of regulation, rather than siloed bureaucracies acting independently.

The latter option may seem more robust (i.e. more eyes per project), but I think in today's day and age, we have to adopt more effective systems.

**Edit:** On re-read of your comment, I think we mostly agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 19:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something important to consider here is that this development is removing federal environmental regulation.  Provincial regulation of these projects will remain intact.

I think this is a smart move.  Rather than Environment Canada directly regulating these projects, they should be mandating the level of scrutiny that the provincial bodies bring to bear.  Alberta Environment, and the Environmental Resources Conservation Board (ERCB) have a lot of expertise and personnel to oversee in-situ enhanced oil recovery projects, so it makes sense not to double-dip.

In general, depending on the sizes of the projects, I think it's a good model for the federal regulatory bodies, to be auditing and working through the provincial bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political satire magazine Frank to return </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 03:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 18:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're misunderstanding the timeline, though the article is written in a convoluted sort of way.  If I'm reading correctly, the alleged homicide (if there was any) occurred before any media were contacted for the sale of the video.

We'll probably know more tomorrow, but the real story is that a senior staffer in the Mayor's office (perhaps the former chief of staff) in tipping off the police, has conceded the existence of the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 15:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, having a strong military has loads of advantages and doesn't have to involve jingoism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 05:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Increased military funding, specifically in homegrown R D

There was opposition to military R D?  That's a shame, they have some really good research projects that aren't 'weapons' related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 15:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testers score best in the June exam statistically. Don't know if you want to wait that long. It hasn't been confirmed why that effect occurs (i.e. the test isn't necessarily easier).

Make sure you only practice with what you'll have in the exam. I used to practice with a digital stop-watch, but there's a rule against digital watches or really any computerized device in the exam. My analog watch was a little harder to tell how long I had left by.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 01:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck with the LSAT, I hope you find it less challenging than I did... Always messed up the analytical reasoning games... :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we say no to nosodes? [homeopathic vaccines] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 05:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to agree, the situation certainly feels like hubris. However, given the liability of the personal cheque...the fact that there could be jail-time if it comes to a criminal investigation (based on Coyne's article).  Can you imagine, if you were in Wright's position, not stopping and thinking "this is illegal". Frankly, by accounts, he wasn't even the only lawyer that brokered this deal.

Duffy must have had some leverage.  Again, pure speculation, but I really think there must be something between the PMO and Duffy that forced this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 04:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, now this is where I get more interested in this story.  Why was it so worth it to do this deal instead of just letting Duffy stick it out?  Some pretty bad and obvious consequences are playing out now.

The only thing I can imagine (and I should stress this is my imagination, not a statement in reality) is that Duffy, knowing where the bodies are buried, threatened to roll on the PMO over some unknown scandal.  And, as Coyne called it, this was 'hush money'.  

It's a bit melodramatic, but the whole "If I go down, I'm taking you all down with me" play by Duffy is the only thing that makes sense to me, given the blow-back everyone involved is now facing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the Senate fire a senator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 00:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd be a dark horse, but I'd put my money on Jason Kenney taking the helm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, the net costs could increase with the per-capita costs going down if people are living longer and contributing to the economy more.

However, I think you're failing to acknowledge that the healthcare system we have now is inefficient and inadequate. Hospitals are overflowing. 

Simply throwing more or less money at the problem will fix nothing. We have to implement new systems and technology to meet increased demand, because the old model is insufficient.

So is it your position this is not among realistic means of meeting that demand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 21:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't accept your premise that I expect a program like to be funded simply because it is 'good' or 'moral'. The economic argument is hypothetical, but preventative medicine based on genomics is already widely acknowledged as the direction healthcare is taking, so I would argue the question isn't 'if' but 'when' you want to pay for it, and how much you want that future global market to contribute to the Canadian economy.

From a policy standpoint, advancing the application of these technologies in the Canadian healthcare system should be a priority, not just because it is 'good', but because it is strong economic opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 19:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Avoiding the tough question

Unless I'm misunderstanding, I believe the question is whether investing in genomic sequencing technology for healthcare in Canada for the general population will be worth the cost.

Logically, apart from pathogenic illnesses (viruses, infections, etc.) and physical accidents, all other illnesses and disorders that remove people from the workforce must be the result of hereditary predisposition or gene mutation.  

Numerous examples are already available for predicting such disorders with genomic data, such as the one in the linked article for mutated BRCA-1 (breast and ovarian cancer).

It makes sense that the total cost of developing such tests for the general population (which are currently on the order of a few thousand dollars and are continuing to fall, as per the link in my previous comment), will be a lower economic burden than letting them get sick and fill hospitals (which is the current strategy).  Hospital associated infections (HAIs) already kill more people in north america than [car-accidents AIDS or breast cancer](http://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=beating-back-the-bugs).  i.e. you go to the hospital for one thing, get sick with a drug-resistant infection, and stay significantly longer or never come out at all.  Any measures that reduce the number of people making extended stays in hospitals is probably going reduce the healthcare economic burden.

Implementing genomic testing should be examined in a larger economic analysis, I agree, but for the sake of argument let's assume I'm wrong.  Even if such a program operated at a economic loss, it would be still be morally worthwhile to provide such care rather than letting Canadians simply get sick.  Really, this is the underlying argument for having universal healthcare in Canada in the first place.

 They'll just be dying of a *different* disease at high cost

Actually, predisposition to these disorders would also be detectable.  However, they would be more linked to elderly individuals, rather than tax-paying younger people getting cancer or heart disease in middle age.  /u/Darth_Face2021 makes some excellent points in this regard as well.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 17:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The cost has fallen

I actually said the cost is *falling*, research and development by groups all over the world continue to push down the cost of this technology and this [trend](http://www.genome.gov/sequencingcosts/) is expected to continue.  

 which thing in healthcare should we stop funding

I think we can reasonably agree that the cost of patient care for degenerative disorders (so illnesses that progressively get worse over time) is higher when treated at later stages than if it is if detected earlier.  This measured in terms of time spent in healthcare facilities, treatments, and attention from personnel, but also lost productivity when patients are out of the workforce with illness for extended periods of time.

Implementing large-scale genomic diagnostic medicine for preventative care could be economically viable in the sense that early detection of illness (also providing information to patients of what they are 'predisposed to') could allow early treatment for disorders.  Therefore, less would be spent in aggregate to keep people healthier overall.

So, which thing in healthcare would I stop funding? The majority of the really sick people, because they would no longer exist.

The topical example in the article if of Angelina Jolie spending a few thousand dollars to learn she's predisposed to breast cancer and ovarian cancer (mutated BRCA-1 gene), so she's having elective surgery to prevent those eventualities.  Overall, these procedures cost less than if she actually had cancer and then had to be treated for it, with chemo, radiation, antibodies, etc., on top of these surgeries.

 The other half of the question

This is the direction of medicine in the 21st century.  Better data, more timely treatments.  Canada can get ahead of other countries in developing and implementing these procedures and treatments.  At the same time build databases of genomic information that can be licensed to other countries that want to implement similar programs.  So there's further economic arguments to generating the intellectual property first.

I'm not suggesting that all these practices should be implemented as government-funded programs.  Rather that there is a burgeoning global market for these technologies, Canada has a highly trained life-sciences educated population that we're currently just losing to the US.  This is one of the areas that if we invested in now we could be a powerhouse in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 14:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be very much in favour of this.  The cost of these procedures is falling, and with a strong investment, Canada could become a leader in preventative and personalized medicine through the application of genomic data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should genetic testing for cancer be available to all Canadians? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 14:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toronto Mayor Rob Ford denies crack cocaine allegations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 18:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 04:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @acoyne:
 So Duffy is claiming the PMO is *lying* when it admits the PMs chief of staff was involved? [10:20pm]

 That should stand up well. [10:20pm]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 03:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole affair just sounds too ridiculous to be true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 02:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit, while I briefly enjoyed the novelty of hidden comment scores, it's begun to feel a little irritating that I can't tell when I'm debating a point with someone how much support I've captured compared to them.  That might be a little childish though, and perhaps the quality of my arguments will improve if they're based in conviction and not 'scoring points'.  I still comment fairly frequently despite the score-hiding, so it's not harming my desire for discourse.  

If other users feel like me, it might be worthwhile keeping the hidden comment score, just so I don't develop too much of a confirmation bias for my views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 00:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be curious to see whether there is any legal precedence for actions like this with respect to the elections act or other legislation governing personal monetary transactions and gifting to elected or appointed members of government by party staff-members.

Really, the fact that money was given by Wright get Duffy to make certain statements and actions to the public in his capacity as a senator, regardless of whether it involved legislation is tantamount to... giving^a^bribe  I don't even want to write it because it sounds overly inflammatory, but it's not exactly untrue.  Duffy could have sued to keep the money like the other senators under scrutiny.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 23:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a staff-member within party is spending $90k of personal money to avoid negative media-attention for their party, then that is in a sense a $90k contribution to that political party.  Especially when considering that Wright is acting on behalf of the party by interceding on Duffy's behalf.

Annually, a private citizen is [restricted to $1100](http://www.elections.ca/content.aspx?section=res dir=ces document=part3 lang=e#36) in total contributions to a political party...

/u/Broseidon241 also makes a really good point on the [prohibition of gifts and other benefits](http://www.reddit.com/r/CanadaPolitics/comments/1edzk5/pms_chief_of_staff_paid_off_mike_duffy_senate/c9zfoe4)

Wright should be restricted in gifting that much money to help his party, and Duffy should be restricted from accepting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 20:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which would still be a political contribution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 19:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, now if the money is a personal cheque, but as a gift it's purpose is clearly politically motivated:

 buy your way out of bad press

Does this then qualify in any way as an illegal political contribution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 16:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, no taxpayer money, and no party money... What other possibilities are there?  The only thing i can imagine is whether Duffy had any assets, maybe real estate, that were 'sold' for recompense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 06:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could still be an ethics violation in that case I would imagine.  At the least it's an example of cronyism and yet another piece of negative media attention...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 05:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say (assuming any of this is true), that they couldn't possibly be stupid enough to use public money.  However, if this can actually be tied back to Harper's chief of staff...  Why would anyone in the PMO be going anywhere near an ongoing investigation with a 100ft pole?  

Is it just hubris, or is there some reason they didn't want to allow Duffy to fall under the bus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 02:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little late to the party for anyone to see this, but I think it's going to be **poverty**.

I could quote a [bunch of statistics](http://www.globalissues.org/article/26/poverty-facts-and-stats) about how many children are currently in poverty, food production vs. those going hungry, etc.  Chances are you've heard it before, know it's a problem, and shrug it off as unavoidable.  Scarcity economics after all is the basic tenant of our global society, and many governments already invest a lot into social programs for various issues.  However, the number of [people living in poverty is increasing](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poverty_in_the_United_States), so the problem is actually getting worse.

Reddit has seen a lot more discussion of [income inequality](http://youtu.be/JTj9AcwkaKM) in recent years, I think a possible program that is going to increase in popularity in the future is the idea of getting rid of poverty by systems like 'minimum income', or the 'reverse income tax'.  There are several of these proposed systems that work in different ways to offset negative incentive effects to personal economics.  However, they're all often tossed out as simply 'just giving money to poor people' and a lot of 'give someone a fish, vs. teach someone to fish BS'.

Good video of a Canadian Senator [discussing the subject](http://youtu.be/tI-LDQCmW5E). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could just mean a few thousand threatening letters going around demanding $5000 from each recipient for infringement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House essay: Information counts in policy-making </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 18:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 19:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you like Kenney over Baird, and where would you see him going?  

I feel like Kenney's outreach to immigrant communities makes him a difficult asset to replace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 17:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I'm willing to bet there's no changes till after the next election. I think the CPC mentality is that their electoral base appreciates consistency. A cabinet shuffle is an implicite admission of the need for 'correction', instead of dependably staying the course.  

Suggesting a cabinet shuffle feels like making up news because there was nothing at hand to report on, or to inject extra drama into current events... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 16:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the media predict a cabinet shuffle a little while ago that never happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Hall: Hitting the reset button on a tired government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 16:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 09:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it that the currency is falling or that the greenback is rising?  Or does it even matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 21:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beyond merchandise export, what would the effect likely be to the services economy?  I was discussing in another thread the other day about whether a fair amount of R D had left Canada as manufacturing had declined.  The other poster brought up Nortel and Blackberry, but I was thinking more about Biotech like [Merck leaving Montreal](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/montreal/story/2010/07/08/merck-closures.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The loonie is set to fly south  deep south, says TD Economics [projected for 2014] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 20:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 07:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Mulroney started the GST

[The GST replaced a hidden 13.5% Manufacturers' Sales Tax](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Goods_and_Services_Tax), which based on some quick googling had a pretty long precedence

Regarding fisheries, that was definitely an intervention.  However, that might qualify as a legitimate intervention in that the market would never engage in a moratorium on its own to preserve fish-stocks.  Cod would just be fished to extinction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 06:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Harper though, the article lists plenty examples of his economic interventions.  I'm curious how they stand up in comparison to:

* Clark
* Mulroney
* Chrtien
* Martin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 05:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to make examples of intervention from Pierre Trudeau, but technically it is *since* P.Trudeau.  So compared to Clark, Mulroney, Chrtien and Martin, what are the biggest examples of government intervention? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 03:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the definition Coyne gives for the proper relationship between government and markets...  I wouldn't mind seeing a column with policy examples where government intervention was appropriately executed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coyne: New research council mandate shows Conservatives hostility to markets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 02:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 01:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  American's can't afford their own goods. So them threatening to cut off a market as big as Canada's would be near suicidal for any business at the moment

It would hurt them immensely, but it wouldn't be suicidal.  For us it would be suicidal.  A big agenda item of the CPC is to divest Canada from its dependence on the American economy.  If new trade agreements with BRIC countries avoids strenuous copyright and IP and helps us achieve that goal, your domestic goal would be realized.  Harper does seem to favour bilateral agreements over things like TPP, so it's a real possibility.

You might find some [inspiration in this story](http://www.npr.org/blogs/money/2013/05/03/180912847/episode-224-the-cotton-wars).  It was all about how Brazil managed to out-maneuver the cotton-lobby in the USA.  If non-IP/Copyright based industries can be encouraged to flex their influence against the entertainment lobby there will be further possibilities for reform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 00:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but to be devil's advocate here.  Well, not really devil, let's say the pragmatist's advocate.  How are you going to advocate to Canadian politicians that the value of your proposed policy reforms to IP and copyright outweighs the vested interests of the US entertainment lobby?

[The USA receives 73% of our exports, and we buy 63% of our imports from them (merchandise, not services)](http://www.statcan.gc.ca/tables-tableaux/sum-som/l01/cst01/trad45a-eng.htm).  The US could simply *threaten* retaliatory action on our goods and services and it would cripple our economy.

I'm not saying your reforms aren't worthwhile or just, but I am saying the scope shouldn't be domestic Canadian policy, but international trade.  Like you said, China, Russia, Brazil and India, the largest emerging economies on the planet have little interest in adhering to western copyright and IP laws.  

If you structure the economic arguments of your policy reforms around achieving free-trade agreements with those countries, enshringing relaxed IP and copyright regulations (rather than TPP and the EU trade deal going on), then you might have a chance.

However, again, to make domestic policy changes in Canada, I'm convinced you first have to make it economically viable for Canada to piss off the USA, which right now is unrealistic, if not impossible.

Canada doesn't want strict IP and copyright.  The bill we ended up getting was actually pretty generous compared to the DMCA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 18:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trade issue is a serious one though.  While I support everything you're working towards, correcting the problem domestically won't be enough.  

Are there any positive economic/trade arguments for more relaxed copyright restrictions?  Apart from strengthening the public domain and spurring more creativity, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 18:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of just making it mandatory, I'd rather that failure to complete the long-form census be associated with a flat tax to incentivize its completion.  To those that value their privacy and dislike the census, that's fine, just accept the monetary cost of your exclusion added to your annual income tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 16:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Money for that research *sometimes* comes from federal grants

Gross domestic expenditures for research and development (GERD) federally in 2010 accounted [for over 20% of all funding](http://www.statcan.gc.ca/tables-tableaux/sum-som/l01/cst01/scte01a-eng.htm).  Provincial funding accounted for ~6%.  Institutions covered ~17% of funding, while business accounted for ~46%.

So, a lot of the money for pure research *does* come from federal grants. More than the two examples you have provided combined.

 The question is whether or not pure research is being done in Canada. The answer is yes, in universities.

The question isn't whether pure research is being done, the question is whether *less* will be done by these policies.  Clearly, if a major source of funding for this work will be further partitioned to business-related research, which already makes up half of all GERD, apparently with limited results, then the answer is yes, less pure research will be conducted.

 or simply income through publishing

Someone needs to show me how I can get paid for publishing...  Get me my Robert Bordens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 04:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost want to say 'no' just so that we have something to discuss, but the closest I can come is 'no brainer'.  Apart from just health and safety benefits that accompany regulation there's also tax revenue.  I'm curious what the median annual income of a sex-worker is and what the loss in income-tax revenue is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 04:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However (summarizing the interesting result in the podcast), Japan and the EU could simply 'threaten retaliation' on unrelated goods and inform those parties in our country.  Lobbyists on behalf of those industries would then contact our government to change our trade policies on those items. 

I don't know if this would work in Canada though, since it sounds like we're pretty pro-tariff lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really interesting to read today after listening to a similar story from NPR Planet Money about a WTO trade dispute between Brazil and the US [regarding cotton](http://www.npr.org/blogs/money/2013/05/03/180912847/episode-224-the-cotton-wars). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 23:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Every university in this country is engaged in pure research

Money for that research often comes from federal grants.  Those grants that previously did not have an 'angle for remuneration' have now had that angle added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  to bring the result of private research and discoveries in the public domain

I'd never stopped to consider that if trade-secrets were the fundamental protection for IP in private research, it would be a big obstruction to the dissemination of new knowledge over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 22:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious what the magnitude of political donations that come from pro-SM groups, and total number of votes for that matter.  It seems weird that there isn't at least one of the big three federal parties suggesting this needs to be ended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 20:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a problem with keeping supply management in the interim, if it's destined to be used as a bargaining chip in international trade negotiations going on right now.  However, will have to wait and see if that's the reality or not.  The way it is now, it's a too regressive force on cost of living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Selley: Big Pizza gets cheaper cheese. We get the crusts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 20:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 19:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The treatise looks like a great read, thanks so much for linking to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The laws of conservation of funding clearly [apply](http://www.explosm.net/comics/3155/).

In all seriousness though, I'm just saying that if the total annual budget for federal research funding remains the same, or is reduced, and at the same time the NRC executive is directed to more strategically direct funding towards 'economically viable research', then some pure research that might have traditionally been granted funding won't occur.  That research is where the accidental eurekas that change the world occur.

Some research doesn't sound so fancy when it's first being proposed.  [Gregor Mendel](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gregor_Mendel) did nothing but make observations of pea-plants for years and it wasn't till after his death that he became famous as the father of genetics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 18:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concede the two options aren't necessarily exclusive. However, in practice the current administration has elected not to fund certain areas of pure research, such as climate and environmental pollution subjects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 18:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Many people like to paint industry as some kind of evil edifice.

I don't think the concern is that business or industry is evil in any way.  The concern is rather that in trying to pursue research from the perspective of getting a payoff at the end of it, that other valuable studies will fail to be conducted because they weren't seen as important enough, or economically beneficial enough.

 Neither of these are mutually exclusive.

They're mutually exclusive since there isn't unlimited funding for all projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 18:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever inspected a facility?  Civil works, mechanical piping, electrical systems, control loops?  Ever seen how high the stack of different drawings there are, the 3D models prepared for even mid-size projects?

Inspection is not easy.  That's why the responsibility for safety is ultimately with the engineer, not the regulator.

The inspectors seem to have made it clear that before the BP spill there was no real concern about backups and shutoffs.

[Deepwater Horizon missed several inspections](http://abcnews.go.com/blogs/politics/2010/05/federal-regulator-repeatedly-failed-to-inspect-deepwater-horizon-including-for-onequarter-of-obama-p/) because the MMS didn't have enough personnel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 18:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with this. Industry R D took a real hit with manufacturing in general over the past few decades across several sectors. The examples of Nortel and Blackberry mentioned above and a lot of biotech as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 18:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  enforcing regulations for the first time in 19 years then

Could be a little more efficient, but better than the error going completely unnoticed until an 'incident'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 17:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, I totally agree with this.  Monoclonal antibodies discovered in 1975 was so far ahead of its time it couldn't even be realistically patented.  Today, they make up a $50B global market of biopharmaceuticals.

However, I feel like a lot of pure research in math and science is conducted and then never applied until decades later, sometimes forgotten in the interim.

The answer isn't to remove funding from basic research to give towards research that appears more economically lucrative.  The answer is increased funding for *applications of research*, where entrepreneurs are given the training and resources to apply novel research to new markets and start new businesses. 

Trying to turn research towards business is a mistake.  Turning business and entrepreneurship towards research would be of greater benefit.

My argument might seem like semantics, but I don't believe it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Research Council now focused on serving business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 17:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Temporary foreign workers hired in areas with EI claimants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 17:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 14:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...to warrant rigorous oversight

Really, you shouldn't need a regulator in the first place to avoid making an unsafe design, that's what the engineers are for.  The NEB doesn't have those kinds of resources.  Engineers have an obligation to protect the public, not to please the regulator. 

However, mistakes happen, no design is perfect. It helps that regulators see all designs from all companies, which help shape their guidelines.

The problem here more realistically, is that Enbridge had a pump-station design that they cookie-cuttered over a hundred times before someone noticed a problem. It's a pretty common issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 03:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuff like this is why I always hate discussion about 'loosening regulations'. Regulation can be made more efficient, but its existence isn't without purpose.

I remember working on a complaint from a regulator about a pipeline project, where the regulator basically had no teeth so the complaint had been ignored for years.  The regulator had noticed a problem on a line (that had already been built and was operating) a major failure possibility that had escaped everyone's notice.  The matter was easily resolved with a half-hour's work and a $50 valve, but it could have been a different story.

Regulators remind me of intelligence agencies in that the public rarely learns of their successes, only their failures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 00:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The leaked [video story](http://globalnews.ca/news/502394/exclusive-video-obtained-by-global-news-reveals-calgary-developers-plan-to-control-city-council/) was from April 22:

 Global News has obtained a recording of a November meeting hosted by Cal Wenzel, founder of Shane Homes. In the video, Wenzel presents a plan to defeat select members of city council who are perceived to be anti-development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nenshi: Its healthy to have a debate about Calgarys growth [Calgary Mayor's OpEd Response to Leaked Global News Video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 00:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enbridge breaks safety rules at pump stations across Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 23:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 20:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You don't need a detailed study to determine that local demand for refined product is at least 1 order of magnitude too small to support a single multi-billion dollar refinery.

I'm assuming your comment is suggesting that the demand for these products is already near to where the existing north american refining capacity is.  

 Who is going to pay for that study? Because it would be a waste of money.

Parliament, April 2012.  Refer to [section 4.2](http://www.parl.gc.ca/Content/LOP/ResearchPublications/2012-27-e.pdf) (pdf) 

Recommend referring to Figure 4.  There seems to be some economic incentives of increased refining in Alberta.  However, it is cheaper (based on the report) to transport crude, rather than refined petroleum products though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 20:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suggesting that if something doesn't exist, it must not be economically viable, because the market would already have produced it sounds too much like a tautology.

 The market should be able to find the most efficient way to extract the oil.

I think you might be failing to consider the role of government as an agent of capital investment in the free market.  The most efficient extraction techniques were derived by [research funded by government as well](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alberta_Oil_Sands_Technology_and_Research_Authority).

The short-term economics might favor simply selling synthetic crude by the Keystone pipeline to refineries in the US, or shipping it to markets in China by Northern-Gateway.  However, the long-term economics may favor Alberta selling fully refined petroleum products.  Furthermore, these two economic strategies are not  mutually exclusive.  The cost of developing new refining capability (and applying new technology developed since the existing refining plants in the US were built) may be too high to easily entreat private capital investment, despite economic opportunity.

Government has the power to be a very big fish in the ocean of capital investment.  It might not be efficient, but it has deep pockets (i.e. taxpayers), that benefit from such strategic investments in a market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 17:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand this article is from 2011 and not currently relevant, but I would like to see an economic cost/benefit breakdown of increasing refining capacity in Alberta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 17:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he change his views after this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we were an [autonomous collective](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=JvKIWjnEPNY#t=50s)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 04:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've misunderstood GMI then. It's only paid out to those below the earnings threshold. Hence the 'reverse income tax' terminology associated with it. Wouldn't make sense to arbitrarily pay everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 03:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spending on social programs that would likely be supplanted or made obsolete by GMI would offset a number of the costs of such a program. Therefore such a policy could be spending-neutral.  Furthermore, Canada already possesses a system for redistributing tax-revenue to low-income earners, so there would be no additional bureaucracy to manage such a system.  The United States similarly maintains the [Earned Income Tax Credit](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Earned_income_tax_credit).

Regarding your math, 27 million Canadians aren't beneath the poverty line.  Rather [9.4% of Canadians fall in that category](http://www.indexmundi.com/canada/population_below_poverty_line.html), therefore your estimate is off likely by a factor of 10.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 19:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guaranteed Minimum Income (GMI) is a really interesting concept tried at [pilot-scale in Canada](http://theglobeandmail.com/news/national/to-end-poverty-guarantee-everyone-in-canada-20000-a-year-but-are-you-willing-to-trust-the-poor/article560885). There's also a conservative Canadian senator, Hugh Segal who's a big proponent of it. His talks on YouTube are great.

**Edit:** Was on my phone earlier, so couldn't add the link to [Hugh Segal's discussion of GMI](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tI-LDQCmW5E). Highly recommend it.

**Edit#2:** Milton Friedman was also a major proponent of GMI, which he referred to as a negative income tax, discussing it [here](http://youtu.be/xtpgkX588nM). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 00:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more I consider a program like this, the more I like it. It gives everyone enough economic independence to safely pursue what they want, whether that's entrepreneurship or some other creative enterprise. 

The argument against a program like this is "What will motivate people to do anything if you just hand them a payday."  I hate this argument, because it stereotypes disadvantaged people as lazy, when in reality they can't afford to go after riskier ventures, because it's too dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 18:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or coupon's for vehicle registration/insurance premiums; avoid the taking and giving back and get the insurance companies/service-Ontario to manage it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 16:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I support the use of tolls as a disincentive to traffic congestion and to fund better infrastructure. However, I think it would be important to include a tax rebate system for lower-income families so that there isn't a regressive element to its implementation.

The cost of using public transportation is also too high compared to owning a vehicle, and service is too restricted to get by using it; further contributing to congestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 23:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought...  was it just there wasn't enough public consultation, or was it just a bad place to put them in the first place?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 21:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why were these gas plants cancelled again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scrapped Oakville, Ont., power plant to cost $310M [ON] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 21:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 20:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they have it backwards, the comment scores shouldn't be hidden at the beginning, rather there should be a 'ceiling' value that a comment can receive with respect to the median comment score for an entire thread.

The comment can still be upvoted to infinity for karma addicts, but the posted score on the thread has an upper limit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 20:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured this much as well, though I'm curious how many of these activities Canada is actively engaging in, particularly with respect to Afghanistan.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada can't account for $3.1B in anti-terror funding, AG finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 16:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 04:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're describing an integration of 'on demand streaming' with all potential video-related content without being device-specific.  It does seem like an inevitable result of where things are heading...

I've been giving some thought to this lately, because of the major problem with monetizing streaming and 'on demand' services.  Google seems to have finally achieved [strong revenues from YouTube](http://www.forbes.com/sites/connieguglielmo/2013/04/18/google-reports-first-quarter-profit-that-tops-analyst-estimates-shares-rise-live/), but for a long time the story was that they were losing money propping up the service.  

I think the major problem is that you can't staple boring content (ads) to interesting content and expect people to pay attention when it's not a passive service like tv.

I think a future online business model is going to be a marketplace where instead of having interesting content supported by ads, the content itself will be ads, which will be user-generated.  Content-creators will be rewarded (much like how YouTube does it now), for creating far more effective ads than the ones currently designed.

Look at how much motive there is just on reddit to accumulate fake internet points (karma), if users received monetary rewards for the content they linked and that content was interesting in its own right despite advertising some product or service, you would see very different behaviours.  I guess that's already true to an extent with some of the ads in reddit that look like posts and are usually for amazon content, with some ads getting voted up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 03:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the difference be exactly?  (I've only been following the CRTC stuff peripherally).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vic Toews' office overruled Omar Khadr prison interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 19:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Kingsmith: The Slow and Painful Death of Freedom in Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 17:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up, I was wondering why I kept accidentally reposting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former budget watchdog called 'partisan' by government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 06:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree that he needs to respond, but not necessarily about the ads.  Doing so would allow the Tories maintain control of the conversation.  Trudeau needs to change the conversation and put his opponents off balance. 

Furthermore, TV-spots and mailers are old media and will only reach defined demographics.  He needs to better leverage social-media and put out something that's going to get passed around and shared.  Build more of a following around himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 06:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to believe it's possible, in a non Clockwork Orange sort of way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 05:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will be from a justice point of view; however, alone it will just provide incentive to do the same acts but without getting caught.

Preventative policy I would argue could have a broader age-range.  Since teaching parents would be just as important as youth.  Teaching and instruction of appropriate behaviour.  Institutionalizing empathy.  

If we were in a society where that kind of education was already in place, I believe the response to these political ads would be more than simply a general discomfort, but outright rejection.  The actual response shows how far we still have to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 05:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel the approaches will need to be different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 05:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and one of the things we're learning is just how different the non-adult brain is.

I can totally appreciate that.  It sounds like we both agree regarding dehumanizing activities, but depart at labels. 

Recognizing separate activities as both being acts of social violence shouldn't at all equate the seriousness of their direct consequences to victims involved.  

However, addressing 'root causes' is important for applying corrective action.  Will the policy put forward be to just put kids in jail, or to [teach them](http://www.guardian.co.uk/media/2012/dec/26/twitter-facebook-school-libel-lessons) years in advance to recognize certain behaviours as being explicitly wrong?  Our entire discussion-thread in a way has been a microcosm of the larger political dialogue that's been happening (more so regarding terrorism, not yet bullying, but it could likely head in that direction in the coming weeks). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mr. Harper is not posting all over Mr. Trudeau's facebook account. He's not messaging all of Mr. Trudeau's friends about what a loser he is.

No, he's messaging half of Canada suggesting what a loser he is. (paraphrasing, but not that far off the mark)

Your anecdotes and these ads both represent attempts to demolish a human being to gain power.  The motivations are the same, and that is what needs to be combated regardless of how old the people involved are.

I'm not denying the seriousness of bullying, I'm arguing that the range of the behaviour is wider than you're giving it credit, and tolerating it anywhere is inappropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 04:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Using the same word for both unavoidably minimizes the seriousness of bullying.

I don't want to minimize the seriousness of bullying, but it's not apples and oranges. The psychology is the same.  To tolerate one in a civilized society and say "well that's what politicians sign up for," while decrying the harassment and isolation that youth go through, is hypocritical.

Bullying continues after highschool.  It happens in the workplace, in families.

It's poisonous for everyone.  Youth have the worst of it, there's no denying that, but you can't fix half the problem and expect to get anywhere.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 03:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the contrary, I don't think bullying is ever going to go back to a marginalizing "kids will be kids" sentiment.  Rather, in getting serious about those issues within our society, it might lead to the public being more reflective on what is appropriate for communication between adults, particularly from public officials.  

It wasn't too long ago, I remember seeing[ Elizabeth May getting shouted down](http://youtu.be/Ga8c0Hd6oCo) during question period, unable to finish her question.  I think most people came away from that and similar situations saying "well MPs will be MPs," and "that's how it's always been," and the whole business about three sword-lengths distance between the seats.  

A lot of it really isn't appropriate though...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 02:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, if negative political ads can somehow fall under the umbrella of "bullying" in the public's perception, that would be a very interesting development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trudeau ads not bullying, just part of debate, says PM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 02:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trudeau To Labrador Byelection Voters: Reject Conservative Politics Of 'Division' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 17:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 06:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Premise:  The ELA is being shut down not for economic reasons, or for performing research that's beyond the scope/mandate of the DFO, but as a response to ELA founder David Schindler's persistent and public criticism of the water-usage and downstream impacts of oil sands extraction and upgrading processes.

Argument: The economic reasoning for closing the ELA is fairly poor.  The operating costs for the station are relatively low, [$2M/year](http://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2013/03/19/experimental-lakes-area-tories-scientists_n_2910022.html).  Wheras the cost of closing and decommissioning the ELA is comparatively exorbitant [in excess of $25M](http://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/story/2012/06/15/pol-experimental-lakes-area-budget-cuts.html).

Add to this expense the reputation-cost to Canada of closing it.  It makes us look bad, because it's more than just government research up there, they're halting experiments for [international researchers](http://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/story/2013/03/20/pol-ela-scientists-contact-dfo-for-closure-confirmation.html) and a ton of their grad-students by doing this.  So why do it?  Middle of nowhere, relatively low operational cost, few active on-site personnel... 

The founder of the ELA is a world-renowned scientist, David Schindler.  He's highly respected, and probably one of the most vocal critics of [water-usage by oilsands operations](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/story/2010/10/15/f-david-schindler.html).  

Prof. Britt Hall, an associate professor of biogeochemistry at the University of Regina:
 *"The fact that demolition work has started on cabins at the ELA site is a sign the federal government is not trying in good faith to find a new operator."*  

The criticism seems to be that negotiations are slow, secretive, and [not being made in good faith](http://www.winnipegfreepress.com/local/doubt-real-effort-to-get-new-operator-200996581.html).  The DFO maintains its line that the [ELA doesnt fit within their mandate](http://www.kenoradailyminerandnews.com/2012/10/19/environment-canada-urged-to-take-on-ela), but the political capital being spent to weather shutting this station down is becoming significant.

Despite all this though, I think the CPC is going to look at this as a way out, while still saving face.  They know otherwise it's not going to go away and the media is going to keep hitting them with a sob-story that is going to stink to a lot of voters and it's time to get some distance from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 23:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answered this [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1czgjt/what_stupid_high_school_drama_do_you_still/c9ln60j)

* for the non-clickers, expulsion and wasn't allowed to write his final exams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 19:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't appear to be a done deal yet, have to wait and see if Dept. of Fisheries and Oceans drags their feet on negotiations or allows ON and MB to take over administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 18:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she regretted it. She was on the verge of losing it laughing the whole rest of class. Especially when my friend got in and related pandaemonium going on in the cafeteria.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 17:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole scene just replayed in my mind in slow motion to the Marriage of Figaro.  Fits. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 17:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  I'm willing to bet it's a prank been done a few times though, those student-produced video announcements were begging for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 17:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twelfth Night :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
