<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike and Dave - I went into it prepared to turn it off if it came to it, the scene when their parents visit their place had me extremely close then the introduction to Aubrey Plaza   Kendricks characters elevated the movie which eventually kept getting better. I was also a fan of DeVine from workaholics going into it, so actors I like give me no reason to sit through terribleness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why there are 5 transformers movies and a heap of spinoffs/sequals coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 10:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> only god forgives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No love for the grudge 1   2?

Otherwise hostel freaks me out, it's easy for people to lower their judgements and make bad decisions on holiday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 00:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome movie, this would be somewhere in my top 10 for the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're totally right, alot of what you said is spot on. 

i think though you can extend my statement to other movies in general too...

 for instance my brother in law he typically watches blockbuster style movies   whats in the new release section of his dvd store. The other day he was going through my hard drive with movies he has not seen 85% of and lands on prometheus and says I love that movie let's put it on... he'd rather watch prometheus multiple times than take a chance on something like green room, the witch etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man i'd say it's plain good, really entertaining satire of cabin horror movies.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> charlies farm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOTR

Pusher

Indiana Jones

Taken.... lol jk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what i think big budget video game movies suffer from.

The checklist of tentpoleness handed down to whoever the director is.

- Must be PG13 so the kiddies can pay to watch it.

- Dumb it down so kids in the Philippines can follow along.

- Add forced humor, shoehorn a love interest.

- No practical effects, CGI all the way.

- We need to be able to sell toys, no scary character designs... if needeed make mongoloids like doomsday.

and pretty much whatever is birthed from such a checklist will turn out garbage... best hope would be a indie filmmaker who's a fan of the source with a 10-20mil budget and having creative control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the wailing blew my mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the secret life of pets = toy story but with animals instead... exact same plot.

it's too bad most cinema-goers want familiarity and will rather see something safe over taking a chance on something like kubo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> swiss army man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man i love that movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movie: Valhalla Rising - You can just sit back and take it all in, the imagery and intensity is hardcore.

Actor: Jack Black in "The D Train" - He was unreal, after the movie settles in I completely lose track that this is a  character... played by a comedic actor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 10:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i work at a liquor store and my excuse is always "product knowledge" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hooker has got to be the least productive position in the NRL the recent newbies lichaa/cherrington/mcinnes have all been inadequate except for parcell. 

Parcell IMO should be deserving of big money if he has another solid season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because if he's good and goes pro you can mooch of his money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't get me wrong he went good, just he would have went into the season as a big favorite for rookie of the year at a key position in a team that finished minor prems three years in a row.

eventually being moved to the wing was a telltale indicator he wasn't ready yet at fullback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latrell Mitchell hands down, he's gonna be a beast eventually but the way experts were talking him up after his world club challenge performance... to say the least he did not make an immediate impact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 07:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes no i do have a life and miss games, but it's nice to see weekly/season rankings of who had a blinder or stunk.

and yes there are good players that are not fantasy relevant and I still recognize them as good/great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just a heads up he killed it in fantasy this year, he's also IRL a clutch player who wins games at the death.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they signed really well, have awesome depth, finished off last year hard and have unearthed some freaks... Cleary, Fisher Harris... maybe Martin.

They are top 8 certainties, top 4 hopes IMO... but I do have doubts they can make it to the GF on the back of such young and inexperienced halves if they with martin instead of carty. Finals pressure is a different beast and they need this years experience under the belt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 07:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahh the poor mans feleti mateo, which after his good form became the rich mans feleti mateo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 07:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was my favorite players growing up, that cutout ball he'd throw in front of his backrower   centre into the hands of the winger that strolls over for a try along the sideline was wizardry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was good though for the couple of years at souths, which got him into rep sides... its just he was not able to sustain it.

Tim Smith however was like JT in his rookie season then dissapeared.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense but your roster is one of the worst in the comp, this was a bit of wishful thinking since the knights are terrible and tigers/dragons are also in the running for the spoon.

http://imgur.com/a/E1OdK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your right about parker, wallace too. Will disagree on your assessment of thaiday and our halves in fact since 2015 they've been awesome together ask anyone who plays fantasy. 

Our mix of experience and youth is a good balance even with parker and wallace gone. Gillett, Thaiday, Glenn, Mcguire, Blair - Sua, Pangai JR, Arrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'd say the cowboys are more of a shot at missing the 8 alltogether than the broncos... granville and coote who were instrumental in 2015 had poor seasons last year as well as the depleted prop options so when scott comes of for his rest they will be vulnerable.

We are practically unchanged from last year except that our young bench/fringe player studs are all the better from the experience and we have awesome depth all around to cover origin/injuries and rack up wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is probably the best h2h matchup theres been in the allstars to date, i'm going to have to give the nod to the world team though. That backline is fierce, as are the rest of the selections apart from myles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dreamworld tickets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grasshoppers... i tend to keep from cream based cocktails in warmer weather cause it stucks being stuck in the toilet and getting all sweaty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no way... i'll keep this in mind the next time i'm about to shit myslf and if it works for me...my god sir thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 09:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'll actually try this when iv'e got a day off, thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to do with pernod? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 09:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a liquor store and bought the only two bottles we had in stock at half price $25aud. I saw its 40% and went why not.

It's so weird that it doesn't go well with much and is quite overpowering... not saying it's bad. I tried a mojito with 60ml and it overpowered the bitters/mint/lime. Only delightful drink ive made with it is lemonade, lemon lime bitters cordial syrup, gin, pernod, parfait amour.

Anything I can put it to good use in?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jordan Mcleans finishing move would be the neckbreaker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 09:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> become a craigslist escort?

26yo Athletic Hooker for service, have 6 years experience hooking in Australia   England and am considered a stud among fantasy circles. Can go for 80mins without a break.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, just a good example would be the aus test team... they could realistically go with any of boyd, tedesco, hayne, GI, slater, barba, munster or moylan at fullback and they would do a tremendous job... no need to pull out someone from the super league ever unless a god tier guy like smith/jt or something are there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 11:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She isn't even hot, she knew jack about footy and was surprisingly a non-contributor on the panel unless mimicking whatever the other guys on the panel say to cover her ass.  

I don't get why everyone on reddit has a boner for her, i'd rather tap raelene castle.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> facebook stalking jack de belin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats definately a good move, but robson always gets the nod as first choice for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
