<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 18:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! It took years before my husband and I could get her Mom to work with us. We still have issues, but it's much better now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 18:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have had Barred Rocks, and want to get 50/50 BR's and EE's when we get the new coop done. The BR's were pretty tame and would follow us around the yard like dogs. I hope the EE's are as friendly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 18:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope you guys and the Babymum can get on the same page. I have been there with mu stepdaughter's Mom and so much outside drama can get pulled into that stuff! Best of luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 17:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite Arizona street name so far is Dead Bear Draw. Dirt road up a canyon between Hereford and Palominas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 17:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best advice is to keep it short and sweet. When a situation like this comes up address it in a casual way, giving age appropriate details like "that's not a tail, silly. Boys have different parts in their underwear than girls" then if this leads to another question, answer that one. Building things like that up into The Talk just makes everyone uncomfortable. Same thing with "stranger danger", why their private parts are private, We have ongoing conversations instead of A Talk. My kids are 4 and 8 and they feel comfortable asking me and my Hubs anything, because their questions are just answered with no fanfare. It's only hard if you build it up in your head. Best of luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 17:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is gorgeous! I am hoping to get some EE's in the next month. I think they will be fun for the kids to see how they pattern out and what color eggs they end up laying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Animal Crossing Game Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 20:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Xbox  Minecraft Game Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Gaming Mommies @ RTX 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 20:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  World of Warcraft Patch 5.4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 20:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 01:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We felt strongly because he was a loudmouth douche. The defense does not have the burden of proving innocence,  they just have to prove doubt. The defense in the case proved reasonable doubt. The prosecution left too many questions open to interpretation. In our system you must convict on evidence and whether there is reasonable doubt. You cannot convict someone for being a douche, or he would be in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 19:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a lawyer and this will get buried, but here goes. I was foreperson on a jury for a rape case in about 2006. Everyone on the jury thought the accused was guilty, but the guy had a great lawyer and the prosecution just flat dropped the ball. We had little choice but to find him not guilty.

 As we were all leaving the courtroom, the defendant started yelling across the lobby about, bragging that he knew we would let him off. As the bailiffs ushered him away from us, I happened to get into the elevator with the prosecutors.

They asked me why we found him not guilty and I flat unloaded on them, telling them that we jurors had to live with letting a rapist walk free because they were incompetent. When the elevator opened, the rest of the jury members were waiting on me, since they were worried when their elevator left with me still in the upper lobby with the ranting rapist, and were stunned when the now sheepish prosecutors got off my elevator car. 

I think about that poor woman often, and wish I could express my shame that I had to be a part of the legal process that denied she was raped and let an arrogant, rapist pig of a man get away with it.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-post from /r/gamingmommies Raising Girl Gamers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 18:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Raising Girl Gamers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 18:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  ORIGIN: Spirits of the Past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  A Different Take on Zombies: World War Z Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  The Orange Rhino Challange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Dungeon   Dragons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wine   Mine: Ep. #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 17:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4th of July with the Gaming Mommies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 17:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  RTX Countdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 23:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Web Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 19:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Humble Bundle 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 19:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Obsidian (Lux Series #1) Book Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 19:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Potty Training: Grab the Carpet Steamer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 01:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies now has a subreddit for any gaming parents out there! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 05:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just wanted to invite you to Gaming Mommies new subreddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 04:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Events for July 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 04:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Tutorial: crochet a Cthulhu dice bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 04:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Mommy with a side of geek- staying fit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 04:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a thanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 19:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had to cancel our road trip, but for the awesome reason we are renting a house with an acre of land! Thanks everyone for your tips and advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey bloggers of Reddit, How have you taken your blog from a hobby to Internet Famous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 02:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been blogging on and off for about 4 years, just for fun, but I'm wanting to get more serious/professional about it. I would love any input from those who have turned their blog into any kind of paycheck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 05:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry! My family is just getting over a rough year and I want to give my kids a super awesome trip to remember. I am going to drive and camp from Arizona to Indiana, stay for a week to visit family and friends, then my step daughter will join us for the trip back. We are going to camp and visit state parks like the Blue Hole in New Mexico and visit Crater of Diamonds in Arkansas. We are leaving June 17 and I'm planning a 3 week round trip. I'm trying to raise money to replace a few items of camping equipment and for the trip itself (gas, food, camping fees) I am more than happy to provide any info and will post pics and update from the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 22:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very often see a pick-up with the Obama thing in huge letters across the tailgate at my local Wal-Mart, also with handicap plates. I wonder if they're related? Also, for some reason, it also has big polka-dots all over it....so it's a festive call for impeachment at least! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 22:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I just want to shake people like that and scream at them "Do you actually think if I could get over it, I would choose to continue being a miserable, awkward, shell of a person?" Fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a colossal asshat. Fuck him, we are fucking proud as balls of you. Sorry for the language, I'm having a bad week and don't like stupid, mean people!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 03:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last four years of my life have totally destroyed me to the point I don't even recognize myself. I have hours where I almost act like the person I once was, but it's smoke and mirrors. I miss who I used to be, and I hate the person I am now. I feel like I died and all my time is spent mourning myself, I'm so sorry that you know how that feels. I don't know how we get back, but I hope we can. Internet hugs, fellow drifter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 01:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gorgeous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would appreciate it if you could spread the word for my GoFundMe campaign to raise money for my epic road trip with my kids! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 00:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [HERE](http://www.gofundme.com/2p2xbk) is the info. Thanks, guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend told her son he had to wrap her birthday gift... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 21:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 02:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well sleeping is not an issue.

Umm...
 Slept very little last night and new pup is driving me crazy.

If you want to return a puppy for acting like a puppy and/or having distemper then you should. You are not a responsible dog owner. It's not your fault, not everyone is cut out for dog ownership.
*ninja edit for formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mojo explains CPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 17:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mojo Explains CPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 21:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thursday healing list/Reiki share. Who needs some love? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 16:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 02:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the reigning champ of that shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 02:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often think of my childhood and wonder how I survived. I was generally unsupervised (in a benevolent, small town in the 70's-80's way) and it boggles the mind how many things could have happened. I would ride my bike miles out into the country, without telling anyone I left, would play in the creek or overgrown fields alone, break into abandoned houses, and once broke into the recently burned down Jr High building. All the shit I would have a heart attack if my kids did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 02:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really needed that today, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 02:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are in south east Arizona  and taking the northern route there. We are stopping in Santa Rosa to camp at the Blue Hole the 1st night. The rest is up to how far we want to drive each day. I am shooting for a fun trip over making good time. My Mom has offered to get us a hotel any night the weather is bad, or I just want a bed and air conditioning.

We are headed to north central Indiana, but stopping in Terre Haute for an overnight with friends there. On the way back, I want to go the southern route through Memphis, then Arkansas to Crater of Diamonds. Beyond that I am open to suggestion. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to take my girls on an epic road trip this summer! I could use some help preparing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 23:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am taking my girls from Arizona to Indiana in late June to pick up their older sister and bring her back to Arizona for the summer. I plan on taking 4 days to drive out, camping at state parks along the way, then spending a week in Indiana to see family and fiends before taking another route back. I could use any advice, from road trip tips to advice on camping gear. I also have a [GoFundMe](http://www.gofundme.com/2p2xbk) campaign to raise money for the trip, and would love any advice on promoting it without coming across like I'm begging. My girls and I just really need something positive to look forward to and plan for. I will be [blogging](http://www.hippie-witch.blogspot.com) about the trip for anyone interested. Thanks guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 03:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that stuff! We used to live near the worlds largest ball of paint. We all have certificates somewhere saying we painted whatever number coat of paint on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than the quiet game, what do you suggest for games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish we could but we are in south east Arizona and its a full day to Sedona. I want to get there sometime this year though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We live in bear/wolf country, so that's covered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm planning an epic road trip with my girls, driving and camping from Arizona to Indiana to kick off the summer! Any tips or advice you can offer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 02:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My stepdaughter is coming to stay the summer with us as usual, and I thought it would be fun for her sisters and I, along with my dog Mal, to drive out and get her. My plan at the moment is to take 4 days to drive out, camping at cool state parks on the route, spend a few days visiting family and friends in Indiana, then an alternate route home. My girls are 3, 8, and 13. Any and all advice is appreciated,  as this will be my first solo road trip with the kids due to my husband having to work. Thanks, Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 06:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, sorry  it's (hippie-witch.blogspot.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope to be that classy when we are older! My Dad has dementia and it is interesting the things that are still hidden in there.Much love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 05:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 03:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it! Do you have the pattern, my stepdaughter loves frogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 03:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's French, so it's Le Meatball!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 03:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tell my kids this when they bring me chewed up toys. I have provided places to store toys that are high up and the dogs can't get too, but they leave it on the floor and boom, Mal (Australian Shepard) thinks it's now his toy.
Same with putting down food/drink and walking away. Bruno (Toy Poodle) is like a ninja. He can be dead asleep, but some poodle-fu wakes him to alert him to unattended food and he is wolfing it down with alarming speed, then the girls cry because he ate their food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 03:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 03:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I with I had figured this out like 20 years ago...so much of my life fighting frizz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 03:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just regret I was 37-38 before I figured my hair out :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 01:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run my fingers or a wide tooth shower comb through it, wet down with a spray bottle and let dry them just fluff the roots up with my fingers. I have found that the more hydrated my hair is the less I have to baby it, so once you embrace oil, both your own natural oil from your scalp and adding oils like argan, olive, coconut etc you don't have to be so careful and the curl stays after you mess with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 01:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me a few years of the CG method to work up to 5-6 days between </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 01:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 23:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. People get weird when I say I only "wash " every 5-6 days but the less I mess with it the better it looks. Also, my Mom is a retired hairdresser and was so grossed out about the coconut oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because it has come up a few times in the past few days,my 5th day curls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 18:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 18:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen a similar injury happen and it is the reason we will never own a trampoline. My husband thinks I'm just being ridiculous, I need to show him this pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 04:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 03:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> before you co-wash, put coconut oil in your hair and put it up in a bun for a while, then co-wash well and put in some conditioner to leave in and/or dress your wet hair with gel/argan oil/a **little** coconut oil. The days you don't wash, follow the other awesome tips.My hair type is the same and I only condition it every 5-6 days. The rest of the time I do the spray bottle, finger combing to get out tangles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am relaunching the Healing List on my blog(x-post from /r/wicca </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 02:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am relaunching the Healing List on my blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 02:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you or anyone you know needs prayer, healing, or just a little love and light, please let me know in the comments so that I can add them to my Thursday healing list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 02:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to post you two on my Reiki list on my blog tomorrow. I am losing my Dad slowly to Alzheimer's and I can empathize. Much love, sweetie, you are not in this alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 01:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sending Reiki and prayers, for you and him. Brightest Blessings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 07:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice, solid starter home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 07:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a few of those last time I was in Bisbee, about a month ago. My kids asked me what I was laughing at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 07:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have declined to mentor minors because I feel only an adult can make adult decisions such as what faith they are called to. That being said, my husband and I are raising our kids Pagan, but make it clear that there are many different Paths and if they choose another faith later in life we will support them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 06:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 06:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a similar dream, but in mine the school realizes I should not have graduated and I have to repeat high school. I am 38 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 17:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am living in an RV at the moment. We got it dirt cheap and have been slowly renovating it. We will be in the RV for the next 2-8 months while we are preparing to buy a small house/land and plan to make it a guest house/kids room when we get to that point. Our long term plan is to have a "compound" of several small structures on a property.

The older RV's have fewer "extra systems"to be maintained, as well as fewer bells and whistles as far as design and floor plan,so less to rip out or change to get to your intended plan for it. We have a 1979 Allegro. It needs work to be reliable as far as driving, but we only plan to move it once to our future home site, so that is not a priority. We converted the tub to storage, and will be restoring the loft bed over the driving cabin that the previous owners took down for my stepdaughter when she comes for the summer.

I have seen a lot of Tiny House features that we plan to use as we renovate the RV to make it more livable and user friendly, and after 2 months with us all (5) here, we are getting a practical sense of what really works for us, and what only seemed good in theory.

 My advice would be to keep an eye on Craigslist and buy an older RV that is structurally sound and get to work. If nothing else,you can use the RV as a learning process to see what your practical needs are when you build a Tiny House. Best of luck to you, and I hope this helps in your planning!

Just FYI, here are some pics. The changes here are mostly cosmetic, but you can get some idea. We are going for a Gypsy Vardo theme, so be warned of bright colors!
[Allegro before](http://imgur.com/a/Bz7bw)
[The Vardo](http://imgur.com/a/lhzpH) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 19:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! We live in a rural area now and have found a nice house on a great little piece of land. I stumbled upon the program. I didn't know it existed 2 weeks ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 22:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the color. I love the whole look!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 17:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3b/c, thick coarse, shoulder length. I used to have a lot of oily issues, but can now go with once a week-ish co-washing or baking soda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 07:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's magnificent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 07:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go 5-6 days as well. I just use water and lavender oil in a spray bottle. I comb out tangles with fingers or a wide tooth shower type comb, spray, scrunch, and go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 01:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, "make-up". Sir, can you show me where the mean lady hurt you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 22:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was my thought too
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. There are a lot of movie adaptations that just pulled out the names of the characters and threw the rest of the book in the trash. They do not deserve to be on the cover of the original work, which they obviously have no regard for, no do they give two shits for the original fan base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 20:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know someone who has yet to learn this lesson. 11+ years of going to court over custody/support issues and she still does not understand part of the reason the judge does not respect her is because she is dressed like a homeless lumberjack, does not stand when asked by the court, talked back to the judge, or even over the judge speaking using swear words. The other part of the no respect is that she refuses to get a job, takes her baby-daddy to court 2x a year to get support raised every year because she refuses to get a job, and got caught in welfare/food stamp fraud, but that's another story.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 19:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes I think so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://hippie-witch.blogspot.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 04:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a public blog. Don't want to seem like I'm plugging it, so I wont put a link but the blog is my user name. I've had it for a few years but stopped posting for a while. Trying to get back into the routine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 02:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in a bad place and I am making myself blog every day, and trying to do one spiritually positive thing every day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone here have experience with USDA Section 502 loans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 00:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been looking through our options and this seems to be a fit for us. Just curious about any advice from someone familiar with this program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 06:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a date in highschool the guy asked me "So, are we gonna fuck or what?" It was our 2nd (and last) date and we had barely gotten 5 blocks from him picking me up. I had him take me right back home and he grumbled that I was a bitch on the way back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
