<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8089</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oy vey iz mir...so now you think I should *cook* for you?

(Sorry, you triggered my inner Jewish mother.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan (of beans *or* barley, really).  We can still be friends, though, because you can have all of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I don't want to minimize work done by teachers, 

I believe you, but a lot of people actively do.

 but the job market today is more competitive than post WW2 America. Gone are the union jobs that make enough money to own a home and retire by 50. Those just don't exist.

For better or worse, you are 100% correct about this.  However, I'll point out that -- at least in the deeply red part of the very blue state where I live -- people who come from families where those good union jobs were **blue-collar** (coal mining, steel production, etc.) feel absolutely entitled to the return of those jobs, no matter how unrealistic it might be.  There is an angry, stubborn unwillingness to admit that the prosperity enjoyed by most Americans in the post-WWII was an unsustainable blip that simply isn't coming back.  In addition, a huge part of what got our current president elected was his pandering to the wholly irrational idea that these people are correct in their delusional belief that they A) deserve to make an income that will support a family of 4 on what is actually semi-skilled labor and that B) there is any chance entire industries will ever return such jobs to the U.S. in significant numbers. Those same people, however, want to cut pay and benefits for teachers (who are objectively trained professionals) and shout loudly about how teachers don't deserve the comparatively meager pay they already receive.  The hypocrisy is stomach-turning.

 Every profession is difficult and requires people to go above and beyond, especially those that pay a decent wage.

That's also true, but it's more of a commentary on how corporatism has eroded Americans' expectations about work-life balance, not one on teaching.  If you examine how much "above and beyond" goes on across professions, I think you would find that teachers *easily* come out near the top, even *before* you consider how little they earn compared with others whose work requires similar education, training, higher order thinking, and responsibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only to the extent that they are flattering reflections on him.

Like all narcissists, he is incapable of genuinely caring for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Latkes](http://toriavey.com/images/2011/11/Yukon-Gold-Latkes-Wide-3-640x480.jpg) (Jewish potato pancakes). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Maryland and it *is* different here.  Our teachers work 10 months, usually from the 2nd week of August through the 3rd week of June each year. Christmas break ranges from one week - 10 days, not 2-3 weeks.  Also, it's important to remember that teachers usually work at least 2 weeks before and 1 week after the students' school year, so you shouldn't use the student school calendar as a basis to determine how many weeks teachers work.

I don't know a single teacher that doesn't acknowledge how nice it is to have substantial time off each year, but what I *have* noticed is that people far too often ignore or deny the fact that most teachers **more** than make up for any hours not worked over their summer "vacations" by the amount of uncompensated time they spend working before and after the school day, both on campus and at home.

In addition, people rarely talk about how teachers, who make comparatively little money for their work, also end up spending far more out of pocket to purchase equipment and supplies needed for their work than do people in other professions.  Sure, they can deduct those expenses on their tax returns if they itemize, but the standard deduction for teachers whose situations make itemizing inadvisable is only $250/year, when most teachers easily spend 4-5x that amount.

Maybe this wasn't true for your mother, but most teachers aren't immune to the grind you mention.  Almost every teacher I know works a part-time job during the year and/or works a summer job during that summer break you are so envious of...because they don't really make enough to live on their teacher's salary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, but...he's 70. And if there's anyone in the history of the world that gave fewer fucks about the world he would leave behind as long as he gets his, I certainly can't think of who that would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only kinda-sorta, and this is very much dependent on what state you are in.  There has been a lot of talk about linking teacher compensation to student performance, but it hasn't been implemented in very many places yet.

Rather (at least in the public school system), your pay depends almost entirely on what state and within that, what county, you teach in.  From there, it depends on your highest level of education attained and years of service.

Schools can suffer sanctions (such as takeover by the state) for failing to meet certain standards, but rarely is individual teacher pay impacted by such failures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to cherry pick your statistics.  Massachusetts has the *highest* pay scale for teachers among all U.S. states.

It is absolutely not a "part-time job."  It is a more than full-time job for less than full-time pay in most states.

And I don't know what you think it means to "teach a curriculum," but there is so much more to education than merely being told what must be learned by the students.  Lesson planning, creating formative and summative assessments, handling discipline, differentiating instruction for students at different ability and grade levels, making accommodations and modifications for students with various disabilities, completing administrative and reporting tasks, participating in parent conferences, IEP, and 504 meetings...that's just the *beginning*.

There is so much to teaching that people don't know about, care about, or understand.  The implication that teachers somehow deserve less, not more, than they receive relative to other professions is simply wrong, and a disgraceful sign of what too many people in the U.S. have as their priorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not uncompensated, they don't.  People in professions (or exempt positions) where those types of hours are the norm are making *a lot* more than the average teacher does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teachers typically work 10 months out of the year, not 9.  In addition, while they are required to be physically on campus for 7-8 hours per day, the average teacher either puts in several additional hours at work per day, or does an equivalent amount of work at home.  This means that in those 10 months, the average teacher works far more than the typical number of hours attributable to a full-time employee in virtually any other profession.  To top it off, very few teachers actually take a vacation during the summer months; instead, because they are barely paid a living wage, they typically work a summer job, and often a part-time job during the school year as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm...only half joking...how hard is it for those with U.S. degrees/certifications to move to Australia to teach?

Because in Maryland, where I am (a state that pays its teachers relatively **well**), the starting salary for a new teacher with a bachelor's degree ranges from $41,126 - $48,528.  If you stay in the system and continue to obtain additional education, the pay does go up substantially, but it takes a looong time.  In addition, the **maximum** pay for a teacher with a PhD,regardless of years of service, ranges from $72,579 - $112,743, with the vast majority capping out in the mid-$80k's.

To give some context, teachers in most other U.S. states are envious of those who manage to get into Maryland's system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to this, an important indicator of how much respect a society has for a given profession is the typical remuneration for that profession.

The enormous disparity between teachers' salaries and those of other professions requiring a similar level of responsibility and professional expertise is a direct reflection of how little respect teachers actually get in the U.S...whatever lip service is paid to the contrary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a link to to the wiki**quote** page for *Good Morning, Vietnam*, specifically this quote:

 The Mississippi River broke through a protective dike today. What is a protective dike? Is that a large woman standing near the river going [in Butch voice] "Don't go near there!" [in Girly voice] "But Betty-" [in Butch voice] "Don't go near there! Get away from the river! Stay away from there." I know, we can't use the word "dyke." You can't even say "lesbian", it's **"women in comfortable shoes."** Thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like ["women in comfortable shoes"](https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Good_Morning,_Vietnam) comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My shoes are super comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be so much higher.  His efforts to delegitimize the press are a direct assault on one of the most fundamental checks on executive branch power.  It's a play right out of Aristotle's *Politics*...touching on all of the 3 major ways that a tyrant maintains his rule, *i.e.*, destroy high thoughts, foment distrust among the people, and attenuate the people's capacity for action.  

It's even more sinister than appointing an enemy of public education like Betsy DeVos to head the Dept of Education or an enemy of environmental protection such as Scott Pruitt to head the EPA.

EDIT: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was 1993.  IIRC, the "base salary" was $32/shift flat rate plus bonus for being so much over quota and/or getting people to put their contributions on a credit card.

Because it was a flat rate rather than hourly, it ended up working out to less than minimum wage when you counted all the time not spent canvassing (training/traveling/closing out). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First correct-ish guess!  Not CWA itself, but a sister organization that had a couple of offices, one of which shared CWA's HQ in Minneapolis.  It was called CLEC Canvass Network, and it was intertwined with the genesis of CWA. I think sometime well after I left in 1997, the name changed to Progressive Action Network or some such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close.  Human Rights Campaign.  (Formerly the Human Rights Campaign Fund.)  It's one of the oldest and largest LGBT rights organizations in the U.S., but it's not universally well-liked within the LGBT community for a wide variety of reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Please** let me clarify.  I am *not* talking about get out the vote (GOTV) canvassing.  That shit is great, and to this day I volunteer to do it for worthy candidates/campaigns.  You are 100% right about it being not only one of the most effective methods of grassroots organizing, but the one that is most accessible to the greatest number of regular people who might seek elected office.

The sliminess I'm talking about is really confined to *fundraising*, especially when it is conducted by third-party organizations or those that exist only in order to sustain their own fundraising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've mentioned elsewhere in this thread, I only field canvassed for a few months, but I phone canvassed for the same organization for nearly 4 years.  I'm almost ashamed to admit that I was successful enough at it that they promoted me to "Phone Manager" and were in the process of training me for a Canvass Director position when I got pregnant and decided not to return after my maternity leave.  I'm pretty familiar with what's required to "git gud" here.

Yes, on most nights that simple formula of "just give them a concise rap and have a genuine conversation with them" works, but if I was being honest with myself, there were nights when -- for reasons beyond anyone's control -- it just didn't, and doesn't.  And one of the things I really grew to hate was having to pretend during close-out that a canvasser could or should always be accountable for missing quota when we all knew that wasn't always the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question.

The answer is, by paying us less than minimum wage.  We got a flat daily rate, not an hourly rate, and they tricked their overwhelmingly young, nave employees into believing that it was legal for them to pay us only for the time we actually spent canvassing, not for the travel/admin/training time.

I believe the daily rate was $32 plus bonuses.  Even though quota was $120, many people routinely pulled in well over that, so that helped them stay afloat, and it was one of the big reasons they had so many ways to quickly get rid of employees who weren't making quota.

I'm not entirely clear on what you mean by "another potential 4-5 for the meeting."  I certainly didn't mean to imply that we had 4-5 hours of meetings each day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with anything you've said, with the possible exception of your last sentence.  I'm not certain that for me, the highs made up for the lows.  Tbf, I'm not certain they *didn't*, either.

I, too, as a naturally very shy, introverted person, benefited greatly from the experience and the skills I acquired through it.  24 years later, I can still rattle off the "5 basic skills" of canvassing and frequently find myself applying them in all sorts of professional and even interpersonal situations.

Like you, I was able to broaden my understanding of and empathy for people who are very unlike me.  I met some wonderful strangers along the way, and made friends and had great fun with some truly awesome, like-minded young people.

But...I left feeling pretty bad about the whole thing.  As a disclaimer, I should mention that I field canvassed for only a few months, but I phone canvassed for the same organization for almost 4 years, so maybe a lot of my experience isn't necessarily relevant to yours, but I posted elsewhere in this thread about why I feel the way I do, and I'd like to share my reasoning:

 after awhile, I became very disillusioned for a number of reasons. First, I did the math on how much of what I raised each night was going to pay my salary rather than to the organizations I was fundraising for.

 Additionally, I realized that (with some important exceptions), the groups we were calling for were the big business of the non-profit world...HRC, Rainforest Action Network, Public Citizen, etc. Sure, I cared deeply about the issues they worked on, but if I were to choose organizations that were most effective and efficient in terms of getting results and using their donors' money wisely, these would not be the groups I would choose. This makes sense, if you think about it. If a non-profit is big/bloated/bureaucratic enough to choose to contract out their fundraising, they probably aren't the leanest, most boots-on-the-ground type of group out there.

 EDIT: Forgot a really important point that /u/coachlasso [+1] just reminded me of. The place I worked for paid a flat rate per shift rather than an hourly rate. Only 4 hours of that time was actual canvassing, but another hour or more each day was pre-canvass pep rallies/training/issue briefings and then at least 15 minutes of mandatory post-canvass accounting/close out/dose of kool-aid for making or missing quota, as appropriate.

 When it was all said and done, this organization that screamed so loudly about workers' rights was paying us less than minimum wage and intentionally skirting the wage and hour laws in order to do so by paying us a flat rate instead of an hourly one. That hypocrisy left a pretty terrible taste in my mouth about the whole thing.

TL;DR: I'm really conflicted about it.  There were parts of canvassing that were fantastic and have continued to pay dividends for me; OTOH, there's a lot about the nitty gritty of canvassing that under close inspection, makes it feel less than honorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...I'd forgotten about how awkward and weird that part was.  I must've blocked it out, as I'm realizing I did with many aspects of that job, both the field and phone varieties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only field canvassed for a few months, but I phone canvassed for the same organization for almost 4 years.  We worked with a lot of different groups, including HRC (back then, in 1993, it was still HRCF, actually), and that was my favorite project to work on, since LGBTQ rights are my pet issue.


 felt like I was being a force for good

I did too, at first.  But after awhile, I became very disillusioned for a number of reasons.  First, I did the math on how much of what I raised each night was going to pay my salary rather than to the organizations I was fundraising for.

Additionally, I realized that (with some important exceptions), the groups we were calling for were the big business of the non-profit world...HRC, Rainforest Action Network, Public Citizen, etc.  Sure, I cared deeply about the issues they worked on, but if I were to choose organizations that were most effective and efficient in terms of getting results and using their donors' money wisely, these would not be the groups I would choose.  This makes sense, if you think about it.  If a non-profit is big/bloated/bureaucratic enough to choose to contract out their fundraising, they probably aren't the leanest, most boots-on-the-ground type of group out there.

EDIT:  Forgot a really important point that /u/coachlasso just reminded me of.  The place I worked for paid a flat rate per shift rather than an hourly rate.  Only 4 hours of that time was actual canvassing, but another hour or more each day was pre-canvass pep rallies/training/issue briefings and then at least 15 minutes of mandatory post-canvass accounting/close out/dose of kool-aid for making or missing quota, as appropriate.

When it was all said and done, this organization that screamed so loudly about workers' rights was paying us less than minimum wage and intentionally skirting the wage and hour laws in order to do so by paying us a flat rate instead of an hourly one.  That hypocrisy left a pretty terrible taste in my mouth about the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wholeheartedly agree.  The public education/advocacy/organizing aspects of these jobs are great, and I probably would've continued indefinitely if I had been able to confine my involvement to just that aspect of the work.

But doing it to raise money dramatically changes the dynamic, especially when you do the math and begin to realize just how much of what you raise each night goes directly to paying your salary, rather than into the issue campaigns that most canvassers are genuinely passionate about.

I did field canvassing only for a few months, but I did phone canvassing for the same organization for almost 4 years.  By the end, I was sorely disillusioned with the "make a difference!" narrative these places sell in order to recruit young, idealistic employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lemme guess...the biggest one in the country is PIRG (Public Interest Research Group). The one I worked for wasn't them, but the model was very similar.

And yes, there is an initial 2-week training period when your job is on the line every day for not making quota.  Once you've jumped that hurdle, you basically have 2 weeks of job security at a time.  If you are under quota, on average, at the end of a 2-week period, they put you on an "action plan" (probation).  If you come in under quota for the week again during the next 6-week period (the action plan), they fire you.

Super great for morale.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not at all wrong.  It's super weird; that's why I was careful to clarify that it wasn't me...also that she is my *former* best friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory not me, but...

...my former best friend had a chaotic and tumultuous breakup with a long-term boyfriend.  During the course of their relationship, one of the things he had done was help her to stop biting her fingernails and grow them out.  By the time they stopped dating, she had long, beautiful nails.

A couple of days after they broke up for good, she carefully clipped her nails down to the quick, saving all of the clippings intact.  **She then placed them in an envelope and mailed him her fingernails.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being poor means being willing to do fucked up things for tiny bits of money, so I've had more sucky jobs than I can count.  But the one that stands out to me most is door-to-door political fundraising/canvassing.

This was back in the early '90s.  The way it worked was you had a clipboard, a pen, a petition, and some envelopes. The whole crew would meet at the office and then pile into the 15-passenger van(s).  The supervisors would drive us out to a territory ("turf") anywhere from 10 min - 2 hours away from the office. Then, they would divide us into pairs and give each pair of canvassers a map marked with the pair's assigned turf.

IIRC, we started knocking on doors around 3:00 or 4:00 p.m. and kept at it until 8:00.  In that time, we were supposed to knock on people's doors and talk to them about whatever issue we were working on at that point (when I did my brief stint it was nursing home reform legislation).  Then, we were supposed to get the occupant to sign our petition and make a contribution (preferably check or charge) on the spot.  Our nightly quota was $120.  

If you think that people hate having telemarketers call their houses at dinnertime to ask them for money, just imagine how much they love it when those same telemarketers show up unannounced on their front doorsteps.

Between shitty weather, vicious dogs, crackheads and tweakers answering the door, people's pervasive hatred of trespassers and solicitors, and constant fear of being fired for missing my quota, "field canvassing" was definitely one of the worst jobs I've ever had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Insalata di mare](http://www.gustissimo.it/articoli/ricette/antipasti-pesce/insalata-di-mare.jpg) (marinated seafood salad) or sauted spinach with garlic and olive oil.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have to eat it now.  I genuinely like it and I make a bomb-ass homemade mac n' cheese when I'm in the mood for something else.

That said, this recipe looks really good, and I'm curious to try the evaporated milk thing.  But if the question is tastiest "poor man's dinner," a $0.49 box of mac n' cheese plus another $0.40 worth of milk and butter is waaay cheaper than the recipe that you linked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the often-overlooked Worcestershire sauce, which also is really good in mac n' cheese! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. A couple of dashes of Worcestershire sauce is an especially nice addition to that combo in particular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is.  Even more amazing?  In addition to the can of tuna, also add peas or mixed veggies, some extra cheese, a couple of dashes of Worcestershire sauce, and some hot sauce of your choice.

OK. That's it; this thread is too much.  I'm gonna go make some tuna mac now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lego and Wegmans grocery stores.

EDIT:  How could I forget Subaru </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheese is amazing.  There are hundreds, if not thousands, of different kinds and I could probably name 2 dozen varieties off the top of my head.

My mac n' cheese gets: real American (not singles), cheddar, pepper jack, Gouda, Velveeta, mozzarella (sometimes Havarti instead), and cream cheese.  Each one adds something specific...flavor, creaminess, melty-ness.  It's also one of my favorite foods, but it's a wholly different creature from boxed mac n' cheese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!  Cut up a couple of slices of American or shred some cheddar/pepper jack into it...huge improvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehhh...I dunno.  I guess that depends on your recipe.

I looove homemade mac n' cheese, and the macaroni is really cheap, but the 7 different kinds of cheese I use when I make it from scratch actually makes it *really* pricey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very good point...what's "good" nutritionally depends a lot (like pretty much everything else in life) on one's needs and perspective.  Kinda like how someone studied caloric density to dollar-value ratio in common foods and discovered that if you are, say, homeless, a McDonald's McDouble is one of the very cheapest ways to meet your caloric (and most of your other nutritional) requirements.  

I've also been not homeless, but poor enough that the caloric density of mac n' cheese was regularly a blessing rather than a curse.  So I totally hear you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greek yogurt is an *excellent* addition...it gives it such a nice tang.  I like to add chopped spinach with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boxed macaroni and cheese.

I know it's total shit nutritionally, but I absolutely love it.  Bonus points if you still have a can of tuna in the pantry or some frozen veggies to mix into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm amazed at how what I thought was an innocuous comment has drawn legions of faithful fans of this movie out of the woodwork.

I am 100% aware of its satiric intent, as I was when I saw it in the theater.  I completely understand how great this movie *could have been*,  but for me, it really wasn't.  It was just a juvenile cacophony of disappointment.  I genuinely can't stand *Mars Attacks*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Mars Attacks!*

The Cast: Jack Nicholson, Michael J. Fox, Glenn Close, Pierce Bronsan, Sarah Jessica Parker, Annette Bening, Martin Short, Natalie Portman, Luke Haas, Danny DeVito, Jack Black, Tom Jones, Pam Grier, Christina Applegate.

It was *awwwful*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out 105%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if you have a newer-style high efficiency washer...the washing machine itself.

The wash tub gets mildewey/moldy/rank over time and needs to be cleaned periodically.  HE washers typically have a dedicated cycle for this.

Along the same lines, actually, your coffeemaker.  Not with soap of any kind, but run the brew cycle through with white vinegar and then 2-3x with water.  It really helps your coffee not taste funky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the "I hope that's close enough" really need a  /s?

Also, I'm pretty far outside the upper end of that age range you gave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry...we're talking about pretty, sexy, smart, badass women and you want me to do *math*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~someone~~ hordes of fanfic writers out there ~~is~~ are working hard to create NSFW disney movies

FTFY.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *almost* went with Ariel...so hot.  But I think Belle's feisty-ness ultimately gives her the edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tattoos and have owned a bicycle.  I hope that's close enough.

Belle.

1. She isn't afraid to tell Gaston to go fuck himself, and is aware enough of her own self-worth to not need to get married.

2. She *loves* to read and she's smart.

1 + 2 = smokin' hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Henson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sewing and making one's own clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was drifting off to sleep and remembered something I had saved.  If you haven't seen it already, you really should.

[It's an extremely well thought out comment elsewhere in this thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/nottheonion/comments/5zlct1/jeff_sessions_marijuana_is_only_slightly_less/dez7ebz/) that explores at least the prison-industrial aspect of that system and how Sessions' stance on cannabis is indisputably another example of in the long-standing, consciously racially motivated propaganda war against the drug and the people who use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  That's pretty great, I must admit.

Your mother and I should start a club...for middle-aged white ladies inappropriately obsessed with hip-hop artists (I'm 41; around here, that's basically the same thing).

Tell her I have faith she will solve this, but to please keep it on the DL when she does...the last thing we need is the current administration figuring out where in Cuba he's located. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an extremely complicated issue, of course, but here are a couple of factors:

The nonviolent principles of MLK's movement have been, I hate to say it, over-hyped to a degree.  Much of the progress that is attributed to MLK's nonviolent philosophies and tactics should more fairly be credited (at least in part) to the more radical arm of the civil rights movement that prevailed after King's death.  This is true to a large degree because there is no way in hell we're about to teach elementary school children that Black people rising up and taking militant action is a heroic act...even if it is.  MLK's commitment to nonviolence always had the advantage of being a narrative that was pre-sanitized for your (White people's) protection, so it got a lot more play and a lot more credit than perhaps it deserved in terms of evaluating the drivers of change in the civil rights of Black Americans.

Another big reason is that it wasn't as successful as we like to tell ourselves it was.  The mainline civil rights movement didn't actually work as well as we like to think.  The overt Jim Crow laws that were toppled by Dr. King's movement, by and large, simply morphed into the military-industrial-prison complex which continues to keep a majority of Black people in this country divested of their rights and freedoms, using a method that is merely updated since the days of chattel slavery, not fundamentally different from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome.  And I understand not really wanting to know, I do.

I *am* a little militant and non-conciliatory in my stance on fighting bigotry, but I don't come by those attitudes as a result of lacking any perspective on what has been effective in the history of civil and human rights movements, especially here in the U.S.  I take the positions I do precisely because I have spent a lot of time learning about what actually works to drive social change and ensure equity.

Hint:  It's not being well-behaved.

Source:  See username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to sacrifice any sacred cows here, but you may wish to look into what is often described as the [radicalization of Martin Luther King, Jr.](https://u.osu.edu/aaascec/files/2015/01/the-radicalization-of-martin-luther-king-jr-1sekp22.pdf) that occurred during the last 3 years of his life.

By the time he was assassinated, King himself was increasingly uncertain that his strategies had managed to erode American racism in any lasting, meaningful way -- despite the seemingly substantial progress he had led.

King may have said, "Darkness cannot drive out darkness; only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate, only love can do that," but by the time a racist gunned him down at a motel in Memphis, Tennessee, even he wasn't so sure about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Harness that anger but control it and present your arguments in a level fashion and educate.

You mean like this post elsewhere in the thread in which I summarized some of the most relevant and distressing parts of the NAACP LDEF report and linked the full text of the report itself?

 "An unrelenting hostility toward civil rights and racial justice has been the defining feature of Jeff Sessions professional life. At each step of his legal and political career, and across a variety of issueswhether voting, criminal justice, diversity in higher education and employment, education equality, immigration, or LGBTQ rightsSessions has stood opposite the civil rights community and the principles of
fairness and equality."

  "Sessions has consistently criticized the work of civil rights organizations and the lawyers who
work for themespecially when they appear before the Judiciary Committee as nominees for judgeships or other government positions."

  "Sessions has exhibited a reflexive assumption that civil rights experience renders one unfit for government service, often referring pejoratively to nominees with the ACLU gene or the ACLU chromosome.

 "Sessions has affirmatively stood in the way of desegregating the Southern District of Alabama and placing Alabamas first African-American judge on the Eleventh Circuit Court of Appeals."

 "Despite overwhelming evidence to the contraryincluding the detailed findings of the DOJ and federal courts across the countrySessions denies that race discrimination in voting exists."

 "From Sessions time as a federal prosecutor, two events in particular warrant further discussion: (1) Sessions selective prosecution of Black civil rights activists for legitimate voter assistance; and (2) the impact that failed prosecution has had on the political participation of racial minorities."

"Education" doesn't have to ask permission in order for to be effective.  If it did, advertising and marketing wouldn't be corporatist wet-dreams. No one has a responsibility to speak the truth in a way that makes bigots comfortable with themselves.

 I recognize that the people on the other side are not evil incarnate. 

Well, that's an awkward strawman.  No one said anything about "evil incarnate."  However, let's not whitewash the "blue collar values" that have gotten so much positive spin during the past election cycle.  I live in a deeply red county; approximately 72% of registered voters in my county voted for the current president.  The hatred and naked ugliness that exists in a day-to-day way is real and pervasive.  Where I live, racism, anti-semitism, and xenophobia are all issues I have to actually worry about.  And if I won't go so far as to characterize all people with those beliefs as "evil incarnate," I'm perfectly OK with saying that holding such beliefs (and not actively seeking to rid oneself of them) makes you a pretty shitty person.

 They just do not know any better.

I beg to differ.  A lot of it is acculturation and being steeped in environments where that thinking is commonplace, even the majority view.  But a lot of it is a choice to be hateful despite knowing better...often because fear is stronger than compassion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't address your "preconceptions" because I don't think that's what's relevant here.

I *am* angry.  I won't deny that I am angry because I have every reason and every right to be, as does every American who is a member of a marginalized group or who simply cares about equity and justice.  My refutation of your point is not based on the fact that you are incorrectly sensing a certain intensity and disapproval, even harshness, in my tone and attitude.  Rather, my point is that this intensity, disapproval, and harshness A) is wholly earned and warranted by the despicable views and actions of the bigots occupying positions of power and B) does not rise to the level of hatred, bigotry, or intolerance merely because I refuse to be silent about their ugliness or because I insist that they be accountable for it.

My anger is appropriate and in direct proportion and response to the evil of institutional civil rights abridgment in this country; I will not concede that righteous indignation toward those who betray the ideal of equal protection under the law is in any way morally equivalent to their bigotry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None taken! You, too.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just going to leave this without a response, but there was one phrase I kept thinking about:

 Honestly, you sound a little hateful

Honestly, I'm so tired of this sinister false equivalency.  **It is not hateful to call attention to someone else's bigotry or hatred or to fairly expect that they be held accountable for it.**

Asking me to "find some middle ground" with people who have not only fought in the past, but who, in many cases, continue to work in the present against my own civil rights and those of other Americans, is disrespectful to the people and communities who continue to be harmed by racist ideologies and actions.  Since his appointment as AG, Sessions has characterized the Voting Rights Act as "intrusive" and refused to commit to its full enforcement.  In addition, in direct contradiction to mountains of evidence and federal court rulings, Sessions has denied the historic racial motivations of voter ID laws.  His shitty views continue to harm people, and I won't pretend they don't.

I don't know that I'm "demonizing" Sessions, but I will not for one moment pretend that reprehensible ideas and conduct such as his deserve respect or equal air time in the public space.  They do not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised, actually!  A tiny bit of lemon juice or zest adds a lovely, can't-place-it brightness that contrasts very nicely with the sweetness of brownies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can he do?

To atone for his past behavior?  I suppose he could do pro bono legal work for the next 25 years serving communities that have been impacted by the harm his earlier work has done to them.  That would be a start...after denouncing his family's slave ownership, that is.

What can he do to make him qualified to hold the position of AG of the US? Possibly nothing, at this point.  It's not extremism to hold that there are some actions which permanently disqualify a person from holding certain positions of public trust.  The harm Sessions has caused to Black people (and other marginalized communities) through his past conduct render him unfit for the position he currently occupies.

He can apologize to and seek forgiveness from the Maker he believes should dictate so much of our social policy.  The American people owe him nothing -- especially not the position of highest law enforcement officer in the land.

And as to how "overwhelmed" he must be in facing the group shaming him, well, let's just say that in the face of the harm he has caused to people with far less power than he has, I'm not overly sympathetic.

I hear your argument about the shrill tone that you perceive among opponents of the current administration and the ideology it represents, and how this tactic is, among other things, counterproductive.

That argument is, frankly, nothing but concern trolling.  The majority of those who harbor abhorrent, bigoted views have shown they have no intention of participating in a reasoned dialog on these issues; their **hatred** is not caused by anyone's **tone**.  I'm more than a little sick of this argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.  [The full text of that letter can be found here.](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/3259988-Scott-King-1986-Letter-and-Testimony-Signed.html)

Fuck Mitch McConnell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert Byrd spent years working to undo the damage he knew he had done.  It is disingenuousness of the highest order for Sheffield (or you) to compare his legacy to that of Sessions.

The HuffPo article you link to basically says all the praise Sessions has earned from the Black community comes from his helping to start a single chapter of a civic organization in Mobile?  That's the political leadership of "I can't be a racist.  I have a black friend."

Further, the article concludes by discussing how groups with any credibility in the arena of civil rights are highly skeptical of any suggestion that Sessions is anything other than what his track record shows him to be.

 I do not believe you have looked into this issue with any real effort nor do I believe you are giving an honest effort towards objectivity.

You are incorrect.  I most certainly have; I just prefer more established, consequential sources such as [the NAACP's Legal Defense and Education Fund report against Sessions's confirmation as AG](http://www.naacpldf.org/files/our-work/LDF-Jefferson-Sessions-Report-in-Opposition-FINAL-1-9-2017.pdf) or even [Coretta Scott King's 1986 letter and testimony to the Senate Judiciary Committee opposing Sessions's confirmation as a federal judge](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/3259988-Scott-King-1986-Letter-and-Testimony-Signed.html) outlining exactly how his pattern and practice of racist views and actions disqualifies him from acting as a federal judge, let alone AG.

 Rhetoric and propaganda. Please wake up, America. We are culturally rotting.

The irony is almost too rich to bear here.

Finally, there is no lynch mobbing occurring in the case of Sessions.  Please don't cheapen that term by using it to describe the very deserved public scrutiny of his past statements, actions, and qualifications.  Whatever shaming might be happening is not not only to be expected given his past record and present position, but more importantly, has been wholly earned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called the [just world hypothesis (or fallacy).](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Just-world_hypothesis)

Basically, poor people are shamed because it is psychologically more palatable to believe that people earn their lots in life. For one thing, it makes people feel more in control to think that there is a predictability and an order to why people are poor (they deserve it).  More importantly, it alleviates people's discomfort at seeing the misery of those who live in poverty.  It feels a lot less miserable to look at that reality when your psyche convinces you people are poor because they are unworthy and deficient.  If people were poor because, let's say, the system was unfair, then one's discomfort should stir an ethical person to take action for change.  It's a lot less work to just decide that people deserve what they get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome?  I mean, *some* good should come out of his tenure as AG, and that's probably all we're likely to get, tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When was the last time you publicly denounced racism?

Anytime I encounter it.  Which, I would argue, I have somewhat less of a responsibility to do than does someone who aspires to be a federal judge, or attorney general. Since you'll undoubtedly ask for specifics, the last time I am *on record* publicly calling out racism was at my place of employment approximately 6 years ago.  However, less formally, if and when I am witness to racist behavior or racist speech in day-to-day situations, I absolutely denounce such ideas and actions -- as long as it is safe to do so.

 As far as I know, you haven't.

You don't know enough, and you're wrong.

 Am I now right to assume you are a racist?

No, no you would not be.  A lot of people -- even people who look white, the way that I do -- make it a practice to actively work against racism.  It's not too much to expect from someone in a position such as the one occupied by Sessions, *especially* given the highly reproachable nature of his own record on civil rights, that he stand up and bother to clarify that he is actually doesn't approve of his own immediate family's slave ownership.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You asked this question in reply to my comment, but in the interim, I see that others have provided their own takes on the matter.

Allow me to clarify, as I wasn't precise enough in my previous statement:  I agree that, in and of themselves, family ties to people who did unspeakable things brings no shame upon a person.  I *should've* said that Sessions's failure to affirmatively denounce the slave ownership in his immediate family isn't as damning as his own record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Alabama,

We accept the apology offered on your behalf by /u/MattAU05 for the rancid cumstain on the American judicial system that is Jefferson Beauregard Sessions III.

Please, for the love of whatever backwater shit you believe in, fund some goddamn quality and equity in public education so there might someday be an end in sight to this kind of absurdity.

Sincerely,

Those of us who get how collective goods problems work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selling seashells by the seashore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Already did in this very thread.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nottheonion/comments/5zlct1/jeff_sessions_marijuana_is_only_slightly_less/dez50hz/)

The full report is really worth reading, as is [Coretta Scott King's 1986 letter to Congress in opposition to Sessions's nomination to a federal judgeship.](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/3259988-Scott-King-1986-Letter-and-Testimony-Signed.html)  With a track record of deep racial enmity like Sessions has, a TL;DR really doesn't do it *justice*, so to speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true.  We can credit [Coretta Scott King's 1986 letter to Congress](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/3259988-Scott-King-1986-Letter-and-Testimony-Signed.html) with ensuring that his record couldn't be ignored the Senate Judiciary Committee even as it was quietly endorsed by committee charir Strom Thurmond.  Amazingly, in 2017, Mitch McConnell not only prevented Elizabeth Warren from reading the text of this letter, but also publicly rebuked her for attempting to require that, as the nominee for Attorney General, Sessions be made to face his already-public record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
