<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7624</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I went to a number of theme parks as a kid, but they were never that great. All I remember about them is lines, lines, and crappy food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of those who doesn't actually use their phone constantly. But so many people do, that it's assumed that *everyone* does / has to. People like myself get the short end of the stick, because they think we're just ignoring *them*. No, sir / ma'am, it's not you. I ignore **everyone.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knows about one of my accounts (I admittedly have two). But this one is for stress release and daily motivation, while the other has become famous and specialised, so I don't use it as often. He doesn't know about this one because he doesn't need to know how much time I *actually* spend on Reddit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a chick. I can't stand it. It looks unsanitary to me, and is generally in poor taste. If I had to feed a baby from a mammary gland, I'd do it in private.    
My advice to guys who want to "sneak a peek?" Sure, peek if you want to peek. Leer if you dare. The women doing it obviously are the type of women who don't mind being seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to, and soon. My parents gave me a "unique" (read: stupid) name with lots of middle names. I'm going to simplify it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People's availability. It's assumed they can be reached any time anywhere.     
It has become socially acceptable to have your phone on the dinner table and check it at least once while on the date.   
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was asleep through most of high-school history, but wasn't the beginning marked by the release Zhdanov Doctrine, in response to some stuff Churchill said after WW2? It was just a lot of paranoia. It was a lot of he-said-she-said problems, no one actually can take the blame for starting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thomas Edison. He's still credited as the inventor of a whole bunch of stuff that he only patented, and never invented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should probably get rid of my old ballroom gowns, but they were tailored and expensive. I always think, "I might use it again!" but ten years has gone by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoy the "Horrible Histories" series. I'm an adult and I still do. These days, I enjoy reading biographies, especially of of-timey actresses and other historical figures from the turn of the century. You pick up a lot in the meantime, and it sparks your interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angelina Jolie. She's just become.... weird. Especially around and after her "directorial debut." I'm not sure I like her anymore, and I was a big fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow up, get a job, save up, and go the the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurt a pet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's rude if someone won't take off their shoes at a home party, but it's also up to the host to inform their guests that they'll be expected to take off their shoes before coming in. Some people wear those funky lace-up shoes, specialised shoes, or expensive shoes they don't want to lose. (Unless you're in Japan, where it's a given.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still good stuff. It feels like meditation sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kittens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I probably would. If they bothered me enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err.... Is this a correlation / causation thing? Because brining up your kids into an obese lifestyle is bad parenting. A child-abusing parent can bring their kid to Disneyland every year, it doesn't make them a good parent.    
Bringing a kid to Disneyland is a nice thing to do, but it doesn't cancel out the child abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably spend the last few hours in the arms of the man I love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally I don't care, but if the dude smells or is kinda obnoxious, I'd probably move myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me sad to think about, too. But it's the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you're not spilling and slopping all over the place, I am sure no one will notice. It's all about having an art to it. (I hold my pencil in the wrong way, and still worked as a comic book inker. No one complained after that.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
