<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4888</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those who kill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading in my dimly lit room, when I heard the slightest noise on my bedroom window. I propped my book up on my knees and looked towards the source of the noise. My parents were gone to dinner at the hole in the wall diner in the middle of our sleepy little town. I checked my phone, no texts, no notifications, nothing. The only thing that met my eyes was the time, which was later than I had expected. I felt my brow raise in surprise at the amount of time my parents had been gone. I brought myself to get out of the comfort of my bed and peeked through my blinds to see if my parents may be coincidentally pulling in, as if on cue.

I checked the street, which was barren. I narrowed my eyes at something underneath the streetlight. As I leaned in to get a better look, with my nose pressing against the glass and my breath nearly fogging up my view, I saw the silhouette of a man. Chills raced over my body, freezing my blood solid. I felt my eyes bulging out of their sockets, daring to get a better look at what i was seeing. As I sat mouth open, eyes wide, it waved, long and slow at me. I fell back from the window straight onto the tip of my tailbone and crawled backwards in front of my bedroom door, too terrified to act.

Holy shit. I whispered to no one but myself. I crawled back to my bed on my hands and knees, hoping he couldnt see me. I reached my hand up and searched blindly for my phone. Relief temporarily washed over me as I felt its cold frame in my trembling hand. I instantly called my dad, praying he would fucking answer. Straight to voicemail.

Fuck. I cried silently, the tears were beginning to fall. The fear within them seared my eyes and I questioned whether or not to call the police, or if I was overreacting. I had always scared so easily.

The courageous part of my mind urged me to take another look to see if he was still out there, under the light. What if he was? But then what if he wasnt? I compulsively looked at my phone every second, begging to see my father calling.

Tap tap

My heart stopped. The sheer terror lurched my stomach into my throat and I held back a gag. I couldnt move. My limbs wouldnt work, like the nerves in my body evaporated, and my muscles had turned to dust.

There was no fucking way I was going to pull open my blinds and face whatever was out there. Struggling to snap myself into reality I looked down at my phone in my hand. I attempted to text my dad, but my fingers were shaking so bad as if I was seizing. I sent him numerous, frantic texts and i just hoped my dad wouldnt think I was fucking with him. It seemed like hours had passed in the matter of seconds. I sat in deafening silence, my ears alert for anything. Nothing.

I sat helpless, and paralyzed, too afraid to leave the sanctity of my room. My parents had turned all of the lights off in the house before they left, since i usually dont leave my room this time of night anyway. Going out into the darkness seemed so harrowing. I got down as low as I could, until my chest was touching the carpet and hurriedly rushed over to the window, and listened. There was nothing, no knocking, no breathing, no shuffling, just silence. My eyes searched my room for something to cling to; when i saw a eye underneath my door. It wasnt just an eye, it was a nose, and half of a crooked smile. He was at my unlocked door, staring menacingly at me as i had sat listening for him. The most blood curdling scream escaped my body, as I jumped to my feet, immediately going for the window. I tore the blinds from the wall, and unlocked the window. I struggled to lift it up, since it had been painted over when we first moved in.I threw my eyes behind me to see if he was still there.

My bedroom door stood open. And the man underneath was no longer half hidden, he was fully in front of me. He was no more than six feet away, blankly staring into my eyes with his own cold, dead pair. He was wearing a long, flowing pastel pink dress with blood splattered all over it. His bleached blonde hair was pulled back behind his head. Those eyes. They bore into mine, as I felt that I no longer could escape.

What do you want? I asked him in a pitiful, dry whisper. The tears were pouring down my face and I knew I was about to puke. I searched his long, porous face for his intent. He only replied with widening his smile. He brought his tall, slender frame closer to me with a small step, as if he was taunting me. I screamed at him once more and flung my nightstand at him and threw my body out the window in a final attempt. I hit the ground running, and I ran, and ran and ran.

I looked over my shoulder to see if he was chasing me, and that he was. Except he was moving much quicker than i was.

HELP ME, PLEASE. I screamed at the top of my lungs as I ran down the street in my quiet little suburban neighbourhood.

HELP ME! My cries came out in a stutter as my lungs tried to keep up with me. I couldnt even feel the rocks tearing the flesh apart on the bottom of my feet, nor the winter chill on my skin. All I felt was pure, white horror.

He let out a joyous cackle, crazed and clear as he was beginning to catch up to me. My legs cried for me to stop, the feeling in my feet was long gone, my lungs were gasping for air. I had about twenty feet until i reached our neighbors house. Please, please, i whispered to my body. I leaped the last few feet onto their manicured porch and began violently beating on their front door.

HELP ME, PLEASE! My voice was hoarse, and brittle, but loud. I turned around for a second and he was racing towards me like an oncoming collision. I took everything i had and kicked him back off the porch as he tried to make it up the steps. He fell back a couple steps, My neighbors opened the door looking horrified as they saw what was happening. He met my eyes one final time and gave me the most ominous, sprawling grin a person could form. He pulled at his face, scratching it with his untrimmed nails and blood immediately began pouring out. He leaned his head back and let out a feminine shriek,

HELP ME, HELP ME. He mocked, in a high pitch voice. Which was followed by a low, throaty growl. It rumbled in my skull like thunder; he shook his head back and forth rapidly as if he was a dog shaking a toy. Spit slinging from his mouth, he rolled his head around on his neck, laughing uncontrollably as me and my neighbors watched in awe.

When suddenly he stopped and stared at the sky, totally still. We watched both terrified and intrigued for what seemed like forever, when he began bolting towards us. They pulled me in and slammed the door. I closed my eyes waiting for him to flail his body on it, but it never came. I stepped back and looked at them, and they looked at me.

Thank you. I breathed, relief washed over me like i had just took a dive in a swimming pool. I had only met the two about three times at community gatherings and in passing. They were a gorgeous couple, probably in their late forties and had always seemed friendly.

Go call the police. The wife said gravely to her husband. He nodded, still looking a bit ghostly and headed into the kitchen. She motioned for me to sit on the couch furthest from the door,

Do you want some tea or anything dear? Her voice was soft and sweet like butterscotch, it relaxed me a little further. I shook my head and went to look for my phone. I patted my pajama pockets, confused. I knew i put it in there, but maybe it had fallen out as I was running for my life. Nervous laughter struck me, and im not sure if it was from the shock or the realization that i hadnt died. I just really need to call my parents. I said, looking at the door apprehensively. There was no way I was going back out there without being accompanied by my dad. I dont know if i could even go home again. His face flooded my mind like pain.

Youre okay now. She said, and put a hand on my back. She smiled at me at walked into the kitchen behind her husband. I thought it was odd I couldnt hear him talking to the police, i mean the kitchen couldnt have been that big and the house was small.

I began to bite my nails as I was waiting on the couple return to the living room, but not taking my eyes off of the door. I retraced his face in my brain, and recalled the blood on his dress, the way he screamed at the sky. The fact that he was in my house. How long had he been watching me? Who was he? I had so many questions, but honestly i just wanted to go home to the safety of my parents. They should have been home by now. I looked around the living room for a clock. My eyes landed on an old grandfather clock in the corner of the room, 11:32. You said you needed to call your parents? The wife asked, appearing out of the kitchen, startling me.

Uh yeah, if you dont mind. She just smiled at me, sort of complacently and handed me a cordless home phone. I returned her smile with tight lips. She left me with privacy, thankfully and i dialed my dads number. I listened to the dial tone as i stepped out of the living room and wandered into the hall away from the kitchen. They didnt answer so i dialed it again, and continued down the hallway. It was rather long and painted a dainty yellow, littered with pictures in nice golden frames. As i listened to the phone i looked at the pictures. I found one with the husband and the wife and what must have been their son.

Hello. A voice answered my fathers phone. The phone slipped out of my hand as I made the connection of the boy in the picture. The long sharp face, those dark beady eyes. The husband and the wife with their wide smiles, and long fingers on his shoulders. I heard his pious laughter echoing out of the phone as i looked at the picture beside that. It was the same one essentially except in this one the man had bleached blonde hair in ringlets, bright red lipstick and a face full of makeup. I watched as the couples shadows loomed above mine against the wall. I turned my head to look at them and they wore the same smile as their son. They began laughing psychotically, kneeling over grabbing at their stomachs as if terrorizing me was the most fun they've had in awhile.

What did you do to my parents? I asked, breathless. The air was vacuumed out of my body and it hung on the air like a mist. Their laughter abruptly stopped, as did the laughter on the phone. I heard a noise behind me, and turned, to see the man running at me from down the hallway.

I let out a growl of anger and took the picture off the wall beside me and smashed it in his face before he could come to a stop. His mother and father let out a screech of horror as he fell to the floor, writhing in agony as the glass dug deeper into his skin. Blood was pouring out onto the hardwood floor much more quickly than I would have expected. He began to beat his head on to the ground violently, pushing the glass further in, and producing more blood. The parents grabbed me from behind, the mother took me by my hair and the father dug his nails into the skin on my arm. I kicked and scratched at their clutches to no avail; all the while he had begun to beat his head on the walls, blood covering them like paint. I tried to land a blow on the mother as she began dragging me down the hallway past her son who had completely fucking lost it.

NO! I yelled, kicking him one last time as they pulled me down the hallway. The father struck me in the stomach as reprimand and I choked on my insides. The son stopped his blows and slowly, as if frame by frame turned his head towards me as his parents took me away. His face was almost unrecognizable, covered in blood from his flesh being torn to the bone. Bits of his scalp were missing from his brutal bashings, and a few teeth had fallen out. Glass had gotten lodged in his eyes, and blood was filling them, blanketing the white.

Help me, help me. He whispered swiftly, blood spluttering out like spit. I roared in rage as their hands tensed, they were beginning to drag me up stairs. I caught my hand on the wooden spools and anchored myself on the fifth step. The mother began beating me in the back of the head with all of her might, and as best I could I tried to dodge her blows. The father dropped his grip on me and I fell down hard on the corner of the step. Dazed from her blows and the pain from the fall i was beginning to lose strength. He pushed her out of the way and wrapped both of his hands in my hair and lurched me up the stairs, ripping my nails right off on the spools. I screamed in agony pulling my hand back, getting blood all over my face and clothes. The mother opened the door at the top of the stairs and the stench of iron, and decay filled my senses. I puked from the smell, the pain and the terror; my stomach was knotted in disgust and my body was beginning to go into shock. The two of them lifted me up and threw me onto a pile of something damp. The smell was so strong, like ammonia. It was completely black all around me and i tried to get up from where they had threw me. My fingers went into something wet and cold, like the insides of a pumpkin. I heard the son downstairs flailing once more, screaming in his feminine voice, HELP ME HELP ME. The father began walking towards me, stepping on my chest and compressing the last of the oxygen in my lungs out into a strangled gasp.

Click

It was the chain to the single lightbulb ahead, illuminating the room I was thrust in finally. I screamed.

Bodies upon bodies lay underneath me, covering the floor. Some were still intact as if they had only been dead for a few days but some were decayed beyond human recognition. Their eyes nothing but black holes, mouths hung open as if crying out. I whimpered as I realized what i had stuck my fingers in. I looked beneath me and there were my parents. Except it wasnt my parents anymore, their naked bodies lay at inhuman angle, heads smashed in. My father's jaw was crushed, and hung by the tendons from his skull, his teeth completely missing. My mother was completely void of flesh on her face and body all that remained was the tissue underneath, as if she was burned alive.

The son staggered up the stairs, and fell into the room on his hands and knees. I met his bloody eyes with hatred, and he inhaled deeply, aroused by the scent of so much blood. He was like a fucking rabid dog, and his parents were the creators of this demonic beast. He sat up and ran his hands over his body as if he was caressing curves,

You like my dress? He said through a teeth clenched grin. I ran my eyes over what was left of the dress once more, and the vomit came. The light pink, those pretty lace flowers, they were my mother's favorite combination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
