<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7609</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homosexuality is punishable by death in the Islamic Republic.


Now we now why Iran doesn't say shit like Kadyrov. They already kill gay people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The story has been withdrawn as the individual was misidentified

what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/live/yt7b5q57cgzj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's anti-semitic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French election 2017: Marine Le Pen leading the race as polls open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said that only arabs wants to destroy Israel. Nice strawman. I said that people with Israeli citizenship. They can be arab or Jews or whatever.

Nice strawman though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's because Christians have been allies with Muslims in the struggle for Palestine. They are partners. Jews have not been partners. They've wanted their own state. They got it. Christians are still on the Palestinian side. Sorry bub.

This isn't a reason to be anti-semitic. Many Jews are also anti-Zionist yet they get stabbed. They just anti-semitic. 

 The Judaization of Jerusalem means destroying, revising, and erasing what his been a part of Jerusalem for thousands of years to make it more comfortable for Jews.

The fuck? Do you even know that Jerusalem comes from a Hebrew word? Because it was the capital of the Kingdom of Israel 2000 years ago and hundreds of year before the creation of Islam of christianity? 

They were the one that eliminated Jewish connection to Jerusalem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So you're saying a man who has lived in Tel Aviv with his gay partner for 10 YEARS wants to destroy Israel?

Why not? Many people who have Israel citizenship wants to destroy Israel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antisemitism is generally considered to be a form of racism

Generally doesn't mean always. 

The absence of evidence is not the evidence of absence. I know that might take a while for you to understand, so consider this my goodbye.

Read the text again.

Jerusalem city is the capital of Palestine, it has its religious, historical and civilian place in an Arab, Islamic and human way, and all its Islamic and Christian holy places headed by Al Aqsa mosque is a non-negotiable right for Palestine, Arab and the Islamic nations. We do not surrender it or give any part of it, and all the occupations procedures in Jerusalem such as Judaization, settlement of the city as well as the forgery of the truth, are illegal.

To claim  "Judaization" is nonsense. Because there is a Jewish connection. The context obviously implies that they reject any Jewish tie to Jerusalem. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think five years after the man claimed he would be killed, there would be a follow up. There isn't.

You were the one that asked for another article. 

 The man has lived in Tel Aviv with his partner for the last decade. The couple say that the Interior Ministry has repeatedly rejected their petition to legalize the Palestinians residence in Israel.

What a nation to be defending!

Yeah why should Israel deal with the problems made by people that wants to destroy it? 

And is waaaaayy better the people that are actually making them to flee!

What a terrorist organization to be defending!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're repeating the same thing twice. Lol.

They are not the same thing lol

You can be anti-semitc because you hate Judaism and not because of racial hatred. The same way you can be Islamophobe not because you hate arabs but Islam.


 They don't deny Jewish ties to Jerusalem, nor do they make it a highlight of their charter. 

They do. They completely failed to mention any Jewish tie to Jerusalem and said that it has significance for christians and muslims. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops my bad. Here have the story of how gay palestinians are escaping Gaza because they would kill them

http://www.timesofisrael.com/gay-palestinian-to-hcj-boot-me-and-theyll-kill-me/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right.

Also, not recognizing Jewish ties to Jerusalem is not simply bullocks. It's racist, anti-semitic, revisionist, and a complete lie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You posted one example of a Hamas official being killed. 

To give different sources. Also it is punishable by death in Gaza.

hat happened in January, surely you can find another example in the past 4 months.. right? 

Yes.

http://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Iran-News/Iran-executes-gay-teenager-in-violation-of-international-law-463234

Also lol at this conversation, are you now feeling sympathy for a Hamas commander convicted of theft and homosexuality? 

No. I don't feel sympathy for terrorist. doesn't matter if they are gay or not. That's why I'm not doing apology of terrorists, like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The leak has since been confirmed by Hamas official Ahmad Yousif.

I never said that the leak was fake.

Still, the new leaked charter still is filled with anti-semitic  and revisionist rhetoric like rejecting the Jewish ties to Jerusalem. So it is still bullocks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Literal propaganda

No, it isn't. 

http://www.newsweek.com/prominent-hamas-commander-was-executed-after-accusations-gay-sex-432343

https://www.nytimes.com/2016/03/02/world/middleeast/hamas-commander-mahmoud-ishtiwi-killed-palestine.html?_r=0

Are you literally not aware of the Arab Peace Plan?

Hamas rejected it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/671vqt/west_banks_ruling_party_fatah_calls_for/dgn5gfj/?utm_content=permalink utm_medium=front utm_source=reddit utm_name=worldnews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
