<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8373</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 22:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try and pay more attention on my drive home from work today to see if that's the case.  Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2008 Mazda 3 - Overheating in stop and go traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 20:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm in stop and go traffic, my car's temp gauge will randomly spike and either slowly come back down or stay up at the top for about a minute. 

I've bled out the bubbles in the coolant multiple times and the overheating keeps happening. So I don't think it could be that unless I'm doing it wrong. 

I'm thinking it could either be my thermostat, water pump, or radiator fan.  Can anyone please help me narrow it down?  Thanks!

Forgot to mention: Car has about 104k miles, AC is not on, thermostat was replaced at about 61k miles. 

**Update:** Driving home from work today I watched my temp gauge very carefully.  My car was at normal operating temp by the time I got one, but as I accelerated to get up to 65-70 mph, it started to overheat.  My gauge went from about halfway to around 3/4.  I left off the gas, and it stopped climbing.  I hit the gas a little bit again, and it started to climb so I let off.  Then it started to fall back to the normal operating temperature.  Keep in mind that this all happened in a span of about 20 seconds.  I didn't hit any traffic, so I wasn't stopped at all.  

**Update 2:** Turns out there's a small crack in the bottom part of the overflow section on my reservoir tank.  Pretty sure that's the problem.

**Update 3:** Replaced coolant reservoir and thermostat and that didn't fix it.  Gonna take it to a shop to diagnose. 

**Update 4:** I FIXED IT!  Took it to a shop and they couldn't figure out what was wrong after spending all day on it. I replaced the coolant temperature sensor yesterday and the gauge didn't show any overheating during a 30 minute test drive trying to recreate the problem and on my way to work this morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 20:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it spike after being at normal running temp for a few minutes? Or climb straight up the the top?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overheating in stop and go traffic [2008 Mazda 3] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 20:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm in stop and go traffic, my car's temp gauge will randomly spike and either slowly come back down or stay up at the top for about a minute. 

I've bled out the bubbles in the coolant multiple times and the overheating keeps happening. So I don't think it could be that unless I'm doing it wrong. 

I'm thinking it could either be my thermostat, water pump, or radiator fan.  Can anyone please help me narrow it down?  Thanks!

Forgot to mention: Car has about 104k miles, AC is not on, thermostat was replaced at about 61k miles. 

**Update:** Driving home from work today I watched my temp gauge very carefully.  My car was at normal operating temp by the time I got one, but as I accelerated to get up to 65-70 mph, it started to overheat.  My gauge went from about halfway to around 3/4.  I left off the gas, and it stopped climbing.  I hit the gas a little bit again, and it started to climb so I let off.  Then it started to fall back to the normal operating temperature.  Keep in mind that this all happened in a span of about 20 seconds. 

**Update 2:** Turns out there's a small crack in the bottom part of the overflow section on my reservoir tank. Pretty sure that's the problem.  

**Update 3:** New coolant reservoir and new thermostat didn't fix the overheating problem. Taking it to a shop to diagnose. 

**Update 4:** I FIXED IT!  Took it to a shop and they couldn't figure out what was wrong after spending all day on it. I replaced the coolant temperature sensor yesterday and the gauge didn't show any overheating during a 30 minute test drive trying to recreate the problem and on my way to work this morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 06:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to cancel my order. :( I'm thinking that the remote part won't work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that earlier.  The author's Mazda was manufactured in Canada.  I'm not too sure if the same goes for US models.  The thread that has me worried is this one: http://www.mazda3forums.com/69-interior-modifications/252881-key-remote-flip-key-part-s-compiled.html

Specifically this note: "There are NO flip remotes that can be programmed with 2007-2009 US Mz3/MS3 computer. This is due to a change in the KEU system for 2007-2009 models."  I emailed the seller on Ebay and they told me that their key would work with a 2008 Mazda 3.  I keep seeing contradictory answers everywhere! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flip-out/switchblade style key for 08 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if these keys will work with an 08?  Here's the key I ordered: http://www.ebay.com/itm/301496757252

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a laptop or chromebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 18:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

My girlfriend just got a new job as a marketing coordinator for a local hotel chain.  I was thinking about getting her a laptop/chromebook for Christmas since she'll be travelling around to different hotels and working from there.  

She'll mainly be working with social media websites (Facebook, Twitter, etc.), sending email blasts and writing columns for their website.  As for as I know, she won't be doing any kind of graphic design or other cpu/gpu intensive work.

I'm looking to spend around $150-200 USD.   I was thinking that a chromebook with a 16gb SSD would probably be enough for her.  Which would you recommend? Are there any good black Friday deals on chromebooks?  Please let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 03:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TanningChatum7
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 06:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I really appreciate the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 06:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not super intro gaming, but I do want to play Battlefront. So I think the 970 will do.  I wanted to put more money into the hardware that dealt with the video editing stuff. 

Thanks for the cable management tips! It's my first time building a PC so I wasn't very aggressive with the wires.  I'll try and tidy it up tomorrow after work according to your suggestions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Complete] How'd I do for my first build? $1900 editing PC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 05:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/mgbmt6) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/mgbmt6/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i7-5820K 3.3GHz 6-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80648i75820k) | Purchased For $304.00 
**CPU Cooler** | [Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 82.9 CFM Sleeve Bearing CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-cpu-cooler-rr212e20pkr2) | Purchased For $25.00 
**Motherboard** | [ASRock X99 Extreme4 ATX LGA2011-3 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-x99extreme4) | Purchased For $156.00 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance LPX 16GB (2 x 8GB) DDR4-2666 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmk16gx4m2a2666c16) | Purchased For $92.33 
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance LPX 16GB (2 x 8GB) DDR4-2666 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cmk16gx4m2a2666c16) | Purchased For $92.33 
**Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e250bam) | Purchased For $88.00 
**Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 500GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e500bam) | Purchased For $149.99 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 2TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st2000dm001) | Purchased For $64.50 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 2TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st2000dm001) | Purchased For $64.50 
**Video Card** | [EVGA GeForce GTX 970 4GB SSC ACX 2.0+ Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-video-card-04gp43975kr) | Purchased For $285.00 
**Case** | [Fractal Design Define R5 (Titanium) ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/fractal-design-case-fdcadefr5ti) | Purchased For $85.00 
**Power Supply** | [XFX XTR 650W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/xfx-power-supply-p1650bbefx) | Purchased For $60.00 
**Monitor** | [Asus PB238Q 23.0" Monitor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asus-monitor-pb238q) | Purchased For $153.00 
**Monitor** | [Asus PB238Q 23.0" Monitor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asus-monitor-pb238q) | Purchased For $100.00 
**External Storage** | [Seagate Expansion 4TB External Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-external-hard-drive-stbv4000100) | Purchased For $108.00 
**Other**| VIVO Dual LCD Monitor Desk Mount Stand Heavy Duty Fully Adjustable| Purchased For $43.20 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | **Total** | **$1870.85**
 | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2015-11-10 20:35 EST-0500 |
The prices listed are what I paid including tax, shipping, and MIRs.  So $1870.85 is what I actually paid in the end!  Big thanks to /r/buildapcsales 

Hi everyone,

This was mainly built for video editing and some gaming.  Let me know what you think!


If anyone has any tips they would like to give me, that would be great!  Especially if it has to do with cable management.

http://imgur.com/FCzcs9b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me if you want a promo code! I won't be using mine.

Edit: Gone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would having two 24" compared to one 27" be that much more productive?  After some consideration, I would imagine it would be, but I've never worked on a 2560x1440 monitor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 16:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of these?

http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00B1IAL7W/ref=mp_s_a_1_5?qid=1446044591 sr=8-5 pi=AC_SX110_SY165_QL70 keywords=Asus+ips dpPl=1 dpID=41OAQIluKEL ref=plSrch

http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00906GBBC/ref=mp_s_a_1_9?qid=1446044684 sr=8-9 pi=AC_SX110_SY165_QL70 keywords=Asus+ips

http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B010VG2456/ref=mp_s_a_1_8?qid=1446044684 sr=8-8 pi=AC_SX110_SY165_QL70 keywords=Asus+ips dpPl=1 dpID=4116DYXwnLL ref=plSrch

Do you have any other 24" recommendations? Preferably under $200  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New monitor advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 04:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,

I'm putting together my first build for video editing and I've bought almost all the components except the monitor.  I've been planning on buying the Asus pb278q from Tigerdirect.  With the 20% cash back through Bank of America and a $10 promo discount, the monitor would come out to about $384 in the end.  The next lowest price I could find was on Amazon for $400 (before tax).  

Are there any other better/cheaper/newer monitors I should take a look at?  Or is the Asus pb278q a solid choice at this price? 

Please let me know!  

Edit: Pulled the trigger and ordered an ASUS PA248Q and an ASUS PB238Q through Amazon Warehouse deals.  I ended up spending about the same amount I would have for one ASUS PB278Q.  I figured I'd use the PA for my preview and the PB for my timeline/sliders/etc.  If there are no differences between the PA and the PB, I might return the PA and get another PB to save myself $90. I'll try to update when they come in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on video editing monitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 03:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,

I'm putting together my first build for video editing and I've bought almost all the components except the monitor.  I've been planning on buying the Asus pb278q from Tigerdirect.  With the 20% cash back through Bank of America and a $10 promo discount, the monitor would come out to about $384 in the end.  The next lowest price I could find was on Amazon for $400 (before tax).  

Are there any other better/cheaper/newer monitors I should take a look at?  Or is the Asus pb278q a solid choice at this price? 

Please let me know!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Video editing monitor help $300-$400 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 03:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,

I'm putting together my first build for video editing and I've bought almost all the components except the monitor.  I've been planning on buying the Asus pb278q from Tigerdirect.  With the 20% cash back through Bank of America and a $10 promo discount, the monitor would come out to about $384 in the end.  The next lowest price I could find was on Amazon for $400 (before tax).  

Are there any other better/cheaper/newer monitors I should take a look at?  Or is the Asus pb278q a solid choice at this price? 

Please let me know!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insane weather in Hawaii. Perfect commentary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 09:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 00:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you trying to fill out the rebate form, Newegg customer service just told me that the code: 64748 will work tomorrow and as long as you purchased the case today, 10/22, it will work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-CA][H] Paypal [W] i7 5820K, ASUS PB278Q, Dell P2715Q </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 23:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone has a new 5820K for some reason, I'll gladly buy it!  I'm open to used ones as well, depending on how long they've been used.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 18:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Fry's honor the discount still if I have a code from Saturday?

Edit: Just called. They said no. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you really think the difference between the 5820K and 4790K isn't worth the money?  

I'll take a look at the R5!

I won't be capturing any game footage since I'm not a huge gamer.  But is A-Data a trustworthy brand?  It seems like the Samsung EVOs are really popular.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply!

Oh wow, I didn't know that about the Seagate 3TB drives.  Thanks for the advice.

Sadly, I'm not very close to a Microcenter.  The closest one is about 3 hours away.  I will definitely hunt for discounts and sales on the CPU and MOBO though.  

I'll definitely buy the cheaper ram if I'm not going to need to spend the extra money on it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply!
I think I'm leaning more towards the 4790K and using the saved money to buy 16gb more of RAM.  However, everyone on /r/buildapc recommended buying the 5820K.  

Unfortunately, I ordered the EVGA SSC GTX970 this morning for $285 (with tax and shipping), so it's too late for the AMD R9 390.  

The Fractal Design R5 is a mid tower? Will that be a problem compared to a full size tower? (Sorry for dumb questions, this is my first build!)

That's a good idea for the SSD's.  I was just thinking about using the 120GB for the OS and apps and then the 500gb as a scratch disk.  But in this case I guess I could use two of the 256gb SSDs as scratch disks?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice on new editing PC. 4790K vs 5820K </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 20:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone, I'm torn between these two CPUs for editing.  I've been reading tons of articles and looking at benchmarks, but I still can't make up my mind.  I'll be purchasing parts later today!

**What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.**

I'll be editing video using Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects, and Davinci Resolve.  I'll also be editing photos sometimes using Adobe Lightroom and Photoshop.  

Light gaming will be done, since I plan on buying Battlefront when it comes out.

**What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?**

Preferably under $2000.  I'm willing to spend $2100-2200 if the 5820K is really worth it.  

**In what country are you purchasing your parts?**

United States.

**Post a draft of your potential build here (specific parts please).** 

4790K Build: http://pcpartpicker.com/p/hpYx3C

5820K Build: http://pcpartpicker.com/p/m79MkL


**Provide any additional details you wish below.**

Is the price difference in the 5820K justified?  I'm having a really hard time deciding between the two CPUs.  I'd really prefer to spend less and go with the 4790K build and maybe buy 32gb of ram instead.  But if the added cores on the 5820K will make a big difference in video editing, I'm willing to spend the $200 more.  

Please let me know what you think!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] Video Editing PC. i7 4790K vs 5820K </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 19:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone, I'm torn between these two CPUs for video editing.  I've been reading tons of articles and looking at benchmarks, but I still can't make up my mind.  I'll be purchasing parts later today!

**What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.**

I'll be editing video using Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects, and Davinci Resolve.  I'll also be editing photos sometimes using Adobe Lightroom and Photoshop.  

Light gaming will be done, since I plan on buying Battlefront when it comes out, but the editing is the most important part!

**If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, FPS, game settings)**

Medium performance is fine.  I don't need crazy high settings.

**What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?**

Preferably under $2000.  I'm willing to spend $2100-2200 if the 5820K is really worth it.  

**In what country are you purchasing your parts?**

United States.

**Post a draft of your potential build here (specific parts please).** 

4790K Build: http://pcpartpicker.com/p/hpYx3C

5820K Build: http://pcpartpicker.com/p/m79MkL


**Provide any additional details you wish below.**

Is the price difference in the 5820K justified?  I'm having a really hard time deciding between the two CPUs.  I'd really prefer to spend less and go with the 4790K build and maybe buy 32gb of ram instead.  But if the added cores on the 5820K will make a big difference in video editing, I'm willing to spend the $200 more.  

Please let me know what you think!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pm'd
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 19:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Santa Barbara </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-CA][H] PayPal [W] GeForce GTX 970 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 17:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to build my first PC and I've decided to go the used route for my GPU.  Does anyone have a 970 that they're willing to sell me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [US-CA] [H] PayPal [W] GeForce GTX 970 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 16:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 23:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep this in mind. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fair price on 2007 Prius? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is looking into buying a pre-owned Prius from the local Toyota dealership. They have a 2007 Prius with 88K miles for $10,988. One owner, clean title.

KBB is showing $8,890 as a fair price. What's my best approach at talking the salesperson down to this price?

Are there any specific questions we should ask when we go to check it out? Please let me know if there is anything to watch out for. Any information is helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this price fair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 19:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is looking into buying a pre-owned Prius from the local Toyota dealership.  They have a 2007 Prius with 88K miles for $10,988.  One owner, clean title.  

KBB is showing $8,890 as a fair price.  What's my best approach at talking the salesperson down to this price?

Are there any specific questions we should ask when we go to check it out?  Please let me know if there is anything to watch out for.  Any information is helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
