<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1628</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leal, Scott spar over Roland's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a completed EJS, the record is accessible up to 2 years but the charge is still dismissed (or stayed depending on local practice). There are certain ppl who can access a youth record ONLY when the record is still accessible, meaning an EJS can be accessible for up to 2 years so they can retrieve that record within those 2 years.

At this point, the only way anything would show up on your record is if you were charged as an adult within the access period of your youth record. In that case, your youth record carries over and is part of your adult record. But this did not happen. An EJS is one of the least intrusive sentencing options in the YCJA, reserved for minor offences and not meant to hinder an offender's future prospects.

Nothing at all should be on your record, but if you want to put your mind completely at ease, what you could do is order a criminal record check from your local police force. Then you know for sure. It will not be a complete waste, criminal record checks are good to have for volunteer work or if you go on a school class trip with your child/niece/nephew etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, youth probation officer here. Sounds like you were given an extra judicial sanction, meaning you are given a set of conditions to follow where, if met, the case is dismissed. Usually fingerprints
 aren't taken for these though but not completely impossible.
 Records for EJS are kept for 6 months up to 2 years. Even if found guilty theft is a summary offence and your record would only be accessible for 3 years after sentence completion. You're good to go.


Edit: Incomplete info- to make sure records are sealed, check with the arresting police force to ensure this has occurred. Even if they don't have direct access to that info they are a 1st point of contact and can at least confirm/deny whether your fingerprint files were destroyed.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still would be paying too much at that price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that Maroon 5 is considered a successful group and the $ and fame doesn't hurt, but personally I would want to make music that I could look back on when the lights go out and not be embarrassed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirty dangles boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez man at least make it believable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point? Still a good joke and as it stands now, the Leafs are in and would be making arrangements up until the date they are eliminated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo. Well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your way of finding new music to listen to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also wins the award for one of the best ever interviews:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nqC1TCw9Khk
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the system settings I think you go to addons-manage dependencies-universal resolvers then enter in your RD info. My apologies if this isn't 100% correct, can't access Kodi at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know. Thanks for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart. Did you not think the victim could ID your residence in his statement to police? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much. The CA Montreal one is the best for me. It's funny how the one closest to you isn't always the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
