<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6782</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 04:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm I agree, now I want one. Car looks gud OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 06:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original sequence: http://onlinesequencer.net/72518 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Radio Dept. - Pet Grief - MIDI created in OnlineSequencer, edited in Guitar Pro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 06:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 12:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me like 5 times now. It's god damn annoying and impossible to complete.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 09:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty neat for real CF, how did you get the badge on there? I've got an AvoJDM mesh grill on mine and I was always considering getting a badge on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 07:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this on Club.Lib, nice! What front grill is that you have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 07:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probationary licence. You get them after you pass certain learners tests (different from state to state) and there's some restrictions that you have to adhere to. So yes, basically 'new' (and most of the time, young) drivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 06:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's amazing, any videos of it running or anything or is it still nowhere near complete?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 14:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine's doing some weird stuff as well, pretty annoying because I was downloading for around 3 hours now and it reached 90% and then failed with that stupid error. My connection is usually fine with everything else too even though I'm from Aus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 12:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having this issue too although I usually don't get to 10%. The timer puts up some pretty ridiculous numbers too. At some points it was in the thousands of minutes...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That saved my ass. Cheers! Inspect Elemented both those and copy and pasted into a new sheet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next time I'll remember to check the site before I save... sigh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 16:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 00:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck to all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have to try Paseanos some time soon then! Any recommendations specifically from there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 14:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Bent East, but I love Zack's Pizza on Centre Rd in Bentleigh. Best pizzas I've had considering the price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Radio Dept - Pet Grief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 12:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really... although it seems to have slightly resolved itself over time. I don't know what changed it, but it's certainly bearable now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 07:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiiiiinally. Although I would kill to highlight notes in just one section or selection too...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completed, I really hope it helps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 06:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, still down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 14:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close enough I guess, I wish I could find a bigger model though!

http://imgur.com/a/AdUl2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 00:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 06:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent a PM OP. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Site down temporarily? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 15:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 04:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try restarting the Logitech Profiler (if you're using it). Seems to work for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The loneliness part is by far the worst for me. It doesn't seem to matter if I'm talking to people, or surrounded by friends, I still feel like I'm on my own. Occasionally someone enters your life and that void is filled temporarily, but I don't think it's healthy to rely on others to always counter the loneliness. I'm glad to hear that you're ok. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Honestly I'm not comfortable with uploading the GP file yet, I would rather upload it to places like ultimateguitar myself first and link from there. On top of this, the file will not be accurate at all since I used 21 different instruments to make this. I just wanted to make it sound accurate so I used random instruments to replicate it. So, maybe I will answer with "soon". :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 02:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a some amount of anxiety too. I know for a fact I don't have it as bad as other people, but there really isn't any point comparing everyone's problems. I recently had someone who helped me up to this point, but something happened and I can't really talk to them any more. It really hurts not having them around to keep me company any more, but I have to move on. I am so happy that you found someone to talk to, I know how much it helps. And you're right; there's so many nice people out there, it's just difficult to find! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 02:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, but are you ok? If you need someone to talk to, PM me. I can't really offer that much advice or anything but at the least I'm willing to listen. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 02:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it's still difficult though. That said I know I don't have it the worst... it keeps my head above the water sometimes. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 15:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 15:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! That said, it was certainly difficult to reach out for help, it's something I probably should've done months ago. I do have counselling and many friends behind me now. It is very comforting to come across somebody who cares!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 12:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it certainly means a lot by just posting in this thread! I hope you're doing ok yourself too. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 11:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I forget that most people are inherently good... 

Thank you and Happy New Year to you, and the rest of r/Melb too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 11:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really appreciate the community here until now, this good deed certainly solidified my trust in people. I would absolutely love to meet more new people; it's especially nice during these times of need, and I know there must be others in similar and worse situations right now too. It's just a little difficult to fit in since I'm probably a bit younger than most of the crowd here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 05:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? I posted a MIDI of it myself a few weeks ago... because I made it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I recreated Apocalypse Dreams on Guitar Pro, what does everyone here think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 08:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 01:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 22:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you buy rims you have them forever, go into your HQ and equip them there!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 12:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much yes. There should be some sort of minimum setting where things like challenge markers or other markers can be turned off. I don't see why this isn't a thing already. The map is littered with markers and it's rather an annoyance more than anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There should be a way to turn off the traffic/AI in Free Mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who finds the traffic/AI in this game, in free mode, just a nuisance? Sometimes I even find traffic driving the wrong way on the motorways for some reason. I just want to drive my car on a road without any annoyances or distractions. I wouldn't mind playing offline only if it meant I could roam the world without them. Is there some way to turn them off or keep them at a minimum?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 02:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! There's a smaller lip spoiler thing too that looks nice. Overall the mods for the car are in my opinion, very suitable!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 05:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea why Fraps decided to lose the reds but here's mine after some mods. 

http://imgur.com/a/TArYm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 10:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GXa4X3Hczuw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 03:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I just commented above, uninstalling updates seemed to make some difference. Disabling and re-enabling didn't seem to make any difference. Will try uninstalling it in a while, just need the phone right now and can't risk anything. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 03:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uninstalling updates seemed to do something, definitely less laggy but still not really that bearable. It was almost unusable before but now just very annoying. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 01:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is precisely what I'm experiencing too. I haven't seen any others post this issue either which is why I brought this to attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
