<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 11:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh geeze:~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 11:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checked out. Take my upvote at the very least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i really am sorry about that:/ 

I hope things do get better:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh definitely. Luckily I'm just a sad drunk. I write those sad horror stories when I'm drunk and the more intricate series when I'm sober. 

I mean the best stories are the untrue ones@!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or sober me and drunk me. 

They both write stories, but we haven't determined a winner yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh one of my favorite new authors:)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well don't look at my submission history bud. 

Seriously though. You're just nitpicking. Ignore and move on if it's annoying. 

Report and move on if it breaks rules.

Don't throw a hissy fit on the ooc because certain titles make your dick hole sting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relationship Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My First Relationship Was My Craziest Relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 14 years old my mother sat me down on the living room sofa and told me that she could not afford to send me to the private school I went to anymore. I tried to fake disappointment, but the excitement of going to a school with far less rules filled me with excitement. Dont get me wrong, I wasnt a bad kid, but at my old school we would get detention for even saying the word stupid. 

I told her I was okay with that, and with relief on her face she gave me a hug and told me that she would try her best to make this as good of an experience as she possibly could. 

Let me give you a little bit of background information about my earlier school days. From 1st-2nd grade I was the weirdo that walked around the playground and cried because no one wanted to play with him. 3rd to 7th grade I was the kid that kept speaking up at the wrong times, and ended up being the complete laughing stock of the whole school. My 8th grade year was the worst year for me. My only friend went to a different school, and I was stuck with kids that relentlessly teased me for being an outsider. While other kids started to date; I struggled to even get a hi from a person of the opposite gender.

The fact that I would be able to start again for high school was an absolute relief for me. Plus the lack of rules made the deal even sweeter for me. 

The first week of my high school life flew past before I could even look back. I had already made fast friends with a couple of kids, and even managed to talk to a couple of girls. Basic high school life for most kids, but for me this was heaven. 

On the bus ride back around a month into my new school a girl walked up to me. She looked nervous, but still managed to mutter, wanna ride bikes with me later? She was a very normal looking girl. She had brown hair, green eyes, and tight lips, but I had seen her around my neighborhood a couple of times and we got off on the same bus stop. When she saw me nod yes she smiled and walked back to her seat. 

When we got off at our stop she walked right next with me the whole way back to my house. She didnt say a word, but I figured she was just shy. When I got to my house she just told me that she would be over in 1 hour and walked to her house. I went inside and told my mom that I was going to go bike riding with a friend in an hour. She asked me who it was. I told her it was with the girl that lived in our neighborhood and she started to gush about me finding a little girlfriend. I tried to act embarrassed, but I couldnt help but keep on smiling.

I ran into the kitchen and stuffed a couple of snack in a plastic bag and waited on the driveway of our house until I saw her coming from a distance. I hopped on my bike and rode towards her. She gave me a little wave and we rode around the neighborhood a couple of times. After about an hour we stopped riding for a second to take a quick rest and snack break. I took out two granola bars and we munched in silence. After she took finished her bar she turned to me and stuck out a hand before saying, Hey my name is June. I grabbed it and shook it while replying back with, Hey my name is Jay. After the greeting we hopped back on our bikes and rode around until it became dark. We parted ways with a quick hug, but I knew I met someone special.

We spent hours a day together after the bike ride. Sometimes we would go to the library, other times we would go to the Big Lots in the nearby strip mall, and a couple of times we would hang out in her room watching a couple of her favorite movies. Three months into us hanging out she brought up the idea for us to date. I gave her an excited yes but she told me that I had to ask her. I was still nervous. I knew she was going to say yes, but it was my first time and I didnt want to somehow mess it up. I tried asking a couple of times, but the words would not come out. She kept laughing at my attempts, but I could tell she just wanted me to get it over with. Three minutes and over 20 attempts later I managed to blurt out the question and she gave me a yes with a light peck on my lips.

The relationship lasted 5 months. 4 months of the relationship was amazing. 

The last month of the relationship and the month following were the worst days of my life. 

I could tell the relationship was going sour when June started to criticize every small thing I did wrong. If I went to fast on the bike she would yell at me to slow down. If I talked too much she would simply tell me to shut up. Every single day she would get more and more strict about how I acted, and made sure I acted in a way that pleased her. After a couple of days she grew tired of the yelling and proceeded to start hitting. It was never bad hits, but I realized that she would hit me more often when we were alone. 

I started to ignore her, but she still managed to catch up to me no matter how fast I walked after I got off of the bus. 

The day I told her I wanted to break up was the day that everything truly fell to shit for me. She started by knocking on our door at random times. At first she would only come on the afternoons to knock, but after a week she started to knock in the middle of the night. Several times, my mother would have to get up from her sleep and answer the door. I would hear June ask where I was. My mother was patient at first, but after the first couple of times she started to yell at her to leave us alone. 

June still tried to talk to me on the bus on the way to school and the ride back to our house, but I remained silent. 

7 months and 4 days later June was found dead in the entrance to the woods at our school. There were no witnesses or subjects. For the next two weeks they tried to find some type of evidence on Junes body or through the cameras, but nothing was found. Her whole body was suspended in to the air hanging by a rope. Her midsection was sliced opened with some of her intestines touching the ground.

I am 21 now, and Im working at the library that June and I used to visit. Today, for some odd reason, memories of June filled my thoughts. I decided to look through all of the books we claimed as our favorites. I got to the book that she claimed as her favorite book of all time. 

Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck

I rented it out and took it home with me when I got off of work.

When I got home I sat on my couch and read the book. Near the end of the book was a folded piece of paper. I unfolded it and read what was written inside.

Jay, just know that I really do love you. 

I know I yelled at you and hit you, but I was told to.

Dont roll your eyes. I know you are, but Im not just passing off the blame. 

On my way home your mother approached me. She told me that I needed to make you break up with me. She told me that you had a bunch of problems that made it important you were taken care of by your mother. 

I tried to make you break up with me, but you just wouldnt. No matter how mean I acted towards you. You still kept trying to fix things. I know now that there is nothing wrong with you. There was never anything wrong with you.

I tried to talk to you. I came to your house. In the afternoon and at night, but your mother made it very clear that I shouldnt talk to you anymore. That I should just leave you alone. I tried talking to you on the bus, but I know that I just ruined it all for us. I know everyone says young people like us dont know anything about love, but I did. I really did.

Tomorrow Im meeting with a guy. He told me that he would be able to help me find a way to fix everything. He was sent by your mother. He told me that she was sorry for everything and she wanted us to be back together.

I hope when youre reading this note with me, but if youre not. Just read the book one more time. 

Sometimes we have no choice but to fuck up. Its how we are made.

Love,

[June] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 year old gets macked on by old creepy guy. 12 year old ends up being a cannibal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................Read the rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I act like i hate it but i secretly love people commenting and messaging me about how i should write for black mirror:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All i honestly do is write every day.

I sucked at first but i can see myself fetting better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we all are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite the tragedy. I laughed. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please be careful .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ew bugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Double Check Before Stepping Down From Anything At Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the third time this morning I stare at myself in the mirror. I cant help but be disappointed with what I see. What used to be short and spiffy hair is now a reddish-brown mop on top of my head. What used to be eyes full of passion and lips that spit out words with confidence are now full of depression. I used to be fit and lean, but now I see wiry arms and the start of a gut. I hate how I look now, but it is who I have become. I dont want to go outside unless I really have to, and I dont want to exercise anymore. I dont have a need to exercise anymore. 

Five years ago I was honorably discharged from the military. A year after I came back from my tour in Iraq. I have PTSD now, but it wasnt from Iraq. It was from what happened in Fort Bragg, North Carolina. 

I have been too scared to tell anyone, but maybe even one of you guys will know what the fuck these things were. If you dont believe it, I understand. I wouldnt either.

After using up my month of leave I was stationed to Fort Bragg, North Carolina. Whenever I had some free time in the first couple of days I took the bus and explored the city of Spring Lake and Fayetteville. The first thing I noticed was that there was almost nothing to do in either city. A couple of fast food restaurants here and there, a movie theater with a cheesy arcade next to it, and an unlimited amount of churches. There was a mall, but the mall barely had any stores that I actually enjoyed looking around. The base actually had more things to do at a much better price. 

The barracks werent necessarily a nice place to live, but it had everything that a normal room would have. Our barrack consisted of two floors, and each floor was equipped with 2 restrooms with 8 showers a piece. I was on the second floor with 19 other soldiers.

Three months passed by in a blur. Whenever I needed any groceries I went to the commissary. If I needed anything else I would go to the PX. If I was bored I would either bowl or watch a movie. Other than that I was mostly lying on my bed and reading a book. It may seem like a dull life, but I actually enjoyed my little routine. I wasnt paid all that well, but housing was provided and my food was dirt cheap. 

I was finally happy and at ease, but all good things come to an end.

On a Saturday evening, I was asleep in my room, but I woke up to the sound of something clicking all around the floor. I turned on the lamp and saw hundreds of little bug like creatures fleeing into several holes in the walls of my room. I hate bugs. I really do, but I dont want to be the guy that filed a report for finding bugs in my room. So I turned the light off and went back to sleep. 

Every night. 

Every fucking night.

I would wake up in the middle of the night and hear those damn bugs crawling all over the floor, but I would just ignore it and continue to sleep. 

With each passing night, however, it became harder to fall back asleep. The sound of their movements kept getting louder and louder. I could hardly sleep now. The other soldiers in the same barrack as me seemed to be suffering from lack of sleep as well. I brought it up to a couple of the other guys while we ate our lunch, but they just told me to ignore it. I tried to argue but quickly realized there was no point. 

I kept silent, and the problem was ignored for 4 months. 

The silence was broken by the sound of screaming and wailing in the middle of the night on a Tuesday. It came from the room next to mine. I jumped out of my bed and ran out the room. I knocked on his door, but the screaming continued. I tried to open it, but it was locked. Other soldiers ran out of their room and tried to help me open the door, but we could not manage to pry the door open before the screaming ceased. Ten minutes later Sgt. Harrison came with a key and opened the door. 

PFC Grant was covered head to toe in those bugs, but they have grown in size since the last time I saw them. Each of them had the length and thickness of my index finger. I ran into the room and tried to slap them away, but they held on to Grants body tightly. I tried to pull them off, but three other soldiers ran into the room and drug me out. I tried to run back in but they pulled me back even harder. I finally gave up and watched the bugs eat Grants lifeless body. 

When they scurried off I finally got a chance to see what he looked like now. I almost threw up, but I swallowed back the disgusting bile and tried my hardest to maintain my composure. His face was halfway eaten off. He had small holes throughout his neck and his body. 

I looked behind me and saw that the remaining 18 soldiers had already started to run out of the building. I took one last look at Grant and ran towards the exit. 

I went down the first set of stairs but stopped immediately when I saw the 18 soldiers standing completely still in front of the doors. Just like Grant they were all completely covered by the bugs. I backed myself up and ran back up the stairs. I rushed into my room and jumped on top of my bed and sat on my bed for hours. I kept the lamp on and stayed awake until the morning. 

As carefully and quietly as I could be I managed to get out of the building. 

That day we lost 42 soldiers in total. 

I know that this may seem like a random story to tell all of you guys, but there is something I have noticed in the past couple of months. 

In the movies, tv shows, music videos, news, and everywhere I go, I see those [tiny black creatures] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/). 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes it is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh shit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For each downvote he has made, he will have a sliver of his meat slowly sliced off of his thighs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is what I whispered when I read a couple of the comments, but I would never, ever judge another person's writing. This heartless fool, however, will get what is coming to him very soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a knife in my hand and rage in my soul, I search for the mother fucker that came through and downvoted all of the comments. I don't know who you are yet, but I won't stop until your head is parted away from your worthless body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you very much!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look down at my battered right hand. Try to put my hand into a fist, but it is still much too hard to even move a finger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fun little activity I guess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let's do something a little fun.

We use the comments to create a little horror story.

Max:3 lines

Minimum: 10 words.

Rules: Not really any rules, Just has to be horror and creepy! Also, can not be posted on NoSleep,

Reply to the story in the comments that you want to continue in!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @ban timyoung mwahahahhahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just use the momentum you have to continue to write a couple more standalones. 

Then when you have a lot of people's interests. Drop a series on em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .kill TimYoung </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit:/ I'm gonna sleep anyways.

Whispers "bitch" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck shit god damnit I'm awful sorry:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep using bad words:c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad i don't care about the upvotes XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckkkkkk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha i can make a second part just for you guys!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stahp. You're a great writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will always love my father </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father was amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know how I got these scars?!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Story Behind My 8 Scars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a total of eight scars on my body. Two scars are on my face, three are on my back, two scars on my chest, and the last scar is across the knuckles of my right hand.

I never felt comfortable about talking about how I got any of my scars. There has only been one person in the world I decided to tell about my scars until now. That person is my wife. She has asked me several times while we were dating, but I always told her I would just tell her later when I felt more comfortable. I know it bothered her, but I didnt want to scare her away. Today is the day I finally feel brave enough. I decided to tell my wife and then tell you all because I feel like it may contain some important lessons.

As you know yesterday was Valentines Day. I brought home a letter that I wrote for her with the story of my scars and a heart-shaped box of chocolate. She went to grab for her gifts but I told her to meet me in the bedroom. She followed me in and we sat on our bed. I handed her the letter first. 

This is what I wrote.

Today is Valentines Day and I want to let you know that I love you. Im sorry I have kept this a secret for so long, but please do not be afraid of me after you read this.

Ironically, I received the first scar on Valentines Day. I was seven years old and I accidentally broke the tv my father had just bought. He walked up to me and started yelling at me. I tried to tell him it was an accident, but he refused to listen to a word I had to say. He didnt realize it, but he was holding a small pocket knife in his hand while yelling at me. I closed my eyes while I started to cry, but a pain erupted from the middle of my chest. I opened my eyes and started to scream in pain. I blacked out and woke up on my bed. I had three stitches in my chest and my father was sitting next to my bed. He rubbed my shoulder and told me I was fine. 

When I was 11 years old I came home from school and my parents were in the middle of an argument. I tried to sneak past them, but as I was walking past the entrance to the kitchen I feel something hard smash on my back. I tried to keep walking, but with each step, I could feel glass pieces digging and ripping into my skin and flesh. I heard a gasp coming from the kitchen before I blacked out once again. I woke up in the middle of the night. I was leaned over to my right side, and my father was standing in the corner of the room. When he saw me wake up he put a finger up to his mouth and stood there for a couple of hours. I tried to go back to sleep, but I was afraid of what my father would do to me. 

When I was between the ages of 11 to 14 I had trouble sleeping. I tried to still keep my eyes closed because whenever I opened my eyes I would see my father standing off in the corner of my room staring right at me. I was scared for my life. I tried everything to stay asleep, but it was impossible. I hated my dad, and I just wished that he would go away forever. 

The next couple of years I tried to avoid my father as much as I could. I did a pretty good job until I was 14 years old. It all started on a Friday. I got off of the bus and walked to my house. When I got close I saw my father standing in the middle of our lawn. I tried to walk past him, but he jumped in front of me. With a gruff voice, he said, Dont come in here. Just go. We dont have time to deal with you anymore. I tried to run past him and call out for my mom but my father threw me down on the ground. I looked up at my dad, but he threw some money at me and walked back into the house. I honestly didnt know what to do. My face was bleeding and I didnt want to go anywhere else. I ran to the back of the house and into the shed in our backyard. I stayed there for two days. I didnt leave except the few times I would run to the water hose to drink some water. On Sunday I became desperate. I was hungry and I wanted to be back in my home and sleep in my room. I didnt care if my dad hit me again. My father answered the door and pointed at my room. I ran upstairs and dove under my covers. A couple of hours later my father came into my room with a plate of food. I ate every last bite of the food and placed the plate on the side table. 

I thought about reading a book, but I didnt have the strength to get up from my bed. For a little over an hour, I imagined myself being in a much better family. A family where everyone loved each other and the parents didnt spend the whole time arguing. That is all I ever hoped for, but even at that young age, I knew it was not possible. 

I dont know when I fell asleep, but I woke up and screamed in pain. My chest felt like it was on fire. I tried to get up but something pushed me onto my stomach and held my head down. It became hard to breathe and I started to struggle even harder before I felt something hit the side of my head and the world went blank. When I woke back up again it was still dark. I looked to my left and right but didnt see anyone. I slowly rolled back onto my back and saw my father standing in the doorway. He had a knife in his hands and kept both of his eyes on me. 

I started to shout for my mother, but my dad ran up to me and put his hand over my mouth. I settled down and stared at him. When he took his hand off of my mouth I remained quiet. He still had the knife in his hands and the last thing I wanted to do was make him angry again.

Now you know why I have the 7 scars. 

The eighth scar came from the day of my graduation. Neither my mother nor my father showed up. I wasnt sad, though. I didnt care. I was just glad I was off to college in a couple of months. It was a great day for me. After the graduation, I went with a couple of buddies and went to a party. It was the first party I went to and the first time I drank alcohol. I didnt drink too much, but I still felt happier than I have ever felt in my whole life.

The fun stopped when I got home. 

The first thing I noticed was the blood all over our white couch in our living room. Next thing I noticed was my father lying face down beside the couch. I walked over to him and saw blood all around his chest and midsection area. I turned him around and saw that he had been shot 3 times in his midsection. I was about to lay him back down when his eyes opened and his lips started moving. 

Despite the shots he took, he still managed to have the longest conversation I have ever had with him.

Father: s-s-ave you

Me: What do you mean?

Father: your m-mom didnt want you. I love her and y-you. I wanted it to w-work.

Me: Youre the one that didnt want me. You didnt care about me.

Father: N-no please remember

He took his last breath and never moved another muscle. 

I sat on the ground next to him and tried to think of what he said. Why he would even say anything like that about my mother, and then the memories hit me. My father holding the knife and yelling at me when I was 7; He didnt stab me. My mother bumped into him while he was yelling at me. 

When I was 11 she was the one that threw the dish at my back. It wasnt an accident. I dont remember what they were arguing about, but he was just watching over me at night so that my mother wouldnt come in. He stayed there every night so that my mother wouldnt come in and try to do anything.

At 14 he had it. He didnt want to leave my mother. He loved her. He really did. He loved me too, but he just couldnt handle the stress and torture he put himself through. That was the only time he hit me. 

I heard my mother coming downstairs. She gave me a smile when she saw me and walked towards me with the gun still in her right hand. 

Before she could do anything I jumped on top of her and punched her in the stupid face for every single scar, for taking the life of the only parent that loved me, for making me hate my father, and for still being able to smile through it all. I dont know which bone on her face cut through the skin on my knuckles, but I know one thing it is the only scar I can appreciate.

When the cops came they asked me question after question. I answered all of them honestly. I was not charged. It was all self-defense. 

That is how I got my 8 scars. I want you to promise me one thing. To still love me the same way you have always loved me. Please dont think of me as an evil person. I love you and I will always love you. 

Forever Your Valentine, 

subject8631

My wife looked at me with eyes full of love, and I knew I didnt mess up by letting her know.

I just wanted to share this with you guys, because we tend to forget who cares for us and who is trying to kill us. Please be careful with whom you [trust] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to say I am super excited for the two things i have with you guys, I look forward to the end product!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well done OP maybe i will choose you in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was not chosen. Sorry guys. The app will not work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you just gonna copy and paste now? 

Let's start something new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even a story posted..

Not even a comment on nosleep made...

Feels self entitled enough to make a rant on the ooc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why the fuck are you still here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that time, and that was the best thing you could come up with.

good job for utilizing facebook memes for an insult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh good job! You know how to copy and paste:D

Now learn how to: Ignore and Move the Fuck On! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that even an insult? 

I don't want to be a Stephen King. 

You however, seem like a copy and paste of a fuckboy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love being worshipped?!? hahhahahhah you're fucking funny as fuck dude. I actually don't even see myself as one of the better writers on here. I started 3 months ago. I never came off as cocky. I was just saying that the authors do not deserve your tiny little bitching session. 

Solution: Get off of your fucking high horse and go back to your goddamn anime and darksouls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ummmm you having a word seizure or are you sucking dick while you type? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Reddit does still contain little whiny asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does talking like a little sarcastic asshole make you feel better about yourself? I'll plug in my FB because I actually make the content instead of writing down complaints like a little bitch. 3

We take scrutiny. 

It's called messages, but your neanderthal brain couldn't possibly fathom such a logical response! OH NO

I could never ask that from you... Never,,,

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and you're acting like a whiny brat. It's not hilarious. Just a bit sad to be quite honest. I'm sorry you have the need to rant about a type of story or a couple of sentences from a story to write a post about it on the ooc. 

Incorrect. NoSleepWorkshop is for single stories. Not NoSleep as a whole...

If my comments stop any other reader from bashing and ranting and whining about a certain group of stories and decide to just move on to another story they actually enjoy I have done a much better job improving NoSleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but... it's still a couple of stories. That... You know. Take hours to write...

I don't complain about other stories because i spend a fair amount of time to write my stories, and i know other people do the same. They just have a different method of writing. 

It's just the ooc is here to make NoSleep better. Not whine about a general group of stories that will never go away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find story bashing an annoying trope that needs to stop, but whatttt do i know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kinda had a you won't believe what happened! feel haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the majority is between the ages of 18-30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But momma sez i can't think good.

Sorry sorry. I just really liked that story :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got you if you need any info about shrimp chips. Even the spicy kind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha definitely!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go through my submitted!!! I have a bunchhhh of em lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aspiring author! Started off as a hobby!

I started about 3 months ago haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yesss it really does haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha not my first removal! It's all good haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making a new story now don't worry!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> clickbait title. haha it was my own fault!:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was removed. haha sorry i didn't delete it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait what? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *bows

Thank you so much so proud :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh shit i never saw this!!! THANKYOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should've kept it a secret. swear to go. all of those beer and shower things we've done together.

*glaring* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WAIT. You're not a soccer mom? I just thought you forgot to wax a couple of decades -.- I'm done talking to you Feyed.

DONE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Stands up to applause the great answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice to meet you Mr. 15  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhh so i wrote a story about an app called life is beta.

your app is in beta:p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pheromone Spray was Deleted so here you go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know by the time everyone is done reading the next sentence most of you guys will be shaking your heads and calling me an idiot. I bought one of those pheromone colognes online. I never really believed in any of that, but for some odd reason, this one just seemed to make complete sense to me. Plus at only seven dollars a bottle I figured the worst case scenario is losing out on seven dollars. It was called Lust Enhancer and in 5 days it would be in my mailbox.

Im not going to lie. For the next 5 days, I checked the mailbox to see if it happened to come in early but walked back into my house with a slight feeling of sadness. I just really wanted more people to pay attention to me. As a bisexual male that never got the attention of either gender I wanted, no needed, something to help me obtain some sort of romance. Im 29 years old and I havent even gone on a date before. I havent had my first kiss before. I sucked a dick back in college, but the guy never called me back or even acknowledged my presence after that.

Yesterday evening when I came back from work I checked my mailbox and found a small brown box inside. I grabbed the box and ran back inside of my house. I excitedly tore open the box and a piece of paper fell out. On the top it said Instructions and right below it was only one simple sentence.

One spray every 3 days.

I took the small bottle out of the box and looked it over. Inside of the bottle was a thicker clear liquid. Whenever I moved the bottle the liquid slowly moved towards whatever direction the bottle was at. I set it down on the table and watched the liquid slowly settle back down. I wondered how it would come out of the bottle so I uncapped it and sprayed myself in the neck.

When the liquid hit me in the neck I let out a loud gasp. It felt like water hitting my neck, but I could feel the liquid moving. I dont really know how to explain it any better other than that it felt like the liquid dug into my pores. I tried to rub out whatever was left, but my neck was completely dry. I could feel myself start to panic so I took a couple of deep breaths and started to rationalize with myself. Im just tired. Cologne does tend to dry up as soon as it touches any type of skin. The liquid was not moving. Maybe it was just running a little bit because I sprayed so close to my neck.

After I managed to calm myself down I ordered a pizza. I was hungry and curious now. Whoever came up to the door will definitely be affected by the cologne if it is real.

40 minutes later someone rang my doorbell. A 30 something-year-old guy was standing outside with a pizza in his hands. I walked up closer to him and asked him what the total was. With a look of confusion on his face, he told me that it would be $14.19. I asked him if there was anything else I could pay him with, and to my excitement, his face started to go from confused to somewhat turned on. I grabbed him by his arm and pulled him inside.
I wont go into details, but I got a free pizza. He was a biter which I liked, but at times he bit a little too hard. I didnt care. I loved it. I woke up this morning to see another person lying next to me for the first time. I gave him a little kiss on the cheek and he woke up. I asked him if he wanted breakfast and he nodded his head. While I was in the kitchen making some eggs and bacon he walked into the kitchen and told me that he was fired last night. He also told me that this was his first time ever doing anything with another guy. I laughed and told him to sit down.
After breakfast, he started to look a little distant. He kept being short whenever I asked him a question, and by 2 pm he snuck out of my house while I used the restroom.

It didnt really make me sad, though. I mean there are plenty other people around where I live. Take, for example, the lovely brunette that lives 3 doors down. I had a crush on her for the past 2 years, but I never had the courage to even talk to her.

That is when I messed up. I grabbed the bottle of cologne and sprayed my neck two more times. It felt like the liquid went inside of my pores again, but this time I was fine with it. I walked over to her house and knocked on her door. When she opened her door she looked at me for a second and asked me if I lived a couple houses down from her. I laughed and told her that I did and that my vacuum cleaner just broke down. She gave me a little laugh and told me that she would go get hers for me.

I was overflowing with confidence that moment. Without a second thought, I took off my shoes and walked into her house. I walked up to the little hallway she walked into and saw that she was pulling the vacuum out of a small closet. I walked up to her and hugged her from behind. She jumped up in surprise and shoved me off, but after a couple of seconds, she noticed my smell. She walked back up to me and slowly licked my cheek before I blacked out.

It was nighttime when I regained consciousness. Pain erupted from all over my face. I got up from the bed and walked out the bedroom door. The girl was lying on the ground snoring. Her mouth was covered in blood. I bolted out of her house and ran back home. My cell phone was charging on my living room sofa next to the bottle of cologne. I grabbed the phone and dialed 911. I saw my face from the front facing camera on my phone. Most of my face has been torn off. There are bite marks around each gash on my face. There is almost nothing covering the bottom of my right eye. My cheeks are pretty much gone.

Im in the hospital now.

The doctors asked me if I remembered anything, but I remained silent. I cant blame her for this. I can only blame myself. Im here to give you all a warning. If you find a pheromone spray called Lust Enhancer get it.
It really works, but please only spray once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well. Look at buzzfeed. It's simplistic as hell, but they still draw in a larger crowd. The more popular websites are simplistic. People just want everything to be simple. 

NoSleep has all ages that read, but yes, a lot of our readers are mostly young adults to early 30's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thank you! it is still on here . It's called Please Help Me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I kept reading other great NoSleep stories and I remembered wanting to write when I was around 8 or 9. So I decided to start off with a series.(Did Terribly) Then started doing single stories. After a couple of slightly successful stories I decided to keep going lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we both had out own delusions of grief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pshhh read your own stories haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blah i know:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember. Only one spray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :/ i don't think there is a next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how scared I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the link is in the bottom of the story lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must. Resist. Making. Dumb. Joke...

GAHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was made by a previously banned user. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am planning on working on a book! I just have to piece together some stories and add meat to them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a stand alone story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was creppy to me. My wife was ignoring her kid. She was acting like a doll was her kid. The whispering really freaked me out. Im sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just making an unnecessarily mean comment to make your point even clearer:/ failed joke:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Zooey thanks you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Just like his username says. He's just trailer trash. 

He's using the one computer their whole family uses to display hatred:) My daughter shows more promise than him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can leave:) go back to your little black mirror dick sucking festival:) i make my content. You just gag on the dicks of professional writers. 

Seriously:) you are dismissed:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck outta here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wife Is Taking Care Of A Baby Doll More Than Our Daughter  /r/nosleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wife Is Taking Care Of A Baby Doll More Than Our Daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the day my daughter was born I could tell that she was something special. We named her Zooey and she was the smartest baby I have ever seen. Every single month I loved my special little girl more and more, but for some odd reason my wife distanced herself away from Zooey every single month. By the 6th month my wife barely even gave Zooey a glance. I could tell it made Zooey sad, but I didnt really want to bring it up. I just wanted my daughter to know that I loved her very much.

Zooey said her first word when she was 3 months old. 

Daddy. 

She never really said Mommy or even Mom, but my wife never seemed to mind. If anything she finally looked to be in a much better mood. 

By the time she was 6 months Zooey started to walk. She would still fall sometimes, but I was completely blown away by how strong willed her young mind was. Instead of crying whenever she fell she would just pick herself back up and continue trying.

On Zooeys first birthday my wife was busy with work so I shared a very special day with my daughter. I got her a chocolate cake for her to smash and devour. She didnt touch it, but she looked perfectly happy with staring at the cake with a look of wonder on her face. We spent the rest of the day playing with her presents until it was her bedtime. My wife didnt come home until 10 pm. I asked her where she was, but she just put her hand up to my face and walked past me and into our bedroom. 

I sighed and watched tv until I fell asleep on the couch. I woke up to the sounds of my wife and Zooey talking. My wife was trying to get her to say Mommy, but Zooey kept clapping her hands while saying Daddy! with a wide smile on her face. That was the last time my wife tried talking to Zooey. 

On the day of Zooeys 2nd birthday my wife told me she was going to stay later at work. I tried begging and reasoning with her to stay, but she just told me it wasnt worth it. I heard sniffles from behind me when my wife left the house. I turned around to see a tear stricken Zooey staring out the door. She asked me if mommy didnt love her, but I just hugged her and told her that we both loved her very much. After I pulled away from the hug Zooey asked me, Why doesnt she talk to me? I told her that mommy was just stressed, and to not let it bug her. I got her another cake, but she told me that she didnt like to eat cake. She thought it was too pretty to destroy.

With a nod I left the cake on the dining room table and took out three brightly colored bags from under the table. We have this tradition where I take out the presents for her and rip the paper as carefully as possible. She liked using the wrapping paper as little decorations for her room. The first two presents were just little bow sets and a couple of new books. The third present was one of those baby dolls you can feed and change. She was really excited about the doll. She played with it in the living room by herself until it was time for bed. 

My wife came back home at 11pm completely drunk. She looked like she was crying, but I was far too tired to even acknowledge that she was there. She did it all of the time to Zooey and now me. Our marriage was falling apart and I really didnt know how to fix it. I thought she was just going to go into the bedroom, but she walked into the middle of the living room and picked up Zooeys new doll. After a couple of seconds she started to hug the doll and rock it back and forth. The bottle and the 3 toy diapers were lying next to it and my wife picked those up as well. She put the bottle up to the baby and started whispering to it. 

I was completely at awe at the sight of my wife showing the baby doll more attention than she ever gave Zooey. She sat down on the couch with the doll and took the bottle out of its mouth and continued to whisper to it. The whispering overwhelmed me with curiosity so I snuck up behind her and tried to listen to what she was saying. It was hard at first, but after a couple of seconds I noticed she was saying the same thing over and over again. Please call me mommy.

After a couple of minutes my wife fell asleep with the toy baby on top of her stomach. I walked into the bedroom and grabbed a blanket for her. After I got her settled in I went back into the bedroom and fell asleep. This morning I woke up to the sound of my wife laughing for the first time in several years. I rushed downstairs to see what the source of her laughter was. When I walked into the kitchen I saw my wife twirling around in circles with the toy baby. Zooey was sitting down with tears falling down her cheeks. I picked up Zooey and asked my wife what she was doing. Each time she spun around she said one word at a time. 

Just

Playing

With

My

Daughter

I told her that Zooey was crying, but my wife just shrugged and kept spinning around with the baby.

This annoyed me quite a bit, but I just took Zooey back into the living room and played with a couple of her older dolls with her. After about an hour later my sweating wife came out of the kitchen and said that she was going to the mall with her daughter. Zooey got up quickly and rushed into her room to change. By the time Zooey came out changed into her outside clothes my wife and the doll were already gone. 

Zooeys bed time rolled around and I put her to bed. While I put her covers over her she asked me, Does momma really love me? I nodded my head at her and smiled. I just told her that momma wanted to surprise her with some new clothes. Zooey fell asleep a couple of minutes later with a tiny smile on her face.

Tonight my wife came home around 9 pm. I walked up to her and asked what was wrong with her. She tried to ignore me, but I kept blocking her way until she stopped and glared at me. She shoved the baby doll in my face and shouted, Shes at least fucking real! Do you know how hard it is to play fucking pretend with you? Zooey is dead. Shes been dead. When are you going to stop playing this stupid game? 

I shouted back at her to stop lying, but my wife just fell into my arms and started sobbing. Zooey came downstairs and stared at us hugging. She gave me a smile and walked back upstairs. I started to sob with my wife as memories started to flood in. Our beautiful daughter died 10 days after we brought her home from the hospital. There was nothing wrong with her. She just fell into a deep sleep she never woke up from. The doctors told us that it was SIDS, but I just never wanted to believe it.

After my wife finally settled down I sat her on the couch and walked upstairs. I walked into Zooeys room and saw all of the little wrapping paper from her presents taped on the walls. The toys I got for her were there and the new bed I bought for her just 2 months ago was there, but Zooey was nowhere to be found. 

With a heavy sigh I closed the door to her bedroom and walked into my room. I looked through all of the photos on my laptop that I thought I took with Zooey, but it was just me taking photos of myself.

I was about to close my laptop down, but I decided to reach out to you guys. I am now in the grieving process. My wife was acting crazy, but I was the crazy one all along. My baby is gone, and I just wish I could experience just [one last day with her] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? I appreciate a story that manages to scare me now. 

Kinda like alcohol. 

Nothing better than brewing your own beer.

Then you realize that normal beer doesn't really get you buzzed anymore. 

Sometimes you'll come across a better beer and shocks the hell out of you. You learn from it and make your beer better. 

Horror=beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like how you wrote this comment 4 hours ago. 

Seriously oc. What the hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just more ammunition for stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had to trademark that shit.

Watch me use it in my next story. Swear to glob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'mere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write your own stories.

You'll notice yourself becoming more and more immune to horror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man i wanted to put predictive text on here, but i resisted. 

-.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
