<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9438</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. There was an extra / in OP's link. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/N6K0p
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Page Not Found
Were sorry, we seem to have lost this page,
but we dont want to lose you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you wake up from a coma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fucking sad that people can't respect other opinions... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will just counter what you said with: "It wasn't true communism, Lenin and Stalin weren't true communists". It is pointless to argue with people who are blinded by ideology. I love free market economy but I see the flaws and I want to remove them. That doesn't apply to lefties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just another step in creating socialistic utopia. It starts with these little incidents and then puts you in jail if you want to criticize government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fully agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody reads articles here. That's why clickbait articles with manufactured outrage get to the top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clickbait. An actual quote from the article:
However, the foreman of the jury that convicted her insisted to the Huffington Post that Fairoozs crime wasnt the giggles, but rather how she conducted herself when being taken out of the hearing.
She did not get convicted for laughing. It was her actions as she was being asked to leave, the foreperson said. We did not agree that she should have been removed for laughing.

If you disrupt a confirmation hearing with an unplanned protest, you're going to be arrested.
And she could face up to a year in prison.

Damn dudes, stop with the outrage over fake loaded title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is going on? Are we getting brigaded by someone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a thing or two about focusing too much on politics. Life is too short to not have fun!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do don't worry :) some Americans can convert metric units to freedom units on the fly ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Universal or single payer is MUCH better than ACA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lD_ag67tH3I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
