<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3967</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 21:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what the hikes are like in Arizona (I hike PNW), but I can't imagine CDBs being comfortable at all for any type of outdoor terrain. Especially for 12 miles. I'm not saying it can't be done, but it can be done much more comfortably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 23:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50-60 on beans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see Hasselbeck return as a QB coach. It'd be awesome to see him on the sideline every week in Seahawks gear. Might have a positive effect on our offensive staff as a whole too, possibly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're thinking about point #1 completely wrong. Be your best self for your SO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was posted like a day ago: https://www.reddit.com/r/goodyearwelt/comments/3r7zuq/the_beginners_boot_buying_guide_v20/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Our story of redemption is well under way." Putting this up on my wall so I can read it every morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that Earl Thomas getting launched into space at the end? LOL dammmmnnnn Collins... damn... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 18:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know your TDEE? Are you tracking intake? Start [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started#wiki_fixing_your_diet). It's quite simple, eat less than your TDEE. Stopped losing weight? Reduce even more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 21:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite honestly, the name is what bugs most XJers as far as I can tell. I'm sure if they called it the "Jeep Something-Other-Than-Cherokee", most of us would be fine with it.

Frankly, I dislike it because it doesn't come in manual. However, I'd absolutely consider a KL for a daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 01:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 35 - 3, Seahawks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 23:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is totally uncalled for... It's fans like you that give the rest of us a ba-hahabwahwhahahwahw fuck the 49ers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 21:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ET3 goes off, Kam kills someone, RW completely shreds their defense on his feet. I'm ready for this game to be our 180-degree, turnaround, unstoppable-fucking-diesel-train point of the season.

Bold prediction: Cary Williams gets 2 INTs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 02:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first issue I ever had with my 98. It's probably the original, which is more than a decade old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 21:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you can really feel Brock's frustration in this breakdown. Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 01:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start small. Don't get overwhelmed with the wealth of (mis)information out there. Find your TDEE using [a calculator](http://www.fitnessfrog.com/calculators/tdee-calculator.html) and *stay under that number*. 

Add exercise later, and even then, start simple: walking, jogging, bodyweight, etc.

Remember, motivation gets you started. Discipline gets you results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 21:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Super Six](http://www.supersixseattle.com/) ($) - Delicious Hawaiian bar/restaurant in Columbia City! The Pineapple Cornbread and Loco Moco are absolutely delicious. They also offer bottomless Mimosas for a reasonable $12. This is a great place to take the family or a group of friends to catch a Seahawks game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 20:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could take a look at [the Undershirt Guy](http://www.undershirtguy.com/). I personally like the [Express Cotton Crew Neck Tee](http://www.express.com/clothing/men/stretch-cotton-crew-neck-tee/pro/5051421/cat1830014). Probably the only thing I buy from Express. They come out to about $15 a shirt if you buy two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 20:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that coat. Details on it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 18:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://localtvktvi.files.wordpress.com/2015/08/cry.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 09:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'll have to explore more of these on my own. They all look really interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 09:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I've heard of this place, but never really Googled it until now. Really cool experience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unique or "exotic" restaurant experiences in Seattle for dinner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 23:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings, fellow Seattle redditors! I'm looking for restaurants in Seattle that offer unique dishes or experiences. 

As an example, [Radiator Whiskey](http://www.radiatorwhiskey.com/food.html) offers a **roasted pig head**, which isn't something you can just find and order at any other restaurant. Another example would be [Art of Table](http://artofthetable.net/category/menu/), where you just sit and **let the chefs serve you whatever the menu is for that day**, without you really ordering.

I was wondering if you knew of any other places that offer unique foods or experiences like this. Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 19:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work 40 hrs a week. I live within walking distance (or 5-10 minute bus ride) to work and my gym is right below my apartment building. Cutting down on commute has saved me so much time to do other, more interesting, things with my time.

For reference, I live in Seattle, work downtown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 22:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be in Portland for the game, any suggestions on bars to watch at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 21:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the top comment discussion in [this old thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/2z2odo/buy_vs_rent_a_home_when_renting_isnt_throwing/) interesting.

 A home isn't an investment. It's a housing choice and a lifestyle choice in which you can build equity. Too many people excuse irresponsible home purchasing decisions by simplistically viewing it as "an investment" which it, by definition, is not.

That said, I'd say purchasing a home in Seattle wouldn't be a bad decision right now. It's a great place to live and, IMO, will continue to become a better place to live moving forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 21:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This article from T-Nation](https://www.t-nation.com/training/truth-about-ass-to-grass-squats) offers good discussion on different types of squat depths, including ATG, which is what you're describing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 18:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see anything wrong with it. Chocolate whey mocha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 17:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything longer than a 5k, I'll throw on my Asics. For light jogs and weightlifting, I have a pair of [Inov8 F-Lite 195s](http://www.inov-8.com/new/global/Product-View-FLite-195-Black-Lime-Azure.html). They are relatively comfortable for jogging (minimalist/barefoot) and have a 3mm drop, which is more comfortable for lifting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 17:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "As good" might be subjective. They're processed, but that doesn't necessarily mean "bad". Fresh is usually better than processed though. That said, I love frozen vegetables for the ease/convenience. As you said, they're easy to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 17:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compression underneath your shirts might help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 17:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less filling. On a cut, I try to eat a ton of vegetables. I know, vegetables can be boring and bland, but they can keep you satiated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 00:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dion responded great, seeing Dion cry after the game really touched me. Made me think about me in pop-warner, cyring cause I hating losing. Vets told him to learn from it, grow from it. I line up with that guy 9 times outta 10.

Man, I like that ET3 has nice things to say about Dion. Maybe he's just talking him up to "protect the team" or whatever, but if there's anyone's judgement I trust in the secondary, it's Thomas'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 00:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I always joke with some of the players every now and then that everyone has Madden nowadays, he said. Everybody gets to play, and they're offensive coordinators on their game. Everybody's picking plays, it's been that for years and years. People are the armchair quarterbacks, are going to be able to poke holes in whatever you're doing...

Anytime my friends say that they could do a better job than Bevell at calling plays, I always tell them, "This shit ain't Madden." It takes years of experience and hours of study to come up with an offensive gameplan.

I'm not a Bevell apologist or anything, but I certainly think there very few people who can do his job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 21:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent! Thanks, I really like this Knit Jacket: http://www.uniqlo.com/uniqloandlemaire/common/images/itemlineup/men/itemlineup_m_08.jpg

I wonder, is it too formal to wear casually? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 21:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Yea, I'm using my wife's conditioner at for the time being, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 21:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Yea, I just really like the feeling. Are there benefits to this pump effect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 21:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't overcoats quite long? I'd like it to be about the length of a peacoat. I'll definitely look into one though. They seem a little more formal-looking, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 19:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool. I use a generic brand of conditioner, will that be good enough? Or should I do more deep research into the proper conditioner? Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look into Schott. I haven't seen one at JCrew, but I'll keep an eye out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 19:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically a single column of buttons vs the double. Not as long as a top/over coat. My terminology is all out of whack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 19:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see. I'll look into sea spray. I was using conditioner to try and "soften" things up, not much real change there. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 18:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else here prefer the "car" coat or "walking" coat to a peacoat? Any recommendations? I'm looking for something that works well for the PNW winter, which isn't comparable to somewhere like Chicago. It'd be a near-daily wear to work (standard office downtown). Looking to spend around $200. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 18:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past decade, I've buzzed my head with a zero clip. I'd like to try growing it out a bit longer, no more than 1". My hair is coarse as hell, so it grows out/up/in all sorts of directions. Any advice for someone growing some hair from a buzz? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 18:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ran of C4 and decided to just do cold-brew coffee and a banana as my pre-workout. Any recommendations out there, brands specifically, for supplements that'll give the "pump" feeling that C4 gave me? Would be nice to just add it to my coffee, but I'm open to pills as well.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 22:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 2 years of waiting/saving, I finally pulled the trigger on a blue ET3 Elite jersey just in time for the season to start! It'll probably be the last jersey I buy for a long time...

That said, I'm selling a Grey Elite "12" in 44 (Large) and a White Limited "12" in Large. PM me for pics/price/details! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 07:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll trade you my Reebok Koren Robinson for your ET...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 21:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just from searching: https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/3hwswk/best_place_to_get_ocbds/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 21:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a mug I got from the Apple store at their HQ. I was on a solo trip and stopped in, bought the mug for myself.

http://i.imgur.com/asl26xy.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 21:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To piggy back this Alan Thrall video, [this "tips" video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AHiSvajoans) from him was a great follow up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 21:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I replaced my driver-side switch (master switch?) and it fixed all my power window/lock problems. Cost me $50 though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 09:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks are always smoking (cigs and bud) right outside my apartment unit. We are moving to a different apartment, away from the main Pike/Pine corridor, as soon as we possibly can. We're on the ground floor. It isn't unbearable, but it's annoying enough for us to consider moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 08:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start simple. Small wins each day. Most importantly, [start here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 08:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great read. Will be looking for the bootleg this Sunday! Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 07:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the one on Capitol Hill, but they're all pretty delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A delicious Seahawks Trophy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 01:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 18:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just by using the search from this past week:

https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/3jseoy/winter_bootswaterproof_boots_for_under_100/
https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/3jmx7k/comfy_fashionable_boot_suggestions/
https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/3kalw9/dark_brown_boot_under_200/

Also, /r/goodyearwelt would have some good recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 18:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite plain, white undershirts? 

I've been reading some reviews from [the Undershirt Guy](http://www.undershirtguy.com/tugs-favorite-undershirts/), just wondering if MFA had any recommendations. I currently have the [Stretch Cotton Crewneck](http://www.express.com/clothing/men/stretch-cotton-crew-neck-tee/pro/5051421/cat810041) from Express, but I am willing to explore other options within the same price-range ($10-15 per shirt).

Thanks MFA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 02:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm usually at Ballroom in Fremont. It isn't "Ivar's Brunch"-good, but they do serve a breakfast pizza. I'm used to the vibe there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 22:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you're in the right corral. Nothing more frustrating than having to dodge tons of people in the beginning of the run. Have fun!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 05:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used the Merrell Trail Glove for 3 years before they ripped along the edges. Ran my first half-marathon in them, lifted, and boxed. I replaced them with Inov-8 F-Lite 195s, only a 3mm drop. Love them so far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 01:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Compiz made me feel soooooooooo elite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 00:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/bodyweightfitness might be able to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 23:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rice or beans are generally cheap gainers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 23:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lower the drop, the better. Have you thought about running/lifting in barefoot/minimalist type shoes? I have dedicated running shoes for longer runs, but I jog/lift in minimalist shoes (3mm drop). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 23:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like GoWiWi. Have yet to try my hand at GoHoWiWi. Any details on your GoHoWiWi strategy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 23:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you done such an extensive cut before? I feel like I'd be very ineffective at work and at the gym being at 1k calories a day within the first week. That's just me personally though, why so drastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 23:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In malls? My preferences are usually Nordstrom and JCrew. Once in awhile I'll hit up the other stores, like Gap, BR, AE, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 22:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/3h7mlx/fallwinter_coat/cu52owd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 22:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's ton of discussion on this already. You can search for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue razz is the only way to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 21:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/mealprepsunday will probably be of more use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 23:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good, I'll head to my nearest one and try one on. I've had bad luck with fitting flannels in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 23:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your fitness level? If you are just getting into fitness, read the [wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started) first. If you're already in shape, I'd recommend sprints, hill-drills, ladder drills, and cone drills. You might want to get with people who know how to do the drills, just to coach you up a little bit.

Check out [this list of cone drills](http://www.kingsportstraining.com/blogs/training-blog/8269753-10-best-speed-and-agility-cone-drills).

Also, [this list of ladder drills](http://www.kingsportstraining.com/blogs/training-blog/7694405-13-speed-and-agility-ladder-drills-videos-for-faster-footwork) (by the same folks).

Good luck! CB is one of the toughest positions in football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 19:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Wilson "look off" the safety? Or was the right side his first read, then progressed left? Anyone with more experience reading plays have insight? Just curious, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 07:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the quality and fit of the AEO flannels? How long have you had them and how often do you wear them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 20:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have guessed this, can someone explain the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 01:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's on my new car, which is a crv

http://media.giphy.com/media/6EYsfaxSEOSbe/giphy.gif

Haha, seriously though, we'll see you back when you inevitably get another XJ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 00:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I evaluate and purge every season. Just did got rid of a bunch of stuff that don't fit before going out and buying pieces for fall/winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 01:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to do this myself, but I rarely drive my XJ at night outside of the city. How long did it take you? How do you like the brightness of these ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 00:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starbucks VIA coffee. Camping, on the road, in a pinch, this is my go too instant coffee.

I'd just like to mention that your boss is an asshole. Sorry you can't take 5 extra minutes to make coffee at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it turn out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 22:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any ideas on how to get a Reebok Earl Thomas jersey? I know, chances are slim, but I figure this thread is a place worth asking... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you talked to your family about this? Does your husband support your decision to get back in shape? You need to communicate what your goals are to your family and see if you can get them on board. If they don't want to be on board, they should AT LEAST give you some support, even if it's being mindful of your diet and exercise schedule.

If they can't give you support, /u/Soleria has given you the only other logical solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it's like a 5 minute read and a good solid foundation for more complicated programs out there. [Getting Started](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started). It really can't get any more straightforward and simple than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 20:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't pay for your wedding with debt. I feel like that's a good way to start your marriage off on poor financial footing. Is there anything you can do to slash the budget of your wedding to fit what you can actually afford?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 20:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many different programs [mentioned here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/getting_started#wiki_adding_exercise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rain + Netflix + coffee, my body is ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will end up losing some muscle, so keep your protein intake up. And, yes, the hunger aspect will suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compression shorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6-7pm, 1 hour in the gym. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can eat 3 donuts a day no problem. He doesn't want to but can't help himself when he watches me selfishly pig out.

*Don't do this in front of him.* That's just torture. Join him in eating healthy, even if you feel like you don't need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's better for me to workout *after* work, I'm just more loose and awake at that time. "Better" will obviously vary person to person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 19:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, running is specialized, so I go to my nearest Road Runner store and go through their "test" to find the best shoes for my particular foot and running style.

I did try out some barefoot shoes and found that they helped me adjust from heel-striking to mid-to-toe-striking, which improved some knee pain I was feeling during longer runs.

Anything other than running, I throw on my trainers. I'm actually in the market for some new ones! Currently looking into Inov8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 18:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You can work from anywhere. Last year I worked probably in five or six different cities around the world. Just working from my laptop wherever we decided to go.

I really wish more companies would let developers take advantage of the ability to work remotely. The time to travel for extended periods of time (more than just a two-week vacation) is one reason I find myself leaving jobs and taking month-long breaks in between. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 01:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm coming up on a year of marriage and I had the same conversation with my wife as the one you are having now. In short, we both have two separate checking accounts, but we devote a sum of money for "shared" expenses into a joint checking account. 

We basically wrote down everything we considered shared (rent, utilities, groceries, etc.) and split it according to the percentage of our monthly income. I make more, so I pay for more, it's just the way we decided to do it.

So far, it's worked wonderfully. Everything absolutely essential is paid for, and I still have some money left over for my own personal hobbies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 01:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wailing on the bag is a great workout, but you might as well learn proper technique while you're at it. That said, shadow box first. Look in the mirror, record yourself, have someone watch, etc. 

I'm no pro boxer, but here's my routine (assuming I'm all warmed up) by round:

1. Jab only
2. Jab-cross (1-2)
3. Jab-cross-hook (1-2-3)
4. Any combo above, as fast as possible
5. Every punch is a knockout punch, as hard as possible, good form

The first three rounds, I'm usually focusing on timing and form. The last two rounds, I focus on fight situations (move my head, step in and out). All five rounds, I'm "dancing" with the bag. Feet are constantly moving with a continuous "orbit" around the bag.

I like [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yMQZLqA0zBQ) too.

Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 07:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I don't know why I didn't just do that in the first place... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 23:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seafood (salmon) is usually what I recommend to guests from out of town. Also, coffee. Can't think of a particular establishment that Seattle is famous for in terms of seafood, too many good places to mention.

Shopping center would be on 5th and Pine, ton of shops within walking distance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RHA M750i Tip Sizing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 22:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for some replacement tips for my IEMs. While I like [the Comply tips](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B004HKIAJC) I purchased about a month ago, I can't seem to get a good seal on them. 

I'm looking for triple-flange tips, but don't know what size to get? Are tip-size pretty much universal? 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 20:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow winter-birthday person here (February). Whistler and Leavenworth come to mind. Winter is gorgeous in those places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 20:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to follow this advice when I can, but when I take breaks from the gym, my diet seems to fall apart as well (junk junk junk). It seems like an all-or-nothing thing for me...

I've been getting better though. When I take breaks from the gym, I'll switch to maintenance (adding more, since I'm cutting). Allows me to "take a break" from the diet as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 20:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also worth noting that tracking calories-burned can vary widely depending on various factors, leading to more inaccurate numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 19:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was already dressed, but I felt the gay didn't match my shirt so I quickly changed.

The gay should always match the shirt...

But yes, I can relate, if something just feels "off" about the way I look in the mirror, I'll change it. I try to timebox myself though, sometimes it makes me late to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 19:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously don't understand how some people think they're so goddamn perfect that they just CAN'T POSSIBLY be tracking calories incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 19:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to get new pants for the 4th time in the past 8 months. Any way I can make my waist hella buff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 08:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will sometimes throw a little extra into my workouts if I'm heading out to eat, just to help my conscience. For the most part, though, I workout to be strong and look good. I'm not competing or anything, so I'll indulge too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, I'll say it. [RattleSnake Ledge](http://www.wta.org/go-hiking/hikes/rattle-snake-ledge). Spectacular view for relatively little work. Close to Seattle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hike Lake Serene (further up north) this past Saturday, didn't notice any difference in air quality than before. It changes with the weather, wind-pattern for sure, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 07:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who used to play defensive end in HS, this pisses me off. As a Seahawks fan, it's fun as hell to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discipline  Motivation

Prioritize the gym higher, go whether you are "pumped up for" it or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 23:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take C4 as a preworkout, but I find that chugging some coffee will give me a nice "boost". I only drink water during workouts. After, I'll take whey protein in a shake.

Haven't used creatine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 19:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are the bass on these? I have a pair of M750i that I use for commuting, but sometimes I just want mad bass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 00:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... silk? Probably something [like this](http://silkathlete.me/collections/mens).

I prefer [Nike compression](http://store.nike.com/us/en_us/pw/mens-base-layer-clothing/7puZbgdZ8jj). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
