<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4019</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 3x great grandfather looking dapper af in Alexandria, VA in around the 40s. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 06:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible that the servant's children are the children of the man she's working for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm come to the conclusion that my ancestor, Bertha Stanley Dudley and her siblings, were illegitimate. Their father is listed as David Dudley on most of their vital records, yet I have no proof that a David Dudley lived with their mother Virginia, other than her father. Is it possible that Bertha's mother Maggie put her father's name on all of her children's records? The man I think might be her children's father is named J.M. Green who is about 52 in the 1900 and is living with his son Norman, Maggie, and her three children. Even though he's about 22 years older than her, is it possible that he's the father of these three Dudley girls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does this sound like Bipolar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does this sound like Bipolar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 09:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't go see anyone, we don't have enough money. Sometimes I feel like I have regular depression then it goes away and I feel great. I actually do housework and always ask my mom if there's more stuff to do and when she says no, I get a little sad. This is usually a two week cycle, sometime more or less. When I am in a depressive state, I feel worthless and can't do anything. I've heard that bipolar runs in families, my granddad was an alcoholic, could that me he was bipolar and passed it on to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone be interested in making a concept album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 06:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only a novice, but I'd love to do this! Would anyone else be interested? Trying to get many people in on it

EDIT: [Here's the Google Docs link for our concept album.](https://docs.google.com/document/d/10zVbat66T6gU7KNqOgMilAkUri8bzg5ikrPIyPn-rhs/edit?usp=sharing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone recommend some Tupac songs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 08:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got into his music a couple of minutes ago while listening to Dear Mama, damn what a great song, I thought I didn't like rap. Is there any other deep songs by Tupac that talk about issues or is he like Lil Wayne (in that he only talks about getting hoes.) I know I just offended someone and I'd like to say excuse my ignorance in rap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do country music fans know that they're getting pandered to nowadays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 18:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the mainstream anyways. They always talking about being country. I think they do this because they've realized that they've essentially abandoned their original audience. Also, do you personally think they are pandering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My self esteem/confidence is non existent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 05:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do we start? I was a fat kid with glasses and didn't wear jeans til 8th grade (it wasn't cause I was too fat, please don't ask) so obviously I was a bully's wet dream. My dad is an abusive asshole who only cares about himself and forced me to play sports and yelled at me when I complained. I have no friends currently, I just sit alone in my house all day and can't drive because I was born premature and people always made fun of me when I was a kid. I really never had more than 5 friends in my entire life, they were just people I talked to. Not to mention the girl I care deeply for hates my guts, well I don't know about hate but she definitely doesn't care about me the way I care about her maybe cause I came on too fast, but that's only cause I really like her, she lives across the street. And now I'm 20 with no job (except a volunteer one), no lady, and no friends. My self esteem/confidence is non existent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone want to co-write a song with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 00:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always loved co-writing songs with people since I'm not nearly good enough to write one myself plus it's cool to bounce ideas around! I was thinking sort of a country song? More traditional though with acoustic instruments. Is anyone interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do women want to be treated like men? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you read while you're depressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 06:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been depressed for about a year and a half and I just want to read but find that I can't pay attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you write about when you don't know what to write about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 20:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't written in awhile thanks to my depression but I really do want to write. What do you write about when you don't know what to write about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is that shipping crap coming over to LoT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read another Reddit post on here saying that Guggenheim was bringing that shipping shit to LoT too. [PLEASE GOD NO!](http://giphy.com/gifs/the-office-no-steve-carell-12XMGIWtrHBl5e) So, is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changeable Usernames. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I'd love if Reddit implemented this idea. I feel that a lot of folks have been asking about this for awhile tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILER/S3E13]Question about Hunter and Bobbie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that we will ever see Hunter and Bobbie again?

EDIT: Apparently, I've just been told that Most Wanted has been greenlit so I'd like to rephrase the question if that's ok. Do you think we'll see them again on AoS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, can you recommend some more country songs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 21:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already have an absurd amount since I've been listening to country all my life. I'm not really into the bro country crap. I stopped listening to the local country radio about 2010. The oldest have is Hank Sr. but not really a fan of the production. The only reason I have some songs by him is because he was a friggin genius when it came to music (imo.) I didn't ask for artist because I'm not really an artist guy, if that makes sense. I'm sorry if I'm being picky about music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Stapleton -- Traveller [country](2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tight Ass Country Club [Arrested Development] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First scene of AD I ever saw, I almost went to the hospital cause I choked on my sandwich because I was laughing to hard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's wrong with liking "dumb shows" with laugh tracks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 06:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask because I was watching The Ranch and seemed to enjoy it and then I looked at the reviews and Reddit. I mean, yeah, I get it, it's no AD, IASIP, Community, but what's wrong with that? It has a laugh track, who the heck cares? Do I like laugh tracks? Not necessarily, I actually find them annoying tbh. Is it the best comedy ever? Not by a long shot, the top three would have to be the ones listed above. Maybe I like it cause I've always wanted to live in the country, who knows. I just don't understand why you can't like/watch "dumb" shows and "smart" shows. 

EDIT: Bring on the downvotes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Eady -- Daylight and Dark [Country](2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 03:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any new Esperanto speakers on this sub? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did you join? How fluent are you in Esperanto? What do you think of the language so far? Are you going to get fluent? Sorry for all the questions, I'm just curious about Esperanto growth.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] [S4] Question about Olicity relationship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 01:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich Robinson -- The Way Home [gospel] (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 05:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, do you like the old style southern accents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 04:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 20 minutes a day a good start for a 20 year old fat guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 00:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really abhor cardio, but since I'd like to not die in my fifties, I decided to go ahead and get it over with. Today, I jumped on the bike for about 20 minutes, it seemed pretty intense, my pedometer said I was going 2.2 mph, don't know if that's a good thing or a bad thing. Any who, does this seem like a good start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just ordered the entire series of Community, AND JESUS WEPT, FOR THERE WERE NO MORE SEASONS TO BUY. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember, the Nazis were Socialist too! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 22:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this PTSD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 06:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2009 I saw both my grandad and my grandma die. My granddad died of lung cancer, and we think my grandma died of a broken heart (they married at 16.) That was just some background info. I don't remember my granddad's funeral (maybe I blocked it out?) and I only remember part of my grandma's. It was when the song was playing, I'll never forget that moment and to this day, I can't listen to that song without thinking about the funeral and getting sad. I try to avoid anything that had to do with my grandma. Redheads, mashed potatoes, her old house, and the song. Those are just a few. I'm a guy, 20 years old, and my therapist told my mom about 6 months ago that he thinks I have depression. Please don't bash me, I'm just looking for answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are supremacists not very sharp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 06:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't just mean white supremacists, I mean all supremacists, they all seem to be very dull, why is this? I'm not trying to be rude, I'm genuinely curious about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the likelihood of a revolution if Bernie doesn't win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 19:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is left-libertarianism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does it make sense that a self defined Libertarian loves Bernie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 08:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why, but I really do love Bernie, the more I watch him, the more I like him. Now, I don't agree with everything he says, but what I do agree with him on, I agree vehemently. My question is, why would a libertarian like/love Bernie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a second season of Fuller House confirmed yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 05:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge Full House fan so when I heard that they had a spin off of sorts coming to Netflix, I was really excited! I'd love to see a season two, does anyone know if it's been confirmed yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do you tell the difference between luck and an immune disorder when it comes to fevers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 20:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rarely get the flu or a fever and always get colds during the winter.  I looked this up, and this could be an immune problem, how do you tell the difference? If this is the wrong sub for this question, I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Her parents aren't in any records. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 01:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name is Callie Madison b. 1880 in Caroline County, VA. She was married (according to the record) December 28, 1899 in Caroline County, VA. Her parents are listed as William Madison and Mary Mills ne Madison. Also, on her death record, her parents are listed as Billy Madison and Mary Farrington. I've had no luck with either four of these names and don't have a paid membership on Ancestry. Please, someone help me, I beg of you. These folks are ghosts. I have found Callie and her husband, Leanious Middlebrooks in 1900-1940 censuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me understand the difference between ig and igx? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 14:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read up on it but I still don't understand the difference between the two. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit should make it easier to switch accounts on a mobile browser. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 01:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On my computer I have RES but I feel that the it is kind of bothersome to do it on a mobile browser (unless I haven't discovered how to switch back and forth between accounts.) You have to completely log out. I feel that this is a pretty good idea. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone get sad when Troy left? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 03:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This title isn't worded quite right but I think you get the idea. What I meant to say was "Did anyone else get sad to see Abed without Troy?" Especially in S5E7, when Jonathan Banks and Danny Pudi are talking together, Abed just seemed so unspeakably sad, and it broke my heart. I was so sad that I was crying, and am while I'm writing this. I mean, Troy and Abed are two peas in the same pod, it just breaks my heart to watch Abed without Troy, he seems so much sadder. Please don't make fun of me for saying this, I know they are just characters, but still. Did anyone feel like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the likelihood that Edward IV was illegitimate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 01:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order for him to have been Richard's son, that would have had to been an eleven month pregnancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Unamed (Western) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What do you guys think of this?](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1I3N3qUOQk-PQyOQsSRvcqKI4APFiSFsh7VaLL8RTXBQ/edit) Granted, it's only one measly scene but it's the first thing I've ever screenwritten. Is there anything I can improve on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate my life, what do I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 00:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off: no, I'm not suicidal, I'm too much of a coward, I have thought about it though. Anyways, let's begin. Everything was fine when I was in high school, then graduation came, everyone was going off and they knew what they were doing, and I stayed home all day. I can't drive (eye problems), the girl I love dearly thinks I'm a creep (I have a tendency of coming on to strong), everyone's moving on, and time is passing every second (I know you can't give advice about that XD.) Naturally, with all of these problems, I was diagnosed with depression. On top of that, I have no friends. My life sucks. If I wasn't so afraid of death and a coward about killing myself, I'd do it. Honestly, I see no point in living. Also, I can't go to college because I'm poor. Life sucks.

EDIT: plus I'm fat and ugly (I have a baby face.) [This is what I look like.](http://i.imgur.com/3Tp0mJd.jpg) Albeit, that picture is about a year old but nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I please take another vitamin d pill without ODing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 09:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age 18
Sex M
Height 5"7
Weight 220
Race W
Duration of complaint 3 days
Location (Geographic and on body) everywhere
Any existing relevant medical issues (if any) no
Current medications (if any) cortisol and levothroxyn.

Can I please take another vitamin d pill, I keep having muscle spasms and my bones are really weak, I just want to take another pill! My prescription says twice a week but I don't think that's taking account that it's Winter. Please, I'm dying! The whole bottle has 50,000 IUs and 26 capsules. I took my first one 3 days ago and felt great an hour after then I woke up the next day, and started getting progressively worse. Should I take one every day? That's almost 2,000 ius a day, is that safe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you like a Community Cinematic Universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 06:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All hypothetical, but if it was to happen, what would you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone re-read Captian Underpants as an adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 05:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm almost 20 now and I loved these books as a kid, I've always loved reading but they helped me get into reading more. Is it odd for an adult to re-read these books? I LOVED them when I was a kid. Don't get me wrong though, I have grown up reading wise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 19M - Anyone want to talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 05:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else not a fan of the reformed spelling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 16:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, ognon just looks odd, oignon looks way better and more aesthetically pleasing, if that makes sense. And the circumflex, I like it and I think it's very important in the history of the French language, that's historically where the s was in Latin. Is anyone not a fan of these reforms? Will you follow them? Native French speakers, do you follow them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the likelihood that Henry VIII has living descendants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 04:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I know they wouldn't be legitimate, and I know only Henry FitzRoy was acknowledged, but what is the likelihood that he has unknown descendants out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 3 spoilers] [TV] Is anyone not really that interested in this arch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 07:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I love this show but I feel this arch is probably the weakest so far. The Lord of Light/Melisandre/Stannis arch. I didn't mind them in season 2, I feel that I'm not really that interested in their arch this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy with depression loves to make fake genealogies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 07:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this weird at all? I usually do it with the nobility or the royalty of Europe and the Virginia gentry. Tonight I was contemplating why I do this when I think I figured it out: it let's me have control over time, who is my archenemy. Does this make sense? Is this normal? Lately I've been thinking about how time gets us all. Is this weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do dukedoms, baronies, and the like work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 05:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this isn't the sub to ask this question, I apologize, I don't know where else to ask. Any who, how do dukedoms, baronies, and the like work? How are they named?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL how to read Shakespeare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 04:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for leisure and I've got no money. This is impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Any good comedies like these out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 08:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch a lot of shows but here I'll just list comedy. The Office, Rules of Engagement, Parks and Rec, Community, Arrested Development, IASIP, 30 Rock, Family Guy, and Rick and Morty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CRITIQUE] The Monk's Tale - 3509 words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of my story "The Monk's Tale"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do when the only thing you want to be is a writer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 04:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never wanted to be anything but a writer. But it isn't practical and I don't think I'm good. What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SERIOUS] What happened to country music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 20:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to country music? I remember the 90s and the early 2000s, they seemed ok but 2009 or so, it just got to be all poppy, and not really country at all. I mean there's still some country arists (Alan Jackson, George Strait, and Randy Travis to name a few) but for the most part, they seem like all pop stars to me. They aren't even singing about anything, what gives?

EDIT: There's some new country artists that are actually country like Sturgill Simpson, Jason Isbell, and Chris Stapleton but of course, they aren't nearly as popular as the stuff Trashville is making nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I comprehend ebooks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 01:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I read an actual book, I can understand it and comprehend it well but when I read an ebook, I only comprehend a little of it. Why is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Esperanto a language for Communists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 06:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a stupid question, but is it? Please please believe me when I say I'm not trolling or trying to offend anyone, this is just what I've heard and I want to confirm that it is(n't.) Being a Libertarian definitely goes against communism. A question in a question: is there any other Esperantists on here that are Libertarian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I watch IASIP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 23:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of friends of mine said I should check it out, but would I like it? I love Arrested Development, Community, Rick and Morty, and a lot of other shows. Would I like IASIP? Would you recommend it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Steeldrivers -- Midnight Tears [bluegrass] (2009) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 06:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Willie Nelson - Hello Walls [country] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 06:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Should I worry about formatting right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know formatting is very important, please don't bash me. However I'm finding that the formatting is holding me back from writing at this point, should I just write and worry about formatting later? Is that even allowed? How would you format this "non formatted" script? Sorry for all of the questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Is this overplayed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 07:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's actually one of the only creative ideas I've had since I've been depressed. I'd call it a Crime Western if that makes any sense. I was thinking that it could be about these group of guys (and gals) that tear up a big a crime family in the West. I know it's overplayed, please don't make fun guys. I'm only a beginner after all. Any thoughts on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] How do you write when you are depressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 02:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got this great idea for a historical drama, but I'm finding that all of my creativity is just gone. How do YOU get it back when you are depressed? Also, I should mention that I am an absolute beginner and I don't know what the hell to do :P. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you translate the Subjunctive into English? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it a bit tricky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anything in Latin I can read yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 02:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only just finished Chapter 7 of Lingua Latina and I want to read some real stuff! Is there anything I can read that's actual Latin lit? I know I'm getting ahead of myself and I know there's unlikely any lit I can read. By the way, I have got some tough grammatical concepts under my belt including all five declensions and the Present, Imperfect, and Future tenses all in the Active and Passive. I'm dying to read some real Latin lit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I stick with a language? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to learn a language so badly, but it seems like I can never stick with one. I always get caught up with a new one. The longest I've lasted is Latin (my love.) Now I'm on Spanish and Esperanto. Including those three, I've tried Chinese, Italian, and French (I REALLY want to learn this one). I was thinking of trying Ancient Greek but I don't want to give up on it. Why can't I stick with a language? What's wrong with me? Do you have any tips?

EDIT: I love French but Latin is the one I love the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing and depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 01:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I haven't written a word in about six months and I've recently found out that the reason I have been feeling down this pass year is because I have depression. I want to get back into writing so badly, but everything I have tried to write comes out horrible. Plus I've got no ideas. How do you guys force yourself to write when you have depression? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Principal Parts Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 20:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the principle parts for the Perfect system the same for regular verbs? For example: are - avi, ere - ui, ere -xi, and ire - ivi. Are these always the same for all regular verbs?

EDIT: If no, could you give some tips on mastering the Perfect System? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else cry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 20:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does depression cause me to eat less? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 07:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone up for the challenge in translating this into Latin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 06:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [TRANSLATE IF YOU DARE!!](https://i.imgur.com/Ob8d1yZ.) There will be causalities , but that is a sacrifice I am willing to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does depression cause me to eat less? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 06:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then in turn, I get low blood sugar and get headaches and become dizzy. It's just one viscous cycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any young people like the movie "It's A Wonderful Life?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 06:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Young meaning 20 and down. Do any other teens or twenty somethings love this movie cause most teens and twenty somethings I know call it boring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you make a script? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make a script for a new conlang I'm working on but I don't even know how. Do you have to be good at drawing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help with this sentence from Lingua Latina? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 17:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sed id quod Medus cantat a Lydia non auditur. I think I get the gist of the sentence but I cannot for the life of me translate id quod properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone out there more loyal to their state than to the country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 09:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, don't get me wrong, I love America, but I love Virginia WAY more. There's just something about her. Someone even compared me to Robert E Lee in that regard. I don't know, maybe it's just an old way of thinking, then again I've always been old. Any who, is there any other fellow Americans like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it a good idea to be beginning Ancient Greek right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 03:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only on chapter seven of Lingua Latina right now but I am also interested in learning Ancient Greek. Would it be a good idea to begin Ancient Greek right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL Latin and Ancient Greek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 03:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both languages that interest me to no end, even more so than most modern languages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between flumen and fluvius? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 04:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wiktionary is telling me that they both mean river, so are the interchangeable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do we know definitively where the English word horse comes from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 22:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it be related to some PIE words but then I hear others say that it isn't IE at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Doctor Who] You crash landed into the French Revolution and have to get out before you get executed (you're next.) You have no sonic screwdriver, a non working TARDIS, and no companion. You are completely alone and defenseless with only your wits to save you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 07:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey who are you and what the hell is this thing?" the guard yelled at me from across the square

  The huge crowd looked dead at me, it was so silent you could hear a pin drop.

"What are you all gathering around for?" I asked the guard.

"An execution of course," he gave a sinister smile. "You're next."

"Why am I next, I didn't even do anything!" I yelled.

"Because you arrive out of nowhere with a strange blue box, that is suspicious" he said after he spat on the ground.

"i swear to you, I mean no harm," I said putting my hands above my head.

"Yeah? That's what they all say. Come here." he said grabbing me by the collar on my jacket.

"I'm innocent, I swear!" I yelled but no one was listening.

I looked ahead and saw an old wooden platform above it was a rope.

So this is how I am going to die, by hanging during the French Revolution. 

"Get up there!" the guard shoved me.

   Looking out at the crowd, I saw the crazed people yelling and shouting "hang him!" "kill him already!" Then, out of nowhere, the guard said something: "EXTERMINATE." Daleks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do I add pitch accent to my conlang? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 23:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've asked a lot of folks, and they gave me great answers, but I was too embarrassed to to tell them that I didn't get it. Please don't make fun guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that police officers don't have to protect you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You and your dog discover a time machine in your basement and crash land in Ancient Rome with no way home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 07:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know Latin or Ancient Greek and the dog you have is a German Shepherd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   '      . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 07:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  , '                  .    ' .           ,         .        ?   .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How irregular is Latin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 01:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just diving into the present tense now but how irregular is it? Not just verb wise, overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do CRT televisions last longer than LCDs or LEDs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 06:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just me but CRTs last WAY longer. I mean, the CRT we have is about 20 years old (same as myself.) It's not like we use it sparingly, it's always on. But if you treat LEDs or LCDs like that, they barely last five. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between pitch accent and tone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 18:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking the two up but I still can't find a good definition of what pitch accent is. I mean, are there still tones in pitch accented langs? I'm so confused about what the hell pitch accent is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you make inflections for your conlang? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 21:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the actual inflections, like how do you come up with them? I'm a huge lover of inflections and am trying to make my first inflectional language by myself (I made one before with other people helping though.) I'm just drawing a huge black in how you come up with inflections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help with this sentence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 00:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Circum oppidum Tusculum murus non tam longus est quam circum Romam." It's from Oberg's Lingua Latina. I thought it meant "The wall around the city of Tusculum isn't as long" but the "circum Romam" part doesn't make sense in that translation. Can anyone help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right thigh won't stop twitching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 21:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     Age: 19
    Sex: M
    Height: 5"7
    Weight 222
    Race: W
    Duration of complaint: a half hour
    Location (Geographic and on body): lower right thigh
    Any existing relevant medical issues (if any): Nope
    Current medications (if any, this includes recreational drugs) Cortef and a Levothroxane (sorry for the bad spelling.)

I know 30 minutes isn't long but I'm freaking out cause it's not stopping! What's wrong? I mean, I didn't take my pills today cause I ran out, but this never happens when I run out. Is it cause I'm dehyrdated? I'm really scared right now. Could it be caused by hunger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else get really mad when someone says something bad about Latin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 07:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this doesn't make much sense, but when someone says ridiculous stuff about Latin, I get really mad. Like how it's useless, or EXTREMELY hard, etc. Maybe I'm the only one. Please don't judge me too much XD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it true that there's a Spoken Latin revival? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 02:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially in the American South. I'd love to see Latin spoken again. If this isn't true, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have an Applebees complaint. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 01:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my burger wasn't well done. I specifically asked for well done not for medium rare. Also, my sons chicken was barely cooked. Also, your service was shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid question but, does mastering all of the declensions make your life easier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 17:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like do you have an easier time learning Latin or is it like, "yeah, I mastered the decelensions." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE use the English subjunctive mood a lot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 01:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that I use the subjunctive a lot and more than most. Does anyone else here use it? Also, if you were to use it, would you recognize it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should a beginner worry about feminine nouns in the 2nd declension? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I found out they existed I started freaking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Chris Pratt know that he'll always be known as Andy Dwyer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 03:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this a stupid question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you make a god ortho? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 21:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always suck at making them. How do you even make one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is learning Ancient Greek and Latin at the same time like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 14:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is learning Ancient Greek and Latin at the same time like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 14:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And would you recommend it? Which one would you say is more difficult?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a Latin friend to go through Familia Romana with me. Any interested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 21:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a friend who would be interested at going through Familia Romana or even a teacher if anyone is interested. I suck at learning by myself, I'm sorry if this sounds selfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Translation Challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 11:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The man walked from the bar to his white house. I know, it's a little long. I will post mine tomorrow morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know what to do anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 04:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since graduating high school, I've done nothing but apply for jobs and sit around my house doing nothing. It's been over a year, no one is taking me. I don't even know what to do with my life. I thought about going to the local community college but I don't know what to study. I don't plan to go to a four year cause I know I wouldn't last, so I'm not gonna waste my money on it when I can by a house. Also, I'm not aloud to drive because of my eyes. I mean, my doc told me I can drive a couple hours during the day, but honestly, I don't trust my eyes. I don't want to kill myself and kill someone else. I just don't know what to do anymore. What do I do now with my life after high school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What chord would be the best in the chord progression below? (Guitar) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 22:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been having a really hard time trying to find a chord for the progression. The progression is: G, E, A, so far. I'm only a beginner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "There was ever only one language (besides Latin) spoken in Italy, Standard Italian." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 23:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for the John Cena meme sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 06:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone told me there's an entire sub dedicated to that meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello fellow Latin lovers! I've got a couple of questions for you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, well, I'm a noob when it comes to Latin and I've been using Obergs Famaila Romana, one: is this a good source to use? Two: how have you fared using Familia Romana? Three: if I master every concept in every chapter and do all the exercises, how "fluent" would I be in Latin? Would I be able to read an actual book in Latin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WE'VE GOT MORE NEWS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 07:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've recently discovered that PIE is a language in the West Martian family who is from Proto Martian. We are trying to find sources from Proto Martian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 19 US M - I'm looking for a Skype buddy who can eventually become a good friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 07:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To name a few: history, language history, etymology, conlanging, reading, writing, watching too much TV, sleeping, learning languages, comics, and Latin. If you want to know more, don't hesitate to ask! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone always leaves me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 06:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do. Besides my family and God, everyone else ALWAYS leaves me. They stay around for a while, than just up an leave randomly and because of this, I have no friends. I mean, I don't want a rave of friends, one or two would suffice. What's wrong with me man, how come they don't want me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys have any advice on memorizing the case classes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I've just been using Obergs' Familia Romana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Basic Sjetana Greetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dagyar: good evening

Denmata: How are you doing (formal)

Luzoro levo: Long time no see! 

Mayewa: Good afternoon

Onbora: Good morning

Ya: Hello

Yevan vahiga: Goodbye! 

Zelan aki: Good evening

Zuona sel: Nice to see you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone interested in a Sicilian Skype group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 23:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to learn Sicilian and start a Skype group but there's no speakers of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Sicilian ever going to be on Duolingo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 22:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to learn Sicilian but It's not on Duolingo and there's not many sources on it. Does anyone speak Sicilian and is willing to start a Sicilian Skype group? Ah, I'm dragging on. The point is, do you think Sicillian will ever be on Duolingo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What language family does Sjetana sound/ look the most like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 07:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No one has ever really given me an answer. I personally have no idea, definitely not Germanic or Romantic. What do y'all think?](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NASyfKSUBVDDAKnlDSUwJeZsg6lNPt3RDW7iR4uD2Ho/mobilebasic) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello everyone! What do you guys think of Sjetana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 17:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the main doc for Sjetana](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NASyfKSUBVDDAKnlDSUwJeZsg6lNPt3RDW7iR4uD2Ho/edit) [and here is a Memrise course I am making for it.](http://www.memrise.com/course/785648/sjetana/)

It's a conlang a couples guys and myself made, if you've any more questions about Sjetana or feedback, please let me know!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do a lot of people who learn/know Latin end up being douchebags? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 17:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I begin (and before you begin bashing) I'd like to say: IT IS NOT EVERYONE. Ok, have we gotten that out of the way? Anyways, a lot of the people I come across who speak/are learning Latin are real douchebags, is there a reason why this is? I mean, I was originally thinking because of the better than thou attitude but I'm not sure why now. Has anyone else experienced this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone be interested in Sjetana lessons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 17:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of writing up some lessons here, would anyone be interested?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish is the worst language ever because it's so fucking boring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 13:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, It's just boring as hell, nothing I haven't seen from a romlang before. I mean, grammar wise, it really doesn't have much (I like grammar) and I'm so sick of the fucking articles! Spanish is basically a romlang ripoff of English. There's nothing I haven't seen before, plus the lang is way too easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone interested in speaking/writing over Skype? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 17:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it could even be a group, I've no idea yet. I'm currently using Duolingo but I don't feel I can use it practically, which is something very important to me. Is anyone interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for conlangers: Do you like word order? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of controversy about this subject. Some people love it, some people hate it. Which one are you? I'm not a big fan of word order myself but that's just me.

EDIT: what I mean is do you like a stricter word order like SVO, SOV, etc. Or do you like a freer word order like Latin for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were the Picts of Ancient Scotland actually Assyrians? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 07:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that they found a picture in a cave it resembled the Assyrians, is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have a any recommendations for Sjetana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 04:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you dislike? Doesn't make sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't Duolingo teach grammar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 00:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, sure, if you're on their website they kind of do but other than that, Duolingo really doesn't teach grammar. Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why has Duolingo stopped updating their kindle fire app? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a rea pain in the arse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Acadians: are there any of y'all out there that can help an outsider learn Cajun French? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 08:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely interested in everything about Cajun culture but I heard the language on YouTube and it was gorgoues, I want to learn it so bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know how to speak Sicilian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 08:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't tell me it's an accent of modern Italian, it's not. I'd love to learn it since that's where my family is from! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE BASQUES ARE THE ALIEN RIVALS OF THE PROTO INDO EUROPEANS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 05:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, think about it, it makes PERFECT sense. There's no other explanation out there. The Basques crashed landed on Earth and settled down then later the Indo Europeans arrived and were like "oh shit, my granddad told me about these guys. They were our rivals back home." The only question now is what planet they were from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone I had a bad feeling about does something shitty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 07:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to actually lessen the effects of inbreeding with new DNA being introduced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 00:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In humans I mean. Take Charles II of Spain as an example. Also, how affected would the child be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How difficult is Blackbird to play as a beginner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 00:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's quite possibly one of my favorite songs. And I'd love to (eventually) play along with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Strategy Skype Group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 08:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would anyone be interested in joining? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to take a poem and and put it to music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 04:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a stupid question. I'm new to songwriting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one that doesn't like picks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 22:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's because I'm a lefty playing a righty guitar but they just don't feel comfortable at all, no matter which one I use. It's like I can't strum with one. When I use my hand, I feel perfectly comfortable. Am I the only one who doesn't like\use picks? I've been looking into the guitar community and it seems like most people love them.

EDIT: Is it even worth getting a pick if all I play is country, folk, bluegrass, and gospel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who loves cases? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 14:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I was kidding, I just find cases awesome. Also, my conlangs tend to have A LOT of cases. Anyone else out there like this?

[Like this for instance.](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1tIMnZChXvApJ_kOlvBNnp_2g6wl65oQ3nf-pXdCSwQk/mobilebasic) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song should be my first song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 05:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this problem for years. Every time I try to pick a song, I suck horribly at it. I've been playing guitar like this on and off for a couple of years now, but I don't want to anymore. Does anyone know of any really easy country songs? Any with fingerpicking? I'm really tired of having this problem. It's so discouraging :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it ok for a tonal language to be heavily inflected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love grammar, try not to judge me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone be interested in an Esperanto group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 16:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only an intermediate beginner but I'd like to write and speak in Esperanto. Is anyone interested in an Esperanto Skype group? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All right, I've got a lot of questions for you seasoned worldbuilders! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you can probably tell, I'm a rook at worldbuilding and I've got quite a two questions. If you're up to it, read on.

* How big can a world be? Because I've got plans to build a huge world that's really in depth.

* Do readers like in depth worlds?

So far I've really gotten into the history and lore of the world. I would imagine this helps the world seem more realistic. I plan to add even more though because I enjoy doing it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the song "Blackbird" by the Beatles about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 06:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone told me it was about racial matters in America and others said he made it randomly. Which one is it truly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does she always like my Instagram pictures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 03:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this sounds childish, but just stay with me for a second. I've never even talked to her, we're just "friends" on social media because we went to middle school together. At first she only just liked pictures of me but now she's started liking stuff that she's not even interested in (I.e. football.) I mean, it just doesn't add up to me. In case you didn't know, I'm a guy. We're both nineteen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this show for girls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 04:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or does it have a girly feel or neither? PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE don't just bash me for saying this, it's just what I've heard. Is this true? If so, what is it actually like? It looks really cool!

EDIT: Also, how scary is the show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you guys go to make your maps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 00:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how do you do it? I'm talking to the folks out there who make it on a computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blackberry Smoke - No Way Back to Eden [southern rock] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 19:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When no one expected you to get the answer right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 18:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does it seem like everyone on social media is witty or funny? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed this a lot ESPECIALLY on Tumblr. Why is this?

EDIT: I've also noticed this a lot on Reddit as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/techsupport, my computer has a black screen and it's on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 15:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I cannot turn it off no matter how long I press the start button. It's an HP laptop running Windows 10. I haven't had any problems with it in the past but when I went on it today, it went to a black screen and won't let me turn it off. I already tried to hold down the power button. Other than that, I don't know what to do. I'm not very tech savvy.

EDIT: The wifi light keeps going from a whitish/bluish to an orange to off. The power light keeps going on and off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swish! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 22:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fear that people are getting more stupid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 18:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this arrogant, I don't mean it like. Anyways, from what I've observed, this is true. It's a pity too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you know which words to make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this sounds like a stupid question, bu how do you know which words to create? So far, I've been using the Swadesh List but I've created all the words on it (that I know of.) Now, I don't know which words to create. I know this sounds stupid. How did you decide which words to create? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm here to promote our conlang Sjetana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 19:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does our conlang look? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here it is: /r/Sjetana. What does it sound like? What do you think of it? Hate it? Love it? Is it too close to English? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of the conlang? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a Memrise course it Sjetana if you're interested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is kind of our book of Sjetana. What do you guys think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of our conlang thus far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 23:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you become a better conlanger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 03:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did everyone on /r/conlang become a better conlanger? I want to try to be a better one because I feel like I suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's our conlang coming out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 03:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else not enjoy the Hobbit movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WARNING: This post will be somewhat long.
Now that we got that out of the way, did anyone else not enjoy The Hobbit movies? Don't get me wrong, I'm a Tolkien fan. Let's start from the beginning. When I was a preteen, I LOVED the Hobbit and was completely enthralled by Middle Earth. After I finished The Hobbit, I checked out LOTR. LOTR was a little harder to read and a lot darker, but I got threw them and enjoyed them thoroughly. When I discovered the movies, I watched the hell out of them and loved them. So when I found out that the Hobbit was coming out, I was like: HELL YES, FINALLY! However, I couldn't even make it through the first hour of the movie, it was just WAY to slow. I always didn't like how they added stuff from LOTR, I thought that took the "feeling " of the Hobbit away. I didn't like how they cut the Hobbit (WHICH IS A SMALL BOOK) into three boring parts. It probably would've worked (and been better) as a standalone movie. Sorry about my ramblings at the end. The point is, am I the only one that feels like this?

***EDIT*** I just watched it a couple of minutes ago for the first time. I know, I'm late. How were the last two? I ask because I don't plan to watch them. I don't even plan to finish the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello /r/fantasywriters! What are the "no-nos" in putting a language in your story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask this because I've seen this done very badly (Eragon for example) and I don't want to make this mistake. How do I avoid doing a language very badly in my story? How did you avoid doing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello /r/fantasy! What are the "no-nos" in putting a language in your story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask this because I've seen this done very badly (Eragon for example) and I don't want to make this mistake. How do I avoid doing a language very badly in my story? How did you avoid doing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitchen Sinking is a drug, do not mess with it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 06:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone, I'm Dylan and I'm a conlager. I recently got into kitchen sinking while making a language, it was so fun and addictive, like [these.](http://i.imgur.com/PGuWCte.png) But before I knew it, I was adding useless cases and unnecessary declensions to my language. It feelt so good but I knew in my heart that it was so wrong. I'm here to tell you folks that kitchen sinking is a real drug, don't mess with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does a beginner go about making a conlag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 23:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently writing a fantasy story and want to make a couple of conlangs for it. I know they aren't necessary, but it's something I'd like to experiment with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers and readers: Can you check out my fantasy world I'm making for my story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 19:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else obsessed with the English language and its history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 03:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it's a pretty weird thing to be obsessed in. Since it's such a weird interest, sometimes I think I'm the only one that's interested in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of my world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 23:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one that can't finish an ebook? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 18:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that I don't like them; the're very convenient. However, I can never finish them. When I read a regular book, I have no problems but when I read an ebook I can never get through it. Does anyone else have this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would any experienced worldbulider be interested in checking out my world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 07:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a beginner myself. The problem is, I don't know if I'm doing a good job or not. Would anyone be interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I make an in depth world like Tolkien? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 06:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DISCLAIMER: I'm not talking about his ideas, nor do I want them.

How do I make an in depth world like Tolkien? I mean, I've written a lot of history for my story thus far. Is that a good start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forearm Tightness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 15:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age 19
Sex M
Height 5"8
Weight 230
Race W
Duration of complaint A couple of hours
Location (Geographic and on body) My forearm
Any existing relevant medical issues (if any) Can't think of anything else
Current medications (if any) Hyrdocortisone and Leythroxine (spelling?)

A couple of hours ago when I woke up in the middle of the night, I noticed my forearm muscles were tightened for some reason, They weren't tightened enough to be painful, just discomfort.It faded away mostly but it's still there in very small discomfort. Is this a sign of something more or just random muscle tightness? Someone online said it could be the beginning of MS which scared the hell out of me. Yes, I'm a hypochondriac.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do people on the internet write with such horrendous grammar, spelling, and punctuation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 22:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it more difficult to understand someone if they don't write well? I'm just curious as to why folks do this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the likelihood of Haley and Andy getting together? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 18:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And do you want them to get together? I personally want them to get together because they'd make a great couple. When i saw the season six finale, I cried like a baby; it was so sad. I know it isn't real life or anything; the romantic inside of me is too dramatic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you all have any advice on making a plot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 21:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had trouble with plots, although I'm an excellent world builder. Would you all have any advice on how to make\thicken a plot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does it make sense that I love American football but hate watching it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 06:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it sounds crazy, I really do. However, it's true. Don't get me wrong, I LOVE football, I love everything about but I can't even watch a full game without getting distracted by something else. Please don't make fun of me y'all, I'm being serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Absorbing sunlight, but just you wait. Once he's done standing there for a few minutes he will fuck you up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 06:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YOU BETTER FUCKING LAUGH! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 05:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How were learning Romance languages after Latin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 07:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it easier? Was it harder? How so? Please be specific as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seasoned Esperantists, I've a question for you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 02:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you happen to have any tips on mastering the Accusative case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cxu iu volas praktiki Esperanton kun mi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 18:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cxu mi faras ion malgxustan? Mi estas komencanto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are Americans voting for Bernie Sanders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 16:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't they know that his universal health care plan will raise taxes? Do Americans love paying taxes or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cxu vi parolas Esperanton? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 14:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cxu vi parolas Esperanton? Mi estas komencanto.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't extroverts understand introverts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 06:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They think we're freaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else noticed that English is just a random strand of words? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 05:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does "said" go unnoticed by a reader? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 17:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always heard this but I've never heard a reason. Why does using "said" as a dialouge tag, go unnoticed by the reader? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Esperantists make words out of thin air? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 02:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean by this is lets say for example "ami" becomes "amegi" or ameti (to like?) Is this even aloud in Esperanto? Often times I find that I don't remember the "official" word but I make new word on the spot. If this is aloud, would people understand me? Or "mojosa" could you make "mojosi" (to be cool)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is there such a bias for introverts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 13:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you want me to do something, TELL ME. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 13:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want me to do something, TELL ME. This escpeically goes to my mother. Don't mumble behind my back to tell me to do something, TELL IT TO MY FACE. Sorry, this is a HUGE pet peeve of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there something wrong with me? My mother seems to think so. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 00:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom always tells me to "be more social" and to "get out of the house more." The problem is, it's exhausting to be social. If I have to be anymore social, I'm going to go crazy. Now since "I don't socialize enough" she's having me go talk to a psychologist. Is there actually something wrong with me? How do I convince my mother that I believe I introverted?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got a question for the folks who know Latin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 02:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you learn Latin? Do you learn to speak it or read it or both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
