<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is just what a communist sympathizer would say! Now give me those names!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/uuL6cJPz3Nk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was /r/The_Donald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back the league of women voters to run all I mean ALLLL the debates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is though you have to work inside the system. Green Party, Libretarian Party, and the even greater extreme Constitution party (they want Christian theocratic law as the law of the land) are all wildly out of step with centrist views and know they create a system that makes the parties become worse. 

The fact is we need to get democrats in who will pass laws that limit the size of political parties so that no one political party can be too big. That you run on platform NOT PARTY and you join a party once you get into office.

Lastly we need Democrats who will push for alternative vote / Instant-Run off voting as well as mail in ballots / online voting with a verified 2Fa system and online ballot verification and paper receipt.

This would allow a concession to the republicans saying you can have a national ID system that has a smart chip on it that then acts as your passport and also you use for signing contracts. Look to Estonia for a country that did it. There National ID is amazing with 2FA and Puplic key encryption on the card itself with chip / pin support.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Estonian_ID_card#Cryptographic_use

I can't fucking believe we put uniquely identifiable powerless RFID in god damn United states passports when federal government agency ID cards have had Chip authentication for over 15 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pain is a sign your body is breaking down and damaging itself. You should stop if their is serious pain. Soreness is one thing. Pain is warning bell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the plot of that movie. The bigger message is the adults work so hard willing to sacrifice the children (The next generation) so they can survive when all that really matters is that the next generation survives but with education so they don't become feral animals. 

It really is such a powerful movie if you can understand the message it was trying to get across. Save the children, and make sure they have the knowledge to keep the human race alive. It reminds me of the concept of you can't get the parents out of poverty but if you can get to the parents to teach them how to raise their kids you can get the kids out of poverty. Look up information on the Harlem Children's Zone non-profit and founder Geoffrey Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked with him as a fellow intern this last year at an internship at a major tech company in Oregon, yeah he is a prick. Active T_D poster and was actually banned from posting on KotakuInAction because he would Dox and stalk people even within the KiA group he felt "didn't support the cause". He had to be removed from a company Women in Tech event for interns because he would interrupt the speakers with MRA ranting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> an "alleged Billionare" many people in the Billionare community throw  doubt that he actually is currently a billionaire. Multi millionaire yes but Billionaire? Never have been. He has been a Billion dollars in debt though from the records of one Bankruptcy, but that is the closet he has gotten to the word billion in connection with his name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahahahaha oh that is rich. go back to /r/MensRights  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to tweet out to @SonicTeam or @Sega and see if they will license this design from you because shit ... I want to purchase a mass produced one ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J. Robert Oppenheimer, the director of the Manhattan Project, cited the Bhagavad-Gita on the occasion of the first atomic explosion, called Trinity, in the New Mexico desert, quoting, ''I am become death, shatterer of worlds."

His colleague Kenneth Bainbridge was more direct replying, ''Now we're all bastards.'' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/SnusTheMus 

better NBC link

www.nbc12.com/story/34850802/state-sen-found-with-teenage-boy-in-hotel-room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you do a tutorial video on how you do these? I have never learned how to do After effects. I know how to edit decently enough in Premiere with basic layer effects for simple motion graphics. But I want to start making some myself. I got some video clips I have started collecting but I don't know much about After Effects motion text effects at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ground shaking progress then! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my Salvadorian American fiancee's way to my gringo Irish Polish German English Catholic mut heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First conviction under Oregons new revenge porn law and currently on the run from the law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would pay to have her play the Devil in a movie. Like seriously evil twisted sadistic devil. That last episode shit! That was an inspired performance. I got shivers from it with vibes of [Viggo Mortensen as Satan in The Prophecy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mPoyezWAghE) and [Peter Stormare as Lucifer in Constantine](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hlyN600B6jA)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thatHappened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some people just can't tell the difference sadly. Brown is brown to racists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [racist pets .... weird!](https://youtu.be/_r-_Va-QrHE?t=6s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean in prison on death row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if its a black woman they don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enter the fact T_D is part of the Dark Enlightenment movement which has a corner stone of it that want a return to Feudalism. Where wealth means citizenship and voting rights and power. There is a growing segment of the predominantly only male sect of the tech/silicon valley sector who are jumping on to this idea. Peter Thiel is one of them as he even wants to make a "floating city" where slavery can be legal. 

- http://www.vocativ.com/culture/uncategorized/dark-enlightenment-creepy-internet-movement-youd-better-take-seriously/

- http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2016/12/16/alt-right-dark-enlightenment-group-seeks-campus-safe-space.html

- http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Neoreactionary_movement

- http://www.publicmedievalist.com/dark-enlightenment/

- https://techcrunch.com/2013/11/22/geeks-for-monarchy/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, on their earth it's illegal for people to travel in from other alternate realities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When is the next meeting at Willow creek by the way. I missed the last one because of career development event I had to go to. I'm in Washington County as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power Rangers Snipe Trump in latest Comic issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeahhhh no they haven't. When ever there has been a War and Economic collapse Nazi party rose to power, Pinochet rose to power, Mao, Stalin, Mussolini, PolPot, Franco .... shall we continue this list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact is a private business can perfectly refuse service to anyone as long as they are not a protected class. so you can say to a nazi, "Sorry sir no service for you. You are a nazi and I have the right to refuse service to anyone who isn't on this list of people who are minorities have have been abused by people like you."

If they don't leave you can then call the police on them for trespassing. You have a right to free speech but you don't have the right to that in a private establishment. If nazi's want to do that they should open up their own bar, with blonde blue eyed hookers and swastikas. But I doubt they will be able to keep it open for long because you know .... Nazi bar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so what then? Just don't play at all and take your ball home? The point is if you want change in the democrats you got to get off the arm chair and go volunteer at the DNC office near you. You want change but the fact is you need to be the agent of it. The system is only this way because the people who we RE-ELECT every single time run the same party line and same party games. If you wanted change go from within and then pass laws on the local level that allow third party centrists to rise to the top instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/ltNd0EO.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lost his speedforce remote projection buff. Up until now he wasn't really there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes .... a source called "the federalist" isn't at all bias 

 Addressing slavery in the Constitution, James Madison set out with a view that African American slaves as an "unfortunate race" and believed their true nature was both human and property. On February 12, 1788, Madison, in the Federalist Letter No. 54, stated that the Constitutional three-fifths compromise clause was the best alternative for the slaves' current condition and for determining representation of citizens in Congress. Madison believed that slaves, as property, would be protected by both their masters and the government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MULTIVERSE!!!!!!!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I find out Jontron's parent is an Iranian refugee from the Iranian Cultural revolution and Jontron is ranting anti-immigrant / anti-refugee stuff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pay raise play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called bigot-o   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we have a refresher course every 10 years instead for all drivers? that would be swell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it hilarious you think i got this from watching young turks. I can't stand any reporting like that. BBC world news monotone reporting and npr thank you very much. Also this was from the Washington Post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gasoline tax is at a rate that was set in the late 80s and hasn't scaled to inflation. It's supposed to cover road repair. Also Luxury cars should be taxed higher as well to cover the road work too as well as heavier cars and trucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact kid that you can't see the difference between the two means conservitive propaganda poisoned your mind. Yes there are democrats who go in poor and come out rich but still for the fact they make money they do things like fight for school kids lunch and breakfast programs, they fight for funding public education for higher teacher pay and lower class sizes, they fight for public science research and public university education.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone with access to the speed force is either a scientist, or has a criminal record. So if it is either most likely they would be in some DNA database for criminal records or law enforcement or clearance related junk or you might be able to find relatives in one of those systems with plot powers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that one line though makes me laugh cringe, "There are things in the dark, Dark things " yeesh that is just ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The electoral college was created to give power to slave states that had lower populations, and well supported slaves. It was entirely racist to begin with. 

 The delegates to the 1787 Constitutional Convention had a variety of reasons for settling on the electoral college format, but protecting smaller states was not among them. Some delegates feared direct democracy, but that was only one factor in the debate.
 
 Remember what the country looked like in 1787: The important division was between states that relied on slavery and those that didnt, not between large and small states. A direct election for president did not sit well with most delegates from the slave states, which had large populations but far fewer eligible voters. They gravitated toward the electoral college as a compromise because it was based on population. The convention had agreed to count each slave as three-fifths of a person for the purpose of calculating each states allotment of seats in Congress. For Virginia, which had the largest population among the original 13 states, that meant more clout in choosing the president.

https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/five-myths-about-the-electoral-college/2012/11/02/2d45c526-1f85-11e2-afca-58c2f5789c5d_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now Ranked choice voting would be swell too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Carrey has is moments in drama. Just don't watch The Number 23. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have to say him straight face, stone cold, "coming out" in this movie showed a very amazing sense of positive normalization from someone who normally you wouldn't think would be for gay rights. The down right matter of factness where he says I'm gay and be mad dogging Franco, like "why wouldn't I be gay? There is nothing wrong with being gay." moment I went awwwwww and that is as a large loudmouthed straight guy too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but to call him normie enrages the beast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You will never see a modern democrat or liberal say this, only "conservatives"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8T9fk7NpgIU)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, In order to get wiretaps you need to go to the FiSA court. The FiSA court is a top secret court setup after the passing of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act of 1978 ("FISA" Pub.L. 95511, 92 Stat. 1783, 50 U.S.C. ch. 36). FiSA "Act" in the United States federal law prescribes procedures for the physical and electronic surveillance and collection of "foreign intelligence information" between "foreign powers" and "agents of foreign powers"

In order to do wiretaps on us soil to United States citizens who are "agent's of a foreign powers" you have to show evidence to a judge that keeps the records sealed. The judge then has to ok the wiretaps with warrant that is kept on private clearance only record with all the evidence and reasons for the wiretap. The house intelligence committee is allowed access to these requests and typically they are actually done by a joint task force of the FBI and NSA with NSA providing analyst support while the FBI does the.

Basically this law and this court is a check and balance that allows the government to have both accountability after the fact to show they did everything above board with proper legal coverage for them and the people they investigated. This also protects the evidence collected in wiretaps as legally recorded and collected materials so that the chain of evidence is kept secure and also clear of how its operated. 

While normal citizens can't get FiSA court records until they are declassified the fact is the FiSA court is again a check box that must be filled to protect your rights as a citizen for later record purposes. The FiSA court was potentially abused during GW Bush's time in office with the fact they tried to bury any records of tap on innocent muslim americans and the kidnapping of Muslim Americans and foreign citizens in non combat / war countries with rendition to black CIA interrogation sites. 

But that is beyond the scope of the the FiSA court wiretap warrants though and goes into a whole other kettle of klusterfuk fish and human rights abuses as well as encroaching on the sovereign soil and foreign rights of foreign citizens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets me translate that into 4chan for you, as I don't think he will get it otherwise.

"Go An hero yourself normie scum" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look ma! I am Polyadicticool Actorvist now too! I post PePes, stuped normie faggggggs. Now where are my tenddies and waifu pillohhhh! RREEEEEEEEEEEE /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gfycat.com/HardtofindMiserableArmyant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need buffy in these dark times. Buffy really allowed a lot of stuff to be addressed socially. An animated show would be no different I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Did someone say Music Mister!!!](http://dai.ly/xalno9?start=73)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An example of what private-public partnerships do to public roads in the United States because a certain party won't raise bloody taxes to have public infrastructure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was an official "Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Animated Series" greenlit by 20th Century Fox in 2002, which would have taken place during Season 1. However the animated series never went past the initial 4 minute pilot, and show creator Joss Whedon announced the series as dead in 2005 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was an official "Buffy the Animated Series" greenlit by 20th Century Fox in 2002, which would have taken place during Season 1. However the animated series never went past the initial pilot, and Whedon announced the series as dead in 2005 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/dWoNSFs.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Previously on Buffy The Vampire Slayer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oX1SJYXhsXg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah well my reply was pretty much fuck you in longer than 7 characters and got a point across. You have to engage the enemy to take away their weapons. [Silence is complicity, a fragrance by Ivanka.](https://youtu.be/F7o4oMKbStE) ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think there is something there that wasn't there before a manly beard was shaq attacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Shitpost] So Barry Allen what is it that you do again for work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it is rather true, 1 facebook like = 1 prayer is the extent of trump supporter caring i have ever seen. Most republicans I know won't do anything for anyone if it doesn't help them in the end or make them look good somehow to other people. Humble brag is pretty big in republican land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait ... i can hear the compassion of the Republican peoples right now! Their love, their warmth, their empathy .... their's is a nation of love ... [let us take a moment to listen for just a moment to their love and compassion verbalized.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8T9fk7NpgIU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might I suggest this good sir /u/darthvalium while on your quest. [Take this it is dangerous to go alone.](https://greasyfork.org/en/scripts/24527-reddit-downvote-r-the-donald)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted for Bernie too. I then voted for Hillary in the actual election because of thing called PRAGMATISM. 

But again Republicons = Bernie Antithesis.

Democrats who run party line ... ehhh they can be dicks but they tend to be dicks that still have some sort of soul that cares about the rights and general wellbeing of everyone who isn't a millionaire unlike republicons. I have this thing called healthcare because of democrats, if not for them I would have been denied for pre-existing condition and not get the meds I need to make it through the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/sz3pw1Z.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie, looking kinda [ / Supaidman](http://i.imgur.com/FbH70XZ.gif) And i dig it if it was on purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for Mohammad is Jesus as Buddha is love, for it will forever be the way I see it, alright, the way that i'll see it.
Loved listening to this song when I was in high school and would spin it when I deejayed. Still on my chill tracks playlist. Probably one of the things i loved about Maryland growing up in the 90s was how amazing the dance music scene was there. Man I miss Buzz Life and nations. I used to come into Yoshitoshi all the time to get a few records once a month before you closed the store. Your store closing, Bush getting elected, the dot com crash, and graduating high school all happened in that year for me and It was kind of really harsh. But Thank you again for your music.

If you want to feel old I was 14 when the track came out and I'm 32 now.

I always felt the Rave Act and the death of the Capitol Ballroom / Buzz Night / Alchemy kind of put the nail in the coffin of electronic dance music in america. It was relegated to fluff or filler stuff afterwards by mainstream culture. What is your view on this assessment?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have seen it in the 80s. Cyberpunk galore from that time period shows just how fetishized it was, read Stephenson's Snow Crash and Gibson's Sprawl trilogy (Neuromancer,Count Zero, and Mona lisa Overdrive . Now it's permeated to middle america as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for Mohammad is Jesus as Buddha is love, for it will forever be the way I see it, alright, the way that i'll see it.

Loved listening to this song when I was in high school and would spin it when I deejayed. Still on my chill tracks playlist. Probably one of the things i loved about Maryland growing up in the 90s was how amazing the dance music scene was there. Man I miss Buzz Life and nations. I used to come into Yoshitoshi all the time to get a few records once a month before you closed the store. Your store closing, Bush getting elected, the dot com crash, and graduating high school all happened in that year for me and It was kind of really harsh. But Thank you again for your music. 

If you want to feel old I was 14 when the track came out and I'm 32 now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This pleases the republicon overlords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think there is something there that wasn't there before a beard was manly shaq attacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what made Joss Whedon such a great director. These exact same scenes are in Buffy The Vampire Slayer tv show, or well similar and the sarcasm between everyone is a lot more natural. It would be interesting to travel to a universe where Whedon got to also direct the Buffy The Vampire Slayer movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell us, did it awaken [something there that wasn't there before?](https://gifsound.com/?gifv=7ETIS61 v=gBRpjdMD77w s=39) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way he tilts his head back is like how a cat tilts it's head back when you are petting under their chin just right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the cover Gary Jules did. I actually first heard the song in an Anime Music Video back at the 2003 Otakon Convention. Had me silently crying my eyes out as it was paired up with FLCL.

http://www.animemusicvideos.org/members/members_videoinfo.php?v=12663

Not available at all in HD which greatly saddens me.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WJK_N5nRfks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually first heard the song in an Anime Music Video back at the 2003 Otakon Convention. Had me silently crying my eyes out as it was paired up with FLCL. 

http://www.animemusicvideos.org/members/members_videoinfo.php?v=12663

Not available at all in HD which greatly saddens me. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WJK_N5nRfks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Iliza Shlesinger and her three specials.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.therichest.com/expensive-lifestyle/entertainment/10-successful-comedians-accused-of-stealing-jokes/

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joke_theft

amy schumer pissed off the "but my mens' rights" crowd and now you are going after her, what about going after Robin Williams or Conan O'brien? Hell even Denis Leary has stolen jokes and I don't see people going off the kilter for them!

I don't even like amy schumer she is too abrasive for me but seriously it happens and even beloved figures like Robin Williams are accused and people have proof of him doing it.

http://entertainment.time.com/2013/06/20/patton-oswalt-on-the-unsavory-business-of-joke-theft/

Anyway if you don't like Schumer check out Iliza Shlesinger and her three netflix specials. [Party Goblin for the win!](https://youtu.be/k1EfHpx400U) [No More Mermaids too.](https://youtu.be/_SQWH8TEeUI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like low energy fail from an edge lord 12 year old. Keep the nazi that coming hilter killing jew jokes to bloody 4chan turdshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just add sexism, misogyny, and talking over women and you got yourself the first synthetic neckbeard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chad is the quintessential white preppy rich frat jock guy you saw in 80s horror movies. Chad, Taylor, Steve, and Richard are about 6 names black community started having for these frat asshole. Basically a brocoder is a Chad, a Wallstreet stock guy is a Chad. These are people who usually say they did everything on their own and had no help but don't count mom and dad paying for school, giving them all the school supplies they needed, the car at 16 and 18 when they partied to much and crashed the first one. 

They are the type of people who are like affirmative action is racist against them and don't even take the time to think that affirmative action helps level the playing field or tries to help play catch up for a minority demographic who do not normally get to make the same educational, political, career, or personal connections someone who got in on "donation acceptance" into college gets.

Chad is Ebay CEO's Meg Whitman son who's mom donated 10 million dollars to Princeton and her C grade student son gets in and then she donates another 10 million to keep him from getting expelled after he was in a drunken on campus altercation while underage.

Chad in the end or Taylor or the rest is akin to saying Bonnie, Barbie, BonBon, Ashley, Veronica when referring to rich privileged kids who complain when the system doesn't cater to them and their Affluenza.

But granted the names do change over time because what rich people named their kids in the 80s are now what white trash people name their kids in the 90s and so forth.

[Freakenomics podcast and book did a rather great story about this.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UaU9vmL8i3Y) They also did a thing about what is in a name. It compared people who had "black sounding" names verse "white sounding" names and found that black sounding names with the exact same resume were 33% less likely to find a job than a white sounding name with the same resume meaning black people with black sounding names take up to 5 weeks longer to find a job interview.

https://vimeo.com/21839331 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bird of freedom ... GET HIM!!!](http://i.imgur.com/A0458i5.gif)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They Live, so you should die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit .... Trump is a retarded President Business! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you have records of emailing ahead of time about this? This is a hostile work environment and if you have records of this conversation then you got them dead to rights for a lawsuit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What atrocity?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nazi punks, fuck off" clear enough for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only watched the last two seasons of parks and rec and after the show ended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think your point was poorly formed and only serves to uphold a narrative of offhanded dismissal of progressive viewpoints.

whaaaaaaaaaaat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are conflating denouncing racism with doing good deeds of public service. Denoucing racism is something that should be as simple as breathing. Nazi Punks Fuck off. I'm talking about actions like volunteering at soup kitcken once in a blue moon and then bragging about how generous you are. 

Volunteering should be a humble action that you do. You should do it because you want to help. 

Again calling out bigots should not be anything special. Its a civic responsibility to do it and should just be muscle memory and instinctual. 

Again i think you are missing my entire point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia has fucked up priorities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I pray a solider will do his duty and defend us from enemies foreign and domestic ... with his side arm pointed at his the coward's head if he even thinks of doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "[Have you ever noticed how other people's stuff is shit, and your own shit is stuff?](https://youtu.be/4x_QkGPCL18)" - George Carlin
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where would you get that from my post? Racists lack empathy, ergo they are bad people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called humility, and donating to a charity or helping at a soup kitchen once in a while doesn't make you a good person. Its not a scale measuring good deeds to bad acts. A good person is humble, modest with their deeds and actions. They also know that no matter what they could still be doing more to help and remember their luck for what they have. Good people have emapthy and the ability to see the world from the perspective of others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You tube , a place where its a prank bro, cat videos, neo nazi japanese lolita cross dressers, and random videos of seemingly ranting on any topic by 70% uneducated arm chair pundits seem to gain credibility as good resources. 

Anythig dealing with that stuff should come out of a university and here is the thing juat because some tit with a web cam makes a video about a subject doesnt make it a citable and vetted source. I mean hey lets go learn about programming from temple os creator terry davis! What about an indepth debate about women's issues in tech with acclaimed youtube pundit jontron! Oh how about we sit down and watch a video about the reptile people and hollow earth and demon warding with filter and diet supplements sales man alex jones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank ayn rand for that selfish trope of conservative america </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is the best example of Chad I can imagine. Born on third base and says he got a grand slam when he is walked to home plate from foul balls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm honestly surprised this didn't get brigade with hate because it was an environmental focused post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hehehehehe captain Canuckle! it's me Flapjack!](https://youtu.be/IQWkyXAiR50) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy crap this show just knows how to perfectly mock the internet. This I feel has a much bigger meaning than just cable jokes. These entirely feels like it was an internet community mockery with mom having to come fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/iamverysmart calls to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Her father is Puerto Rican and her mother is IrishEnglish

-*sweep*- -*sweep*- -*sweep*- 

don't mind me. Just sweeping 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is a timeline ... i'm putting my dick in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they give cause or are you at an at will state? Also what industry are you and what state? Also it never hurts to sign up for Medicare or food stamps if you qualify. I'm assuming you file taxes jointly though so the income might be listed as too high then to qualify.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to watch [Key   Peele](https://www.hulu.com/key-and-peele) .... you really really do. It takes the torch from Dave Chappelle and almost makes the critiques about geek / pop culture / black culture / race relations / general couples relationships .... almost wholesome while also being sharp witted and blue humored at the same time. 


Basically Key   Peele are what you get if  Black Nerd Comedy   David Chappelle had a baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republic of Ireland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/KotakuInAction's new sidebar image, its very ... humble, not at all cringiest thing you will ever see </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northern Ireland you mean right? Cuz my extended family in South Ireland is like laughing their asses off at how fucked they see England and Wales going.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a direct blood relation of polish catholic citizens who were put in Dachau concentration camp for speaking out against the nazi riegme as political prisoners who were tattooed on their arm, fuck you and your anti-semitism. Hunting down Nazi war criminals is sonething that needs to be done. There should never be some excuse made is that they are an old man now or something. Justice must be served for the millions killed. The nameless unmarked graves where thousands were buried like trash. In those graves were jews, polish, germans, catholics, jehovas witnesses, romani, ethnic slavic people, disabled, amputees, russians, gays, and lesbians. Their haunting ghosts seek justice and cry out in agony with a resurrection of populous fear rhetoric promoting nazi propaganda again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insert someone screaming "fascist, nazi, socialist, commie dictator!" 

I mean because gun control is the devil's trick to take god given guns from true red white and blue blooded americans. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CEOs and board members should be held criminally liable in cases of death, serious injury, or defects in products it would actually make their pay reasonable for all that risk then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your "moral beliefs" are entirely are based on religious dogma that you see as the only religious faith and you do so make your choices to make your faith the only faith that is not democracy that is again a perversion of the system too. When these people constantly try to sidestep the protections of separation of church and state that again is them trying to break democracy and install christian theocracy / christian Sharia Law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The right to practice religion is fair and equal its when single religion imposses its views on others thatvits not fair. Using evangelical religous doctrin as a non questionable excuse for policy is using religion for the sake of corruption. Theocracy is not democracy and this is why separation of church and state is vital to democracy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you are saying it sarcastically. Man its hard to read sarcasm from insanity now in these dark times. Just help a brother out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me something ..... https://m.imgur.com/dSUtYns.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants to live in peace as a white person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But you cant look at individuals all the time. You have to look at the whole picture to see what best helps or hurts a culture so people get equal access and treatment and tries to make up for short falls of the system to level the playing field in the past. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not racist ..... but  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I open the door. i looked. i shake my head, and now i close the door and sigh in sad lament. Why cant people just not be dicks and treat everyone, women and men, equally with considerations for a few biological differences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need /s tags now more than ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dog whistle politics usually refers to the use of certain code words or phrases that are designed to be understood by only a small section of the populace. Generally speaking, these are phrases that have special meaning to that subsection entirely independent of its meaning to others, and represent a particularly insidious use of loaded language.
The term alludes to the sound of a dog whistle, which can only be heard by the intended audience (the dog). In theory at least, dog whistle terms are only noticed and understood by the people they are intended for. In practice, the meaning is often understood by others. For example, negative references to "ghettos" are taken by pretty much everyone to mean "black parts of town."


"Family values", "law and order", "states rights"

- https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dog-whistle_politics

- https://www.google.com/amp/www.theroot.com/8-sneaky-racial-code-words-and-why-politicians-love-the-1790874941/amp

- http://money.cnn.com/2016/10/19/news/dog-whistle-trump-clinton/

- http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Dog_whistle_politics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://vid.me/wzqT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the loving adulation of the german people. The chancellor is such a hard worker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be new kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's rich coming from that gold palace living fucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait for it son, researches already said HOLD MY BEER 

- https://www.wired.com/2016/06/clever-attack-uses-sound-computers-fan-steal-data/
- https://www.wired.com/2015/07/researchers-hack-air-gapped-computer-simple-cell-phone/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump foundation was shut down after it was being investigated for fraud in 4 states. Mostly becuase of the reporting how Trump used Trump Foundation to buy a huge painting of himself to hang at Mar-Largo resort, that he used it to personally buy a Tim Tebow signed helmet, and last because it used Trump foundation donations to pay for the replacement of a flag pole he had too tall for Florida rules. 


It was hilarious as his son cried out that they did so much to help people. But later it was found out that no organization has any record of any donations from Trump Foundation. In particular to military veteran support groups trump said he made a 10 million dollar donations to. The Washington Post called up all of them and all of them reported not a single sent or contact from the Trump Foundation for a donation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You misogynist malcontent bitterly rabid rangers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the funny thing about Hillary and "her friends" they have done more for aids treatment, international poverty, women's rights, developing nation female self empowerment, universal eradication of polio, universal access to education, and donated billions of dollars to other NGO and international government UN organizations to do the same. 

What did Trump donate to? Himself for a signed helmet of Tim Tebow, a huge painting of himself that he hung up in his private resort, and a replacement of a flag pole because he was sued for violating Florida law ....

Oh wait i forgot he didn't donate any of that money. It came from donations made to the Trump "charity" which is under investigation by 4 different state attorney generals for fraud and violations before he shut it down ... but that still doesn't stop the fraud investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dysfunction is in the republican party. They started this game with Newt Gingrich 26 years ago in 1995 with the first government shutdown. Since then it has been the republicans in tea party and far more extreme forms that have shut down are government an additional two times and made actually passing laws nearly impossible because they became the least productive congress IN THE HISTORY OF THE UNITED STATES ON PURPOSE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot ... um i forget the department's name ... oh thats right Rick Perry for department of energy, or the agency that funds clean alternative energy research and oversees our nuclear regulatory and nuclear weapons stockpile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait so you are saying voat isn't racist enough for your taste?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm alive thanks to the affordable care act. I have medications that keep me from trying to kill myself and I have therapist and doctor that keep me sane while i'm going to school with support from the American with disabilities act making sure I get help for my issues and accommodations for my disabilities.  I actually have a 3.7 GPA in Computer engineering and i'm in the honors society now because of that extra help protected and supported by democrats. I also am able to afford to go to school at 32 because of pell grants covering my classes. So When i look at the teams and i see them as the ones who cheered for this video clip right here of Ron Paul ... [yeah i think there might just be some evil ass fucks on the republicans team.](https://youtu.be/8T9fk7NpgIU) 

There are inept people on the democrats don't get me wrong but democrats typically in the last 30 years have done nothing but make sure people got treated equally and had protections under the law for the rights to vote, have fair representation for their vote, had legal representation if they couldn't afford it, and pretty much made sure that kids had food if they were poor, kids could go to school, and kids like me with learning disabilities didn't get tracked into an education track with kids who liked to burn things or eat paste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone says being gay is a sin, being transgender is sin, being able to control when something gestates inside of your body but said hey you can't limit mentally ill people, (my self included one I'm depressive Bipolar type 2, with panic attack disorder, and Persistent depressive disorder aka dysthymia ), or spousal abusers or people with restraining orders from buying guns I got issues with them. When 4 of the people on the science and technology Congressional committee including it's chairman believe the world is only 10,000 years old I got issue with that.

peace and prosperity for only one group of people, race, or religion is not peace and prosperity for all. The Republican party is an extremist cult now that only helps those who mockingly wave the conservative jingoism flag around while caring a cross and shooting people who are minorities who dare question their edicts from "god" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sadly think the innocent days of Jimmies rustling is long gone and i really only wish it would return. We are in darker times now. 4chan is an agent of the state now. They are the brown shirts and they are the the state meme alchemists. They work for the government now with arrogant smiles and slack jawed laughing free of charge with maniacal cult member like glee. Memes have been weaponize and perverted from simple innocent jokes of innocent human folly to something cruel, something vicious, something unclean.

Notice how every meme on 4chan for example now is entirely racist as fuck and nazi like as fuck and always promotes a political autocratic anti democracy populous idea. The bitter loneliness of incels and /b/tards who grew up past 20 and still stayed on /b/ or moved to /pol/ as their only outlet have become these demonic ghouls of internalized rage and bitter vile. Its like watching the wild men of the woods and the Easterlings join Sauron's army against their own kind for only limited folly.

From Anarchists, to Libertarians, to Fascists the tumble of political leanings 4chan and dark realm of memes have been corrupted and perverted. Its like watching propaganda run by retards but because its bombarding people so often its like being hit with a hammer over and over again until you finally scream "2+2=5" or there are five lights when there was only ever four!

There is no greater truth but the truth sold to you by the state now and empirical evidence that contradicts that "truth" is thrown on the book burning pile with great applause and laughter from the peanut gallery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically GOP is prepping for Apartheid white minority government right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie doesn't actually make great legislation. We need to have centrists and I'm not talking Neo Con Democrats either. Democracy requires middle line compromise, but the right wing party is off in the desert of insanity for the most part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are few democrats i would very much keep who have morals and ethics and have shown they are actually good at what they do. Such as Al Franken and Elizabeth Warren. They actually do stuff to protect the rights of citizens and not just some fantasy for the gun lobbyist gun makers either, like the right to privacy, the right to not be conned by banks and other financial institutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigel Farage is a guy i would love to see have his ass though his mouth on a pike. He just has such a punchable face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keith is actually the nerd, a chad is a white guy who is a preppy mother fucker who most likely votes republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell is a Gigawatt?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just him, The entire Trump Cabinet, elected and office staff of the GOP, and a list of corporate tools from the DNC as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [In the words of the GOP audience, LET THEM DIE!!!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8T9fk7NpgIU t=6s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
