<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1841</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly 21 years. Diagnosed at 3 :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodnight, and GODSPEED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A possible ending I wouldn'tve minded was Light winning, and then Ryuk kills him anyway. Something like "I told you Light, in the end the only bad person left will be you". Light begs for his life for 40 seconds, and Ryuk returns to SR after his death. Or something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its true it never made sense to me that that scenes in 0.2...I assumed KH appeared to collect all the fallen hearts post war but i dunno ultimately.

Ill definitely watch that GJ video, but what still bugs me is that even if there are two coexisting versions, Luxu wouldn't need to be there to record the events himself if Xehanort also has it. Why bother going to all the effort of passing the blade down if he could just witness the events himself? MoM would know either way.

Ultimately though I really have no idea. KhX's story likes turning my brain to spaghetti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not BBS he's watching. Master Xehanort owns Luxu's keyblade at that point. Its the first keyblade war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have an upvote sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thank you! :) The main inspiration behind it was FFXV. I really wanted a sense of camaraderie between my team, what better way than to give them all a goal in common to protect? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit amen to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
