<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9866</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falcon 9 Rocket With Dragon Spacecraft Vertical at Launch Complex 39A [3000 x 2000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [U.S. National Library of Medicine's page on aniridia.](https://ghr.nlm.nih.gov/condition/aniridia) 

This gene is called a [homeotic gene](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Homeotic_gene) which is a type of master gene that controls the formation of specific body parts during development. Many homeotic genes are interchangeable among species such as *PAX6* gene in humans, mice, squids, and some other animals and the *eyeless* gene in fruit flies. 

 [Expression of that gene looks like this in fruit flies.
](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/2e/19/73/2e19730b624986b128df205cfb47dc4a.jpg) As a human, I'm glad our similar gene *PAX6* expresses no iris rather than no eye at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A normal human eye has a colored iris surrounding the pupil (dark area where light enters). Mutations in PAX6 cause eyes to develop without an iris, a condition called aniridia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> crow goes tobogganing using a mayonnaise lid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Sirs, With Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 04:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful work! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took this photo this January, this beauty was along the shore of a local river with about 20 of its friends of several species of gull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ring-billed gull (Larus delawarensis) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you count penguins from space? From their poop smears, of course </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, David. I'm sorry you went through all that fuss. I loved the research, the treadmill, and the shrimp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello and thank you for speaking with us today!

How do you feel about the shrimp treadmill? It is one of my favorite "silly sounding" research topics. Were there any facts that were overlooked with this study given its oddness?

Thank you again for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello and thank you so much for being here to answer our questions!

This is fascinating research on something I think most of us don't put much thought into. When you say it is possible to design a personalized diet is this something our general practitioners are aware of yet or is this still in the research phase? If so, how long do you believe until we can really start incorporating this knowledge into our everyday lives?

Thank you again for your time, it's appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took about 20 or 40 years to make (depending on which article you read, I am seeing both years used), so several generations to get this massive dam. I have been unable to find how many currently are living there. I'm looking, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [National Geographic page](http://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/b/beaver/) on beavers.

[Parks Canada page](http://www.pc.gc.ca/eng/pn-np/nt/woodbuffalo/natcul/beaver_gallery.aspx) full of photos of the dam.

[Parks Canada video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t40z21ZtVq0) of the dam, in Wood Buffalo National Park of Canada.

If you open Google Maps you can see it [here](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Largest+beaver+Dam+in+the+world/@58.271435,-112.2544277,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x53b76aac4c14e1b1:0xf5bd60b121769202!8m2!3d58.271435!4d-112.252239).

The first person to explore the dam was [Rob Mark in 2007](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/edmonton/world-s-largest-beaver-dam-explored-by-rob-mark-1.2771964). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beavers build dams to slow down currents in river, lakes and ponds. This allows them to build a home that won't wash away and gives them space to swim. The largest beaver dam in the world is in Alberta, Canada and measures 2,790 ft (850 m) in length. It is so large it can be seen from space! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Parks Canada video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t40z21ZtVq0) of the dam, in Wood Buffalo National Park of Canada.

If you open Google Maps you can see it [here](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Largest+beaver+Dam+in+the+world/@58.271435,-112.2544277,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x53b76aac4c14e1b1:0xf5bd60b121769202!8m2!3d58.271435!4d-112.252239).

The first person to explore the dam was [Rob Mark in 2007](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/edmonton/world-s-largest-beaver-dam-explored-by-rob-mark-1.2771964). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The largest beaver dam in the world is in Alberta, Canada and measures 2,790 feet (850 m) in length. It is so large it can be seen from space! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, Ethan! Thank you so much for taking the time to speak with us today.

I've worked on a similar project before, taking blood samples to assess which organisms particular mosquito species were feeding on to help track the West Nile Virus. Awesome way to use drones! How is your data looking so far and is the government interested in implementing management practices based off of your findings? This could be so beneficial if properly paid attention to by management teams.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary for the busy:

 A new WCS study in India shows that three carnivores  tigers, leopards, and dholes (Asian wild dog)  seemingly in direct competition with one other, are living side by side with surprisingly little conflict. Usually, big cats and wild canids live in different locations to avoid each other.

Yet in four relatively small reserves in Indias wildlife-rich Western Ghats region, WCS researchers have found that they are co-existing, despite competing for much of the same prey, including sambar deer, chital, and pigs.


[Journal article link.](http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/284/1848/20161860)

**Abstract:**

Species within a guild vary their use of time, space and resources, thereby enabling sympatry. As intra-guild competition intensifies, such behavioural adaptations may become prominent. We assessed mechanisms of facilitating sympatry among dhole (*Cuon alpinus*), leopard (*Panthera pardus*) and tiger (*Panthera tigris*) in tropical forests of India using camera-trap surveys. We examined population-level temporal, spatial and spatio-temporal segregation among them across four reserves representing a gradient of carnivore and prey densities. Temporal and spatial overlaps were higher at lower prey densities. Combined spatio-temporal overlap was minimal, possibly due to chance. We found fine-scale avoidance behaviours at one high-density reserve. Our results suggest that: (i) patterns of spatial, temporal and spatio-temporal segregation in sympatric carnivores do not necessarily mirror each other; (ii) carnivores are likely to adopt temporal, spatial, and spatio-temporal segregation as alternative mechanisms to facilitate sympatry; and (iii) carnivores show adaptability across a gradient of resource availability, a driver of inter-species competition. We discuss behavioural mechanisms that permit carnivores to co-occupy rather than dominate functional niches, and adaptations to varying intensities of competition that are likely to shape structure and dynamics of carnivore guilds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study says despite direct competition, tigers, leopards, and dholes are living side by side in protected areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas Byrdsong, Aerospace Engineer at NASA Langley Research Center - 1963 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specimen collected from a cranberry bog for my research and preserved in alcohol. Photo taken in the lab with macro camera set up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Water bug (Belostoma flumineum) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why You Should Donate Your Medical Data When You Die: Organs are not the only item of value from the deceased </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This term is where I get my punny user name from. :) As an ecologist, I greatly enjoy studying the roles of organisms within their ecosystems. Currently working on a cranberry bog succession study where we are looking at the change over time (0-60 years) of cranberry bogs and which plants and invertebrates are found as the years change and the bogs take back the land from the growers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article summary for the busy:

When youre a small pre-mammalian creature, sometimes the only way to protect yourself against fearsome predators like saber-toothed carnivores is to turn your saliva into a venomous cocktail. That is exactly what a therocephalian therapsid called Euchambersia mirabilis did about 257 million years ago (Permian period) in what is now South Africa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Pre-Mammalian Reptiles Were First Terrestrial Vertebrates to Produce Venom, Paleontologists Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The life of AT-Steve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvelous Mantis by Takamichi Irie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An ecological niche is the role and position a species has in its habitat and environment. This includes what it eats, where it lives, the time of day or night it is active and all interactions with the biota and abiota of the ecosystem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In front of Madame Tussaud's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for speaking with us today.

Have you had any close calls while doing field work?

Is there any way to slow ice shelf loss at this point or are we now in mitigation mode?

What has been the most surprising data to come out of your research?

Thank you again! Your time is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/sciencefacts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Water bug (Belstoma flumineum) captured for my research and preserved in alcohol. [OC] [2048 x 1365] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Image Credit   Copyright: Evangelos Souglakos

[NASA's page on the photo.](https://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap170214.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rosette Nebula </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honeybees let out a whoop when they bump into each other - A vibrational pulse produced by honeybees, long thought to be a signal to other bees to stop what they are doing, might actually be an expression of surprise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that is a nightmare! Rare too, I believe. That diver is incredibly lucky to not have been hurt by all that thrashing as at that point the shark wouldn't have been thinking about eating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be my Number 1 any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can in my class. :) Tea, coffee, water or whatever. Preferably in a reusable container as this is an environmentally centered course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just glare from my lamp. It's only tea and a mug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you ever shame someone over tea if they enjoy it? OP's in a dorm, it's not always easy to deal with loose tea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In front of the bull's ass in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grading papers and writing up an exam is easier with a nice cup of Earl Grey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most abundant gas in the atmosphere is nitrogen, with oxygen second. The composition of the atmosphere, among other things, determines its ability to transmit sunlight and trap infrared light, leading to potentially long-term changes in climate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy birthday, Charles Darwin! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is Charles Darwin's birthday! The father of evolution was born February 12, 1809 and published On the Origin of Species in 1859. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Great recommendation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really wonderful. I love everything about this exchange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is definitely evidence of extinction by overhunting, but yes habitat loss is a huge factor. We're currently forcing many many species to the brink by habitat loss. It really is a shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it does correlate to humans landing on that particular island, likely a mix of hunting and habitat loss sadly. We are great at causing extinction, both locally and globally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Danish astronaut has captured the best-ever images of rare blue flashes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divers have pulled a 1,000 year old tortoise skeleton from a blue hole in the Bahamas with much of its DNA intact. It is the first sample of ancient DNA retrieved from an extinct tropical species which could provide insight into the evolutionary history of the Caribbean tropics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divers pull 1,000 year old tortoise skeleton from a blue hole in the Bahamas with much of its DNA intact. It is the first sample of ancient DNA retrieved from an extinct tropical species and it could provide insight into the history of the Caribbean tropics and the reptiles that dominated them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is too cute! Glad you guys had fun together, the pizzas look great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When asked about their bromance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sweet Darcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pulled it dead out of the larger colony for photos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dubia roach (Blaptica dubia) [OC] [2048 x 1365] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dubia roach (Blaptica dubia). Testing new macro set up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding this. You want coated pasta, you've got a dry pile under all that delicious topping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Caramelized onion meatballs with asparagus and pasta in Alfredo sauce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discovered a way to create LEDs that can also detect and absorb light. They modified tiny versions of LEDs, called quantum dots, and created nanorods in which quantum dots directly contact two semiconductor materials. One allows movement of positive charge, and the other the negative one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Springtime fashionable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do! Great observation. Very cute little guys and gals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full and free journal article [*A New Species of Dwarf Lemur \(*Cheirogaleidae:
Cheirogaleus medius *Group\) from the Ankarana and
Andrafiamena-Andavakoera Massifs, Madagascar*](http://static1.1.sqspcdn.com/static/f/1200343/27358083/1480545032610/PC30_Frasier_et_al_Cheirogaleus_shethi.pdf?token=%2BFedS4jMrvcbAhnhvt8GgTJcUWk%3D).

**Abstract:**

A new species of dwarf lemur, Cheirogaleus shethi sp. nov., of the C. medius group is described from the dry and
transitional forests of northern Madagascar. This species can be found along the forest corridor from Ankarana Special Reserve
east to the Analamerana Special Reserve down to the Bekaraoka forest in the Loky-Manambato Protected Area. This species is
genetically distinct from other members of the C. medius species group and is sister to a poorly known lineage in Sambava. The
identification of this new species highlights the importance of northern Madagascar as a reservoir of biodiversity.

Cynthia L. Frasier et al. 2016. *A New Species of Dwarf Lemur (*Cheirogaleidae: Cheirogaleus medius *Group) from the Ankarana and Andrafiamena-Andavakoera Massifs, Madagascar.* Primate Conservation 30: 59-72 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new dwarf lemur species, Sheths dwarf lemur, has been discovered in the dry and transitional forests of northern Madagascar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sci-News article [*Cheirogaleus shethi: New Species of Dwarf Lemur Found in Madagascar*](http://www.sci-news.com/biology/cheirogaleus-shethi-new-species-dwarf-lemur-04594.html).

Full and free journal article [*A New Species of Dwarf Lemur \(Cheirogaleidae:
Cheirogaleus medius Group\) from the Ankarana and
Andrafiamena-Andavakoera Massifs, Madagascar*](http://static1.1.sqspcdn.com/static/f/1200343/27358083/1480545032610/PC30_Frasier_et_al_Cheirogaleus_shethi.pdf?token=%2BFedS4jMrvcbAhnhvt8GgTJcUWk%3D). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new dwarf lemur species, Sheths dwarf lemur, has been discovered in the dry and transitional forests of northern Madagascar! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/47_Tucanae):

47 Tucanae (also known as NGC 104 and Caldwell 106) is a globular cluster located in the constellation Tucana.

47 Tucanae is the second brightest globular cluster in the sky (after Omega Centauri), and is noted for having a very bright and dense core. It is one of the most massive globular clusters in the Galaxy, containing millions of stars. The cluster appears roughly the size of the full moon in the sky under ideal conditions. Though it appears adjacent to the Small Magellanic Cloud, the latter is some 210,000 light-years distant, over 10 times farther away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 47 Tucanae, a huge, ancient globular star cluster about 15,300 light-years away from us, harbors a central black hole about 2,200 times more massive than our Sun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 06:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lower than average at the equator, then even lower at the poles. Highest between the two.

 I was in a rush to post after being away for a few days dealing with preparing for lectures and creating my students' first exam. :P I assumed the fine folks here would understand what I meant. I'll be more specific next time. I just hated to leave things empty for two days.

It'd really be wonderful if you guys could also post! I'm sure you have a lot of great facts to share with everyone. I love this sub, I'm happy to run it, but I also have teaching undergrads and research to do which folks are relying on me for because they pay me to do it. :) 

I'm honestly sorry I rush sometimes and titles get wonky. Help me out, make your own posts (in accordance to our rules). I'm excited to read about what interests you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raven Enjoying the Snow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheers to these wonderful sirs! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salinity is lower at the equator and decreases towards the poles. This is due to greater precipitation near the equator and lower evaporation near the poles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually the reports we get on posts are not very friendly. I'd love to take a minute and thank the few people who left either funny ("Confused doggo") reports or very sweet reports (We are glad you like the sub! We love modding it). 

Please keep up the great work with your wonderful posts! We wouldn't have such a successful sub without you guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello and thank you for being here to speak with us!

Library science is not a common route to take. What about this career path spoke to you? 

How do you handle plagiarism when you find it in journal articles? What is the action plan?


Thank you again, your time is very appreciated.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are some excellent butts. They've got my upvote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys played a great game. Please don't be sour. Ryan was wonderful, be proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist flying in!

That is a juvenile hawk and likely still learning how to properly hunt. I'm sure this hare really threw it for a loop there! 

Predators don't start off being great at catching prey, they have to learn. This hawk is probably about a year or two old and hasn't been away from home for very long. It'll get better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complete with shaded tail overhang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full and free journal article.](http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/1359104516687612)

**Abstract:**

There is a growing focus on child wellbeing and happiness in schools, but we lack self-report measures for very young children. Three samples (N = 2345) were combined to assess the psychometric properties of the How I Feel About My School (HIFAMS) questionnaire, which was designed for children aged 48 years. Testretest reliability was moderate (intraclass correlation coefficient = .62). HIFAMS assessed a single concept and had moderate internal consistency (Cronbachs alpha values from .62 to .67). There were low correlations between scores on the child-reported HIFAMS and parent and teacher reports. Children at risk of exclusion had significantly lower HIFAMS scores than the community sample (mean difference = 2.4; 95% confidence interval (CI) = [1.6, 3.2]; p  .001). Schools contributed only 4.5% of the variability in HIFAMS score, the remaining 95.5% reflecting pupil differences within schools. Girls scores were 0.37 units (95% CI = [0.16, 0.57]; p  .001) higher than boys, while year group and deprivation did not predict HIFAMS score. HIFAMS is a promising measure that demonstrates moderate reliability and discriminates between groups even among very young children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emoticons Help Gauge School Happiness Level in Young Children (between 4 and 12 years of age) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full and free journal article.](http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/1359104516687612)

**Abstract:**

There is a growing focus on child wellbeing and happiness in schools, but we lack self-report measures for very young children. Three samples (N = 2345) were combined to assess the psychometric properties of the How I Feel About My School (HIFAMS) questionnaire, which was designed for children aged 48 years. Testretest reliability was moderate (intraclass correlation coefficient = .62). HIFAMS assessed a single concept and had moderate internal consistency (Cronbachs alpha values from .62 to .67). There were low correlations between scores on the child-reported HIFAMS and parent and teacher reports. Children at risk of exclusion had significantly lower HIFAMS scores than the community sample (mean difference = 2.4; 95% confidence interval (CI) = [1.6, 3.2]; p  .001). Schools contributed only 4.5% of the variability in HIFAMS score, the remaining 95.5% reflecting pupil differences within schools. Girls scores were 0.37 units (95% CI = [0.16, 0.57]; p  .001) higher than boys, while year group and deprivation did not predict HIFAMS score. HIFAMS is a promising measure that demonstrates moderate reliability and discriminates between groups even among very young children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emoticons Help Gauge School Happiness Level in Young Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Scientist Studies Whether Solar Storms Cause Animal Beachings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opening section for the busy:

A long-standing mystery among marine biologists is why otherwise healthy whales, dolphins, and porpoises  collectively known as cetaceans  end up getting stranded along coastal areas worldwide. Could severe solar storms, which affect Earths magnetic fields, be confusing their internal compasses and causing them to lose their way?

Although some have postulated this and other theories, no one has ever initiated a thorough study to determine whether a relationship exists  until now. NASA heliophysicist Antti Pulkkinen, who works at the agencys Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland, has teamed with the federal Bureau of Ocean Energy Management, or BOEM, and the International Fund for Animal Welfare, or IFAW, to determine whether a link exists.

Strandings occur around the world, involving as few as three to as many as several hundred animals per event. Although a global phenomenon, such strandings tend to happen more often in New Zealand, Australia, and Cape Cod, Massachusetts, said project collaborator Katie Moore, the director of IFAWs global Animal Rescue Program. Headquartered in Yarmouth Port, Massachusetts, IFAW operates in 40 countries, rescuing animals and promoting conservation to secure a safe habitat for wildlife.

These locations share some key characteristics, such as the geography, gently sloping beaches, and fine-grained sediment, which we think all play some role in these events, she said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA scientist studies whether solar storms cause animal beachings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NASA's page [here](https://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap170205.html) and write up:

Some moons wouldn't survive the collision. Tethys, one of Saturn's larger moons at about 1000 kilometers in diameter, survived the collision, but today exhibits the resulting expansive impact crater Odysseus. Sometimes called the Great Basin, Odysseus occurs on the leading hemisphere of Tethys and shows its great age by the relative amount of smaller craters that occur inside its towering walls. The density of Tethys is similar to water-ice. The featured image was captured in November by the robotic Cassini spacecraft in orbit around Saturn as it swooped past the giant ice ball. Cassini has now started on its Grand Finale Tour which will take it inside Saturn's rings and culminate in September with a dive into Saturn's thick atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odysseus Crater on Tethys by Cassini Imaging Team [1020 x 1020] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe the talking crow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Created by [Taylor Made Fossils](http://www.dinostatues.com/). They make a lot of life-sized dinosaur and prehistoric reptile statuary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ankylosaurus fiberglass statue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, you're right. They all start to blend together for me after a while. Especially if I'm not a fan of either team. P Stew and Ian are so adorable, either way. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bigger and heavier a player is the more mass he has and the greater the force required to break his inertia. This is why a running back will look to make quick cuts to the left or right to evade a tackler, the running back has less mass and can more easily change direction than his opponent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An NFL lineman can sweat through upward of 138 fl oz (9 lbs) of fluid! To estimate for the amount of moisture lost, trainers subtract a player's postgame weight from his pregame weight. The difference is approximately how much fluid they have lost and not yet replaced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confused about last year's Super Bowl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, keep the racism out of this sub. All racist comments will be removed and users will be banned when appropriate. This sub is built on the love of animals, cuteness and interesting facts.

Leave your nasty attitude at the door. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My body is ready for some football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Banana bread for breakfast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugging his paw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not annoyed enough to kick it off! Love these guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is really interesting because it means their genome was undisturbed or changed by any incoming genetic flow until the easterly migrations of the Bronze Age. Everything they learned about farming came through communication with outside groups and not from genetic lineage or through marrying outsiders. That would suggest trade and relative "peace" with other societies at the time. Very cool article!

The journal article *The Neolithic Transition in the Baltic Was Not Driven by Admixture with Early European Farmers* can be found [here](http://www.cell.com/current-biology/abstract/S0960-9822\(16\)31542-1?_returnURL=http%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0960982216315421%3Fshowall%3Dtrue). 

**Highlights:**

* A degree of genetic continuity from the Mesolithic to the Neolithic in the Baltic
* Steppe-related genetic influences found in the Baltic during the Neolithic
* No Anatolian farmer-related genetic admixture in Neolithic Baltic samples
* Steppe ancestry in Latvia at the time of the emergence of Balto-Slavic languages


**Summary:**


The Neolithic transition was a dynamic time in European prehistory of cultural, social, and technological change. Although this period has been well explored in central Europe using ancient nuclear DNA [ 1, 2 ], its genetic impact on northern and eastern parts of this continent has not been as extensively studied. To broaden our understanding of the Neolithic transition across Europe, we analyzed eight ancient genomes: six samples (four to 1- to 4-fold coverage) from a 3,500 year temporal transect (8,3004,800 calibrated years before present) through the Baltic region dating from the Mesolithic to the Late Neolithic and two samples spanning the Mesolithic-Neolithic boundary from the Dnieper Rapids region of Ukraine. We find evidence that some hunter-gatherer ancestry persisted across the Neolithic transition in both regions. However, we also find signals consistent with influxes of non-local people, most likely from northern Eurasia and the Pontic Steppe. During the Late Neolithic, this Steppe-related impact coincides with the proposed emergence of Indo-European languages in the Baltic region [ 3, 4 ]. These influences are distinct from the early farmer admixture that transformed the genetic landscape of central Europe, suggesting that changes associated with the Neolithic package in the Baltic were not driven by the same Anatolian-sourced genetic exchange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient DNA analyses show that unlike elsewhere in Europe, farmers from the Near East did not overtake hunter-gatherer populations in the Baltic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Gurche's website is [here](http://www.gurche.com/main_frameset.htm). He is also famous for his recreations of early Hominins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sue the T. rex by John Gurche </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick summary:

Nearly a decade after being logged, vegetation in forested areas severely burned by California's Cone Fire in 2002 was relatively similar to areas untouched by logging equipment. The findings of a U.S. Forest Service study shed light on how vegetation responds to severe wildfire and whether further disturbances from logging affect regrowth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegetation resilient to salvage logging after severe wildfire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick summary:

Nearly a decade after being logged, vegetation in forested areas severely burned by California's Cone Fire in 2002 was relatively similar to areas untouched by logging equipment. The findings of a U.S. Forest Service study shed light on how vegetation responds to severe wildfire and whether further disturbances from logging affect regrowth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegetation resilient to salvage logging after severe wildfire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Conjunction of Four by Maxime Oudoux](https://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap170204.html)

NASA's description:

On January 31, a waxing crescent Moon, brilliant Venus, and fainter Mars gathered in the fading twilight, hanging above the western horizon just after sunset on planet Earth. In this combined evening skyscape, the lovely celestial triangle is seen through clouds and haze. Still glinting in sunlight, from low Earth orbit the International Space Station briefly joined the trio that evening in skies near Le Lude, France. The photographer's line-of-sight to the space station was remarkably close to Mars as the initial exposure began. As a result, the station's bright streak seems to leap from the Red Planet, moving toward darker skies at the top of the frame.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On January 31, a waxing crescent Moon, brilliant Venus, and fainter Mars gathered in the fading twilight, hanging above the western horizon just after sunset. [1920 x 2877] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juno Completes Its Fourth Flyby of Jupiter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tally ho! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack of the Magpie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human empathy can even extend to dogs: empathetic people interpret dogs facial expressions more intensely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photo with Santa! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Roasted in the oven at 400oF until browned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, you too! Should be a great game. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wings are a common Super Bowl food. I also love making my own nacho cheese dip. Puff pastry in mini muffin tray filled with a little apple pie filling for quick grab desserts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pigs in a blanket are my favorite go to! Crescent roll dough wrapped lil'smokies are delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My very kind inlaws sent us an Omaha steaks package and it had filet and sirloin among other things. I also like ribeye, but this is what we had on hand. Super nice of them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Filet Mignon with red wine reduction and sauteed red onion with a side of roasted asparagus, Brussels sprouts and crumbled bacon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful view! I hope you had a great time. Winter camping can be a real joy of you're properly prepared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't downvote him or her. They are correct that usually there is an issue. With an animal this young though it's likely exhaustion and separation from their pod. When I was doing endangered shore bird research I had friends in the Marine Mammal Stranding program and they said the same thing. 

I came across a dead Humpback whale and that was a big issue for another story.

Thank you for chiming in, it's appreciated. You've got my upvote. :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he or she has its pod waiting for it it's got a good chance. If alone, I'm afraid not. It's very young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Pepperjack cheeseburger with bacon and guacamole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the full and free journal article.
](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep41679)


**Abstract:**

Social relationships can have important consequences for fitness in animals. Whilst numerous studies have shown that individuals often join larger groups in response to perceived predation risk (i.e. fear of predation), the importance of predation risk in driving the formation and stability of social relationships within groups has been relatively ignored. We experimentally tested how predation threat influenced fine-scale social network structure using Trinidadian guppies (Poecilia reticulata). When perceived predation risk was high, individuals developed stable and more differentiated social ties compared to when perceived risk was low. Intriguingly, social differentiation coincided with shoals being somewhat smaller under high-perceived risk, suggesting a possible conflict between forming stable social relationships and larger social groups. Individuals most at risk of predation (large and bold individuals) showed the most exaggerated responses in several social measures. Taken together, we provide the first experimental evidence that proximate risk of predation can increase the intensity of social relationships and fine-scale social structure in animal populations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Predator threat boosts friendships among Trinidadian guppies. Researchers discovered the fish developed stronger and more stable social bonds when they thought predators were in the area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this sub usually takes prehistoric reptiles as well as dinosaurs, and it's a beautiful piece. Glad you liked it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone interested here are the Highlights and Abstract from the journal article found in the journal [*Circadian Entrainment to the Natural Light-Dark Cycle across Seasons and the Weekend*](http://www.cell.com/current-biology/abstract/S0960-9822\(16\)31522-6?_returnURL=http%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0960982216315226%3Fshowall%3Dtrue).

**Highlights**

* Living in the modern electrical lighting environment delays the human circadian clock
* The human circadian clock adapts to seasonal changes in the natural light-dark cycle
* A weekend camping trip prevented the typical weekend circadian and sleep delay

**Summary**

Reduced exposure to daytime sunlight and increased exposure to electrical lighting at night leads to late circadian and sleep timing [ 13 ]. We have previously shown that exposure to a natural summer 14 hr 40 min:9 hr 20 min light-dark cycle entrains the human circadian clock to solar time, such that the internal biological night begins near sunset and ends near sunrise [ 1 ]. Here we show that the beginning of the biological night and sleep occur earlier after a weeks exposure to a natural winter 9 hr 20 min:14 hr 40 min light-dark cycle as compared to the modern electrical lighting environment. Further, we find that the human circadian clock is sensitive to seasonal changes in the natural light-dark cycle, showing an expansion of the biological night in winter compared to summer, akin to that seen in non-humans [ 48 ]. We also show that circadian and sleep timing occur earlier after spending a weekend camping in a summer 14 hr 39 min:9 hr 21 min natural light-dark cycle compared to a typical weekend in the modern environment. Weekend exposure to natural light was sufficient to achieve 69% of the shift in circadian timing we previously reported after a weeks exposure to natural light [ 1 ]. These findings provide evidence that the human circadian clock adapts to seasonal changes in the natural light-dark cycle and is timed later in the modern environment in both winter and summer. Further, we demonstrate that earlier circadian timing can be rapidly achieved through natural light exposure during a weekend spent camping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trouble getting to sleep? Scientists say go camping! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the full and free journal article.
](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep41679)

General Statement on posts - Please read at least the abstract before drawing any conclusions from the news source. News often misses important or interesting points and to really understand what the researchers were getting at it's important to understand the journal article. This is of course meant in no offense to the article's writer, but it is a common issue with only reading the news source.

And as always, please direct all comments at the specific content of the original post, or the specific scientific article it is based upon and do not post anecdotal comments.

**Abstract:**

Social relationships can have important consequences for fitness in animals. Whilst numerous studies have shown that individuals often join larger groups in response to perceived predation risk (i.e. fear of predation), the importance of predation risk in driving the formation and stability of social relationships within groups has been relatively ignored. We experimentally tested how predation threat influenced fine-scale social network structure using Trinidadian guppies (Poecilia reticulata). When perceived predation risk was high, individuals developed stable and more differentiated social ties compared to when perceived risk was low. Intriguingly, social differentiation coincided with shoals being somewhat smaller under high-perceived risk, suggesting a possible conflict between forming stable social relationships and larger social groups. Individuals most at risk of predation (large and bold individuals) showed the most exaggerated responses in several social measures. Taken together, we provide the first experimental evidence that proximate risk of predation can increase the intensity of social relationships and fine-scale social structure in animal populations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Predator threat boosts friendships among Trinidadian guppies. Researchers discovered the fish developed stronger and more stable social bonds when they thought predators were in the area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists report on latest Deepwater Horizon oil spill impacts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a chart to visually express just how deep this is.](http://www.deepseachallenge.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/mariana-trench-graphic-30812.jpg)

James Cameron did a special on it, the website is [here](http://www.deepseachallenge.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Challenger Deep is the deepest known point in the Earth's seabed hydrosphere, with a depth of 10,898 to 10,916 m (35,755 to 35,814 ft). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dimetrodon by Simon Stlenhag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientific terminology, yes, they are all Cetaceans. Porpoises and dolphins and whales are differentiated in common terminology due to size, tooth shape and a few other characteristics. I made a comment about differentiation before, I'll copy and paste here:

Size isn't the determining factor between what is a whale and a dolphin (though all are [Cetaceans](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cetacea) and technically whales). 

Dolphins have sizes that range from 5 ft to 30 ft whereas whales range from 10 ft to 115 ft. You can see the overlap in size between the two differentiations. 

Dolphins belong to different families than whales; [Delphinidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oceanic_dolphin) (oceanic dolphins), [Iniidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iniidae) (river dolphins), [Platanistidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Asian_river_dolphin) (South Asian river dolphin), [Pontoporiidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_Plata_dolphin) (La Plata dolphin), and [Phocoenidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Porpoise) (poirposes). Whales are separated into two sub-orders; [Mysticeti](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baleen_whale) (baleen whales) and [Odontoceti](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toothed_whale) (toothed whales, which includes all of the dolphin families). Beluga whales belong to family **Monodontidae** in sub-order **Odontoceti**.

Some whales have baleen, all dolphins are toothed whales. Dolphins and whales are also shaped a bit differently (their heads for one) and dolphins have [flat, spade-shaped teeth](https://aqua.org/~/media/Images/Animals/Atlantic%20bottlenose%20dolphin/animals-dolphin-slide2-web.jpg) as opposed to [cone-shaped teeth](http://cdn1.arkive.org/media/52/52BB8F48-E222-4CDF-8E72-95DCC4440D91/Presentation.Large/Pygmy-sperm-whale-mouth-and-teeth-detail.jpg) (the photo is a Pygmy Sperm Whale) of other whales. Adding to the differences list, all baleen whales have [two blowholes](http://i.imgur.com/ZcsCcmm.jpg), whereas toothed whales (so not just dolphins) only [have one](https://img1.steemit.com/0x0/https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Bottlenose_Dolphin_KSC04pd0178_head_only.JPG).

Also, for characteristics that differ dolphins from porpoises please see NOAA's page [here](http://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/dolphin_porpoise.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist swimming in. This is adorable!!

This little cutie is not a whale, but a ~~porpoise~~ dolphin (whoops mistype). It's a [Heaviside's dolphin](http://www.arkive.org/heavisides-dolphin/cephalorhynchus-heavisidii/) (*Cephalorhynchus heavisidii*). Easy to ID with that dark body and little white stripe. Kind of looks like a baby Orca!

These beautiful animals have a really short range, occurring only off the west coast of South Africa and Namibia. They live in family groups, or pods, of 2 to 10.

Here is the Time article about this rescue [*This Kayaker Saved a Beached Baby Dolphin*](http://time.com/4362676/baby-dolphin-kayaker-rescue/).

Technically all whales and dolphins and porpises are whales or Cetaceans. Porpoises dolphins and whales are differentiated in common terminology due to size, tooth shape and a few other characteristics. 

I made a comment about differentiation before, I'll copy and paste here:

Size isn't the determining factor between what is a whale and a dolphin (though all are [Cetaceans](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cetacea) and technically whales). 

Dolphins have sizes that range from 5 ft to 30 ft whereas whales range from 10 ft to 115 ft. You can see the overlap in size between the two differentiations. 

Dolphins/Propoises belong to different families than whales; [Delphinidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oceanic_dolphin) (oceanic dolphins), [Iniidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iniidae) (river dolphins), [Platanistidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Asian_river_dolphin) (South Asian river dolphin), [Pontoporiidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_Plata_dolphin) (La Plata dolphin), and [Phocoenidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Porpoise) (poirposes). Whales are separated into two sub-orders; [Mysticeti](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baleen_whale) (baleen whales) and [Odontoceti](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toothed_whale) (toothed whales, which includes all of the dolphin families). Beluga whales belong to family **Monodontidae** in sub-order **Odontoceti**.

Some whales have baleen, all dolphins are toothed whales. Dolphins and whales are also shaped a bit differently (their heads for one) and dolphins have [flat, spade-shaped teeth](https://aqua.org/~/media/Images/Animals/Atlantic%20bottlenose%20dolphin/animals-dolphin-slide2-web.jpg) as opposed to [cone-shaped teeth](http://cdn1.arkive.org/media/52/52BB8F48-E222-4CDF-8E72-95DCC4440D91/Presentation.Large/Pygmy-sperm-whale-mouth-and-teeth-detail.jpg) (the photo is a Pygmy Sperm Whale) of other whales. Adding to the differences list, all baleen whales have [two blowholes](http://i.imgur.com/ZcsCcmm.jpg), whereas toothed whales (so not just dolphins) only [have one](https://img1.steemit.com/0x0/https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Bottlenose_Dolphin_KSC04pd0178_head_only.JPG).

Also, for characteristics that differ dolphins from porpoises please see NOAA's page [here](http://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/dolphin_porpoise.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist swimming in. This is adorable!! Thank you for the ping.

This little cutie is not a whale, but a dolphin. It's a [Heaviside's dolphin](http://www.arkive.org/heavisides-dolphin/cephalorhynchus-heavisidii/) (*Cephalorhynchus heavisidii*). Easy to ID with that dark body and little white stripe. Kind of looks like a baby Orca!

These beautiful animals have a really short range, occurring only off the west coast of South Africa and Namibia. They live in family groups, or pods, of 2 to 10.

Here is the Time article about this rescue [*This Kayaker Saved a Beached Baby Dolphin*](http://time.com/4362676/baby-dolphin-kayaker-rescue/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NASA's page on the photo and summary:](https://www.nasa.gov/image-feature/goddard/2017/hubble-captures-brilliant-star-death-in-rotten-egg-nebula)

The Calabash Nebula, pictured here  which has the technical name OH 231.8+04.2  is a spectacular example of the death of a low-mass star like the sun. This image taken by the NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope shows the star going through a rapid transformation from a red giant to a planetary nebula, during which it blows its outer layers of gas and dust out into the surrounding space. The recently ejected material is spat out in opposite directions with immense speed  the gas shown in yellow is moving close to one million kilometers per hour (621,371 miles per hour).

Astronomers rarely capture a star in this phase of its evolution because it occurs within the blink of an eye  in astronomical terms. Over the next thousand years the nebula is expected to evolve into a fully-fledged planetary nebula.

The nebula is also known as the Rotten Egg Nebula because it contains a lot of sulphur, an element that, when combined with other elements, smells like a rotten egg  but luckily, it resides over 5,000 light-years away in the constellation of Puppis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hubble Captures Brilliant Star Death in Rotten Egg Nebula </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. George Carruthers and Apollo 16 Far Ultraviolet Camera/Spectrograph [2464 x 3000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. George Carruthers and Apollo 16 Far Ultraviolet Camera/Spectrograph - April 1972 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Australian government's page on them.](http://www.environment.gov.au/cgi-bin/sprat/public/publicspecies.pl?taxon_id=64389)

The turtle allows algae to grow on its body, likely for camouflage!

Given their very limited range and how long it takes them to be sexually mature, they are listed as *endangered* on the [IUCN Red List](http://www.iucnredlist.org/details/7664/0). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mary River turtle (Elusor macrurus) is found exclusively in the Mary River in Queensland, Australia. It takes 25 years for female Mary River turtles to reach maturity and 30 years for males. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Australian government's page on them.](http://www.environment.gov.au/cgi-bin/sprat/public/publicspecies.pl?taxon_id=64389)

The turtle allows algae to grow on its body, likely for camouflage!

Given their very limited range and how long it takes them to be sexually mature, they are listed as *endangered* on the [IUCN Red List](http://www.iucnredlist.org/details/7664/0). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mary River turtle (Elusor macrurus) is found exclusively in the Mary River in Queensland, Australia. It takes 25 years for female Mary River turtles to reach maturity and 30 years for males. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review: 75152 Imperial Assault Hovertank | Bricks to Bothans Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'A very sassy individual:' Orphaned crow being trained at Atlantic Veterinary College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists believe that humans began using fire to cook food in a controlled way around 1 million years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, bby! 3 I love it! It's great looking through all the posts. I'm excited to contribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And also, I sweat.

Yes! This is my problem. I'm fairly sweaty as I don't regulate my body temperature very well. I am almost always too warm. Women's antiperspirant doesn't work well. I'd have to pay double for the special kind, whereas men's regular works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The price differences are really ridiculous! Especially for an inferior product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually prefer men's deodorant because I like the smell and it usually works better. Marketing to a gender is ridiculous, sex chromosomes are not involved with scent preference. And for the record, I sweat a lot if I am even remotely warm. I need something that works, not just smells like flowers or baby powder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 10:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to help. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick summary:

Its not quite Jurassic Park: No one has revived long-extinct dinosaurs. But two new studies suggest that it is possible to isolate protein fragments from dinosaurs much further back in time than ever thought possible. One study, led by Mary Schweitzer, a paleontologist from North Carolina State University in Raleigh who has chased dinosaur proteins for decades, confirms her highly controversial claim to have recovered 80-million-year-old dinosaur collagen. The other paper suggests that protein may even have survived in a 195-million-year-old dino fossil.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Scientists retrieve 80-million-year-old dinosaur protein in milestone paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not an ant it's a wasp (Family [Mutillidae](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutillidae)). The symbol is correct. Common names can be odd sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is *Siebenrockiella leytensis*'s [Arkive page](http://www.arkive.org/philippine-pond-turtle/siebenrockiella-leytensis/image-G32593.html).

An interesting sentence from ther Arkive page:

As this rare turtle is known from so few specimens, its biology remains unknown

Really puts things into perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Palawan forest turtle, also known as the Philippine pond turtle, is one of the rarest turtle species in the world. It is only found in five municipalities in Northern Palawan, Philippines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bridge Scene Done in Lego </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist sauntering in. Because this very cool pupil contraction is a form of courting ritual!

The [flame bowerbird](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flame_bowerbird) (*Sericulus aureus*) is, as you can see, absolutely breathtaking! I love the vibrant colors. Bowerbird males build shelters called *bowers* to attract females. Depending on the species the structures will differ some, but most form an archway and are decorated with brightly colored doodads. 

You can see a few examples here: [Photo 1](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/--7p8NNLQFf0/UhbhP0rP6RI/AAAAAAAAClA/AgYenZqxP3k/s1600/bower+bird+3.jpg), [Photo 2](http://www.viralforest.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/Satin-Bower-Bird-Nest.jpg), [Photo3](https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/23/32154075_b242c23aa8_b.jpg). The more elaborate, the more the ladies are impressed! Once they lure a female they begin their courtship dance. 

These differ by species, but for the flame bowerbird a big part of the dance involves a wheezing call and the pupil fluctuations you can see in the gif.

The BBC Earth video can be found [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1XkPeN3AWIE) and just one on the flame bowerbird [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TT4kpr2efEs).

Check out BBC's article [*The Crazy Courtship of Bowerbirds*]
(http://www.bbc.com/earth/story/20141119-the-barmy-courtship-of-bowerbirds) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note, the video says crow, but that beauty is a raven. You can tell by size and the chest feathers. Could also be a female, impossible to know from this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raven thinks he's sneaky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Routines of 16 Top Olympians created by /u/Owaves_101 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For more information, you can check out the [Wiki page](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schmidt_sting_pain_index) or check out Science Friday's podcast talk (or read the article) [here](http://www.sciencefriday.com/segments/from-nettles-to-volcano-a-pain-scale-for-insect-stings/).

[Hymenoptera](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hymenoptera) (which means membrane wing) is an Order if insects including bees, wasps, ants and sawflies.

* [*Breaking Trail* episod](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tXjHb5QmDV0)e with the host being bitten by a Bullet ant

* Same host, Coyote Peterson, [being stung by a Tarantula Hawk](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MnExgQ81fhU)

* [Coyote Peterson and a Velvet Ant/Cow Killer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EF-oSVCCqzU)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Schmidt Sting Pain Index is a pain scale rating the relative pain caused by different hymenopteran stings. It is mainly the work of Justin O. Schmidt (born 1947), an entomologist at the Carl Hayden Bee Research Center in Arizona. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dione's lit hemisphere faces away from Cassini's camera [1041 x 564] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martha Chaffee, widow of Roger Chaffee, their children and acting NASA Administrator Robert Lightfoot, place wreaths at the graves of Apollo 1 crewmembers Virgil "Gus" Grissom and Roger Chaffee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City Volcano Jackhammer (30350) was a really cute little build! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two handsome devils </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just hanging out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
