<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8351</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god....I just "yelped" at work from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many Republicans does it take to screw in a light bulb?

- I don't know, they are screwing the country too much to worry about a light bulb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it incredibly shocking that you were able to do it twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *FLOOF* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you not see the support base that Trump has? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when this makes it to the front page, you need to microwave a camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you went directly from the Bicep Flyer (invitation) to the Bicep Cake, that's how you really get them hooked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want this to be good but I will not buy games till I see how the reviews are anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't there suppose to be a kill switch on it like on jet skis and boats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never a dull day here in US Politics it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of dead skin cells there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I thought I use to have a cold toilet seat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a ruff neighborhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I was hoping for a [Beverly Hills Ninja](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKdaOkrWEfw) moment :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I support neither party, I support the Constitution and the right that "We the People" should have. I have never heard that before but if you think that this administration has not caused a political revolution you have tunnel vision. 

Just look at all the offices in Virginia where people are running now, even in steadfast Rep held positions for years because having a Dem run would mean nothing. Revolution is coming, for good or bad, it is coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless the GOP does something soon, they WILL get destroyed in the 2018 and 2020 elections. The People are into politics more than the past 50yrs and if they do not start standing up for the Constitution and the American People they will be ousted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump BOUGHT the place for 50mil and SOLD it for 100mil during a time the HOUSING MARKET WAS CRASHED, in what world does that make any sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like a younger Mark Hamill here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You thinking he will last 4 years is laughable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will his supporters say when he starts selling off National Park land to the highest bidder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least someone's advertising is on point! If only I had the Switch and the game, I would definitely buy some pizza because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet she lights up a black lit room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think if they spend another $1.50 on bubbles they would save money from damaged returns they keep getting.

Also, its fucking Google. They should've designed a bubble pouch or contoured box that the phone went in for shipping. The latter could save on shipping cost, also while protecting the phone more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be something that breaks the people and when violence happens, it will be waves and waves of it like the ocean breaking on the shore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a Rob Schneider movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must've been some low hanging fruit of the loins there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother had the "when you smile you show teeth" so he just put his chompers together and tried to show as much teeth as possible. You went a different direction I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked for Mickey in Florida, didn't kill myself but I did get out when I could afford to move away from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a Christian that caused terrorism](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-3134689/Dylann-Roof-devout-Christian-baptized-Lutheran-faith-went-church-camp-regularly-attended-Mass-reveals-pastor-family-attend-church-services-pray-massacre-victims.html)

[Wisconsin Sikh Temple massacre, Aug. 5, 2012](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wisconsin_Sikh_temple_shooting)

[Tennessee Valley Unitarian Universalist Church shooting, July 27, 2008](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Knoxville_Unitarian_Universalist_church_shooting)

[Army of God, responsible for numerous property crimes, the group has committed acts of kidnapping, attempted murder, and murder.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Army_of_God_(United_States)

Do you need more help seeing the truth that there are terrorists on both sides or are you good now?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generalizing 1 sub sect of religious people (ISIS) to EVERYONE else is the definition of fear mongering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, isn't she the "Trump" of France? Trump used the same fear mongering to win the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/The_Donald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the animal that Godzilla was based off of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fargo checking in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why hasn't he wifed you yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **LORDY** **LORDY** **Lordy** *holds* *up* *cross* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Typical* *r/food* *comment* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit!! *unzips* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you wrote that today as a 2nd grader you would get in-trouble and have possible repercussions because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be overjoyed with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This was a mission that was started before I got here. This was something they wanted to do, he said. They came to me, they explained what they wanted to do  the generals  who are very respected, my generals are the most respected that weve had in many decades, I believe. And they lost Ryan.

I am at a loss for words on him always wanting to point out "I am the best there ever has been and my team is the best". To me it means the exact opposite if he has to try and reinforce himself all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only hope, with everything going on, that the GOP dies as a party after these years we have TD as President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeezy Peezy President Meezy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they measure the impact crater it looks like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the video](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/transcoded/e/ea/Reichelt.ogv/Reichelt.ogv.240p.webm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Sega Game Gear takes less batteries than that thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like a Street Fighter victory dance here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but IT would find it EASY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I would giggle too holding a dog doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you stupid enough to think your email can't be traced back to you?  That's what I want to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, that did happen in Olathe, Kansas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how long will this shit keep going on before the GOP has the balls to do something about this Totalitarian President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now now, who can say they never hit the spot where a taste of beer sent you over the edge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Devil is just standing by taking pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you are not 8 years old and that is a picture of your parents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me laugh everytime I see this posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they know that will weaken their followers. They want "YES" men and women instead of people thinking for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how he gives everything he is holding to the safari driver lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [C-Span Video of Betsy DeVos speach](https://www.c-span.org/video/?424394-101/betsy-devos-delivers-remarks-cpac) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wife him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss the days of Hulk Hogan and Randy the "Macho Man" Savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First copy paste quote I have done in my account, troll more why don't you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hate begets hate; violence begets violence; toughness begets a greater toughness. We must meet the forces of hate with the power of love."

- Martin Luther King

I would also add "Fear begets fear" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 Comments and I see none of them, some people are shadow banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, and right now America is a 50/50 for Tea Parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that kid's mind just exploded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems right considering the size of that coffee mug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND he wants to go after Recreational Marijuana use. Coincidence? I HIGHLY doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Some people just want the world to burn." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that's-a-Reddit for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rather have that than a degloved penis, yes there are pictures on Google... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could make this as the loading bubble instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One and Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL Well maybe we do need the Mean Jesus to come back and show Christians how to be Christ like. 

You know, the Jesus that ransacked the sellers in the temple, the one that taught to love your neighbor as yourself, the one that said "don't look at the speck of dust in your neighbor's eye when you have a plank in your own". Christians today are led more by fear and preachers that teach the old testament instead of what Jesus taught. 

Ugh, sorry...ranting here but having to go to Christian school as a kid and having Bible classes I actually researched things myself instead of believing everything that was told to me. I could go on and on with this but I will leave it with this: Jesus and his teachings do not agree with what Christians are preaching and doing now-a-days.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they just want a strongman who can just rule by decree.

You should tell them that's how dictators start.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if he did his JOB instead of treating it like a business that he and his friends can get rich off of. For "draining the swamp" he sure has put people into powerful places that have NO RIGHT to be there or are associated in some way to profit off of the position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  leave you a burning world.

My grandma thinks this way and says that means Jesus will come back....fml

Edit: I will say she WANTS this to happen....that's a Pentecostal Christian Republican for you. She also defends Trump adamantly all the time and I refuse to watch the news with her anymore because she doesn't listen to facts and just shouts over you to prove she knows what she is talking about. She gets her news from FOX, CBS, and Facebook and thinks she knows everything there is to know about Trump and Democracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean "billionaire" since no one really knows how much he has since he never released his tax info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely kittens. Who doesn't enjoy those little fluff balls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sooooooo incredibly biased that it goes past hilarity to absurdity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will preface this by saying I am a 6'5" bearded male.

Anyone familiar with rentals in Florida is that most of them have a screened in pool. Well, I was out there just chilling and enjoying the weather one night with my 4 other roommates and we noticed a dark spot under the glass patio table so we backed up and turned on the lights. Well that black spot was a Wolf Spider and the light scared it so it took off. 


Did you know the Wolf Spider is one of the fastest spiders in the world? We didn't and were surprised when it took off SUPER FUCKING FAST toward the open door. The roommate that turned on the light, slammed the door shut behind him and it turned skittered past us with blinding speed. All of us screamed like little girls while jumping up on chairs or running around the corner. The roommate that was inside locked the door to make sure we didn't let the spider in, so we had to run out the back in the darkness hoping that a spider did not latch onto our face, legs, and soul.


Needless to say, we did not go back out till the morning and we found the spider at the bottom of the pool. We left it in there all while day, while we went to work, to make sure it was dead before we scooped it out.


TDLR: Wolf spiders can move 2ft in a second; screamed like a girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like my grandma but with the microwave. I recently moved in to help her around the house, cook for her, and drive her places but EVERY TIME I cook she wonders why I do not use the microwave.

Grandma, I went to culinary school and NO I will NEVER use a microwave to cook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T_D be like: "BUT OBAMA!!! AND EMAILS!! AND HE IS WORKING WHEN AT MAR-A-LAGO!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Boy, yu shur do got a perrty mouth" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magicians still exist? Or is he a "Magician" when that's what the lady's want him to dress up as? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You definitely rolled a nat 20 on your CHA check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what will be the straw that breaks the camels back? At this point....idk....I have very little faith in democracy anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Washington Post breakdown on emails](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-fix/wp/2016/07/24/here-are-the-latest-most-damaging-things-in-the-dncs-leaked-emails/?utm_term=.17cfca4468e1)

[Wikileaks 2016 Democratic National Committee email leak](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2016_Democratic_National_Committee_email_leak)

[Class action lawsuit alleging election fraud by the Democratic National Committee thrown out of court, DNC attorneys have admitted that the Democratic party is corrupt and attempted to prove that Bernie Sanders donors knew this all along and therefore cannot sue them.](http://yournewswire.com/democratic-party-attorneys-admit-dnc-is-corrupt/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's the secret, 5 year old boys are easy. It's like caring for a cat. An old cat.

Yea, just wait till they are in their teens and want to stick their penis in everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We might have literally elected a fucking child molester President of the United States because EMAAAAAIIIIIIILLLLLLS

No, it was the DNC and Debbie Fucknuts that he was elected. You don't rig a fucking DEMOCRATIC ELECTION and expect the masses to just vote for the candidate you push down our throats. 

I did not vote Trump AND would not vote for Hillary, DNC caused this mess and we need to accept that fact if we want to grow as a nation and make sure that people in charge are HELD FUCKING ACCOUNTABLE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am glad I have not bought it yet. Maybe in a few months I will see how it is doing and if it worth the purchase later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [OK, Michael](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1zUbhwIlGfg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would Putin kill his own operatives, because that is the same question.

[Alexander Litvinenko](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poisoning_of_Alexander_Litvinenko) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takes one to know one, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading your post history is ENTERTAINING. Calling the Ukraine government illegal, talking about dash cams, just being an angry Russian...it explains so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they will find any poison...

edit: Looks like the Russians are already down voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when you browse r/All and r/Popular(now) and go by rising there is a TD post every other one to 5 in a row and a different sub and then 5 more TD posts. This is even at night when most of the USA is asleep there are posts still pouring in. 

Just doesn't seem possible that 371,756 "Centipedes" can keep a 24/7 post vortex going without some sort of paid help or outside (US) help.

I know I can change it so I don't see their posts but it just seems odd that they can have more posts on rising then any other sub out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  These folks dont handle criticism well at all.

Yep, and if you do you get a ban hammer. What I want to know is how they are able to post 24hrs a day MANY "new" things all the time without having people dedicated and paid to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am barely holding it together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am out farming some Pot, enjoying the weather and making lots of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I want to say I am deeply sorry for your loss. You could have her character enter the godhood as a goddess/god and influence your party from now on? Maybe have them become an angel and your party has a quest to help them to godhood to help guide the party from now on from above? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, the Republicans will take care of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the fucked up thing is his voters/followers will eat it up and still be oblivious to everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would add to others in that the customer is not always right. Stick up for your employees when the customer is wrong and you will have loyal employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lioness is a she </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The group said consideration of ACT and SAT scores in applications upholds "white supremacy" because it restricts opportunities for the poor.

Da fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally, a view of Trump that symbolizes why he does the things he does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That being said, I don't understand how his approval rating is above single digits. 

Lurk in TD and you will see the fanatics that ignore all the data and everything happening in this administration. That is what you call pure hatred of the Democrats, and it blinds people from the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shin..Calf...either way it hurts like a mofo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, this is a total repost from yesterdays joke. I just want to see how many upvotes it can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has so much sugar rushing through her she has the jitters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really do not know African ~~history~~ genocide if you think Saudi Arabia is the worst of the countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Fuck it~~

Don't pay attention to these big holes we dug and the 12 year olds with guns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternative Bricks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember taking my feet off the pedals and going down a hill and just letting momentum do its job. 

I also remember the pedals nailing me in the shins after when I wanted to put my feet back on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how you change laws? You start by having underage girls sending pictures of themselves in their underwear to Politicians and then they either need to change laws or go to jail also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thank every time too. I know it takes a lot of time and energy to DM, and sometimes patience when us PCs do the opposite of what you expect, but I am ever grateful of all the effort that is put in week after week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must've not been wearing a red shirt that one day he died.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was waiting for her to drop the baby when she saw it move again...I must be on reddit too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must be a "hacker" since I am on the computer now....where did I go wrong in my life? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit Armor of Hexes is VERY OP

Curse BBEG and if you get hit, you only have a 50% chance of ACTUALLY being hit.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true, I use to work for a Janitorial company and women's bathrooms were the dirtiest. The only time I was worried about someone's blood loss was when the feminine hygiene container was dripping blood onto the floor and it pooled into the 8" x 8" tile square. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it in the theater for a few more days and you will have a Homemade Pickle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sweet sweet embrace of Death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the "takedown" at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "News" died long ago when all the news agencies started being bought out by the few. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
