<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This year's OOTS calendar now available as a Gumroad PDF, as are calendars from previous years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I THINK THEY'RE CALLED TRUMPET MUTES, NOT "CAPS" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'D RATHER BE MORALLY STRAIGHT THEN HAVE SUPERBOWL WINS

THAT'S NOT TRUE, AND YOU KNOW IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think [this might be video from the yacht.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nSAoEf1Ib58)

Or completely opposite; one or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHICH DID YOU FORGET, XVI OR XXIII? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE SEAHAWKS ARE MASTER OF THE EAST WIND, BUT IT REMAINS TO BE SEEN IF THEY WILL ADVANCE TO LEVEL 13 AND EARN THE TITLE "MASTER OF WINTER". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IN THE SPIRIT OF THE HOLIDAY SEASON, I'D LIKE TO PRAISE A GREAT FORMER PLAYER OF MY TEAM'S UPCOMING OPPONENT.

KEN ANDERSON SPENT HIS ENTIRE SIXTEEN-YEAR CAREER WITH THE BENGALS.  HE WAS A FOUR-TIME PRO BOWLER, EARNED THE 1981 NFL MVP, WAS SELECTED FIRST-TEAM ALL-PRO IN 1981 -- WITH TWO SECOND-TEAM ALL-PRO SELECTIONS IN OTHER YEARS -- AND TWICE LED THE NFL IN PASSING YARDS FOR A SEASON.   HE THREW TWO TOUCHDOWN PASSES IN A LOSING EFFORT IN SUPER BOWL XVI.  HE DESERVES TO BE IN THE PRO FOOTBALL HALL OF FAME.

TOO BAD HE NEVER GOT A SUPER BOWL RING.

OH, WAIT, NEVER MIND -- [WE TOOK CARE OF THAT FOR YOU.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ken_Anderson_(quarterback\)#Coaching_career) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor 1981-1982 San Diego Chargers.  Survived the heat and humidity of Miami and overcame the Dolphins deep into overtime, with players exhausted and cramping.  Their reward was a trip to the coldest wind chill ever recorded for an NFL game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little did the Steelers know that 1983 was Terry Bradshaw's last season, but obviously Marino would have been a better draft pick than Gabriel Rivera, even an alternate-universe stone-cold sober Gabriel Rivera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although a case can be made for Ben Roethlisberger.  Very different eras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps the most famous call of this nature is [Ahmad Bradshaw's non-fumble in the NFC Championship Game against the 49ers.](http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-playoffs/09000d5d8263fe84/Bradshaw-s-controversial-near-fumble)  The ruling [was the same: forward progress stopped.](http://www.nfl.com/news/story/09000d5d8263fcc3/article/niners-harbaugh-nofumble-call-analogous-with-the-tuck-rule)  The Giants went on to win Super Bowl XLVI; the 49ers went home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some long-ago teams not yet mentioned, from the [list of teams with the top DVOA or estimated DVOA of all time](http://www.footballoutsiders.com/dvoa-ratings/2014/historical-dvoa-estimates): 1967 Raiders, 1976 Steelers, 1968 Colts, 1987 and 1995 49ers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw in the 2010 Patriots, who outscored their opponents 518-313 to post a 14-2 record in the regular season, but then lost to the Jets in the divisional playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crossunfit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steelers-Lions.  Lions finally make the Super Bowl!

And they're #25 in weighted DVOA and #26 in DVOA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least the icing snuffed out the fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it could have been [this play, too.](http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-game-highlights/0ap2000000240138/Polamalu-leaps-in-for-sack) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately, a ban on [leaping over the line to tackle the quarterback](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gWuxsd8xD8I) is not being discussed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collection of drafts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wherein I post draft comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why this talk is a little premature; it's highly unlikely, but the Colts still could be Super Bowl LI champions.

Then again, my team hasn't fired a coach since LBJ was a lame-duck president, so what do I know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not forget Week 17 last year, when Buffalo defeated the Jets to knock them out of the playoffs (and let the Steelers in). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 14:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the same principle as the "founder effect" in population genetics and linguistics: more heterogeneity at the original site, and more homogeneity at the colonized sites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I won't go down with the ship*    
*And I will throw my hands up and surrender*    
*There will be a white flag upon my helmet*    
*Postseasonless, and always will be* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atmospheric refraction... and an infinitesimal amount of gravitational lensing, [less than one millionth of one degree.](https://www.reddit.com/r/askscience/comments/21lo0t/just_how_much_does_earths_gravity_bend_light/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fun times in Cleveland today!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmLA5TqbIY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In many cases, QBs did indeed call plays.  Some coaches used shuttles, of course, and other techniques for calling plays from the sidelines.

[In this particular case:](http://www.encyclopedia.com/people/sports-and-games/sports-biographies/terry-bradshaw)
During his years with the Steelers, Bradshaw called all of his own plays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cairo is 164 feet.  The Capitol is 289 ft.  Not even close.

The only structures taller than the Capitol in the district are the Basilica, the Old Post Office Pavilion, the National Cathedral, the Washington Monument, and a radio tower.  [Source.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_tallest_buildings_in_Washington,_D.C.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when /r/GenerationGap was active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was an all-American punter in college, and [here's his 91-yard punt in the NFL.](http://www.nfl.com/videos/philadelphia-eagles/0ap2000000153487/Randall-Cunningham-91-yard-punt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think the Steelers are the team that's going to finish second in the AFC North?  Possible... but a quote comes to mind.

*"None of you seem to understand.  I'm not locked in here with you.  You're locked in here with me!"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/11 was a terrorist attack in which most deaths resulted from defenseless civilian targets.

Pearl Harbor was a military strike on a military base, in which the attacked base fought back.

OP's larger point that there is a lot of American naivete about war is well taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, the only real conflict (not including any of that 'glorious' nation founding stuff) on US soil, is fast fading into the mist of history.

I'm curious as to what you consider to be the list of "real conflicts" fought on U.S. soil, and which one is fast fading into the mist of history, leaving the others to all be "nation founding".  Was the Civil War "nation founding"?  Was Pearl Harbor not a "real conflict"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could somehow reflect that emitted light back into the molecules, you could get the **l**ight **a**mplified by **s**timulated **e**mission of **r**adiation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it like cheering for a team with an NFL MVP?  I was quite young in 1978. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One other thing to remember about that era is that many quarterbacks, including Bradshaw, were calling most of the plays.  No helmet radios. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, long time no see!  Hope you are well.

I'm apparently blind and can't find the "export csv" button; would you post a screenshot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, last chance on the ChangeTip account.  Sorry to keep bothering you if this doesn't work.

$0.00624778 /u/changetip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I already donated $1, but am trying to clean out the last of my ChangeTip account.  If this works, it works; but if not, sorry.  I realize it's a pathetically small amount, but you seem like the most likely person to still have a ChangeTip account open...

$0.00624779 /u/changetip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Export tip history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a long history of tips sent and received at ChangeTip (like 300+ sent, 1000+ received.)  Any way to export it before ChangeTip closes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You reminded me that [it's always a good time for a Public Service Anouncement about why fans should stay off the field.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fC3xNSiRTDc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Linkety.](https://soundcloud.com/the-bill-simmons-podcast/ep-48-nfl-divisional-lines-w-cousin-sal) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Discussed in the comments of OP's post here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/5h00k7/i_made_a_map_of_all_the_us_waterbodies_using_r_oc/dawct4c/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  [More discussion of Utah's salt flats in this map here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/dataisbeautiful/comments/5h00k7/i_made_a_map_of_all_the_us_waterbodies_using_r_oc/dawdcf1/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map of bodies of water in the continental United States, by /u/WF835334 [OS] [2048x1243] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct.  For anyone confused, Mr. Spock on *Star Trek* does not use the title "Dr."  But Dr. Benjamin Spock, pediatric best-selling author, did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 13:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, each guy with the bat is only caught at most once per innings.  In a similar(ish) sport with four bases, each guy with the bat can be caught three or more times a game.  So in that other sport, there are many more boring catches, but also many more interesting catches, although only a small fraction are barehanded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 15:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asphalt, or in this particular case, dark soils in the aptly named Death Valley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 14:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll find that 56.7C is the highest temperature ever (reliably) recorded on Earth **in the shade, in the air.**  The highest temperature ever reliably recorded on Earth **in the sun, on the ground** exceeds 90C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boiled chicken is also acceptable in [Wenchang chicken.](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wenchang_chicken) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people say we take grammar way too serious**ly**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> XKCD map of the USA with state name parodies [740x507] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 13:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using adjectives when you should use adverbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IF ONLY THERE WERE AN "NFC WITHOUT THE SOUTH" FLAIR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derek Jacobi's [portrayal of Alan Turing in *Breaking the Code* appears to be on YouTube.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S23yie-779k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/obnubilation replied and [nailed it.](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/5fburh/selma_is_100_historically_accurate_but_imitation/dajifsg/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, more to the point, Alan Turing in *The Imitation Game* was the dumbest codebreaker in human history.  Alan Turing in real life was not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ENJOY THE TASTE OF THIS SALT... oops, sorry, let me know when the Trash Talk thread goes up during the week of the game against the Bengals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 02:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to imagine an 18-week NFL schedule with 16 games and two byes: it actually happened in 1993. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steelers-Chargers, Week 17, 1994.  Starting QB Neil O'Donnell is pulled partway through the game to keep him healthy for the playoffs; Steelers have already clinched #1 seed.  Chargers win 37-34.  Chargers earn #2 seed and the bye.  Chargers edge Dolphins in the divisional round.  Chargers edge Steelers in the AFC Championship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "badly run" is going a bit too far.  Badly run franchises don't make it to two Super Bowls and win one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My public Bitcoin wallet address </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18go42ZSjHbN8cgFE7H8WH2rHBwu4aNDgT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a perfectly reasonable explanation why someone such as your sister-in-law or /u/goblueM's dad would do this.

Are they blind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we need Tottenham to get in the EL to give Cameron Carter-Vickers some playing time so that Bruce Arena will call him in and cap-tie him in March before England snaps him up!

^(Wait, you mean Prem fandom doesn't revolve around consequences for the USMNT?  And CCV is nowhere near an England call-up?  Oops, sorry.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 03:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... and don't delay too much, because ChangeTip is not long for this world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 03:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, we can just tip by name, right?

Congrats! /u/SeamusMichael $1 /u/changetip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Brons" is a nice touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NFCN, check

NFCE, check and double check

NFCW, check, double check, and triple check; only the Niners have dodged the Steelers

Three out of four divisions ain't that hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 10:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never omit from the "grand total" the people who only remember to donate when it's time for the next drawing thread...

$1 /u/changetip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 10:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the dying days of Changetip... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the ALS do-it-yourself experiment inspired by any similar situations in the past?  One that leaps to mind is two participants in the AZT double-blind trial, one who turned out to be receiving AZT and one who turned out to be in the placebo control group, splitting half of their pills with each other.  When there were literally no other treatments for AIDS, taking half of two pills -- that the patients couldn't distinguish from one another, except that one set of pills was prescribed to one patient and another set of pills to the other patient -- ended up giving both patients a dose of AZT, albeit a dose reduced by half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the bare minimum flair... at Chotchkie's or otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably /u/The_Big_Lebaneski voted for Amy Schumer's second cousin, once removed.

Also, I encourage everyone in North Carolina to vote **against** Aaron Burr's fourth cousin, seven times removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 05:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Moon can't crush us.  If the Moon approached Earth, the Earth's tidal forces would tear the Moon apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even downballot?  Bernie needs our help in the House and especially the Senate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton 48, Trump 38 is the topline number in that poll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to bet reddit gold on the election results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 02:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats really want 51-49 in the Senate.  A 50-50 split with Kaine elected Vice President would give Democrats control, but would put that control at risk just ten months later, in the November special election for Kaine's Senate seat that will have temporarily been filled by an appointee of Virginia's Democratic governor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick, all the cows left months ago!  Close the barn door! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you who are new to following polls closely, this is the famously accurate poll from *The Columbus Dispatch* that is also famously bizarrely conducted **by mail**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the famous Columbus Dispatch mail-in poll has a narrow Clinton lead in Ohio, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 13:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that in 2012, it took days after the election to know the Florida result.  Thankfully, unlike in 2000, the election didn't hinge on Florida in 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 13:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't miss it: in polls-plus at 538 at this exact moment, Nevada is white.  50% Clinton, 50% Trump.

(Yes, I feel pretty confident personally that Clinton will take Nevada.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may well be.  But two years of control are better than none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mid-term elections?  Heck, control of the Senate could be back at stake again in Virginia's 2017 special election if Tim Kaine is Vice President, which would necessitate that election to fill his old Senate seat.  But better ten months of Senate control than zero months, and better still two years than zero years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The great attraction to Pennsylvania for Republicans late in campaignsMcCain-Palin in 2008, Romney-Ryan in 2012, and Trump-Pence in 2016is the Keystone State's lack of early voting.  It is always the last-chance saloon to swing a ton of electoral votes, no matter how long the odds.  By way of contrast, Nevada, for example, may already be practically locked in for the Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe firmly in Nate Silver's model and his 99/100 record in calling states in the last two elections.  The one consolation is that his model does **not** account much for GOTV, and there appears to be an unusually large discrepancy between Clinton-Kaine's powerful ability to get out the vote and Trump-Kaine's fecklessness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1a) Clinton gets into the White House, Democrats take over the Senate, and the Democratic long-shot House takeover comes through.  Bernie and other progressives are critical constituents in legislation getting through Congress.

1b) Clinton gets into the White House, Democrats take over the Senate, but Democrats miss out on the House, although they narrow the Republican majority.  Bernie and other progressives are key players, although balanced by House Republicans.  Bernie and other progressives in the Senate are critical constituents of Senate-only votes, such as confirming federal judges and Supreme Court justices.

1c) Clinton gets into the White House, but Republicans maintain control of both houses of Congress.  Bernie and other progressives are relatively unimportant.

Dear fellow progressives: strongly consider voting for those downballot Democratsprogressive, centrist, or otherwisein the House and the Senate too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Vonnegut was *incensed* at being burned?  I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to bet reddit gold on the election results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Eight is Enough*?  But Dick Van Patten died last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about time.  This is one of the big reasons to have put Kaine on the ticket: near-fluency in Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't dream it, be it."

 *The Rocky Horror Picture Show* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Donald Trump:

If you wanted the rights to domain names, maybe your family shouldn't have changed their name to a common word used in trick-taking card games and a few other contexts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Cuban.  He remembers being so poor that he ate ketchup sandwiches.  I don't think he's that afraid of losing his wealth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam Wang is 98/100 in calling states in 2008 and 2012.

But Nate Silver is 99/100. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, you know, Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who hasn't read [Katy Tur's article from August in *Marie Claire*](http://www.marieclaire.com/politics/a21997/donald-trump-katy-tur/) should do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... infidelity is still nominally illegal in 21 U.S. states, 5 of which consider it a felony.  It's almost never prosecuted, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The brother's... fifteen-year-old wife?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to being the adult, also, you know, you're married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the circumstances, can we not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democratic nominee **literally taught Sunday school.**  But conservative Christian evangelists are still sticking with their Republican "tribe". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordered, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, therefore... stay with me here... when presented with such an eighties/nineties New York/New Jersey mogul/developer/casino owner, we shouldn't elect him as president? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, not betting 50 reddit gold against 1.  Presidential mortality rate per year alone has been a lot higher than 2% over the history of the nation.  If you want to shorten the odds, though, let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will bet you reddit gold right now that Tim Kaine won't be president on November 2nd, 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is one of the reasons that Bill Clinton wasn't removed from office.  The other is that not even all of the Republican senators were convinced of his guilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too bad that there's no easy way on reddit to invite a whole subreddit to a thread.  Your comment would be well served by further discussion from /r/SquaredCircle redditors.

Here, it's outside my area of expertise, but let me try to summon them:

#AND HIS NAME IS JOHN CENA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, such an outlier increases the probability that Clinton is actually winning significant numbers of Republicans in Florida, even if not 28%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only did the Democrats maintain Senate control in the 2012 elections, they actually gained two Senate seats.  It wasn't until 2014 that the Republicans took Senate control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senator Richard Burr's [great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-grandfather was Benjamin Burr.](http://freepages.genealogy.rootsweb.ancestry.com/~battle/senators/burr.htm)  Benjamin Burr's [brother was Jehue Burr Sr.; Jehue Burr Sr.'s son was immigrant Jehu Burr.](http://www.burrcook.com/history/burr.html)  Vice President Aaron Burr's [great-grandfather was the same immigrant Jehu Burr.](http://freepages.genealogy.rootsweb.ancestry.com/~dav4is/ODTs/BURR.shtml#BURR100)  That makes Senator Richard Burr the fourth cousin, seven times removed of Vice President Aaron Burr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SpontaneousHamilton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Deborah Ross has beliefs    
Burr has none.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't immediately see [Trump's appearance at the end of a Russian oligarch's music video, after the Miss Universe models,](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iuZUNjFsgS8) on your list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/ComradeManafort, please call your office.  I repeat, please call your office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well analyzed and described! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 10:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the total capacity of all incoming forms of transportation to the USA?  Road, rail, ports, airplanes.  How many orders of magnitude is it below 650,000,000 per week?

I ignore walking.  I suppose you could try to line up 650,000,000 people along the US-Canada border and the smaller US-Mexico border, but you've just pushed the question a few feet away: how do all those people get there in the first place?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, asset?!  I certainly have no evidence of that.  The video does demonstrate Trump's Russian ties, and raises questions with no good answers, like: did Trump perform in the music video as a favor to a Russian oligarch, or for pay, or did Trump pay to appear?  Any of the possible explanations would appear to be unsettling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please.  [The Crocus Group is Russian.](http://crocusgroup.com/crocus/about/)  Being born in Baku when it was still part of the USSR does not disqualify Emin Agalarov from having become a Russian oligarch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether Comey is sitting on evidence of Trump's ties to Russia I do not know, but I do know that [Trump is sitting at the end of this music video that is itself evidence of his ties to a Russian oligarch.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iuZUNjFsgS8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That article is pure revisionist history.  Bill Clinton was already well ahead in the polls heading into the weekend before election day.  It certainly wasn't because of the indictment that George H. W. Bush lost the election.  There was even a catchphrase at the time: "It's the economy, stupid!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're not Sam Wang, so my disagreement is with him, not with you: I think Nate Silver provides good justifications for his cautious probabilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear British brethren who assigned this headline to this article written by an American-educated Frenchwoman: no, the Attorney General of the United States did not "plead the fifth", you tossers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fahrenthold has literally been working on this story for months.  So if you mean "painstakingly building a massive edifice out of straws", maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is presumably the long-awaited story about the Trump Foundation that Fahrenthold has been working on for months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1989, was Webelos still separate from Cub Scouts?  (It was once separate, right?)  Anyway, yes, 11 would be the age of starting to be a Boy Scout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subtitle from the article:
And put Indiana's Mike Pence a heartbeat away from the presidency.

Gay-conversion therapy, AIDS-spreading Pence?

#NO THANKS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I greet women who want to be kissed on the cheek (yes, particularly French women), they typically clasp my arms.  They don't try to block me with a forearm shiver to my chest, like Jennifer Hawkins did to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just locker room talk.  Please ignore [the .gif posted](https://media.giphy.com/media/3oz8xxMMsCXjOKECjK/source.gif) by /u/thepotatoman23.  He's clearly an agent of Eris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right; Machiavelli was *warning against* what have come to be called Machiavellian tactics.  But he also demonstrated his expertise at analyzing those tactics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were feeling particularly Machiavellian in my election analysis (which, honestly, I'm not really; Director Comey hasn't earned that level of suspicion) I might surmise that James Comey is trying to push Democrats into releasing the long-awaited Trump October surprises.  Machiavelli might wonder what Comey gains from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton Leads Trump  And Obama And Reagan  In The Newspaper Endorsement Race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 15:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Substituting "Romney" for "Donald", some conservatives [alleged exactly that four years ago; they were wrong.](http://www.politico.com/story/2012/10/conservatives-jobs-data-are-phony-082070) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 15:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am proud to vote for Hillary Clinton in the general election, and at this point I find rehashed Republican scare tactics from eight years ago to be, frankly, tiresome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't assume.  VOTE!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, add him to the George Romney list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 12:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof.  Has to be one of the worst injury derailments of a projected career of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not just another long-range basket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 12:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton Voters Aren't Just Voting Against Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polls May Be Underestimating Evan McMullins Chances In Utah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Hombres, Nasty Women (schmoyoho featuring "Weird Al" Yankovic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1056: Top Five, Certainly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> xkcd: Life Goals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman Accusing Trump of Inappropriate Sexual Conduct Speaks Out at News Conference With Gloria Allred </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ana Navarro mocks Trump's use of Spanish in debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TENTH Trump accuser comes forward: Karena Virginia claims Donald groped her breast at US Open in 1998 while asking her, 'Do you know who I am? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton Probably Finished Off Trump Last Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Trump Wins, Here's How The Map Might Look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
