<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9140</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 06:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out There from Hunchback of Notre Dame

(Also Disney's most underrated movie!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A taco bowl from Trump tower

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're argument is a false equivalency.

Watching porn is not the same as creating porn (irrespective of how you define uploading nudes of yourself)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I appreciate the armed forces and soldiers who serve, this bumper sticker is just silly.

The only foreign power that ever invaded America also spoke English (England...of course)

There are no wars in modern military history whereby if we lost, then the outcome would have been "time to scrap English and brush up on my kanji" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Artist. 

Classic example of Hollywood congratulating itself for how awesome it is.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Florida Party Pack:

A T-Shit that says "Spring Break - Daytona '97"

A Signed Jimmy Buffet CD

Bath Salts

An Ora quick home HIV test

A wallet card with the numbers for: police, fire department and Miss Cleo psychic hotline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but seriously. Do I really even have to post this?

Clearly I *fucking* do

http://www.snopes.com/oxford-butts-study/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Famous Fisherman Hauls in Brick of Cocaine off Miami Coastline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your salary will soon be your secret in Philadelphia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy Bob Thornton as Willie in Bad Santa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Swanson is so going to kick my ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac and cheese, polish sausage, jack Daniel's, crock pot

...mmmm drunk food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three students charged with kidnapping classmate for sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone that works in investment management, I'm going to turn this into an ELI5.

Bernie Madoff promised his investors the same performance as stated above: **10% to 12% in annual returns**

Madoff Securities was a ponzi scheme and he stole $20 Billion.

It is **against the law* to promise a specific level of investment returns and that is why you will hear/see the phrase "past performance is not indicative of future results" in **all** advertisements. For example, at the bottom of every page of the SEC filing below.

Now For the ELI50:
Calculation of investment performance can be *very* complex. 

Are your returns asset or time weighted? 

Are you using a geometric or arithmetic mean return? 

Is your performance being impacted because you're harvesting tax losses?

There are just some of the basic things to consider. If you really want to plan for future, then I would perform the research yourself instead of listening to "financial gurus" (Suze Orman is another one that comes to mind.) We live in the age of data and it's never been easier to spend an afternoon learning what you really need to know.  

http://www.aol.com/article/2009/03/12/warning-signs-madoff-investors-ignored/1486147/

https://www.sec.gov/comments/s7-24-15/s72415-201.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using one of the 2,000 AOL "Free Hour" CD-ROMs my family received as a drink coaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said the same thing about Sex and The City after the first two episodes!

...infer what you will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wu Tang Clan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zwartboek (Black Book). It's a Dutch WW2 film by Paul Verhoeven and it's awesome.

Also Eastern Promises by David Cronenberg is another great film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I enjoy the music of Sevendust"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Everyone Has AIDS"

-Team America: World Police </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heading into 9/11 the markets were already feeling the pain of the Dot Com Bubble bursting. As far as markets were concerned, the 9/11 attacks were like adding gasoline to a fire.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dot-com_bubble

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number of times I googled "Is X a symptom of Y" where X is any symptom and Y is every deadly disease.

I'm a total hypochondriac but Xanax is wonderful :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They legitimately enjoy Jimmy Buffett's music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say a wiseass response to this, but then it dawned on me, I think there is actually a correct answer: condoms

While not technically food, heroin mules have been ingesting large quantities of drugs for years i.e. there is historical precedent for condoms being consumed even if they don't provide nutritional value (but then again, neither do pixie sticks).

If drugtraffickers can "safely" consume (and pass) heroin that way, then I think the Saw VIII victim that you describe above could conceivably beat the torture trap without having to actually eat shit and potentially contract god knows what diseases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horatio Alger, Jr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This list forgot:

22. If I tell you I can't pause this game to talk to you right now, then that's because I **can't** pause it. It's not my fault that Hideo Kojima decided Metal Gear Solid cut scenes need to be 45 fucking minutes long and, if I don't take copious notes, then I won't understand why Otacon has diarrhea 3 games from now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know lmao.

I originally meant for it to be only two sentences of snark, BUT then I thought, "If I only say that I sound uninformed. If I'm going to be snarky, then I need to be giving maximum effort" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The urinal is bad, but I think people that sound like they're having an asthma attack in a stall is worse.

You just sit there thinking to yourself, "Either they are *very* constipated or having a heart attack.  If it's the latter they better realized I'm not helping until I beat this level of Angry Birds" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the major exception of course being, Keanu Reeves' facial expressions; all of which were computer generated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone get my ski parka cause clearly hell has frozen over.

A person on the internet passed up the opportunity to be snarky and was instead *complimentary* 

Time for bed before a comment can spoil this moment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The riskiest thing about this picture is the 15 year old computer tower behind the poster.

I half expect a follow up post to be a news story about a computer lab fire in Reseda, California. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a gross oversimplification of a much more substantial economic policy. See below

1) First the US Govt gives tax breaks/incentives to corporations (with good lobbyists)

2) Then they give tax cuts to those in the highest tax brackets

Thus, the companies have higher earnings and pay lower taxes.

This makes the executives (1%ers) look good, who get paid more for better than expected company performance

In turn those same executives are taxed at a lower personal rate on their performance based pay (or taxed at lower rates in end around ways that regular people don't understand like ordinary vs. interest income)

So the government both loses tax revenue to the corporations *and* the individuals running them. But that's okay, because everyone in Congress will get jobs at those same companies when they are finally voted out of office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celebrity hacker gets longer sentence than expected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, their definition of renewable energy is "unpaid interns pedaling bicycles hooked up to generators"

When reached for comment, Larry Page said, "we've done away with those stupid brain teaser questions and just started asking our potential interns if they take spinning classes. We've found their level of misery on the job is about equal until we remind them they're helping the environment. Surprisingly this motivates them! I couldn't believe it either! I mean, I'm a fucking a billionaire and we have kids from UC Berkeley and MIT on spin bikes pedaling like hamsters on a wheel.  And because kids always wants to work at google, we'll always have interns! I love America!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch the Epcot Spaceship Earth Transform into the Deathstar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials: Passenger hit train's emergency stop to get phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry Tate: Office Linebacker

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=RzToNo7A-94 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's being smug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rash of OD's claim six lives in Philadelphia Sunday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump unloads on China in Twitter rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 07:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Army Corps of Engineers wont grant easement for Dakota Access Pipeline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 07:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprisingly, Max Martin heard it and immediately said,"it's a start, but I'll make you famous!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're a "DJ" that plays songs with "dance steps", then you're actually an iPod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 07:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ministry of Silly Walks is about to be replaced by The Ministry of Absurd Bribes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 22:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the pet owner's extended scowl at the end as though *we* put the cat up to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on Reddit less than 3 weeks and I've now seen this clip on the front page twice.

I'm starting to understand why redditors get annoyed about repetitively seeing posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And since I haven't seen it mentioned, this incident also inspired the song "Hey Man, Nice Shot" by Filter.

No, that's not a poor-taste joke. This is true.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hey_Man_Nice_Shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slipknots' newest masks have way less of the "Americana rural discord" vibe and way more of  the "Big Bird and Mr. Snuffleupagus BDSM Nightmare" vibe.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving directions...to other people's homes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex-gf worked at a daycare in college as part of her education major.

One day when she announced it was nap time a little boy responded, "Oh good, cause shit I'm tired"

I will remember this story on my deathbed and laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG I don't know why but this reads like a scene out of classic Jim Carrey.

Tell me you can't hear Lloyd Christmas saying, "Thanks, but I already know what it tastes like."

(Not trying to rub it in but this is "other people paying to see you say it" funny) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story is the exact opposite of the old "Penthouse Forum." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I LOVE when I post something with an error in the title! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Jeffrey Dean Morgan audition for the role of Negan or did he just sent a copy of The Watchmen to AMC and they were like "That'll do nutbar, that'll do"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 01:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You better copyright that image now!

I feel like I'm looking at the loading screen of Grand Theft Auto 6. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confusion on elk's face: priceless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and that does nothing for the person looking for their keys. Maybe put them somewhere that someone will find them *instead of the bottom of a mailbox.*

By the time the keys arrive in the mail, the person who lost the keys will have either bought replacements or changed the locks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I guarantee you there's no problem. I guarantee it."

-Mario Mario, noted plumbing entrepreneur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually from a little piece called:

"Tim Burton's Dream Wedding: Concept Art" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither do I.  That link should just open (it did for me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dog's face says it all

"Really, you're going to let a 5 pound dog eat 3 pounds of cheesy tater tots? Okay...but I'm not cleaning up the mess." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF prompted that hilarious jump!? 

The action looked so contrived I expected the dog to pull out a piece of paper that said "Send Nudes"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's a penis joke in there somewhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the latest internet craze: replicating the Japanese school system! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Search For Video Game May Be Why Crashed Colombian Plane Didn't Refuel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And clearly that soldier was *running* because that's the same face my dog makes when she sticks her out the window of a moving car! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I'm following your comments.

Your second comment re: tax incentives and cheap labor, sounds like it is critical of the practice of globalization i.e. tax incentives to keep companies here are better than companies moving jobs overseas

Your third comment re: Companies playing states against each other, sounds like you are defending the practice of shipping jobs wherever a company gets the best deal. In this case it would be accomplished by exploiting the best state tax scenario (Most likely incentives).

If I'm understanding you correctly, then it sounds like you're okay with companies exploiting incentives to lower costs, but only under the condition whereby the company maintains its domestic presence.

This doesn't make sense to me because:

-Companies moving jobs between states still results in people losing jobs. National unemployment may not rise but people in State A still lose jobs people in State B.  This is very much an argument for the right of the company to do what it needs to operate

-However, your second point appears to state a company does not have the right to operate by taking jobs overseas i.e. there is a limit to which we will allow them to effectively manage their payroll and expenses.  This is an argument for the right of the worker i.e. the populist argument.

These two arguments are diametrically opposed as outlined above (again presuming I'm understanding you correctly).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just use this interactive sliding scale at Wall Street Journal.

All plain English results and breaks it down by race, etc

http://blogs.wsj.com/economics/2016/03/02/what-percent-are-you-2/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Gen. Jim Mattis, Trump chooses a warrior monk as secretary of defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What just happened with Carrier is crazy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm impressed you found indigo lights! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 06:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xanax plus alcohol is a HUGE no-no.

If your BF did not intentionally mix them, then there is nothing you should do. I have a friend who, sadly, has a Harry Potter style scar on his head for the rest of his life from mixing xanax and booze.  Why you ask? Because when he was blacked out he smashed his face against a concrete step outside his dorm in college. I copied something info from internet below (notice what's in bold)

Signs of concurrent alcohol and alprazolam abuse include:

Drowsiness

Slow pulse

Slurred speech

Slow breathing

**Memory problems**

Impaired coordination.

Dizziness.

Unsteady gait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 06:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liberal: Shrink the size of the federal government (and really all government).

There is *a lot* of fiscal waste in government!

(What should be cut is probably where me being liberal comes back into play!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little guy looks like he's in a sanitarium for anxiety disorder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive only been on Reddit two weeks lmao! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took Money Out of ATM Today and Received Sequential Bills. Apparently That's Actually Something That Can Happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple answer: Lobbyists and who they pay

Example: lets say tomorrow the US government learned that potatoes were the primary source of global warming.

Oregon and Idaho would flip their shit because of the number of potato farmers and the impact it could pose to their local Economies. Before the US could pass a law to regulate potatoes, Oregon and Idaho would hire lawyers and lobbyists to ensure the US government didn't screw with their potato farmers, processing factories etc. They'd probably also fund studies to show its not potatoes but those assholes in Kansas and their corn that's the problem.

Now replace Oregon and Idaho with Texas and handful of other states. And the "potato farmers" with Exxon (who has billions of $).

At its core global warming is a regulation of capitalism issue (not regulation of the environment.) The hallmark of capitalism is the "free market economy" which many misrepresent as "unfettered economy." 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the states keep making changes to the odds of winning.

Translation: Additional gimmicks, etc reduce the likelihood of winning. As such, jackpots grow larger and larger enticing more people to play.  More people play, more money is taxed on the eventual winnings.

The cost of the ticket never needs to increase because they are artificially deflating the value of your $ over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KPMG is low balling you because they know they can.

Think of it this way. There are 4 large accounting firms at this point and, if you hire one to audit you, etc, no one thinks twice because they are the gold standard.

Thus, you getting to put on your resume for a future role "I interned at a gold standard accounting firm" has additional value beyond your salary.

Further, sometimes you have to take a lower paying job to get to a better one later.

Don't think of it only as money in your pocket now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First question: where's the job?

JC, Salt Lake, APAC or other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a lot of options that aren't client facing depending on your firm.

Do you like options, then you can work your way towards a Series 4 - Options principal exam

Do you like compliance, then consider working towards the Series 14 NYSE compliance officer 

Maybe you want to be equity trader, it's client facing but not the same, then you can get a series 55 - equity trader license

There are A LOT of options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of it is driven by where you work in the company.

If you're an Ops person, then odds are on they'll let you work your two weeks.

If you're in a client facing role, or a role with inside information, then there is a high likelihood you will be immediately dismissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in financial technology. Tell me your interests and what you want to do, then I can answer you better.

Knee jerk reaction, 

CFA - waste of time if you don't want to be a portfolio manager or analyst
CPA - waste of time if you don't want to be an accountant
CFP - waste of time if you don't want to be a financial planner
CMT - waste of time if you don't want to be an equity trader

If your focus is truly tech, then all of the above will have limited application. Generally speaking, if you have any of the above, then you will make way more money using them *in their intended fields*. Otherwise, you're like Tim Tebow trying to be a baseball player.

IE You weren't good enough to get a job as a CFA analyst, so you took a job in financial tech.

Again, tell me what you want to do and I'll try to give you some suggestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in the industry and a lot of people that I interview for roles on my team look at my LinkedIn profile first (and I do the same re: the candidates.)

However, that won't help you much in the interview. You're better off learning about the company instead of the interviewer. Hiring managers want to see you appreciate who the firm is and that you want to be a part of it.

Did they create the first mutual funds?

Did they start off as a cotton trading commodity firm?

Were they founded by a Secretary of the Treasury?

All of those are real questions I learned the answers to by reading about the companies where I interviewed and/or worked.  Culture, values and fit are just as important as your resume.

Do your homework in regards to all of the above and you'll have a leg up on your competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "WTF is a Seven-of-Nine?! I just need a new roof for my garage!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No disagreement here! The jury is showering the guy with money (no fucked up pun intended) but no one's saying "uhhhh...WTF...you couldn't overpower an old man assaulting a child?"

(If anyone is, then I missed that news story) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The winning bidder immediately said they, "Did it for the lulz" and "Do you really think I have $90k you fuck-puppets?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...you're telling me wine snobs are full of shit?

You mean bouquets of douchebaggery and a hint of asshat aren't real?

Well there goes that Sommelier certification! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is DEFINITELY coming.  They don't charge that way *yet*

As cable TV falls behind streaming service and over the top solutions (like HBO GO), more and more of what's broadcast will be internet based.

The big thing to keep in mind is the age of industry.  Cable is having to adjust to what the market wants but they're slow to catch up (e.g. I live in Philly and can now get Netflix through my Comcast TV package as a standard offering; however, I've been steaming Comcast on their internet service for 6 years)

As that industry pivots from "cable" to "internet" there will be adjustments.  This change in billing will be one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have the same problem. When I went in for a minor surgery my doctor explained to me it's about metabolism and genetics.

Some people's bodies/organs are just more efficient at breaking down and evacuating drugs (of any type). As a result, the drug may not have the desired effect.  

This link is very science-y but it breaks it down further

http://www.merckmanuals.com/home/drugs/factors-affecting-response-to-drugs/genetic-makeup-and-response-to-drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Orders Penn State To Pay McQueary Another $5 Million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because when there isn't a lot of something (supply), everyone is competing for the same thing...which means you have to pay more to outbid the other people who want it.

Diamonds are the perfect real world example.

Diamonds are abundant on Earth; however, the sale of diamonds is controlled primarily by the DeBeers diamond cartel.

They intentionally restrict the supply of this *very* common rock to drive up the price. With everyone wanting a diamond engagement ring, and the number of diamonds intentionally limited by DeBeers, everyone has to pay more to get that diamond.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree with the previous poster, as someone who works in Banking/Finance/Investments I can tell you the real reason is:

Checks bounce.  Bounced checks have huge fees which means money for banks (they were $25 to $50 almost 20 years ago!)

Electronic transfers remove the potential for bounced checks I.e. Banks lose the revenue from bounced check fees

To offset the loss of revenue, they charge an upfront fee for electronic transfers.

This same thing happened with overdraft fees a few years back. Checking accounts were free but overdrafts incurred huge fees.  When banks could no longer charge them without customers opting in, free checking evaporated overnight I.e. They charge a fee for those accounts now to make up for lost revenue from overdraft fees.

If this were called explain like I'm 50:

The hardware costs cited above are ultimately capitalized and depreciated by any financial institution as that's an asset to the company. So while yes that is also a motivating factor for the fee, IRS accounting rules offset the initial investment to build all infrastructure and applications required to process the electronic transfers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Says Pot Should Be Treated Like Cigarettes And Booze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's *just* like a German shepherd.

Mine is almost 5 and still lets me lift her like a puppy despite the fact she's a 95 pound beast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cow looks like an ewok!

NO ONE TELL DISNEY OR GEORGE LUCAS!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fjrst time?

I'll keep this in mind the next time I send flowers to a smoking hot Norwegian girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which of these things is not like the others?

Hint: It's the guy in plaid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute, Trump's election prompted this?

Not China or Russia or any of the myriad countries in the Middle East that crackdown on citizen usage of the internet.

This is the internet equivalent of "Not In My Backyard."  Remind again why The west suddenly gives a shit about internet censorship when it's been happening around the world for years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand this is technically dedicated to Scientology, but if I can ask a fun question, how awesome was it filming Salute Your Shorts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lactic acid being released into your blood.

When you run you deplete oxygen levels in blood.

When oxygen levels are normal, your body breaks carbs into water and CO2.

When oxygen levels are low, lactic acid is released as well. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two reasons:

Reason 1:
White rice is milled and polished (i.e. processed and refined). These two steps both make it white and remove nutrients

Reason 2:
As a result, white rice also becomes a short chain carbohydrate (sugar) whereas brown rice is a long chain carbohydrate. 

Long chain carbs (often called "good carbs") take longer for the body to break down and use as energy i.e. after you eat them you are not fuller, long.

Short chain carbs (often called "bad carbs"), are broken down more quickly i.e. you are hungry again sooner

Tangential:
There are over 40,000 varieties of rice i.e. it's not quite as simple as people would have you believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holocaust-themed ice dance sparks outrage - CNN Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea's Park asks parliament to decide how she can quit, opposition cries foul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we all hate Tara Thornton after season 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King of Queens.

Kevin James might be the biggest benefactor of nepotism not given a kingship thanks to a royal bloodline.

Yes, Adam Sandler, this is your fault! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong advice.

Write every email as if they will be read to the public by a government regulator.

The CEO frequently has no clue WTF is going on (see: Wells Fargo). If you write an email like your mother, and the government, are going to read it, then you'll probably be more careful about what you say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, WTF!?!

We as a people need to come together and say, "Enough of this nonsense! I demand we return to a time when only 8 people understood a cartoon in the New Yorker and even they said it wasn't funny" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only In America Can You Take A Picture of Your Crime and Plead "Not Guilty": Playboy Playmate Pleads "Not Guilty" In Body Shaming Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one on every campus.

On mine it was a guy named Dana...he was awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who feels like she look like a Final Fantasy Boss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's telling you that you need an LIT...it knows...technology always knows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That joke is actually from a time when the "steel wheelchairs" tour was a play on their album title "steel wheels"

...not because any of us honestly thought Keith Richards would still be alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...to teach the man who threw it what an apostrophe is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the company that:

Marketed baby formula to new mothers in poor countries violating a World Health Organization marketing Code

Employed Child Slave labor to pick cacao

Hired a private security company to infiltrate an anti-globalization group

AND had the gall to sell us bottled water whose name is "naive" backwards

Comes...

oh whatever...

clearly no one gives a shit what these assholes do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hilarious if only because Australia can institute "Pay-for-performance" in prison, but in American we can't institute that for *teachers in schools*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Belichick destroyed Tim Tebow's NFL dream as only Bill Belichick could </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Informationisbeautiful.net


Dedicated to distilling the world's data, information and knowledge into beautiful, interesting and, above all, useful ..


http://www.informationisbeautiful.net

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ken Bone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story, short: The Commerce Clause

The Commerce Clause is a section of the US Constitution "which gives Congress the power to regulate commerce with foreign nations, and among the several states, and with the Indian tribes.

Civil Rights Changes were passed under this.

Essentially, discrimination in business interferes with capitalism and government regulation.

Since no one can theoretically lose money by not entering your home, the government doesn't care.

https://www.law.cornell.edu/wex/commerce_clause </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio State tweets that active shooter is on campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin aides wife sparks uproar with Holocaust-themed skating routine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 05:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome skills!

Thought it would be funny if he could **only** play a guitar that size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wash. Post and Snopes.com Discredit "3 Million Illegal Alien Votes" in 2016 Election as "Twitter Born Conspiracy Theory" and "Unproven" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great idea. Instead of:

Luxury Tax it can be "Waste Money Getting An MBA As You Have No Work Experience"

The Railroads Can Be Citibikes

Electric Company and Waterworks should just be replaced as bills you pay called "College Loans" and "Overpriced Fair Trade Coffee"

And all the properties on the cheapest section of the board should be various of level of awful.  

For example, Mediterranean and Baltic aves need to be "Your Parents' Basement" and "Your Parents' Attic"

Finally, Boardwalk should be "Your Own 1 Bedroom Apartment!!"

I'm liking this game! Someone make it happen!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's from contrails! CONTRAILS I TELL YOU!"

-Billy Corgan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snopes.com Dismisses "3 Million Illegal Alien Votes" in 2016 Election as Unproven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And even though I posted about the salad w/Fries, I definitely agree.

The problem is, I lived downtown and options were verrry limited (especially after the farm to table place closed) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
