<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 00:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I can't speak for people with physical disorders that affect how they look. I imagine that's harder to cope with. But still, your depression adds a layer to your appearance all the sake and you'd still look a lot better without it no matter what disorder you have. You'd still look better if you looked happy.

And yeah I know some people have big issues with how they look. I have them myself. Like I said I hate looking at pictures of myself. I hate looking in the mirror because it usually makes me feel worse. But perhaps confronting these issues in this way is an important step? How do you become comfortable with yourself if you won't look at yourself?

I think this is perfect for people who have self image issues personally. Makes you think you may not always have them and that it would make comparing the photos down the road more intense or something. I dunno, I think if you have a self image issue then seeing yourself look physically better would be worth a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 16:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sad as fuck man. No offense, because I used to do it too. But it didn't bring me much joy after a few times so I quit, and I felt shitty pathetic for doing it on reflection. People shouldn't have to do this to look forward to something, but sometimes it plays out that way and they do, and it bothers me I guess.

If you want, and I know it's kinda sketchy to do, you can give me an address or box to mail to and I'll send you regular packages. I have no idea where you live, so what I have to send you might all be stuff you find locally. But I imagine that would be funner than spending money and maybe it would be more interestijg to get some random shit instead of specific stuff? That's what got me when I tried it, I think, I knew what I was getting and I felt like it was too contrived, maybe? I dunno, but yeah, if you want I'll send you stuff that I think is cool or that I'd think you may think is cool for free. 

I'm tight on funds but I could do standard shipping once a week probably. Probably more or less depending on your preferences. I know this sounds silly but man I don't want you to have to buy stuff on Amazon to have something look forward to because it might just make you feel worse like it did me, and if I can help with that I would be really happy to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take a picture of yourself the next time you feel really down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 16:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today, I took a random photo of myself. I hate doing that, and I avoid photos at all cost usually. I was a kinda ugly person on a good day, but as you know deep lasting depression takes a toll on how you look because you just stop giving a fuck, which I have done years ago. So I'm a mess aesthetically and I'm usually ashamed when I see myself in photos. But all the same I snapped a picture in hopes it might be angled just right and everything that'd id look okay enough so I could upload it to Facebook since my profile picture I have now is a good 4 years old.

Anyway, I took it, and instantly knew I couldn't upload it. I, as usual, looked the opposite of any sense of the word attractive. I'd share it just so I don't have to explain it, but I'm embarrassed by it. But as I went to delete it I got a huge surge of inspiration from it.

Before I deleted it, I studied it and felt bad about what I've become and how far I've let not caring take me. Standard stuff, really. 

But then I thought this would be perfect for a success story. If I beat my depression and started living a more proper life, in a few years I could take a new happier photo and put it beside this one. When I make friends they will look at it and say "holy fuck that's you!?". I thought about how with a good recovery I could post the two photos side by side and I would bet with a good title and sub placement it would make the front page of Reddit. People will tell me I did a great job, and a few will tell me about their depression and say my photos ment something to them or inspired them. 

With this disgusting photo I have a chance to make a personal development and then quickly but still in a way thoroughly tell my success story in a way that will matter to people. And like I said, maybe inspire them. Maybe become something they regularly mentally reference and think "goddamn I want to do what that guy did." Isn't that a big deal? Wouldn't that be worth a lot of pride? Wouldn't something like that make you happy?

Probably not. The value I would get from seeing this photo next to a new and improved me won't be as intense as I'm imagining it, but that's because by the time I create it, I'm going to be used to happiness again. I'm not going to be desperate for it like I am now, I know. Instead I'll look at it and think "wow" too, and I'm going to be really proud of myself and take every compliment knowing I've earned it.

I know I'm rambling you all, but I'm fucking inspired. I'm motivated. This is something I haven't felt in YEARS. I've looked at hundreds of photos of myself in this state and never felt this. This is the first time that since I've developed my depression I feel like I can actually get past it and feel like I have a real reason to get past it. The satisfaction I'd get will make it worth the work. I've literally never felt that. I mean I have, but there was always self doubt alongside. A sort of "fuck yeah I can do this... Wait, no, look at yourself. It will take years if mental restructuring. I don't think I can actually do this" its hard to explain kinda but you know what I mean. But I'm confident on this one finally.

So I wanted to share my idea. Take a picture when you're feeling depressed. When you feel ashamed of what you are, save it. You're probably thinking "well I look okay", and you might. But even when you dress well depression takes a toll on your looks after a while. Happiness just shines physically. I can't put how into words, but it does. So save your sad photos and imagine looking at them down the road next to a picture of a happy you. Imagine all of the deserved compliments you'd get from people online and the friends you'll make along the way, and then imagine not even needing them because you're already happy. Imagine inspiring someone just like you to do the same thing.

It sounds cheesy as fuck, but I think if it motivates me it.might some of you too. But I think being able to compared these pictures will instill a deep sense of pride you might not be familiar with. It could feel like what it feels like when people see photos of themselves performing great big accomplishments. And I don't think it would ever get old either. So I really.suggest you try this and think about what it could be like. And even if you can't see yourself becoming better based on the idea of a future picture, save it anyway just in case you do beat your depression. It will be fun to compare it later, if nothing else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 10:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been doing (trying) this for quite a while. It feels like it just makes things worse, or at least less comfortable on my end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
