<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I see a picture of Macklemore... I don't know why this bothers me so much-- </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 08:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul's Boutique

One of the only true masterpiece albums of the rap/hip hop genre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 22:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to deliver food to a large Strip Club and a massage parlor where the girls flat-out told me they fucked for money.

Saw lots of boobies and pussies for free.

Never got laid. Not once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 08:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thought--look what happened to Ariana Richards.

Followed immediately by--

What the fuck happened to Laura Dern? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 00:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [STEELE JUSTICE!!!](http://movies.netflix.com/WiMovie/Steele_Justice/70146958?locale=en-US) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve McQueen and Ali MacGraw on GAY MARRIAGE and the BIBLE-- </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 22:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/AdviceAnimals... Is it just me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 21:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 21:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... Especially after you spend the cash on an inflated ticket price and then get raped at the snack bar... Why not sit there and actually enjoy what you paid for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We get it... The New Pope does everything with less pageantry than the Old Pope... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 21:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 20:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a bad idea... But I have a feeling that Risk Management would step in and say that the liability to the company should anything happen to these Theater Monitors is not worth being sued over.

It's unfortunate... But like all corporations they care more about making money than any other priority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have managed 4 different movies theaters... 22 screens, 10 screens, and two 6 screens--this would not work. It would kill my payroll and crush any hope of a P L bonus.

At both my 6 screens we very frequently operated on a skeleton crew of literally 3 people. 1 Box Office Cashier, 1 Connectionist/Usher and 1 Manager floating between all positions while also playing the role of Projectionist.

So normally I would be available in the box office to help sell tickets. We tear the tickets as we sell eliminating the need for an Usher at the door. Then I high-tail it across the lobby to the Concession stand where I help bag popcorn and pour sodas. Then I run upstairs somewhere near the correct time and start the projector (threading first if it's a film print and not digital). Then come back down and repeat the process until movies start getting out, at which point I have Box Office keep an eye ion things while me and the Connectionist go clean the theater for the next show.

Every corporate owned theater chain has similar staffing policies. They will expect you to operate with as minimal staff as possible. The 3-MAN Skeleton Crew system had already been established at the first 6 screen I took over and the District Manager flat-out told me that he wanted it to continue. When I moved to another 6 screen, I was asked to implement the same system there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 07:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [STEELE JUSTICE!!!](http://movies.netflix.com/WiMovie/Steele_Justice/70146958?locale=en-US) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 05:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be funny.

Everybody tells me I'm funny and it's always been that way and I've been aware of it the whole time. It's effortless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 05:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been no new news in over a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What in the hell happened to this movie??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 05:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 05:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes Google Image Search is the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I could literally spend hours looking at all of these beautiful images... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 05:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work!

I knew something was fishy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new hardest working man in Show-Biz? ERIC ROBERTS is slated to appear in 57 films in 2013--47 of which are already in post-production! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 22:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 20:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PEPPERONI CHIPS:

Place 3 paper towels on a paper plate (THIS IS ESSENTIAL).

Make a spiral of Hormel Pepperoni slices, slightly overlapping, until the entire plate is cover in pepperoni.

Microwave for 2 minutes.

The Pepperoni will crisp up and have a crunch just like a potato chip.

Eat with cheese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they were not "equally" fantastic.

Willy Wonka and the Chocolate factory is fucking awesome. Gene Wilder is unbeatable.

Charlie and the Chocolate is another Tim Burton phone-in. Depp is Depp.

Nothing equal there. Willy Wonka is much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlie Sheen -- Platoon:

"It's in the eyes, man!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobody Uses This Joystick [FIXED] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 15:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 05:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest... I'd have to say it's a toss up between Blade and Iron Man.

For those who can't remember... Blade was awesome. So awesome in fact that we can essentially thank it for ushering in the modern era of Marvel films. It performed well at the box office and made money on DVD. Plus it's Rated R. And unashamedly so. The blood and gore are awesome, the fights are sweet and Wesley Snipes and Stephen Dorff are at the tops of their games.

Iron Man is just pure fun. Period. Joy and action. They really got the casting right, and that--as much as anything--makes it great. The story isn't perfect--but the tone and the direction overcome the narrative flaws and make it irresistible. I rarely meet anybody who didn't enjoy it.

The Avengers would be a close 3rd--but I have a tendency to prefer individual vs team stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 16:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this magnificent collection of Celebrity Icons ends with a picture of...

BRET THE HITMAN HART??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 05:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rise of fucking Kim Kardashian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 21:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes. SHould I delete this post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIL WAYNE vs. GARY COLEMAN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 21:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 25 year old friend with the hand tattoos from Boondock Saints.

He still loves the movie (in fact I think he also like the sequel) but he says the thats are the worst mistake of his life.

He works in the "industry" in LA and gets fucked with all the time.

I just felt like sharing that story.

Note: I would prefer that you not kill any animals on my behalf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 21:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad... I clarified this in another comment somewhere in here... It's mostly LA movies that blatantly reference Hollywood people and the Industry.

In some cases, though, directors choose to use the city of LA like a character, and that sometimes bothers me as well.

Die Hard is not an LA movie. Collateral is. Does that make sense? Die Hard is also the greatest action film ever made (*fuck you, people who think Ghost Protocol is the best*)--so it's impossible to hate.

Pulp Fiction is about 50% jerk-offy... But it gets a pass because it's strengths definitely outweigh that particular annoyance. However--Jackie Brown does not get a pass. Does that makes sense?

Similarly, Bogie Nights gets a pass... But 2 Days in the Valley does not. I realize this is insanely subjective--I'm just trying to clarify my opinion. It's a fine line in my mind between good and suck.

LA Confidential is totally an LA movie... But because of the historical setting, and (like Pulp Fiction and Boogie Nights) the overall awesomeness of the film, I give it a pass. Gangster Squad on the other hand is a failure.

Finally Mulholland Drive... An LA movie for sure, BUT--made by David Lynch. Love him or hate him, it's going to be a mind-scrambler. Although I personally do not like Mulholland Drive, it's not because of the LA thing. I do hate Justin Theroux as well, but I can tolerate him in this. The truth is, if I ever direct a hollywood feature, I will blatantly steal 2 shots from Mulholland Drive and brag about my theft.

To encapsulate how I feel I can sum it up by mentioning the  most offensive LA Jerk-Off of all time... A little TV show you may have heard of called Entourage. A show where everything always works out for everybody and we get to see how things "really work" in the city of angels. Where people without real jobs never worry about money or relationships, and where life is better than anyplace else in the world. Fuck off, Hollywood. Suck your own dick in private like I do.

The "Industry" already has enough self-gratification throughout the year... And every award season they get to gather in groups and circle-jerk each other off. I would prefer it if they limited their jerking to off-screen. It's kind of like when Puff Daddy used to say "Bad Boy" in the background of every Notorious BIG song... It's like--just produce the record and stay the fuck off the track, bitch. That's how I feel whenever I smell insider LA material in a film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 14:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insane Clown Posse does not count as "eye candy".

^ See what I did? I intentionally misread what you wrote so I could drop another diss on ICP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 14:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't mad... But I always come off that way. Dammit.

Sorry, everybody... My passionate hatred of Boondock Saints has gotten the better of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 14:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A whole goat??

Now I feel like a bully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 03:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking kidding me?

You're either young (25 or under) or don't know very many people.

Take a second to think about what you just said... EVERY SINGLE PERSON you've ever met enjoys Boondock Saints on occasion. You don't even know ONE PERSON who doesn't like it.

Sounds legit.

P.S. You can clearly see, based on my original Juggalo comment that it's 50/50 just here in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, reddit.

It's 10 UpVotes to 11 DownVotes... Don't let the Juggalos win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 20:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know... I liked Drive a lot--but I didn't love it. And to me it wasn't as guilty of being an LA stroke-fest. What I really wanted was to surgically excise Albert Brooks from the film completely and then add one more car chase in the 3rd act.

I should really expand that comment to include anything that references the industry. There's nothing worse than a movie about a struggling screenwriter--as an example. No, I didn't particularly like Adaptation, even though it wasn't a bad film.

I'll give you a harder to spot example that drove me nuts... Inglourious Basterds... The Nazi Officer is talking to the Blonde Jewish girls while she hangs letters on the theater marquee and she says something like "I'm French... Here in France we respect our Directors"--it's almost as if Quentin Tarantino should have just stepped into frame and delivered that line himself.

I guess I just hate how Hollywood loves to pat itself on the back and suck it's own cock as if anything they do is important.

Worst LA movie of all time... LA Story. Fuck that movie.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 19:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Moonrise Kingdom--but not because of Murray.

And it doesn't surprise me that you got downvotes.

Forgot about Mad Dog   Glory. I always viewed that movie like a wasted opportunity or dropped ball. So much potential with so little delivery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 16:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray is at his best when he's part of an ensemble cast--Ghostbusters and Rushmore being good examples.

As a "star" or "leading Man" the only 2 films I like of his are Groundhog Day and Scrooged (although Scrooged has a dumb ending). I would rather be water-boarded than have to watch What About Bob? or Lost In Translation again.

I 100% agree that his reputation is overrated. And I think it has a lot to do with his persona outside acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 16:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an upvote.

We were just talking about [this very subject](http://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/1aecd5/on_january_21st_1982_a_screening_of_blade_runner/c8wpbp2) the other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 16:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before and I'll say it again... If you like Boondock Saints, there is a 80% chance that you're a [Juggalo](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Juggalo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 16:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I have finally found people who understand me here on /r/movies.

I've posted very similar sentiments in the past regarding Big Lebowski and have received a lot of support.

I won't say that it sucks--in fact, John Tutoro makes me laugh out loud... But the rest of the movie is like a big inside joke jerk off about LA. And I hate LA movies.

In fact, I just moved away from Los Angeles and I hate them even more.

The Coen Brothers have directed some of my favorite films of all time, but The Big Lebowski is not one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 15:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck does my "UPVOTE!!!" get 6 downvotes??

Fuck you, reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 02:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPVOTE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 00:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of Shawn Wunjo... But he looks like somebody who didn't get enough attention as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that about the existence of two books that sound fake but are 100% real... "The Vagina Ass of Lucifer Niggerbastard" and "Robocunt and the Rug Niggers of Afrofaggotstan" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 00:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 20:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FALSE!

2001 is the greatest film of all time!!!!!!!

Okay... It's my favorite film but I can't defend it on this topic. That's why I've never been super-critical of Blade Runner... I know what it's like to love a film other people consider boring.

P.S. 2001 is more beautiful : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 20:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh... VHS.

I don't even miss it for the nostalgia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now see... I remember Sledge Hammer. In fact, I own the complete series on DVD and have yet to revisit it.

But if The Charming ran opposite The Cosby Show, then it makes total sense that I can't remember it. I never missed The Cosby Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a troll or a hater. I like it. I just don't love it. But it's a breathtaking film to look at for sure.

I have actually seen it many times as a "grown up". I did Blu-ray QC for many years, and I was the project manager for the 5-disc Complete Collector's Edition Blade Runner release (with 5 versions of the film).

After watching each version multiple times (including the fucking work print) I came to the conclusion that my personal favorite version would be an as-yet-to-be-created Fan Edit using the newest "Final Cut" version (2007) but mixing in Dekkard's voiceover from the International Cut (1982).

I admit it. I like the voiceover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 14:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blade Runner is a good movie, but it's not great.

They are 100% correct that it is dull before Zohra's death. And it doesn't get much better afterward.

It's one of the best looking, boring films of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 07:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was alive. I was a watcher of television. I have a great memory.

I can not remember ever seeing or hearing of this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 06:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More:

[Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Charmings)

[Cast Photo](http://images.tvrage.com/shows/6/5679.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1987 there was a TV show on ABC call THE CHARMINGS that chronicled the life of Snow White and Prince Charming after they wake up in the Los Angeles suburbs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 06:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 15:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one that sticks out most recently--which made me actually "What the fuck??" out loud in the  middle of a packed theater was in A GOOD DAY TO DIE HARD when Br Swillis hangs and swings from a spinning/crashing helicopter and times letting go so perfectly that it flings him into a nearby building through a window.

He walks away from this without injury.

Still better than Die Hard Part 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 15:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the classics have already been mentioned, so I will drop a very memorable bad-guy quote from a mostly forgettable movie, THE MECHANIC remake with Jason Statham. Tony Goldwyn is the bad guy and is given the best line of the entire film--

"I'm going to put a price on your head so big, that when you look in the mirror your reflection's gonna want to shoot you in the face." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 03:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckin [JOHN CENA](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_K6TcATg_aw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 17:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Upvote.

What a huge letdown.

I still fantasize about a day when all the people involved with be desperate enough for money that they make a movie or mini-series to tie up all those loose ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 17:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [STEELE JUSTICE!!!!!!!!!](https://movies.netflix.com/WiMovie/Steele_Justice/70146958?locale=en-US) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 16:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird Science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 2008, DMX and KRIS KRISTOFFERSON starred in a movie together called LORDS OF THE STREET. WTF?? That's the most awkward coupling since Bruce Wayne and Rachel Dawes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 06:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 04:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an /r/MagicSpells subreddit?

If so, can we come up with an incantation to expedite the death of Bieber's career? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 23:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TEXAS would be that loud-mouth Fat Kid that everybody either loves or hates, while ALASKA would actually be the Fattest Kid in School that nobody even talks to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seen on CRAIGSLIST today... Jesus, AUSTIN, what decade are we living in?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 21:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 21:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit--triplets! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 21:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck happened to [Val Kilmer](http://blog.newsok.com/nerdage/files/2009/06/val-kilmer-bw.jpg)??

Is he trying to compete with Marlon Brando or Michael Jackson for worst image transformation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy Crystal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 22:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 00:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 15:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 15:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A thirty-something Filipino MILF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I get into a crowded Elevator with a friend, there is a 90% chance I will drop my keys and make a fart noise when I pick them up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 15:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be crazy. Cheese is awesome.

And you can develop a palette for it like Scotch or Wine.

Start with something like String Cheese (which is just Mozzarella).

Experiment with mild cheeses like Emmental, Leicester, Cream Havarti, etc.

Make a move to Medium (semi-hard) cheeses like Swiss, Colby, Monterey Jack, Gouda, Provelone and Cheddar.

Cheddar is your gateway cheese into the harder stuff.

Work your way up to a nice Sharp Cheddar. Then take the leap to aged Cheddar. If you can eat a 5 year aged Sharp Cheddar, you should be able to tolerate numerous other "strong" cheeses.

Before long, you'll be snobbing it up at Wine   Cheese parties, noshing on Brie, Camembert, Stilton, Limburger and Roquefort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of my 80's Crushes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 05:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 01:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul's Boutique - Beastie Boys

Steady Diet of Nothing - Fugazi

IV - Led Zeppelin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 17:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bozo the Clown Show.

I lived in Chicago as a little kid. Other people my age didn't get to watch Bozo and Cookie and the Grand Prize Game.

WGN eventually became a part of basic cable in many states, so oddly enough, people younger than me who grew up outside of Chicago sometimes remember Bozo.

Sidebar: That was also back when/where the number for Empire Carpet was 588-2300 and not 800-588-2300 (which is now called Empire Flooring). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 15:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOW!

That's what you get for being Black in Indiana.

I NEVER had anybody arrested, and I had off-duty cops in my theater every Friday Saturday. Sure, we fucked with many people and scared the shit out of them, but never actually arrested. That's crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 15:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ORIGINAL POST](http://i.imgur.com/DMZ6t.jpg?repost=yes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm not usually one for FB posts, but wow. Just wow." [ILLUSTRATED] - Friendly Reminder Courtney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 15:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MOVIE THEATER Managers and Employees... What are some of the most funny/crazy stories you remember? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 14:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Managed a 22 screen Movie Theater for the better part of a decade.

My favorite story is the time one of my Ushers called me to report some theater "hoppers". I go down to investigate and it turns out to be 2 guys in those Olympic Racing Wheelchairs. Their arms were freaking bulging with muscle even though their little legs had atrophied. I clearly see them roll out of one auditorium and just wheel on over to another.

I shout "Hey!"

Without a second of hesitation one of them screams "GO GO GO!" and they blaze down the hall and smash out of the back exit. I didn't even bother chasing them. I was too impressed. I just turned to my Usher and said--

"Let 'em go. They earned it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 06:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ORIGINAL POST](http://i.imgur.com/c5al9RO.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Nope, no bigots here." [Illustrated] -- Common Sense Pee Wee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 06:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After reading about the IKEA Horse-Meatball scandal... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 05:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 04:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ORIGINAL POST](http://i.imgur.com/kIVAb9u.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Footprints in the Sand" [Illustrated] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 04:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 01:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Z Cavaricci Pants](http://i119.photobucket.com/albums/o135/diabloDM/Old%20School%20Stuff/DSCN1483.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 02:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original Post = [THIS](http://i.imgur.com/Hqqa8Ax.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Didn't I just save you?" [ILLUSTRATED] - Good Guy Atheist  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 02:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 22:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Wedge is so darn thin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 16:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No question...

[BLAKE](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_vvAhyR-6PAM/TIJXyHNP7DI/AAAAAAAAF0M/3Beexmxv43c/s1600/Blake-glengarry-glen-ross.jpg) (Alec Baldwin's character) from **Glengarry Glen Ross** - He goes on a motivational speaking tour and ends up coaching a rag-tag group of college nerds in the rough-and-tumble game of getting laid.

Close second...

[PORKINS!](http://27.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lko4qwonVy1qag1uwo1_500.jpg) from **Star Wars (Ep IV)** - Basically, he wakes up on a floating chunk of the destroyed Death Star and has to use his wits, cunning and insatiable appetite for anything edible to make his way through the ruthless galaxy and get home to his cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 06:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a second--Scar's not Jewish??

Well, that changes everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 05:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kings of the fucking Universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 04:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scar was gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 02:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Simba's not the only catty one in this thread. Meow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Gay bros can raise babies" [ILLUSTRATED] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 01:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See... Now I really enjoy In the Mouth of Madness. To me it succeeds it keeping you frightened after the movie ends--the mark of a great horror film.

Event Horizon just doesn't do it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never used the word forgettable.

Also... We all know Laurence Fishburne's greatest fear was to get fat and fade into irrelevance--which has sadly come to pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like my Sci-Fi better without God.

Just a personal choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Really? I've never been described that way before... But re-reading my post--I can see how you would think that. It does come off a little douchey.

My knee-jerk reaction would have been to post: "*Event Horizon?? That movie sucks. You guys are silly.*"

Somehow, I don't think you would have like that any better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 04:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. If Sunshine had a better third act it would be one of the all time greatest sci-fi films ever.

As it is, it's highly dismissible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 04:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear I'm not trolling or commenting just to be contrary... But every single comment in here is praising this film and I just have to say--I think it's awful.

The director (Paul W.S. Anderson) is a complete hack who is only responsible for one entertaining and watchable film--Soldier (notice I didn't say it was a good film).

Event Horizon is a great example of Horror films that began appearing in the late 80's and early 90's that focused more on momentarily shocking the audience with a FLASH on screen and a STING on the soundtrack. It's not like The Shining or The Exorcist where you return from the theater and walk into your dark house afraid of what might be there. You leave Event Horizon and forget about 99% of it.

The story is so puerile in its imbecilic cosmology that it ends up shackled by it's vague concepts and half-assed pseudo-science. It's as if he pitched the studio on a 50/50 mix of Alien and Hellraiser and tossed in some Black Hole mumbo jumbo without even bothering to do some Wikipedia research. 

As far as the execution, it didn't look awful--but the neither did Alien Vs. Predator or The Three Musketeers. In fact all of his films have a flashy gloss about them, but they all suck. He's like a less talented/successful version of Michael Bay. With Event Horizon he utterly failed to deliver anything close to original or frightening.

I can understand being frightened by this movie when you were young, but try it again as an adult and I think the cracks will show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 03:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dooooooork </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
