<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do you have a source for the medical properties being lost after burning marijuana? Not questioning it, I'm genuinely curious and have a friend I'd like to send that info to.

I have a list of articles on my home computer. I'm at work at the moment, but here's one i remember:

https://mic.com/articles/76853/the-science-of-smoking-weed-how-marijuana-affects-your-molecules#.QSGUJp7Dx

Best part if the linked article:

Sorry to break it to you, but you do sound dumb when youre high  and that's because you have temporary brain damage. See, there are also CB1 receptors in your hippocampus, the area of the brain that processes short-term memory and spatial navigation. Because you're over-stimulating this portion of the brain when you smoke pot, your neurons cant function well and actually resemble brain damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it.  We use "OIS" for Officer Involved Shooting.  I was a bit confused.  Operational Stress Injuries is a great term that doesn't have any connotations associated with it I can think of.

Unfortunately, there are still an overwhelming number of people and agencies who think PTSD isn't a real thing, and only something "lazy people" pretend to have because they no longer want to work, or were never strong enough to do the job in the first place.  Both of which are horribly, tragically, incorrect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pot isn't a narcotic, but it listed on the federal Schedule 1 drug list.  Marijuana itself has a lot of useful medicinal properties.  However, almost all of those medicinal properties are lost when marijuana is heated up to it's burning point.

Burning marijuana actually activates most of it's psychotropic properties.  This, coupled with the fact, most indoor grown "medicinal" marijuana has been selectively bred/engineered to be more psychotropic than the marijuana used by humans throughout history.

Many people throughout history who have used marijuana for medicinal purposes, or even religious/ceremonial ones, ingested marijuana by eating it (without cooking it), or brewed as a tea.  This ingestion method highlights the medicinal properties of marijuana, while minimizing the psychotropic properties of it.

If anyone is confused as to what "psychotropic" medications are, what they're used for, or why this is a big problem for "recreational" use, answer this:

Would you use any of the following in a recreational way:
Adderall, Abilify, Ambien, Buspar, Benzodiazepines, Cymbalta, Haldol, Klonopin, Paxil, Prozac, Lithium, Seroquel, etc.

I'm not saying people don't use these in a recreational way, but they're controlled because they are all highly addictive and seriously alter brain chemistry.  If anyone thinks marijuana isn't addictive, I would love to speak with you and see if I can change your mind.

Just remember, there's a difference between "addiction" and "dependence."  Opiate narcotics, for example, create a physiological dependence, meaning there are physical withdrawal symptoms associated with their use/abuse.  Alcohol also creates physical dependence.

Many other drugs hijack the brain's dopamine/pleasure/reward system, which creates an addiction, but don't have the same "dependence" problems.  Marijuana certainly is no different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the tax has been nice.

How has crime been as a result?  Have any crimes gone down?  What about up?  Traffic accidents related to marijuana use?  What about homelessness?  Has there been an increase of transients in the cities where dispensaries are located?  What about calls related to people with mental health issues?

I'm sure the tax increase is nice, but I would imagine all the other bullshit increased as well.  Gotta say, I do like the username though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comments/replies that video are awesome.  Great reminder that as a law enforcement officer, no matter what you do, you're wrong and people hate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   job related OSIs

What are OSIs?  We still have a lot of work to do to address/prevent suicide from happening in the first place.  This is a huge step toward breaking down the stigma of stress/mental health concerns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also point out the fact in the same address, George Washington also wrote:

The great rule of conduct for us, in regard to foreign nations, is, in extending our commercial relations, to have with them as little political connexion as possible. So far as we have already formed engagements, let them be fulfilled with perfect good faith. Here let us stop.

Again, not limiting our own military size/power... But stating, as Washington did over 200 years ago, we shouldn't be getting involved in "nation building," or overgrown military establishments in other countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My head isn't buried in the sand at all.  I'm well aware of the threats out there.  Some are real, some are not.  I'm also not saying we shouldn't have a strong military, or even the strongest in the world.  But I do believe our military should not be used as the world police.  

Sometimes allowing smaller countries to have civil wars without anyone else interceding isn't the worst option.  When the US constantly intervenes in foreign politics, and commits US troops for prolonged periods of time, we either do not have enough military personnel for other matters that may need to be addressed, or we enlist new people, and increase/bloat the size of the military.  This costs money, a whole lot of it.  Sometimes that money could be better spent elsewhere, like in the US, instead of pouring it into foreign territories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: George Washington warned: Avoid the necessity of those overgrown military establishments, which, under any form of government, are inauspicious to liberty, and which are to be regarded as particularly hostile to republican liberty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Or they were sharing another meme that's "never too soon." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too often we judge other groups by their worst examples, while judging ourselves by our best intentions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This quote, "Too often we judge other groups by their worst examples, while judging ourselves by our best intentions." was said by former President George W. Bush at the interfaith memorial service for the five Dallas Police officers who were shot and killed in 2016.

http://www.wfaa.com/news/local/dallas-ambush/read-full-transcript-of-former-president-bushs-speech-at-memorial-service/270770750 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you left out the part where you puked.  Mine would have been right after the burpees.  Like all of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://imgur.com/6lnquf5

Maybe some exterior/fender repair as well... and new windows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wonder why he waited until he was found not guitty on the 2nd murder case. Still funny tho

You're assuming he did himself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry.  Can't work my phone this morning.   This was in /r/Advice animals

http://imgur.com/a/SRPG6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm gonna slow down just in case... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  One of this days I'm going to hit the concrete base of a pole and get written up.

I did that.  The concrete pillar was painted day-glow safety green.  Scraped against it at about 2mph.  Supervisors didn't find it as funny as I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few of the people I've worked with over the last few years wore clear plastic Oakley glasses w/ black frames.  The lenses were anti-glare for better visibility while driving at night.  The other bonus was eye protection since we have a lot of people who like spitting in our faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  More like "This seat is Taken"

Co-starring Forrest Gump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, do you wear any glasses at night (either prescription, or clear) for anti-glare purposes?  I've been hearing more and more people recommend them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a movie about the U2 spy plane incident... It's called Bridge of Spies, staring Tom Hanks.  Actually decent movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  $25 Casio from target, $10 sunglasses from Kohls

I wear cheap shit at work too due to my history of losing or breaking stuff.  But since I moved to swings from graves, I really suggest shelling out extra money for polarized glasses.  They're well worth it, and allow me to see people in cars better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What a nightmare. Thank goodness it's over.

Unfortunately, it's not over.  There's still a lot of legal bullshit to go through.  The family of Stephens may likely sue various law enforcement agencies in multiple states for multiple things, including alleging they shot him in cold blood and disputing the statement he shot himself.

Also, the families of victims are likely to launch lawsuits against various government/law enforcement agencies for failing to protect them or keep Stephens locked up/in a mental hospital instead of allowing him to be on the street.

I wish it was over, but for some, it's only just beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing screams/seeing something that requires immediate action would be considered an exigent circumstance, both for policy and any 4th amendment violations.  As long as the officers acted reasonably based on the facts known at the time, they're covered for any real or perceived law or policy violations.

If you hear screaming, or see people suffering physical harm, and sit there waiting for backup, you'll likely be forever branded a coward, and will have a hard time keeping your job.

That being said, working in a jail/prison/custodial setting is different.  If inmates/convicts are fighting each other, no one will think badly if the officer waits for cover.  It's been proven time and again many "fights" are diversions or intended to set up ambushes of officers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
