<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6966</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Al-Hamza Division (VSO) celebrating inside Jarabulus, turkish-syrian border. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 00:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 19:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those martyrs die after YPG decided to attack Manbij, which is in line with their own interests, despite announcing a campaign to liberate Raqqa. YPG didn't attack Manbij as a favor to the US, but because they need the town to connect the cantons. And the USAF backed them anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 19:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why should the YPG fight the wars of the US anymore?

Why should the US fight the wars of the YPG anymore? Their air support and failed regime change in Syria caused YPG to grow that strong in the first place. What reason has the US for cleaning up their mess if the YPG doesn't grant them political cooperation with Turkey? 

This a partnership: the YPG will have to give something in return for what has received. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Forces of Martyr Ahmed al-Abdo repelling Daesh assault in Eastern Qalamoun. Claims of 1 SVBIED   5 vehicles destroyed, 2 captured   32 militants killed. 2 rebels killed   4 wounded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US doesn't go along with one demand by the YPG = **KURDS HAVE BEEN BETRAYED - NO MORE FRIENDS THAT THE MOUNTAINS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why everytime that the US impose a condition over the YPG or doesn't fully back all of their demands this sub starts to moan about "how the Kurds have been betrayed"? Where is the nuance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JFaS drone footage of government armored units under precise mortar fire inside Technical College in Ramouseh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... findings of the OPCWs Declaration Assessment Team report  which is marked *highly protected*

 In a *confidential* two-page summary of the report ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First footage of the Turkish-led operation in Jarablus against ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  OPCW Director-General Ahmet Uzumcu writes that the majority of 122 samples taken at multiple locations in Syria indicate potentially undeclared chemical weapons-related activities. Many of Syrias explanations for the presence of undeclared agents, he added, are not scientifically or technically plausible"

The US is just echoing what the OPCW itself is claiming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How do you know they've lied? Because USA accused them so?

Again, is the OPCW itself making the accusations in Syria, not the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The city itself will probably be "liberated", but I have my doubts if the FSA can manage to take also the southern countryside without bolstering their numbers first, because there are very slim probabilities that the TSK will keep pushing inside Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So, how does it make sense, that while you surely still have chemical weapons, accuse other country, "they may" still have chemical weapons?

Maybe because Syria explicitly agreed to destroy those weapons and then lied about it and because the ones making the accusations are not the US   Russia, but the OPCW? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A FSA recruiter in Turkey is calling for young men to come to Karakamis to join Jarablus operation. Said arms/vehicles will be supplied. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 19:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Zenki said that they were ready to open a corridor if YPG wanted, not that they actually opened one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another attempt to smuggle weapons   ammunitions from Azaz to supply ISIS was stopped by security of FSA Liwa Jund al-Islam. The weapons were being hidden inside oil transport trucks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 19:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be precisely a non-IS emirate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fastaqem Union: drone footage of failed push by government forces in vicinity of Air Force Technical College in Ramouseh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report of russian TV in southern Aleppo. Shows drone footage of rebel supply convoys being targeted while crossing through Ramouseh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure that he was not the one who filmed the beheading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Didn't we see some of these guys riding into battle with JFS

I think that we have never seen that actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A kurdish and PKK friendly independent state is no buffer, but an open invitation to invade for Turkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did produce the previous shelling of Turkey in Afrin a high toll of civilian casualties? I might be wrong, but the impression left is that turkish shelling seems more like a threat that actual collective punishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooperating how? They tested AaS political will once, and after that I do not know of any kind of action that can pass as "cooperation". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian Ambassador Jaafari: French intelligence conducted the chemical weapons attack in Eastern Gouta 3 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never seen the US working under that assumption. If its just for communication the US will probably leave the channels open (they have channels with the Taliban and Hamas), but they have never cooperated with Ahrar, and probably never will if this merge comes to fruition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Claims that MIT (Turkish intelligence) visited Damascus recently </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont  understand why Zenki, who has clashed with Nusra in the past and was still trying to get Coalition support again is the one merging with the hardliners instead of Faylaq al-Sham, an actual member of Jaysh al-Fatah. Can we be sure that those are the actual names of the new super-faction and that is not just someone's speculation based in the beheading incident? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the US would be openly cooperating and talking with Al Qaeda as they have open communication channels with Ahrar Al Sham

I doubt it. Those channels will probably be closed from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bombed back into the Stone Age: North Hama residents pay to live underground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an encircled Damascus suburb, rebels take aim at regime checkpoint as civilians pay the price. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 14 Hezbollah fighters have been killed in Syria over the past two weeks, according to Iranian media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jordan vows to let Syrian refugee kids into school even if parents lack proper papers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be deploying that kind of hardware without at least a camouflage net. With the RuAF in the skies one should be more worried of losing this valuable artillery piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The jihadists have already pasted their peak and they're not going to come out of this war.

I dont want to sound "salty" too, but this has been said one thousand times in this war and at least a dozen of times just before the rebels captured Ramouseh and the Artillery Base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exiled local council of Jarabulus, in turkish-syrian border, calls FSA factions to expel ISIS from the town. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The photographer knows some of the kidnappers of the beheaded kid (or at least took a selfie with them), but he didnt participate in the beheading. This was already discussed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The loss of his children's lives are bad but ultimately the father holds some degree of responsibility just as Russia does for carrying out the strike.

The level of responsability here still leans heavily towards the RuAF. The activist take a risky action because feels compelled to do so for ethical reasons; the RuAF mainly acts because is instrumental to achieving certain political and military goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/SyrianCirclejerkWar is leaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popular demonstration demanding JFaS exit of al-Qaboun neighborhood, Damascus, which is a under a truce agreement with the regime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My arabic is shit, but for what I understand the people is claiming for the return of the stolen weapons by Nusra, as the do everyday, and the Div. 13 commander is announcing that the issue will be solved soon; nothing about a dissolution. A proper translation will be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol - "HEZBOLLAH AXIS - Romantic Relaxing Music 4" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have manpower to do much else really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Fastaqem Union shooting Fagot against 2 groups of regime soldiers in South Aleppo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would fly through the Mediterranean, seek refuge in Germany and then join the refugee Olympic team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like bad fanfiction inspired by the treaty of Svres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tour inside recently liberated al-Rai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Other" in French </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here http://wikimapia.org/#lang=es lat=36.511124 lon=40.738048 z=19 m=b search=syria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurdish Asayish clashing with regime forces around "Assyrian Church of the East" in Hasaka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SOHR: 13 casualties at least in regimes shelling and the targeting exchange in Hasakah city </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 01:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are different levels of mishandling. Hillary Clinton committed mistakes that just would have merited administrative sanctions, not criminal charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 00:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My uneducated view

That is the problem. She wasn't safe from the law thanks to money and power, but because she never broke the law to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then you dont have proof that they are Nusra, just your baseless conjectures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria 'is being swallowed whole by its clients': Assad may be losing control over his own militias </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely because is a country of laws is that she is not in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any source on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Families in Asayish-controlled neighborhoods start to flee to the countryside due to artillery shelling and bombing raids by the government in Hasaka. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is growing too fast, we need to take measures to keep r/worldnews backed jihadists out of the sub, like more ~~active moderation~~ repressive mukhabarat and more ~~nuked~~ "barrel bombed" threads.

About the lack of women, I suspect that is due to the emphasis that we put on combat related news, not something that really interest women. I believe too that people start to get into geopolitics when they are older, and as such a respectable portion of our young western male user base just come here to see combat footage and reenact war tourism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq: Cleric's Call Against Anti-LGBT Violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 06:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The worst place on earth': inside Assad's brutal Saydnaya prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Common ATGMs in the Syrian Civil War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Around 20 deaths and 30 wounded after four bombing raids over the city of Idlib today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relative calm in the streets of Hasakah since this morning after yesterday clashes between pro-government NDF and pro-YPG Asayish. Both parties agreed to implement truce to retrieve the deads and treat wounded civilians and militants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only objection that it comes to mind would be that Qatar wants these factions to join JaF, while the US will prefer them to unified between themselves or stay separated. Turkey might be worried of losing leverage and manoeuvre space with the turkmen groups that manipulates against the YPG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merger talks in North Western Aleppo between FSA Mujahideen Army, FSA Levant Front, FSA Fastaqim Union, and FSA 1st Regiment face foreign objections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [article](http://www.enabbaladi.net/archives/98276) claims that Brigadier General "Deeb Bazzi", Director of the Technical Air School, was probably killed in this attack. That could explain why they targeted the BMP instead of the soldiers, knowing that the officers usually will be next to the armored vehicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the shells used by ISIS to launch chemicals attacks in northern Aleppo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems that armored assets are more important than normal infantry, as in combat will be more difficult to find extra armored vehicles than extra infantry reinforcements. Or at least the rebels judge it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authenticity   Development Front on the why of the rupture with the US-backed NSyA - [Translation needed] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst threat to Assad's rule is not the rebels, ISIS or foreign intervention, but the client network itself that was used to enforce such rule. If the economy collapses before the war ends, the local warlords will cannibalize what is left of the State, and with it any capacity of centralized action. After 5 years, the trend seems to be a regime that is devolving into factionalism, while the rebels learn to converge in large coalitions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like that [silly sword](http://staticmass.net/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/dvd_conan.jpg) of Arnold Schwarzenegger in "Conan The Barbarian". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS launches toxic substances through artillery shells in the the town of Maree, northern Aleppo countryside, causing casualties among civilians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Local Council of Al-Bab", exiled in the FSA-held city of Azaz, rejects legitimity of SDF-sponsored "Al-Bab Military Council". Denounces SDF rejection of revolutionary principles and of "discrimination   displacement" of arab and turkmen population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 06:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I edited it as "YPG", but the original tweet just says "Kurdish Self-Management forces". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YPG forces arrested 14 civilians for conscription in Efrin, Aleppo   taken them to unknown destination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 06:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dying for Assad; Liwa Fatemiyoun (May-August 2016) - Article in french </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA at doors of al-Rai in their battle against Daesh in northern Aleppo countryside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New military council formed to combat ISIS in Syria's al-Bab - ARA News (English subtitles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 01:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jihadist shock troops. In Syria they spearhead the assaults, are better equipped, better trained and arguably more motivated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After being hit by snipers inside rebel-held Madaya, 10 year old girl is unable to move and is under immense pain. The UN claims that she cannot be evacuated after failed rebel-government agreement regarding Madaya   Kefraya. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the participation of six clubs, "2nd Hasakah Karate Championship" for kids born between 2001   2006 is held in Qamishli </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghosts of the Desert units raided ISIS positions al-Karah area near Akashat, Iraq. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 03:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> bellingcat - Reports of Chlorine Gas That Targeted Civilians in Aleppo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 14:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ghosts of the Desert: Fighting ISIS from within </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To fund, arm ISIS? No, it is not there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched it again. And the headline is still missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He absolutely didn't say that. Can you pinpoint the exact minute? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graduation of third group of fighters of FSA Fataqem Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this new nasheed that rebels have been using lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Jaysh al-Nasr releases new promotional video of recent operation on the southern Aleppo countryside near Khanasser corridor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see the evidence that you have that will prove that it was indeed "an insignificant affair involving a few hundred men on either side" then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, it was in a Syria Deeply report:

 (...) rebels captured a number of ISIS fighters, who told them the group sent around 1,200 fighters, four tanks, a Russian-built BM-21 Grad multiple rocket launcher, and 10 cars filled with explosives (...) Some 1,500 fighters joined the counterassault from various major rebel groups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always relevant: [Abu Hamza, "The Man, The Mullet, The Legend"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dmzbv8uI6cE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A famous TOW operator from the FSA 1st Coastal Division. Responsible for 10-20 confirmed TOW strikes on regime armored vehicles. He has become some sort of pet for the sub.

He is also the incarnation of virility, as is explained in this [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s0nvprmbExQ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 men detained in Azaz, northern Aleppo, by FSA security, accused of buying ammunition in the market and sending it to ISIS inside oil tankers, alongside with hashish   cocaine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 12 civilians including 5 children died in Armed Opposition artillery shelling on Al Hamdaniyeh in Aleppo city, Aug 10. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Shajul Islam   the medical situation in Syria - Report by Bilal Abdul Kareem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian bombing of ISIS in Raqqa produces high toll of casualties: 27 civilians dead   55 wounded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civilians deserted Saraqeb while needs of civilians increase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ARA News enters ISIS headquarters in Manbij </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The back and forth in the Azaz region was an insignificant affair involving a few hundred men on either side

The last assault on Mare involved at least ~~2.500~~ 2.700 militants on both sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? There is people evidently suffocating in the video, and I went out of my way to include an *alleged* and quotation marks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suffocation cases after alleged "chlorine attack" today in Aleppo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.middle-east-online.com/english/?id=77739

The OPCW claims that Syria still produce and weaponize chemical weapons as of today.

Press release of November 23, 2015:

...with respect to several incidents in the Idlib Governorate of the Syrian Arab Republic between 16 March 2015 and 20 May 2015, the report of the Fact-Finding Mission concluded that they likely involved the use of one or more toxic chemicalsprobably containing the element chlorineas a weapon with an outcome of exposure [that] was fatal in six cases in Sarmin, including those of three children in the same family (S/1319/2015);

This doesn't prove that the government is responsible now, but it sets a precedent of plausibility and proves that rebels are not accusing the regime just for shit and giggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqs Yazidis confront the reality of life under the Kurds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a small but strategic mountain village, residents are ordered to leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian Opposition factions in the Syrian Civil War: a brief guide to Syria's armed opposition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 dead, including one child after airstrike in Maarat al-Numan, Idlib. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinions Divided on Nusras Split from al-Qaida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 07:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video is edited so badly: the pixelated logo, the intro with rock music, the pop nasheed, the desynchronized sound effects added over the artillery scenes... It is  retro, more proper for a 90's afghan guerrilla than for the syrian rebels of today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Central Division releases promotional video of its operations in the lifting of Aleppo siege </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia blanket bombs town near crash site as residents receive text message demanding return of crew remains: Help us if you do not want pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On life in Manbij: We were lucky if the Islamic State even remembered our existence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Not al-Qaeda" / JaFaS footage of the "liberation" of Ramouseh district. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Charles Lister](https://twitter.com/Charles_Lister). Not very loved around here and is bashed as a "Qatari shill / al-Nusra apologist", but he indeed knows his Al-Qaeda and intra-rebel mechanics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French fighter of YPG: I came to Syria to fight ISIS and prevent terror attacks in France - ARA News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Army of Victory occupy the Water Station near Atawainh village after violent clashes in Hama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ISIS has more honour than the NSA. They are truly the lowest of the low

Having a foreigner telling you how to stand is a rather mild dishonour compared to systematic torture, executions and reinstating sexual slavery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rejoining with the rest of Aleppo is it probably their priority. *If* this is true, maybe Fatah Halab and JaF are planning an operation towards the north to reopen the road to Turkey and reverse the SAA   YPG gains of February.

That doesnt change the fact that they will probably fail in an attack; Azaz pocket have maybe 3 thousand of fighters at most, certainly less than those inside the Efrin Canton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A deal was achieved in which the rebel-held Sheikh Issa was handed to the YPG in exchange of letting the supplies go to the besieged Maree through Afrin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deir Ezzor: an unidentified group assassinate members of ISIL in Mohasan; ISIL executes a citizen in al-Bukamal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 19:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Incendiary Attacks in Syria Linked to Russian Bombs - bellingcat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 17:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vacuum bombs destroy MSF-supported west Idlib hospital, capping bloody weekend across province </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 17:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 06:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think the truth of the matter is that Jaish al-Fatah had this plan in the works for quite a while, at least five week according to SRO on Twitter.

Yeah, back then when the government was advancing in Mallah there were a lot of rumors about JaF not wanting to counterattack in north Aleppo after taking to many losses, and Fatah Halab insisting in trying to keep Castello road open. In retrospective JaF was right and groups like Zenki suffered a heavy toll, but it was still a reasonable decision for Fatah Halab; refusing to defend Castelo would have been practically the same that make a "leap of faith", hoping that rebels of Hama   Idlib will manage to break the siege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is obviously them just trying to brag. While is true that Fatah Halab wanted to keep pushing through Mallah Farms to reopen Castello road against Jaysh al-Fatah's plans in South Aleppo (which eventually showed itself as more productive in lifting the siege), at the end of the day this operation still counted with many faction waving the Fatah Halab flag inside and outside the pocket. Certainly JaF alligned groups, mainly Ahrar, Faylaq al-Sham and "not Al-Qaeda", spearheaded the attack, but Jaysh al Islam, the "inghimasi" of FSA Mountain Hawks Brigade and Nour al-Din al-Zenki, the rocket barrages and the militants of Jaysh al-Mujahideen in 1070 complex, etc, definetly played a roll in securing the flanks and busting the manpower during the attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Promotional video from Syrian Revolutionaries Front, linked to FSA Southern Front, in clashes in Daraa against Daesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to write in the end: /u/Naenil for Mod King.

 And stick this [comic](http://imgur.com/AJWZtSW), that I ~~stole~~ ~~repost~~ draw in its integrity, to the fronpage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liwa Sayf al-Mahdi: A Syrian Army Shi'i Militia - by Aymenn Jawad Al-Tamimi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 05:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nour al-Din al-Zenki reaching Ramouseh garage, Ramouseh roundabout   Mig 21 plane model at dusk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SVIED attack by JaFaS/al-Nusra on "automated bakery" of Ramouseh before Fatah Halab's assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siege economics, humanitarian aid and the FSA inside Aleppo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 00:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The following is a transcript of two chain of tweets from [@tobiaschneider](https://twitter.com/tobiaschneider) ([here](https://twitter.com/tobiaschneider/status/756919087389929473) and [here](https://twitter.com/tobiaschneider/status/762014800062849024)), which i found interesting and decided to organize. Letters in **bold** are my editing.

......

Next episode of Syria conflict economics: What's the difficulty in delivering aid to besieged communities?

Let's do some simple back-of-napkin math: [Price differentials of imposed shortages as net profit to regime.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CoEfmHwW8AA1X9Z.jpg)

*Estimate nominal pay regime fighter : 45,000 Syrian Pounds or ~$90 USD*

*Estimate cost of living family of 5, regime: 200,000 SYP or ~$400*

*Estimate cost of living family of 5, siege: 400,000 SYP or ~$800*

*Estimates families besiege by regime: 172,600*

*Estimate total siege profiteering: 34,500,000,000 SYP*

That's roughly ~$70 million monthly net wealth transfer from opposition to loyalist communities. Regime pay does not keep up with prices, but local profiteering fills gap. [Regime pay does not keep up with prices, but local profiteering fills gap.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CoEhYtSWcAAlmYY.jpg)

*Pay shortfall familie of 5: 155,000 SYP*

*How many loyalist families could siege profist alone support?: 222,709 or roughly one million individuals.*

Further, besieged families often pay extraordinary prices by way of remittances, which have become significant forex source of regime. Thus, direct humanitarian aid delivery - bypassing local militias - threatens loyalist community patronage and punishment system. Sieges and collective punishment are an integral component of regime survival beyond immediate military benefit. Unlikely to change. 
In other words: Direct aid and economic assistance to rebel communities could seriously shift balance on the ground without strategic risk.

**Example**:

[Regime forces impose "tax" of 100 SYP per kilogram of food stuffs in al-Tal, Damacus.](http://www.enabbaladi.net/archives/95415) If siege is indeed total, that would be at least $500,000 a month revenue. Enough to top up 1,700 soldiers salaries to meet cost of living. Immediate consequence: Food shortage in al-Tal. Once remittances arrive, likely enough revenue to sustain local NDF.

**In relation with recent rebel offensive and subsequent break of Aleppo siege**

Politically is very important that FSA and associated groups from inside town played crucial role in capturing Ramouseh, reestablishing supply Control of access and check points to rebel and regime Aleppo. Post-offensive will define political balance in North Syria; with hundreds of thousands of civilians on both sides, control of bottle necks can be worth millions of USD a month.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the splintered faction of TaS. Most of Tas apparently is still working inside the Levantine Front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Western Aleppo have been a frontline for a long time, and has been through worse. Rebel may keep advancing, but a total liberation of Aleppo will take years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Militants from Fatah Halab, in recently taken positions inside Ramouseh, shows ghanima and iranian currency left behind by government forces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Western Aleppo will not collapse anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Propaganda video with message from leaders of Fatah Halab (English subtitles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   like they did in Idlib

Well, Fatah Halab, as their names indicates, its located in Aleppo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It look like the building of which they are inside in this video is the one that they are bombing earlier today in this other video:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uvCLGnOWXzA

Apparently consists in an "Automated bakery" close to the roundabout:
http://wikimapia.org/#lang=es lat=36.165146 lon=37.131869 z=17 m=b show=/35490237/Automated-Bakery search=syria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Fastaqem Union advancing into Ramouseh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statement by Fatah Halab promising safety in houses, mosques and churches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rebels capture the mass of buildings in the neighborhood Ramouseh in the city of Aleppo during the clashes with regime forces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 14:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Humanitarian Corridor" Proposal Deeply Flawed: 39 aid organizations object to the concept of "humanitarian corridors" out of Aleppo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 04:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reports SAA recaptured quarries south of artillery base in Aleppo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the silliest accusations of chemical attacks that I have seen in this war: 

"*My backyard grass is not as green as the one from my neighbor... this must be due to jihadist chemtrails, and certainly unrelated to the cronic lack of water that strike all of Syria.*"

This as well might be a picture of a patch of grass in my own backyard after my dog pissed over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activist reporting that militias and Regime soldiers are trapped in the artillery building (?) and RuAF is just bombing everything around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? They are rebelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 42 deaths due to torture by influential parties in Syria in July 2016: 41 killed by government forces   1 by armed opposition factions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea why they thought that translating news about cats is more important than any other videos from SMART News. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First Cat Shelter in Besieged Aleppo (English subtitles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FSA Mountain Hawks Brigade (Syrian rebels) assaulting SAA positions in the village of Amiriyah, southern Aleppo, August 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governing the Most Dangerous City in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 08:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idlib countryside overflows amidst displacement, Provincial Council lacks 70% of the needed aid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 08:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Syrian Army has been dropped by the Authenticity and Development Front coalition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 02:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 02:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... so "operation rooms" are actual rooms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video from Authenticity and Development Front clearly shows otherwise.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NMMVbsCxtyQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent statement from the Local Council of Daraya related to the deteriorating humanitarian situation in the besieged city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 20:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a soldier from the Authenticity and Development Front, the same one from where the New Syrian Army was recruited by the US. Do not try to spread misinformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tribute to martyr Abu Muslim al-Raqqawi, who recorded his own death after being fatally wounded in combat, by Authenticity and Development Front. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 20:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artillery guns in Syria - Compilation of all towed artillery guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite advances by FSA Liwa Suqour al-Jabal in yesterday's clashes between Fatah Halab and loyalists inside al-Ramouseh district, regime forces managed to retake some positions after " hysterical " airstrikes by RuAF   SyAAF.

More or less what is in the description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The woman in the white helmet: I dont want to be a spectator; I want to save lives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aleppo's Decisive Battle - Reliable summary of advances and losses until August 2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 08:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captive Syria: Inside Syrias jails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is apparently from New Aleppo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be the best to just think of 1070 AC as a "no man's land". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New map of south Aleppo from Step News. Shows rebel advances from inside Aleppo's pocket and loyalist counteroffensive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SCD confirms that at 23:10 on 1 Aug 16, two barrels containing 5 canisters were dropped by helo in Saraqueb. Chlorine suspected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The report very clearly says 189 killed by the Coalition and 156 killed by ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be great if everyone put "rebels claim that..." before announcing advances without visual confirmation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AaS shows aerial footage of "liberated" areas in al-Shurfah and farmlands in southern perimeter of Ramouseh Artillery Base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fatah Halab announces start of offensive in al-Ramouseh area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.middle-east-online.com/english/?id=77739

The OPCW claims that they still produce and weaponize chemical weapons as of today.

Press release of November 23, 2015:

 with respect to several incidents in the Idlib
Governorate of the Syrian Arab Republic between 16 March 2015 and
20 May 2015, the report of the Fact-Finding Mission concluded that they
likely involved the use of one or more toxic chemicalsprobably containing
the element chlorineas a weapon with an outcome of exposure [that] was
fatal in six cases in Sarmin, including those of three children in the same
family (S/1319/2015);  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once a haven for the internally displaced in west Aleppo, new wave of airstrikes drives out Atareb residents; no place is safe around here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
