<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend there doing just that at the moment. He's had some issues not connecting to data but having a connection to the network. Given the data-only SIM that's basically not having service at all. Advised him how to reattach haven't heard back if it worked yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you found in this situation however, it is at times necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "American" mentality? Do you know how many places in the world this guy would have just been blown away and hang the safety of the kid? 

When one is endangering that many lives through entirely volitional behavior it  doesn't matter why. Those around him deserve to get to wherever they're going without getting pulled out of their cars and watching their children speed off not knowing if they'll ever see them again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Car wasn't occupied and rolled backwards. Camera would have been showing horror to nobody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and? People spend far more on other things for far less content.
Things are priced at what ~~people will pay~~ **a seller or business THINKS people will pay**, not at what real value it has.

FIFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and only a month after the fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friend's sister is traif...but she's the only one that doesn't sound like a complete Okie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess; it'll get dusty on the shelves of Amazon and after the first eighty or so sets sell it'll drop to $250 for black Friday and sell out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What box set ISN'T a collectors edition?

[This Harry Potter set](https://www.walmart.com/ip/Harry-Potter-Complete-8-Film-Collection/17753370). Simply all 8 movies.


You have me with that one. Still doesn't address the 4k/value issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What box set ISN'T a *collectors edition*?  The Warner Brothers 50 best film collection was only $200. This is SIX MOVIES IN A FUCKING WOOD BOX. They didn't even use real leather on the bindings.  Profiteering at its finest and an insult to fans.

EDIT: In addition, this is a 1080p blu-ray set with the extras on DVD. You know very well that this will all be re-released in 4k UHD soon. What then, buy the inevitable 4k UHD *collectors edition*?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an actual fuel dist issue on an SEL I had back in '02 or so. Was taking to the dealership for service because I know the SM personally. Told me where to go find a reman for cheap. $500 later all in smooth as glass. Miss that car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle Earth (Lord of the Rings) Blu-Ray Set has a list price of $799 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came for this comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next up: the resultant /r/justrolledintotheshop post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before : "Yyyyyiiiiiisssssss!"  
After : "Bbbrrruuuhhhhh" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username czechs out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm deleting comments so I don't have to deal with Summer Redditards like yourself make the same comments over and over.

Nah, you just don't like getting the downvotes you clearly deserve. Or you're just trying to make "summer Reddit" a thing...at the end of summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the facebook meeem reddit! 

Why do I detect same shitposter under a different name... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro, you're an ultrafaggot. Go away. 

What precisely is an ultrafaggot and are you saying it's undesirable to be one?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, isn't summer over yet? 

Shut up and smell my scrote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy your shitposting while you can kiddo, before you know it you'll be back in school. 

Yet you're the one deleting your posts. Reddit says....you ARE a shitposter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jungle Book - I wanna be like you [scat] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 09:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 09:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an absolute fucking shitpost. 

I'm glad you recognize your shitposting tendencies. You should work on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gordon Ramsay is about to bork things up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron never did learn to drive, but he did skill up significantly in destructiveness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 01:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Walken is doing a GREAT fucking job...as a pillow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him you'll be a better tech and do jobs like that when there's better pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double the warranty (10/100 vs 5/50) so they pay half on the repairs. It works out (for them). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Somalia and Brunei banned and criminalized Christmas celebrations and recognition. Somalia ordered security forces to break up any such celebrations while Brunei imposed penalties up to five years in prison for displaying crosses, wearing Santa hats, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately AT T has not rolled out Wi-Fi Calling to the S6 for some inane reason. The LG G4 and Galaxy S7/S7 Edge both support Wi-Fi calling so you'd need to change phones but it will work on Android now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you update firmware? Have seen that happen to friends; Apple will occasionally put restrictions in place that stop charging via third-party/unauthorized accessories but still charge with licensed products. No idea how. They acted just like that as well; you'd plug in, it'd start to charge, then stop after a few minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's some initial teething problems (cameras not working, etc). Check it out fully before you leave the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Axon has had some teething problems with regards to out of the box failures etc according to ZTEs forums (camera not working, power issues, etc), and ZTE are not being very responsive in fixing the issues. The V10 is a much safer bet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not Fi, that's Italy. I had to do the same thing roaming with AT T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to work to stay on Smartone last week to keep LTE but HSPA roaming on 3 worked fine and wasn't awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9 bucks for ketchup?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.heb.com/search/;jsessionid=UhByXM+kPE03Ut3SkAkvV5Dl.store-8336?q=Whataburger

HEB now does mail order. Rotel and whataburger ketchup shipped anywhere you please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you've never had tex-mex vs mex-mex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think he means expiration of the air pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...only if they could have sold every seat which is extremely rare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most first class seats are upgraded elites domestically. Internationally it's upgrades from business or non-revs. I used to do a lot of AA international travel and never failed to be upgraded from paid business back when it only cost 10k miles a leg to do so. Marginal cost is a much more accurate way to view what the AAirpass-holders actually cost the airline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "lost revenue" argument is somewhat specious. It's only truly lost revenue if AA could have sold every last seat in the premium cabin for a premium fare. That's almost never the case. Source: i used to fly  internationally a lot on AA and get upgraded a lot. The actual marginal cost of flying an additional premium class passenger is somewhere in the hundreds of dollars.

The gifting of miles may cause more lost revenue but using those miles is subject AAdvantage availability and, again, those seats do not take precedence over sales. 

My best friend's uncle has one of these with companion pass. He would indeed fly to London to see plays, Tokyo for a new gadget, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's for Nightmareovich International Airport in Wherethefuckistan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://noaudiophile.com/Micca_PB42x/

Photos of the amp and xover.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens when you try another SIM or try that card in another phone? If it's happened several times it is more likely the phone than the SIM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not get the powered Micca PB42X? All in one powered for not much more $$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it doing? Mine would refuse to connect at times and sometimes display "Emergency Calls Only" but it wasn't bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get the phone from AT T originally? If so, it's likely that they have a specific version of the firmware and control updates. Flashing the generic Nexus image might solve that. Fair warning, I don't think AT T Nexus 6 images are available so you'd be 'stuck'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Florida did not criminalize sex with animals until 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S/he seems quite confused, but got one hell of a makeover... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine as well. Here's the original Deems Taylor introduction:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sx8pZuQVYyU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leopold Stokowski (Fantasia Original Soundtrack) - Toccata and Fugue in D Minor [Classical] (Please note: Stereo panning was present in the original; not a modification, edit, or error.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL someone used Super Mario Maker to build a level that is a functional calculator, though it can only add two digits between zero and 7 and takes about two minutes to generate an answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zombie apocalypse. Ground zero. Baton Rouge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 17:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some serious change to have an A P do that so it's airworthy again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 14:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea how happy I was that Reddit is available in China.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 08:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GSM roaming isn't a problem at all with the 5x. It's only on the CDMA side and has to do with a roaming setting that is hidden by the Fi app and set to Home Only by default.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For point to point it'd work just fine even in rural settings so long as line of sight was maintained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3.5GHz is not an unlicensed standard but is considered an 'innovation band' subject to light licensing requirements. Believe it's called the "Citizens Broadband Radio Service"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd be better served to just buy Sprint were that the goal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made in Mexico now, aren't they? *Los inspectores dormian cuando eso pasar la linea.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the TV, if it has a headphone-out jack you can use an all-in-one speaker and the TV's volume control will work. The JBL L8 looks the part and has an aux input. Bonus; all-in-one so less stuff to place or wiring and it'll let them stream from phones etc.

https://www.amazon.com/JBL-L8-Two-Way-Wireless-Streaming/dp/B00I5ODA4Q </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the property is in the US, and the owning entity has over 100 employees, the WARN act would generally apply requiring 60 days notice and other requirements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because they drop that flag doesn't mean they can't/won't pick up another. If you're in a location where a chain doesn't have and might need presence, the owners can get up-front incentives for signing that is likely to go back into the property for repairs and renovations. They may have been waiting for the agreement to run out to do so without paying a penalty. While one wants one's personnel to know whats going on, such sensitive negotiations aren't going to be disclosed until the ink is dry on the contract and there's no danger in disclosure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the word "privilege". Such a cop-out in so many cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 08:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's there as an accommodation. If you don't like it, don't read it. If you ever own your own property, you can refuse to provide bibles. Otherwise, they're present for those that care and can safely be ignored for those that don't. Unless you consider a closed book in a drawer many guests never even open some sort of threat to your beliefs or lack thereof as the case may be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 07:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... i'm stuck at O'Hare airport thanks to a delay and utilizing the facilities. Shortly after I 'engage', another guy enters the stall next to me and makes a call to someone. By the conversation it sounds like a boss. Guy is a total douche, talking at max volume about meetings and sales figures etc. Having finished, I flush at least five or six times, make some violent throat clearing noises, then start singing "Sit on my face and tell me that you love me" loudly enough that it had to be audible. Guy says "Let me call you back" and hangs up. I left feeling a little better about life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 07:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Amazon purchases are shipped by USPS, which could make messing with them a federal crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't seen it before. Not everyone sees everything posted all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good 'ol boy witnesses drunk driving accident that causes bee swarm attack; gives most Kentucky interview possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before that point an upgrade in turntable would be strongly advised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My issue is that the same government that had oversight over Chevron through one branch is attempting to hold their feet to the fire via another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have to force it to USC but it'll roam. I've now tested and roaming has worked in Houston, Salt Lake City and LA. Every time I've forced to the USCC profile it immediately finds Verizon. Only 3G but that's at least good for 1-2Mbps in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that we have USCC it isn't a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh! That'll be excellent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I know of. It's largely going to be small carriers in the boondocks with the addition of USCC as native coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly, you don't travel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For how much data? 3GB on VZW is $80 when taxes and the idiotic "line access fee" are taken into account. That's 6GB data on Fi. Source: had Verizon for a month and was lied to about amount of recurring bill and cancelled while i could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 5x. Confirmed roams with Verizon just fine. The issue is in roaming with carriers that aren't treated as part of "native" coverage. Its only an issue if the R indicator would be on/the carrier isn't treated as 'home' and for USCC Verizon is treated as a 'home' carrier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean once? I roam on Verizon now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When chefs get bored. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 07:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this kitten has been copypasta'ed five times? OP done in by Karmadecay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correction: This is why the cattle raisers ramrodded Country of Origin Labeling legislation through, the USDA blessed it, and the US ate the fines. Nothing to do with food safety; it was marketing and caused beef prices to jump considerably. The packers wanted nothing to do with it because it meant cattle born in Mexico or Canada but fed here (the important part) couldn't be marketed as such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP, have dined at Alinea; they explain quite a lot when they bring the food and where a dish requires some input from you (you'll understand), they'll tell you what you need to do. That said, ABSOLUTELY ask questions. I have only been once and I asked tons of questions. Wait staff were universally incredibly warm and a joy. No attitudes I could perceive. I took someone with me, but it'd be awesome to go alone and just focus on the food too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 11:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Project Fi. $20/month, $10/gb of data, unlimited texting, and when you're on Wi-Fi, voice calls to the states are free. Bonus: runs through US so while ping times suck, Pandora and all your streaming media work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EDGE only in Shenzhen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 09:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China Unicom utilizes all the LTE/UMTS technologies our phones are utilize. So naturally we can't register with them. China mobile only which means EDGE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...that's how he communicates recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wine Cat can't bear to watch you buy that White Zin. Meet Timmus - the official owner of the wine shop I visited yesterday (so I was told). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazed and pleased this is the top comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't ban based upon name alone and new Google Play and Apple accounts are trivial to create. It isn't a bad idea per se but in reality is probably only going to serve to provide another crime for which to convict AFTER something goes wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Landed this morning. Found out this afternoon. Perfect time for vacation here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One Dim Sum in Prince Edward, Hong Kong. Had three different Dim Sum types, total with tip? 9.79. Was absolutely excellent. Food and flavors were simple but very subtle and very fresh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My view? Ask him. "We're moving, getting married and starting over. I've tried to keep up with this but we're making changes with how we handle finances. Do you want to forgive the rent?" Why not? Just get it in writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Every state has a statue of limitations on debt and unpaid rent will fall into some sort of debt category. That statue is not likely at all to be less than a year. So the money would still be due although the landlord cannot say it wasn't paid unless he tries to deposit the checks, they're dishonored, and OP refuses to pay or can't be found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 07:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lebanon may have changed recently but I doubt it. Jordan just turned on but Alfa and Touch are known to gouge roamers mercilessly. AT T doesn't even include Lebanon in global passport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 08:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's probably Bug Tussel wireless which seems to be a roaming system now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 08:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to consider jumping ship to project Fi if the pricing works for you. Now that USCC is native coverage it should be great where you are. AT T is the best by far in some areas but it seems that's not one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 08:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason your SIM has lost its mind. Go into a store and get a replacement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 08:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...so the new owner is buying a time bomb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Belgium arrests two men suspected of planning attack - Breaking News - Jerusalem Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 04:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagined this in Christopher Walken's voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's staying a very nice blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, they couldn't see your face either and the part they could see they aren't likely to recognize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blondescrimination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't be able to use the cruise ship's mobile service but if you're in range of a land based carrier you'll be fine. Data will be charged at the same rate as when you're in the US ($10/GB), texts will still be unlimited, and voice calls will be .20/minute back to the US unless you utilize WiFi calling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...for some reason they declined to patch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy had every reason to say "GET OFF MY LAWN!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##Triggered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 14:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vagina?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 23:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend with a ranch has had two towers on his land since the '80s. The contracts were drafted such that Southwestern Bell or their successors have to provide free phones, free roaming, and free service with all features for his family. No limitations were placed on the term "family".

Now, back then, the features available were things like call waiting, call forwarding, voicemail, etc. No big deal. Things changed rapidly with the advent of data and international roaming. They didn't want to provide either but I believe he threatened to hand out phones to every one of his third, fourth, fifth and sixth cousins and they relented. They go overseas 4-5 times per year and their collective bills (which are credited off), are routinely up over $6k in those months due to data usage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people think they're black if they have a black card too!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting signal therefore it's at least partially compatible. Issue here is likely a lack of APN configuration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A YEAR?? May their legislature all get divorced soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Mother: Son Killed While Fighting ISIS in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Tex Johnson, a Boeing test pilot, was to demonstrate the then-new 707 to a group of airline executives by doing a level fly by. Instead, he barrel-rolled the aircraft. When called in by his boss and asked what the hell he was doing, he said "Selling airplanes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 08:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's for rarely used apps, it's not a bad idea but I think it's a solution in search of a problem. My storage use isn't in apps, its in media and I suspect most others are the same way. Android apps are pretty lightweight as it is. All told I think i'm using perhaps 800MB in apps? I don't think it'd do much to data usage because only apps that are rarely used are archived.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a sealed phone? How would one do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OS I doubt. However I can easily see a situation where older phones are pushed off Fi because they don't have the radio bands to provide proper service any longer. Within the last three years,T-Mobile and Sprint both have largely completely redone their spectrum and what's running on each band. a phone from 2013 is woefully limited for either carrier. As spectrum is added the older phones will only become less useful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the actor portraying "Little Enos Burdette" in Smokey and the Bandit wrote The Muppets' "Rainbow Connection" as well as several '70s and '80 hits. He later played the leader of a planet that'd never heard music on Star Trek:Voyager. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Randy Quaid has lost his mind. Turn down the volume before unmuting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 13:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and after being microwaved that long the DNA would likely be destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or closing on a house and mortgage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you do as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, seriously, that's a shitty cake.

...and that's a shitty post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 02:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cake boss, go do better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... Sure you won't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DC represent! (Or maybe Baltimore) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh OUCH. My condolences OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You take cyanide? You should increase the dose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the best and brightest talent in the world is wasted here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lithium, arsenic, klonopin, list goes on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 22:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...who's also a guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 21:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did someone forget their medication this morning? If you fear for the future over this, please don't dare venture outside ever ever ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 21:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and you're not a doctor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triggered? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 19:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just activate? New number? Or port over? Many strange things happen now with number portability. Doubtful you've been hacked. It can be a typo in the activations process, it can be that you got someone else's number who changed numbers and things haven't fully updated yet, etc etc etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 18:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine you'd get a warning before they just cut you off. I'm sure this is directed towards someone, say, living abroad, never in the states, and using 5GB/month EVERY month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 18:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is close:

http://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16875606066

$50 more but a $25 gift card and an OEM case. Selfie stick I put zero value upon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 17:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nissan Versa is in the same lineup as the GTR. That both are made by the same company speaks nothing to suitability for purpose. LP60 will play records as will the 120. LP60 will have issues in situations the 120 won't and is more likely to damage the vinyl. If you want fully automatic, best option is a used technics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
