<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3460</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/culture/art/8884829/Why-is-Andreas-Gurskys-Rhine-II-the-most-expensive-photograph.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A photo of the Rhine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there are full time professional Pizza Tour Guides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 19:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the most expensive photograph ever sold. It fetched $4,338,500 in 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 17:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the most expensive photograph ever sold. It fetched $4,338,500 in 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 17:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Frozen is not a book!' Elsa costumes take over World Book Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 15:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gypsy Hill killings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Gypsy Hill killings or Gypsy Hill murders are a group of five unsolved homicides of young women and girls in San Mateo County, California during early 1976. The culprit was dubbed the San Mateo slasher.

A suspect has been charged with 2 of them, which opens another question of how may killers were involved and whether or not the serial killings ever took place.

**Timeline:**

* On January 8, 1976, the body of 18-year-old Veronica Cascio was discovered in a creek on the grounds of the Sharp Park Golf Course in Pacifica, having been stabbed 30 times. A transient was arrested, but released for lack of evidence.

* A few weeks later, 14-year-old Tatiana Blackwell was reported missing after leaving her home in Pacifica to run an errand. A body, later identified as hers, was discovered off Sharp Park Road in the Gypsy Hills section of the city on June 6. She had also been stabbed multiple times.

* Paula Baxter, 17 years old, went missing on February 2, leaving her mired car behind. Her nude body was found on February 4 in Millbrae behind the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints on Ludeman Lane. She had been stabbed 4 times, sexually assaulted and hit on the head with a piece of concrete. Her killing was forensically linked to Cascio's.

* On April 1, 19-year-old Denise Lampe of Broadmoor was found dead after a search in the parking lot of the Serramonte Center. She had been stabbed 20 times.

* Carol Booth, 26, was reported missing by her husband on March 15, and was discovered in a shallow grave near Colma Creek on Grand Avenue, South San Francisco on May 6.


Rodney Halbower was charged with two of the murders (Paula Baxter and Veronica Cascio) after DNA evidence linked him to both cases, yet he was not connected to the rest.

More than one killer? Or did he have a partner?

[Article on arrest with photos](http://www.ktvn.com/story/27915011/new-suspect-arrested-charged-in-1976-gypsy-hill-murders)


http://gypsyhillmurders.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
