<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1935</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you saying the girls should police the creepy men who shout creepy comments and police them with the clothes they wear.

Ask any girl, a sister, a friend or a girlfriend and they will tell you the clothes rarely a major factor in cat calling. Jeans or a skirt, it doesn't make a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late 90's, early 2000's. I didn't go to much dances because it wasn't my scene, but spaghetti tube tops and belly tops were a big deal. So were miniskirts. Nothing plunging, but plunging wasn't really in style at the time. That doesn't mean older folks weren't saying the exact same thing you are.

In reality, a lot of teen girls want to push what they wear because they are told they are too young to wear certain clothes, which means they start to associate certain clothes with maturity. When they are old enough to go to proper bars, you see them dressing differently because they see that most people don't actually dress like that on a night out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon is practically like eBay in some places. Lots of third party sellers. These are guaranteed by Amazon, but all that guarantee amounts to is if you complain about a product being shoddy or not as described, Amazon will issue a refund, not the seller. That's pretty much exactly what Steam are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [At any given time there is probably at least one amateur production, but there have been plenty of professional productions too. It has been cast many many times](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glengarry_Glen_Ross). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon has a sellers platform. Basically anyone can open an Amazon store front. This allows smaller companies appear on the worlds largest digital shop front.

They also have a history of nonsense books being posted to scam their Kindle Unlimited offer. Not to mention that it is pretty easy to manipulate Amazon to become a top seller. So it is quite similar to Steam as in, anyone can pretty much join and sell anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Recent memory of them doing that a was just a couple of months ago when they removed a bunch of non-compliant USB-A to USB-C cables. 

Okay, so they allowed them on the store (for who knows how long) and removed them after a while (and I presume complaints). That doesn't really address the issues raised in the article.

And I wouldn't really call that curating. They removed a product that was once available. They didn't vet the product in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing to do with Kardashians. Happened when I was a teen too. Ahhh, clothes are clothes. No one gets upset if guys wears shorts and a tight t. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch.

I agree that a quick algorithm that won't push patches without the executable is something Steam needs (and I'm surprised they don't have). He mentions this is version 1.5 so I'm guessing the patch upload fucked up. Nothing in the article would prevent this. A simple programmatic file check would. It does nothing to fix quality issues though.

Sometimes machine toughness is needed to stop human error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Valve selling games without an executable? That seems unlikely.

What the author of the piece probably means is that the exe fails to launch or crashes on launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon store let in everything. Why would they curate games more than Steam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uPlay now and uPlay 2 years ago are very different beasts. Every month uPlay is getting more and more features and is looking a lot better than Steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does Steam need to curate itself. It is a digital store front. Ebay and Amazon aren't asked to do the same thing. Why is Steam the exception?

The solution offered in the article is bogus too, because that is what Steam used to do and found it led to delays and was a waste of time.

Does the game launch? Do the controls actually work? Does it crash after 30 seconds? Is it what it says it is in its own store description?

Is that enough for proper curation? Probably not. So the game launches in Valve HQ, where every machine is probably a top of the line gaming machine. Does Valve then guarantee that it launches? So when the badly optimized game crashes on 90% of configurations Valve's system is broken.

Test on other configurations? Now the task is about three times as long and that is just the first pass.

While many people describe Steam as a Monopoly (it's not and doesn't even operate like one), it is important that it be as open as possible for devs because it is the biggest store front. While the customers may take a hit for it, it is a boon for every small developer out there. Would I prefer if Steam only had games that sold me top quality 5 star games? Yes. But that wouldn't be very fair competition wise.

Losing 30 minutes to a bad game may make this worth it. If games were installing malware or other harmful software in indie titles I would think differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it is getting pedantic. When The Thing was made, US studios focused on a single movie becoming a hit. So all they really wanted was for The Thing to be successful and worry about sequels after. Just look how different sequels in the eighties were to now.

In the eighties, Die Hard came out and it was a hit. They did a sequel 2 years later (1990) and what did we get? We got a studio who had no idea what made the first film a hit, so they just did the same movie. It's Christmas, McClaine is having marital trouble, there are terrorists. Then they peppered a few cameos from the first movie and called it a day.

Today studios want to build multi movie stories for long term profit and horizontal marketing. The first Thor movie was a fish out of water story. If this was an eighties movie, it would be the exact same thing, except maybe this time Thor is confused in New York. Instead the second Thor movie was a fantasy battle movie and it looks like the third will be a buddy comedy.

The whole idea of a reboot v a remake is very new and I would probably only use it to refer to movies made this millennium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd disagree.

[
Dahl disowned the film, the script of which was partially rewritten by David Seltzer after Dahl failed to meet deadlines. Dahl said he was "disappointed" because "he thought it placed too much emphasis on Willy Wonka and not enough on Charlie", as well as the casting of Gene Wilder instead of Spike Milligan.\[28\] He was also "infuriated" by the deviations in the plot Seltzer devised in his draft of the screenplay, including the conversion of Slugworth, a minor character in the book, into a spy \(so that the movie could have a villain\) and the "fizzy lifting drinks" scene.\[28\]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Willy_Wonka_%26_the_Chocolate_Factory#Development) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The only thing they're adapting is the original film

They have taken the premise and themes and constructed an entirely new story. Even the callbacks are done in a new way.

In LotR there is a single source. For the most part they only took from that source to tell the story. In Batman, they keep story elements from the source and tell a brand new story. In Ghostbusters, they took a franchise that was dead and wanted to bring it to a new audience.

The first time I heard the term reboot over remake, it was how Tim Burton described Planet of the Apes. It was a new story with new elements and generally new rules. Then after Batman Begins the term really took off.

But this is all semantics. The reason why Planet of the Apes was a reboot was because they wanted to launch a new film series with sequels and a new continuity. That didn't work with that film, but did with Batman Begins.

Ghostbusters is a reboot because it was suppose to launch a new franchise. That doesn't look likely now, but it wasn't trying to tell the story again with a fresh take (Point Break, Total Recall, Psycho, etc.) and it wasn't trying to do something with the source (Scarface, Airplane!, True Lies). It was opening a new door for a new continuity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 Angry Men is a popular stage play. If it not being redone with a new cast on stage, it will be redone on film. I have no problem if that movie came out every year with a new cast. It is really about the writings and roles and I'm sure a lot of top talent would love to take a go at it. Same for Glengary Glenross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dahl wrote the first draft to the original, was unhappy with it but the studio continued regardless against Dahl's wishes. Dahl hated the adaptation and stopped allowing his books to be adapted for a while.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you. Depp was more interesting. Even as a kid, I never really felt that Wilder's Wonka was much of a weirdo. Mildly eccentric maybe. The sets seemed to show how crazy everything was much more than Wilder who has, maybe two scenes that show Wonka to be a bit crazy. The rest of the time, he just seems like a tour guide. Depp's character is far more crazy loner billionaire than Wilder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghostbusters was more of a reboot. New characters, new story and new villains. Even the concept of what a ghost is, is different. I would describe Ghostbusters a remake the way I would describe Batman Begins or Lord of the Rings as a remake. In other words, it isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let the Right One In remake was decent but was pretty much a shot for shot remake. I would say it was more pointless than Old Boy, but much more entertaining.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably has enough of a fanbase to go independent. He could start his own site and either host his own videos or use Vimeo or some other service.

Youtube has been a wild west for a while, but now people want to make a living off it and sponsors want to take advantage of personalities, the West has been won (or lost, depending on your side).

Youtube is unique that it pays content creators. Instagram and Twitter have big influencers by they are not paid directly. Also Youtube is losing money every year. I think what will happen is Youtube will phase out its affiliate program or drastically reduce it. You can see this happening already where controversial content is no longer monetizable. I think soon, we will see that there will be a few whales, or everyone just earning less. People like PDP are already using sponsorship from third parties and YouTube is becoming more and more a platform for advertisers and businesses.

This is a YouTube Golden Age. We won't see people make the same money as they once did. And most efforts to crossover from YouTube success to mainstream success are dismally un-entertaining (Fred, Haters Back Off, etc.). I don't think we will see the *superstars* that we see today ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if my sponsor was the family friendly conglomerate Disney, they probably don't like *edgy* humor regardless of context. I mean Frozen had a very subtle dick joke, but they didn't call for the extermination of a race and showed support to a fascist. Not since the Walt died anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A snakebite is half a larger, half a cider and sometimes a shot of blackcurrant. Nothing to do with sniffing glue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. In fact it is in [the first paragraph of the wiki](http://masseffect.wikia.com/wiki/Thresher_Maw). I just got lazy.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uzbekistan bans film over absence of Morgan Freeman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way Valve works on games usually means working on it for months and then getting bored and starting a new project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The choices ended up being incredibly shallow and having little impact, and I'm not just talking about the ending. 

I just finished the series and I didn't feel like they were shallow at all. I met companions based on who lived and died in my old game.

One problem was that the third game spent so much time tying up all the lose ends. All the quests were related to things like the Genophage and the Geth and other events in the game to tie everything up. Some open threads would have been nice.

The ending was fine to me. It made sense, although I wish the war resource mechanic was built into the ending, rather than just unlocking different choices arbitrarily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, the DLC doesn't really change anything.  [spoiler](#s'All it does is have Shep or whoever just repeat the same thing that the Citidal AI described.')

If you do A this will happen.
Shep: I've done A and the thing that I was told would happen happened.

It was a little bit more satisfactory, but the shit storm over the whole thing was embarrassing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repeat that 3 times a planet for a couple of dozen planets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, how did the Thresher Maws end up on every planet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great in-game story reason for it, but it doesn't stop the areas from being repetitive and unfun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The social stigmatisation of hate speech tends to work in real life but there's no such barrier when somebody's using an anonymous account online

I remember seeing a study that said anonymity had nothing to do with toxic internet comments and the same toxicity was visible
on sites like Twitter and FB where people weren't anonymous.

EDIT: [Found it](http://boingboing.net/2017/01/06/using-real-names-online-doesn.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand. A Cameron movie bomb? That doesn't line up with this version of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Some 540,000 complaints and half a million in fines caused by Janet Jackson's 

To be fair, the complaints were brigaded. Some Christian decency group got people to call in en masse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  don't have delivery men/women ringing trying to find my house every time I order from Amazon.

I had a driver who refused to use it and instead decided he call me for three days in a row because he couldn't follow simple directions. No idea how he became a delivery driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does this happen? Not calling you a liar, but I have travelled a bit and have never seen a bus wait at a stop because they were ahead of schedule in any country. Stations and terminals, yes. Regular bus stop? Never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Ghibli films have been excellent without any real conflict. Try harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't played it but supposedly it is one of those rare NES games like Mario Bros that is still playable and not one of those common NES games like Silver Surfer that are completely unplayable and frustrating.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 Buses depart 30 minutes from each other.

The first bus arrives at the first stop and takes all the passengers.
The second bus gets there in 25 minutes are picks up some passengers but not as many, so it departs sooner than bus 1.

Next Bus 1 appears at the next stop. It picks up the passengers. Bus 2 makes it there quicker than the time it took bus 1 to get there because it had less passengers to take. Because not much time has passed, there aren't as many people waiting at stop 2. 

Bus 1 picks up all the passengers at stop 3. Bus 2 is making good time, so when it arrives at stop 3 there are no new passengers to pick up. 

Bus 1 arrives at stop 4. Bus 2 arrives shortly after because it didn't have to stop at stop 3.

It's just maths why it seems 2 or 3 buses come at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was he early leaving the station or early at a stop. The times at the stop are estimated by average journey time, so them coming 10 minutes early may make sense if they are making good time. And obviously they don't just stop if there is no one at the stop. They only wait at their initial destination or a terminal. Never stops.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet Home was the inspiration for RE. It was an 89 NES game and RE is basically a remake in some aspects.

http://kotaku.com/the-nes-game-that-inspired-resident-evil-1687040111 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the venues in bed with Ticketmaster more than the bands.

In a very oversimplified model, here's what Ticketmaster do. They approach a venue and say 'Hey we want to buy all the tickets to your upcoming event. Will you sell them to us at a discounted rate.' The venue says okay. Then Ticketmaster sell the tickets on adding their own fees. 

Ticketmaster tells the bands that they will sell tickets to members of the band's fan club (mostly touts) before releasing to the general public.

Ticketmaster then says if a member of the public (but usually touts) want to resell the tickets they should do it through their other site SeatWave. Here tickets sell for a highly inflated price and Ticketmaster will again add fees and profit a second time from the sale of the ticket.

Add in the fact that bands usually have to sign an agreement that they won't play any other venue in the area for x amounts of days and that area stretches north to parts of Louth, south to parts of Wicklow and sometimes even to parts of Kildare, these bands can't even do a second gig unless they go to Cork (which Ticketmaster covers) or Galway (which it doesn't).

It really is weighted against the fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A working class family could buy a house on a single income with kids. Now our generation is picking having children or saving for a mortgage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The reason why rent   houses prices keep going up is because people can well afford them. 

A certain class can afford them. I don't know anyone who bought a house that wasn't in part funded from parents helping with an interest free deposit (or a handout). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I thought it was well known they predated the famine

The government decided some decades ago to take the line that Travelling culture were people displaced by the famine, which meant they had a duty to rehouse them and undo the famine displacement. If they had accepted they were a distinct culture from the settled Irish, their sweeping legislation would have been seen as an attempt to eradicate a distinct Irish identity/culture, a stance which has been unpopular since the forties.

Basically it was convenient to ignore the oral history of travelling communities because it made them look less like unpopular war time leaders of central Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say that. Their third party selling site charges fees, which means that when a ticket is resold they get a second pay day. Like if you sold your car and then you got a percentage of anytime that car was sold in the future.

They also don't do anything to stop tickets going to touts. They do early releases and batch releases that sophisticated resellers know about but the general public aren't as privy to.

[They have agents who help powersellers, they are absolutely enabling the third party sellers to their own benefit.](https://www.theguardian.com/money/2016/may/15/shady-world-of-the-ticket-touts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything Bernard Manning said was a joke. Doesn't mean they weren't coming from a bigoted place.

Being on a stage doesn't give you carte blanche to say whatever. And Jerry Seinfeld, Chris Rock and others have blamed the audience, saying they were too PC. Jerry Seinfeld who still does jokes about effeminate gay men, and Chris Rock who last year made Asian accountant stereotype jokes at the Oscars.

Both those guys were funny and still are funny but now that people are a little more aware they blame the audiences for being too PC if their outdated jokes fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The general rule is an hour a pint. So if you have had 4 and get a measly five hours sleep you should still be good to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't grasp it because that is not what is going on here. Ticketmaster sell the tickets, then they get hoarded, creating *artificial* scarcity. At three times the value they can make a profit without selling forward all the tickets, so sometimes we see empty seats at a 'sold out' gig.

Then Ticketmaster double dip by charging fees on Seatwave. So they make their money on the initial sale, then they get another chance to charge people for the same ticket.

That is not simple supply and demand, it is an artificial market place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like this is a planned universe. Start with the first Grudge movie and work your way through. Then watch the Ring movies. Then watch the crossover. The crossover is just a cash in. It is not like they planned the versus to happen from the start. There is no narrative to preserve.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immersion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, it is without context, but I was talking to the general trend of comedians 45+ who complain that 'colleges are too PC now' instead of blaming their tired routines on the reason they don't get laughs. The discussion comes up every time someone complains about a comedian taking it too far.

Benny Hill used to chase women around in their underwear and it was all silly and slapstick. In the 80s Ben Elton pointed out that when some women are scared to walk alone at night, maybe we shouldn't be laughing at a man in his fifties chasing around after woman who are trying to get away from him. Nowadays Ben Elton's comedy seems old fashioned.

Tastes change and it is not about people being easily offended, it is about telling dated jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that at comedy gigs you should leave some propriety at the door. But more and more I am seeing the old guard of comedians complain about modern audiences being 'too sensitive' and this is a problem. You can't blame your audience because they aren't laughing at your jokes. And saying you insult everyone equally just isn't a valid excuse.

Comedy is very much a trend or fashion and sometimes things go out of fashion. If college students don't find Jerry Seinfeld's stand up funny anymore it is not because they are over sensitive, it probably because his style of comedy is old fashion and no longer in vogue. Once upon a time Sam Kimson could scream fuck the gays because they brought the plague back and then the crowd would cheer him. I think we can all agree that this sort of comedy wouldn't fly and be inappropriate today. I love Bill Hicks, but I know a lot of it was of its time and it wouldn't be as funny today.

Comedians need to stop blaming audiences or college students for not getting the laughs they used to and admit that they might be over the hill. And it is not about people being too easy to offend. 'Offensive' comedians like Hannibal Burress and Doug Stanhope can have careers today and say off colour remarks. Some comedians need to accept that maybe they are over the hill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  first test in years I passed

Stop drink driving then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes games that are split get updated with a single installer. Pretty sure that happened to Company of Heroes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think long development cycles are one reason. But also the crowdfunding boom that was kicked off by DoubleFine just showed publishers that there is a profitability in niche games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to run with abandoned in an historic city. I don't want to actually know how to find my way around an ancient city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. MP3 is a lossy data format so, no it's not. At the same time, most people won't be able to tell the difference depending on the bitrate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, an mp3 is lower quality. The ebook format is a different product.

Like the same game on PlayStation or XBox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can scan books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say so many horror movies are just plain crap, with or without jumpscares. It is the genre with the most and least innovation. Once someone does something different it will be lauded and the director may go on and rule Hollywood. Gore Verbinski (The Ring to Pirates of the Caribbean), Peter Jackson (Brain Dead to Lord of the Rings), Sam Rami (Evil Dead to Spiderman, Steven Spielberg (Duel, Jaws to everything), Francis Ford Coppola, Roman Polanski, James Cameron, etc., etc.

But then anytime you do get a truly great movie, it is inevitably followed by a bunch of imitators. Blair Witch led to a bunch of found footage movies, The Ring led to a bunch of J Horror remakes, Evil Dead lead to a bunch of splatter movies, Hostel led to a bunch of torture porn. Halloween led to a bunch of slasher movies and then Scream reignited that genre. About a decade after Scream it lead to a bunch of horror movies that deconstruct horror movies (Final Girls, House of the Devil, Behind the Mask: The Rise of Leslie Vernon, Scream Queens, Buffy).

Saying that horror uses just a bunch of lazy jump scares is a lazy way to describe horror. Horror movies are simultaneously going to have the dregs and most creative films out there because they are relatively cheap with high profit margins. It is a genre that a lot of great and terrible directors will cut their teeth on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps a [Knox box](http://99percentinvisible.org/article/knox-box-ubiquitous-key-boxes-for-firefighters/)?

They have a set of apartment keys so fire fighters don't have to break in every single door to get to a fire. They are all over. Once you start seeing them, you see them everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney buy movie franchises for toys. The biggest toys for boys are superheroes and for girls are princesses. Disney have both of those locked down. Star Wars was the biggest selling toy franchise so they bought that.

My guess is next would be a takeover of Mattel or Lego. Maybe poach some big cartoon toy franchise like TMNT from Nickelodeon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it just has to be in the Star Wars universe. 

But why? Why does Ghost World or Donnie Darko need to be in Star Wars? If the movie is a Star Wars movie, I expect Space Wizards, aliens, galactic warlords. I don't want some teenagers in space detention talking about how bad their parents treat them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To a fault. I gave up on Luke Cage and Dare Devil Season 2 because it was superheroes fighting gangsters. Jessica Jones is the best show worked because it was Superhero fighting a supervillian. Otherwise, it's just bullying really. Not very sporting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised anyone would want that. Why have Paterson based on Coruscant? If you want to watch a movie about a bus driving poet, why does it have to be in space. That just muddies the themes. No one would actually want to see a movie about the ordinary lives of the Tattoinites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story wasn't deep, but it was suppose to be a hero's tale or a faery story. It had villains, heroes and resolution. Zootopia was a morality tale with gags and goofy characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zootopia is a fine movie and maybe it broke new technical ground, but the animation award is not a technical award or special effects award. It is an award for the best animated movie, which in the category, Zootopia isn't. All the characters seemed cut and pasted from a book of tropes. The moral was a bit in your face.

I didn't see Moana but Kubo should be a stronger contender. It was aesthetically more interesting than Zootopia, it was more fun to watch. The story wasn't as detailed as Zootopia, but it was deeper and more original. The characters backstory and motives were all there presented from the outset, like in any hero story but they were far more compelling than Zootopia. Also the 'You are my quest' line was more emotional compelling than any moment in Zootopia.

But Disney or Pixar always win, so it's a foregone conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was some jump scares in the first film. They were slow burners but they were there. I don't know why jump scare is a bad word now. Yes they can be cheap (end of every horror trailer), but they can also be fun (Final Destination), or truly scary (breast feeding scene in The VVitch A New-England Folktale). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are large income disparities from people living in Berlin and rural  Ansbach. Heck, there are big income disparities between East and West Berlin.

It's an ineloquent solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Steam let people gift these keys, even if there was a handshake agreement.

Other online retailers aren't so forgiving. Many sites lock region prices to credit card locations so you can't order from their Spanish site if you are in the UK.

This is really shitty for a place like Ireland, which is a member of the EU but the UK market usually refers to the UK Irish market, so things like Brexit and the cost of Sterling crashing can affect Ireland because the prices are lined up with UK prices.

Steam doesn't do this and keys can be redeemed in any market, but plenty of other stores won't deliver to other markets at the reduced price, by geo blocking, card locking and other means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make sense, but weren't a lot of the places built in the boom were rentals and if anyone has ever lived in a boom rental, they were shite. They looked a little modern but everything was so cheap that they ended up falling to bits in moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, if anyone shoved a camera in my face I would be annoyed. If I was doing nothing wrong, but I had a camera in my face by some fuckhead, I'm probably going to lose my cool. 

That said, trust in the police is at an all time low, which is why people are filming them. Some are the am-I-being-detained jerks and the James O'Keefe, David Daleiden types, but I think it is a price to pay for holding a career that depends on serving the public and their trust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unless you have people show ID, name the ticket and treat the venue like an airport which is to slow to do.

Wow, you just solved it.

Bought some pretty sought after tickets for an event in the UK. My ticket is tied to my credit card and I need government ID. This wasn't done on behalf on the UK government, Ticketmaster or the venue, this was done by the people throwing the event, because they are sick of scalpers.

Could be even easier if you just swipe your (valid non-prepaid) debit card and show your ticket. That's how I pick up cinema tickets. Obviously I'd like to see a way for people without cards buy tickets, but that method would defeat most of the bots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, you can outright ban touting, making Seatwave illegitimate, which would get rid of the sophisticated career touts who use a combo of bots and early bird tickets to create an early push on prices. Also it would destroy the conflict of interest that Ticketmaster has with controlling Seatwave.

But you are right. People have been calling for legislation since before the days of Oasis. Every so often a politician will say they have plan to make laws but it never happens. 

Boycotting Seatwave will never work, because it is a fees company. It could easily lower overheads and it only takes a few touts to make it profitable for touts and TM. It really needs enforced laws rather than wishful thinking. Banning selling on your ticket to a mate is a small price to pay, and a price we already have with other ticket operations, such as air travel.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not, but for some people this amount of money isn't significant enough to be a burden, or perhaps it is, but they want to see them anyway.

Telling everyone to just stop buying them is like telling everyone to just stop breaking the speed limit, or stop drink driving. There needs to be a better solution than telling everyone just to try their best.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with voting with your wallet, is that not everyone has the same amount of votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been talk of this since the early days of Slane. Don't see anything changing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know, legislation. It won't stop touting but it means that you know, there are repercussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read history, a lot of the civil rights marches turned violent. MLK himself promoted passive resistance, but it is a fallacy to think that that many people all shared the same beliefs and ideas for protesting.

Obviously there was violence from counter protestors, but not every follower of MLK believed that if you get punch and spat at, you should just sit and take it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, looks like they had web specials first but the full special aired lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bandits had a CH 4 special before RoT if I remember correctly. Either way, they made their audience through YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David McSavage started his career busking comedy and selling CDs. I don't think he ever stopped. Still think he's shit, but he's just doing what he has always done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's blocked so you will access it through directly through Channel 4.

It's a pity youtube can't redirect in these cases. Obviously that would be far to open to abuse, but would be hanfdy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [On the bubble](http://www.phrases.org.uk/meanings/on-the-bubble.html)

It means up until about the fourth season, no one knew if it would finish out its run or get cancelled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 999 you replay for a true ending. It is annoying but hopefully they insert the flow chart in later games into the remaster. In the later games it is really playing through different stories more than a new playthrough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spoiler](#s "I don't think it was the strongest game in the series ever but in a game with different universes and timelines, how exactly can you retcon anything? Every timeline is a new truth and all timelines needed to exist before getting to the final timeline. That includes the multituide of timelines in VLR which amount to a single timeline in ZTD. What was retconned?") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avatar is hated on reddit but it is still the most financially successful movie ever and was critically praised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  sci-fi/fantasy throughout its history has been ignored

Not lately. Every December we get a space drama movie like The Martian, Arrival, Interstellar and Gravity.

Have there been any big fantasy movies since LotR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets be honest. Deadpool was a fun movie, no one denies that. But as far as 'blockbuster' movies go, there is a big difference between a film like Avatar or Terminator 2 and Deadpool.

In the very first Oscars they had two 'Best Picture' Awards. One was suppose to go to the film with the most artistic merit and the other to the 'Best Picture'.

They dropped the Artistic award instantly and every other cermony only had one Best Picture award. Now the Best Picture needs to tow the line between outstanding appeal and artistic merit. Deadpool would not cross those two divides, where films that have brought new methods of film making to the masses like Inception, Avatar and Terminator 2 all did.

Maybe there is something to be said for spliting the awards again. Comedic movies and action movies both have people who complain they aren't welcome to nominations in certain bigger categories.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 09:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A member of staff stopping you isn't wrongful arrest, unless they forcefully detain you. It more likely a case of defamation. You are in a crowded area and someone accuses you of being a criminal when you haven't done anything wrong is an attack on your character.

That's why in most cases, you will be asked to voluntarily come to the back, to weaken any defamation accusations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 09:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a public park. The visible deterrent claim doesn't work because obviously this kid wasn't deterred. Also I'm sure he and others used this route all the time, meaning that someone eventually getting hurt becomes inevitable.

The payout is more to punish the council rather than reward the teenager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly Cameron threw out a lot of world building because he didn't want to over complicate the story.

I imagine we will see more Na'Vi history, different tribes, folklore and a story that brings Earth's interest in unobtainium back to the planet. Perhaps even a new better form of unobtainium and what its actual uses are.

Also a commemorative tank top for Michelle Rodriguez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steam don't set prices. They aren't selling inventory. It's not like they have a warehouse full of codes. They have an agreement to digitally distribute software, which is sold and promoted through their web store front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the one thing Vision is missing in his speech there is the fact that he is actually a fictional character and the reason the enhanced persons have grown exponentially is because they are expanding the fictional world abd for fiction to be successful they need conflict so challengers are created.

This little speech might be a nice in-world explanation as to why all the superhero shit started going down at the same time, but lets not pretend it is a valid real world philosphy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My theory is that it was an oversight by the writers or just an element they didn't really want to explore in a movie about family (and possible allusions to Ayn Rand's philosophy).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's further than 7 main entries. There was the Remake, RE0 and Code Veronica. That bumps it to 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon already have their own app store. Also it is probably easier to sell on Amazon that it is Steam. I don't understand why you think more competition will equal a smaller library? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he feared unwed mothers more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt that it had some good concepts but it never really got a chance to explore them. I can't really call it a good show on that alone. It did have potential though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hasn't it been patched out of Bioshock 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
