<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 22:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy never fails to impress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 21:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tackle...the...guy...with...the...ball.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or a freshman qb with 35-40mph wind at his back.  but nah, lets just call him out instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I remember when T-Mart made his first touchdown he did the blackshirts arm cross sign and everyone was, wtf??  Adrenaline makes you do goofy things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One Hand Grab.....wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an Illinois native so I've been looking forward to this match-up for quite a long time.  Unfortunately my folks moved me out here as a kid and here I am as an UNL Alum decades later.  Big Cubs and Bears fan and I root for the you when they aren't playing my Huskers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm originally from Illinois but I don't remember being held that much when I was a baby...my god boys, are you needy or you just really into us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, every time I see him, he reminds me of a grizzled nfl qb whose sorta letting himself go a bit.  He's a great guy though, love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so much holding...my god, it's like watching a highschool jv game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there a new rule we have to give up a safety once a year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing what can happen when you create a superhero in the lab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did they just huddle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's a lot of time to play and you have a great offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah on a kick return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 18:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [As a man child, I just couldn't resist.](http://imgur.com/sjH7gH0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't want him to leave either, just saying, he is a great coach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 16:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least you found that you can post on Reddit from beyond the grave.

myth busted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 15:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two things, #1...Paul, I haven't seen you in a few years, you're looking old my friend and a little too much like Brett Favre.  #2, I think you'd be a great coach no matter where you go, I'd love to see what would happen if you went to USC or another high profile school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 05:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh it's been quite the journey but that's what makes the adventure worthwhile, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 02:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you and your peers have had to deal with this.  We had similar issues with just about any "non-theatre" student who took Theatre 101 and was required to attend performances and/or assist with building sets.  For 75% of those students, they were a big pain in the ass.  We typically applied our long list of petty revenge tactics such as sending them to the third floor for the board stretcher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 23:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I use don's list gererator for Mame, I just created my "ALL GAMES" and all my different genre's with it.  It's even used in the "how to" video he himself created.

[How to](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R3TXxQWJtc8)

You may be thinking about Don't rom renamer.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 15:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you may need to make sure the roms are named correctly (matching the database).  I found the following utility on the hyper-spin forums to be incredibly helpful for MAME roms.

[LINK](http://www.hyperspin-fe.com/forum/showthread.php?9630-Hyperspin-Naming-Utility highlight=hypersync)

I think I used it for SNES too, but can't remember now.  I used Don's renamer for the others.

I'm nearly done with my software side of this project and I'm on step 987 out of 1000 so its hard to remember exactly but I want to say I renamed all my roms before I was able to or before I tried to use Don's list generator.  I literally hurt my hand sorting and arranging my output lists so be prepared.  Mame is done, now on to SNES/NES/GENESIS.  Going to need an ice pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 22:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, 25% off of 9.99 which comes to 7.49.  Sorry, I fat fingered a number in my comment above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 16:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is on sale for 25% off which comes to $7.49 (sorry if the title isn't completely clear).

I've been playing this game for over a year and a half and I think it's great.  I couldn't recommend the game more.

--edit, I fat fingered a number...doh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King Arthur's Gold - Not (yet) on Steam Sale! 25% off $7.49 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 03:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Bo...he is just a very loyal person, to a fault...but the players stay out of trouble or get the boot and their graduation rate is very high.

If things don't turn around it could be a very hot seat though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 23:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was my friend that happened to...perhaps you had problems reading the application? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was about to start my first semester at college a long ways back...

* Need a printout of your class schedule from admissions to get a student ID.
* Need a student ID to get a printout of your class schedule from admissions.

A friend of mine faced a similar situation at the same college.

* Need to sign up for classes to get financial aid.
* Need financial aid to sign up for classes.

College did a good job of teaching us how f-d up our world really was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N is for Nowledge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 22:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 14:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> regarding #3, I found [THIS](http://forum.arcadecontrols.com/index.php/topic,17175.0.html) and [THIS](http://forum.arcadecontrols.com/index.php?topic=114591.0) the other day.  I think I'm going along the same lines of the second link, creating jig and using my router and then sanding, it'll take some time but I will be happier with the results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 20:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> notice how the third image looks like this:

O+O

it matches what you've linked to, the two slots you can change out.  Good catch!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 19:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can donate to EmuMovies to access that...it's well worth it.

[LINK](http://emumovies.com/forums/index.php/page/portal) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 02:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  Josh Bandera's father caught that first pass.  Maybe that's a sign!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 02:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Lincoln, I'm originally from Rockford.  Moved to Nebraska when I was a kid but spent most my summers back there.  Grew up watching WGN all summer long, it was the only thing that made me feel at home out here  I moved to Chicago after college but then came back to Lincoln to help with my friends project, met my wife, bam, 11 years later I'm still here.

  I really love Lincoln, but every time I get to Chicago it reminds me how much I miss it.  If you need anything, shoot me a message! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 00:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha!  busted a nut on that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 15:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, I use Sketchup for lots of projects, including my mame cab.  It's a great free application.  I just "google" the cabinet I'm looking for and can usually find it, for example "sketchup tmnt arcade cabinet". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 21:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damnitsomuch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 01:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems to me that your DC should move to your OC... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 06:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here you go:  http://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=32-205-069 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 06:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats...it's a great magazine and one of the CPU Mag writers was one of the best bosses I've ever had.  It was a job I had almost 20 years ago and I'll never forget him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 03:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, I love KAG and after playing it for the last 18 months, I still log a game or two a day.  Thank you for sharing this game with Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 21:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here...I was like AWHHHHHAAAAAAATTT??? oh bama.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 18:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That game and the company behind it changed so many people's lives. 

I just graduated from college in 1999, a degree in Theatre.  I took a summer job at "Software Etc" (now Gamestop) while trying to decide where to go next.  The job offered more than my position at local cable company working with Cable Access, and heck, I owned a nintendo and a playstation so I thought, what the hell.  

I spent a lot of time looking at the damn HL box which featured information about Team Fortress Classic on the back.  "Coincidentally" I needed a computer so I could perform some video editing at home and so I used some of my savings to build my very first computer from scratch, mind you I have an arts degree essentially.  Building a computer was incredibly interesting, challenging (at the time) and it was fun.

  I then started playing HL and Team Fortress Classic....then several mods including Day of Defeat.  Then I discovered that I could make maps myself so I put my Set/Scene/Lighting/Sound design skills to work trying to make maps for Day of Defeat and I also start working on various mods (even had a pics of one my maps in PC Gamer UK).  

  I then start working with a mapping design team focusing on Day of Defeat only and many of those maps my team made were in DOD 1.3 and eventually were in the retail version.

  Our team then started to work on our own independent game but things sort of fell apart from there.  However, many of those guys went on to work for big time studios and are still working for them.  Some worked for Valve for a while too.

Right as things started to take off, my wife and I started our family so I focused instead on my "day job", which had become and still is in I.T.  Today I have an incredible job in a field I love but I never would have discovered without HL.

  Think of all those mods and how many of those folks went on to do amazing things in the gaming industry.  I am not one of them but I am truly thankful that HL gave me an excuse to build a PC and gave me an excuse to discover and learn more.

TLDR:  HL made me want to build a computer and now I'm in I.T.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 00:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not having any issues at all.  Watch it on a Roku, a Panasonic TV and my computer.  All work just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 00:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, same here.  I bought a lifetime license and I feel they didn't provide what they promised when I originally purchased it.  They want to force you into the new product but I am going to pass on any new purchases from them, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apparently it's time for the ole I.V. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I thought so too.  He only has 7 rushing yards, that guy can fly so I was surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nm, negated by penalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was tragic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as tight as Braxton's calf muscle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 15:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 second... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 03:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesn't. ..you dont have to go through valve to get on the PC and thats my point.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 02:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kidding... you know what I mean...ffs redditt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im on my phone or I would link to the several interviews where they have.  I saw others link to them in this same thread.  At least try to research an issue you are discussing.

Edit, here is one article.  Sorry I couldnt shorten it.

http://www.examiner.com/article/valve-to-do-away-with-steam-s-greenlight


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have purchased more indie games from developers than from Steam and although your 99% is pulled out of the air and you have no statistics to point to, I agree if I had a choice as a dev, I would want my game on Steam b/c it will get a lot of exposure.  However, I have yet to hear of a game that was amazing and I didn't buy it or hear about it b/c it wasn't on steam. I didn't say, "oh man, I would have bought that if it was on Steam".  Now, I have said that about "Console Exclusives".

But ultimately it is a store...They have tried to offer a solution, a pathway, for indie developers who do not have a publisher and its not perfect, but its going in the right direction.  It sounds like it will be pretty incredible once they get there.

But Valve is in no way the only gateway to the kingdom.  If I want my game on Xbox, you better believe I have to go through Microsoft.  If I want to publish on PC, I want to be on Steam I suppose, but I wouldn't have a big hissy fit if they won't publish my game.  I guess to me it seems that Valve just can't win.

I was in indie game development ages ago.  Many of my former peers are in the game industry today.  There are so many avenues for indie devs now, it's wonderful and amazing and I wish this was all around 14 years ago.  If you make a great game, you will sell it, with or without Steam.  I have 100% zero doubt.  If you have a so-so or niche game, then yeah, you will help your sales by being in the biggest store.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 20:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cheated and used MechJeb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 19:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> b/c Valve is a store, not a platform.  If you want to be on Xbox, you must go through Microsoft, if you want to be on PS3, you have to go through Sony.  If you want to be on WII U, you have to go through Nintendo, etc.

If you want to be on PC, you can go through a number of distribution channels or set up a website, post on Reddit and say, buy my stuff.

If they dont like how Valve does things, then why bitch, use something different.  There are lots of choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 19:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me it sounds like Valve understands there are issues and are working towards a solution.  I'm not sure its worth getting all up in arms whenever some indie developer whines.  What would so many of these indie developer have done years ago when there was no digital distribution.  

  Valve is a store, not a platform, and they are trying to provide a way for someone from a small team/company to market and sell their game without having to beg a publisher to help them, and all they get is shit from folks.  

They have stated it's not perfect and they are working towards a solution that sounds like a win/win for everyone.  You can't make dramatic changes over-night and this "me now" attitude needs to be readjusted.

Indie developers didn't have that sort of avenue at one point and everyone said, "hey Valve, you should look at this".  They then offer it and all I hear is "OMG I bought a shitty game from a STORE b/c I am too lazy to Google the title and learn more about it".  "It's Valve's fault for not playing it".  

I totally agree it's not perfect but don't be an impulse buyer, do some reading FFS and don't blame others b/c you didn't.  There are many AAA games that are AWFUL, should Valve not sell those either? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 14:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I then say "well, that's that" and do some other things.  Check the score last night and they lost...by 2...WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 04:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF did I just turn on...I miss half an inning and its 6-0 with bases loaded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 14:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why football will one day kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 17:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no you do a great job...just busting your chops!  I've learned so much from your video's that I could never thank you enough.  Please keep it up, there are a lot of us that learn more easily by watching your demonstrations.  Sometimes reading documents makes my head spin b/c I'm still new at this and I can't visualize what is being explained.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 16:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this wholeheartedly and it is often considered *the best* of the DC animated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 15:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always felt your videos were like an unusual third person game where the player wears lots of thumb rings. ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 14:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 00:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if someone can start up an Amazon wishlist for them, Ill take some of that action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 22:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is incredible, thank you for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 18:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, Im not sure either.  I honestly started out as someone who wanted to build a mame machine and here I am, with two original arcade machines in my garage going through various stages of restoration.  That is due, for the most part, to what I learned here.

I'd be happy to help /r/cade with its wiki and so forth.  I even asked one time if someone could help me understand how to make changes to the wiki.  I can't seem to make any edits or it's not obvious to my tiny brain where to do that at.  I was going to make one on my own but figured it would be better time spent if I could improve the one on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 17:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in his defense, I too like to take naps during baseball games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, it is a terrible movie IMHO.  When I was in college, I got free tickets to see this and I still felt cheated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 14:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Sandberg and I grew up watching him, Grace, Dunston, Dawson, etc.  Those are my boys.

I read a really great article before Sveum was chosen, talking about if they should give Ryne a shot.  He did everything the old regime asked and but they made a lot of great points about why he wouldn't be a great manager, several which have been mentioned in this thread.  

I think the most interesting one, though, was that we all love him because of what a great person and player he was for the Cubs.  He was an idol for so many of us.  If he failed, and failed spectacularly, it would affect his legacy and what we think of him.

How long did it take Bill Buckner before he could come back to Fenway.  He was a great player whose entire career is now a flash in our minds of a simple error.  

What if Ryne botched a call that cost the Cubs a World Series shot, he'd never be able to survive that.  Not that it would affect how I thought of him but it was an interesting point, one I never considered.

I wish him a great deal of luck and success.  I'm sorry to see that he has to start out like this but sometimes opportunity knocks and you have to step up and answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 15:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video made me sick to my stomach.  It was like watching a horror movie and you know the villain is behind the door.  You want to shout "RUN RUN RUN! What are you waiting for"!

You know when they first sounded the alarm, some folks were saying to themselves, "pfft, that ain't nothing"!  I knew what was coming but I was still shocked by it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 17:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not accurate.  People weren't being paid and 38 couldn't find anyone to bail them out.  The state cut its losses at that point.  AFTER giving them $75 million.  Are you suggesting it should have given more?  

Curt likes to blame the governor constantly, but who is at fault for the years of poor decision making, throwing money around and completely missing deadlines.  You can't blame any investor for saying, I'm going to tap out here.

I wanted them to succeed but this is on Curt and those he hired to help him run the company.  They did a shit job, simple, and you can't go..."no for reals, I will produce a game and make money...starting...now!".  Go back and read the accounts of how the business was ran from the employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 16:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do all the controls fail or just a button or the joystick?  If it is one or two buttons, it may just be the microswitch under the button.  If it is ALL of them, then yeah, maybe a bad connection somewhere.

[HERE](http://www.arcade-museum.com/manuals-videogames/M/Mortal_Kombat_1_1640025101_July_1992.pdf) is the manual.

I don't know anything about this unit but flipping through the manual I see there is a switch test that is built in to test the control panel.  

There is also a troubleshooting guide that references issues with the control panel.  Check it out and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 18:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks great.  I was thinking of doing some lighting effects on mine as well.  I love the kick plate too, great job over all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a great way to put it:

*he's forcing him to accept this treatment because he can't afford not to. That's a special and malicious kind of cunt.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 17:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously have no concept of what it is like to be in that situation.   What was he supposed to do, cry, everyone was laughing, uncomfortably,  then someone tosses some bills on the ground.  

You can be a douche bag apologist if you wish but that's on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 17:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its OK to humiliate a homeless person for laughs as long as you give them money to make you feel better?  OK gotcha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 16:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is amazing.  I see Jody Davis listed at catcher.  I went to my first game in 82 or 83.  I was only 6 or 7 but I remember deciding that he was my favorite player b/c they were chanting his name "Jody, Jody, Jody".  

I also missed the 7th inning stretch b/c I had to take a dookie...totally bummed me out.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 18:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played this in Chicago a few weeks back.  There was a Nintendo event of some sorts out in front of the Navy Pier.

It was certainly an interesting concept but hard to digest in the environment (hard to hear, game was already in progress when I got my turn).  I hope to get a crack at it when I have more time to understand the back story and to get a better handle on the controls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 18:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that escalated quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 18:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glad to see it is going to a good home.  I hope it brings you all years of joy!  At the very least, they are great conversation pieces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 14:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh darn, well I must be remembering wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 21:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to have that unit but that seems kinda high to me.  I could be wrong but I have seen it for quite a bit cheaper and in much better condition.  If it was pristine then that may sway me a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 16:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 15:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say 12:00 - 12:30 PDT, do you mean AM or PM?  Not sure if you are using military time.  No way I can stay up that late but if its at noon, I'm game.

I looked around the site but I couldn't find it...but I am blind, just ask my wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 13:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule 1 of Arcade Club...Arcade Machines Are Heavy as HELL!
Rule 2 of Arcade Club...Arcade Machines Are Heavy as HELL!

I've moved 3 of these buggers so far.  One in the back of my truck...had to lay down b/c it was heavy as HELL.  the second in the back of our mini-van b/c it was raining and the third, my fellow /r/cade redditor down the street hauled one in his SUV.

They are manageable with 2 people but a few more is advisable.  The two I have are in my garage until I can complete their restores, the third my fellow redditor wanted in his basement and it wasn't terrible getting it down the stairs, but certainly the weight was a challenge.

With two people, you typically lay a blanket down in the back of the truck, get it close to the tail gate and then tip into the back.  When unloading, same deal, slide it out until you can use gravity to safely lower it to the ground.  Most units have wheels on the back so you can tip it and drag it around.
  When I purchased my Out Run, which needs a lot of work, I strapped a 4 wheel dolly to the bottom so I could wheel it around to work on.  
  If you want to move into a basement, I know John from John's Arcade recommended a Hand Truck/Cart with wheels on the back.  I think that was a great idea.

Just be careful and congrats on your purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 13:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see how that would be more effective then a van with Free Candy painted on the side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 03:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He took a shoulder to the head and his leg got jacked up.  He looked dazed but he held on to the ball somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 03:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Longest inning EVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 03:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looked incredibly painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 23:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, I drove mine laying down in the back of our mini-van.  Just be sure that everything inside is secure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 21:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you search this reddit, you should see some unique designs.  One thing you could do, which I did, is to use Google Sketchup.  It is a free 3d modeling application.  Then google for "sketchup arcade cabinet" and you can play around with existing designs if you wish.


--edit--

Also I did a quck google search and found dozens of "new/modern/different" designs.  Here is a forum link with quite a few:

[http://forum.arcadecontrols.com/index.php?topic=100359.0](http://forum.arcadecontrols.com/index.php?topic=100359.0)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 21:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks a million, they had the Taito side art I need for my double dragon restore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
