<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8487</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ those are awesome fun bags  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 07:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Avery.  BLAM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple TV (new) remote scrubbing issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 01:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 02:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 13:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleep with a fan on.  Doubt it would work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, you'll gain it back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple TV Siri question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I own all the seasons of Dexter- I hold the Siri button and say 
"Siri, play Dexter season 4"
Responds with 
" Hmm, I'm not finding anything for that."

Ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the new Apple TV switch television inputs with Siri or manually? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone heard of a more specific time frame for new appleTV launch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 23:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master gave Dobby a sock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 06:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I volunteer as tribute  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 01:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She will be a Christian hero.  Martyr for the cause.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 14:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George "the Animal" Steel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iTunes keeps generating playlists...why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 15:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> example:  I have an oldies playlist.  Recently iTunes has generated an Oldies 1, Oldies 2 and Oldies 3 playlist.  How can I prevent this from happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Literally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to YouTube on AppleTV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 12:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Pride parade is actually hurting the gay community by coming across as sexual deviants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 16:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consumer version.   Also, it was 20 seconds, not 20 minutes.  

I've never had that on any iPhone previously.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6 FREEZING! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 11:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else have the issue where iPhone 6 (specifically) will freeze when you open up certain apps (almost exclusively FB)?
It's like it has to buffer or something weird.  
Goes away in about 20 seconds, but during that time nothing works; not the home button, the volume buttons,  nothing. 

Ideas? 

I'm always have the latest iOS installed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Not even sure a delta is needed in this case, but you helped me quell the guilt pretty substantially.   You hit the nail on the head when you connected my feelings of guilt to his long military record. I'm a very empathetic person, so I can sometimes get in trouble by putting myself in someone else's shoes without thinking how it might affect me. Thank you    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV:Need some quick help on this one- I selfishly don't want to invite in a newly homeless Vet to stay with me while he fights the VA to get access to his own benefit money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 12:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As briefly as possible, I belong to a Meetup.com group for Former Fundamentalists and met this gentleman there.  I only attended once, but we've been FB friends ever since ( several months).  He's an ex-Marine who's been through 4 Tours and is disabled because of it- both physically and mentally (PTSD).  He's seen some amazing things and is good part metal and screws because of it.  He's been recently evicted from his place because of anger issues and the VA has somehow been able to restrict the flow of benefit money (I'm really foggy on this part, I don't know how it's even possible) that he receives because of it.   Sufficed to say the guy is homeless as of a few days ago until he can sort things out with the VA.  he actually has full military retired and paid benefits so apparently he fairly well for himself when he's actually getting his money.  To give you an idea, he's had to put his quite expensive car up for sale in order to get some money- hasn't sold it yet.  

Ok so here's my emotional dilemma: I have nothing but respect for the man.  He's seen and lived through things that would cause me to fetal up and cry like a baby.  I'm really torn because he has family about an hour away, he has other friends from the group who've known him longer and in person actually, and I live alone in a one bedroom apt. I suppose he could stay on my sofa? I selfishly don't want the hassle of having someone here indefinitely.  I don't want to have the eventual awkward conversation of, it's time for you to leave.  I'm a little terrified of his PTSD. I don't really know the man except for FB convos we've had and I took him out to dinner once when his posts started getting REALLY dark and hopeless.   

Boils down to, I'm wrestling with feeling guilty, and maybe I should, for not wanting to ask him to stay with me.  Deep down I feel it might be the right thing to do but it scares me and seems like it would be a hassle.  Whiiiich makes me fee like an asshole for even thinking.  

Help me out in thinking this through? 

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 11:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks very exotic. Was her dad a G.I.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of my league or out of my mind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 17:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be as succinct as possible, I'm a bigger guy.  6'2, heavily muscled but chubby.  Used to be in better shape but years and life sort of got the best of me and currently having issues shedding the weight I'd like. 
Online dating seems to net me, what I would consider, really nice women that I'm not that attracted to.  I used to beat myself up for meeting these really cool women who I got along with but stopped seeing because - you just can't fight attraction and the goal is romance. 

Point of all this being: I'm attracted to women who are average sized to thin and seem to get emailed and matched almost exclusively by women who are larger.   I always feel like a dick because I'M A LARGE DUDE myself- is that hypocritical? 

Women seem to be MORE about personality than men are, but let's be honest, women don't date just anyone either. 

I'm sure my confidence hasn't come away unscathed, but I'm fairly gregarious and occasionally witty, and I have a good beard lol.

Sooo, 
Do I just stop dating until I've managed to lose a little weight?  Do I keep dating in hopes I find myself a woman who likes bigger guys?

It's been a frustrating number of years. 

Also, please note I have ZERO against heavier women.  It's just doesn't rev my engine. 

I think I'm in need of some new perspective on the whole thing.

Thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 20:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok.  I appreciate your feedback on the matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a guarantee they will over-erupt? Only reason I ask is that mother has had her bottom two out decades ago and her top ones haven't moved.   Just wanting to make sure I don't have it done if I don't need to.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 out or 2 only? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 35 male.  All my wisdom teeth are in and upright. The bottom two are pressed tightly against the gum and as such are starting to see some periodontal disease because flossing is next to impossible.  I'm resigned to getting those out, but my upper two are in, with plenty of room. I floss around them easily and have no issues. Do I have all 4 out?  

Need some advice here- don't want unnecessary surgery on the upper two if I don't need to. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 14:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAMN YOU APPLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can smell the tuna fish from here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 08:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are the 5% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 20:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad.  It just hit me this morning that I'd like to have this discussion. I didn't give CMV a thorough search.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: You should not give to panhandlers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 11:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK IT! I'll beat him live! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every damn time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 05:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 11:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free alcohol forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the chances that a larger heart like that would be passed on genetically and not just a fluke for that one horse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That definitely helps me understand better. And all those tiny adaptations, over billions of years get us to our present day diversity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect!  Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance of a link to where he answered it?  There are far too many Dawkins videos to sift through- that's asking for a lot. No worries if you can't.  Thanks for prompt response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone ELI5: No good mutations in evolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to this weeks Dogma Debate podcast and the guest (who is a biologist) is very clearly counter-evolution because he claims no positive mutations exist.  They were addressing the issue somewhat and the host moved to the next question leaving me hanging-  a quick google search demonstrated he's not the only biologist who things this is true-  is it possible to get a dumbed down version of where the error is in thinking?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 14:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, having a face is overrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want her to oil-wrestle Salma Hayek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post sex regrets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 15:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds rapey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox 1 kinnect WILL not start up on voice command. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 04:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All other commands work once it's on. 
It worked when I first got it. 
Any ideas? 

Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 05:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For when God is fucking "mysterious." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
