<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7781</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. In a heartbeat. The point is that public opinion isn't moving toward Trump, which would be way more concerning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's just that reality has a well-known liberal bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump Regime and Republicans' errors are gradually forcing their own hands on this investigationlike Sessions' apparent perjury leading to his recusal. If Nunes had simply involved Schiff, this would not be an issue, especially since the hearing last Monday was not being severely criticized for partiality (*i.e.*, the bad optics of most GOP questions being about leaks was a story, but not the main story).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I like to be able to forget that the President's there for two or three weeks at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't agree that he's good for *anyone*, but this is still Interesting and encouraging that there might be lightthat's *not* from a mushroom cloudat the end of the tunnel:

For the first time ever, half of Americans say they believe in climate change and that they are very concerned about it, according to Gallup.

Thanks, Trump.

...

Ditto Obamacare, which in the midst of the GOP repeal effort has risen to new highs in popularity.

The Kaiser Family Foundation tracking poll two weeks ago showed that 49 percent now had a favorable opinion of the Affordable Care Act  up from the mid-30s as recently as 2014.

...

It's also now apparently happening on the Keystone XL pipeline. The same Pew poll showed what was once an overwhelmingly popular project is suddenly polarizing  with more opposition (48 percent) than support (42 percent).

As recently as 2014, Americans supported the pipeline nearly 2-to-1.

...

That Trump brand keeps falling. A new Gallup tracking poll Monday  the first since the health-care bill imploded  showed his approval rating hitting a new low of 36 percent. That's lower than Obama ever got in his entire eight years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why President Trump has been very good for liberals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blame the brake designers for designing brakes that needed maintenance, then the safety inspectors whom he fired, then the engineer for going too fast after he asked him to, then people he invited on the train, ***then*** the conductor for letting them on, then Issac Newton for discovering the first law of motion, then inertia itself for existing, and then the media for reporting on it.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trolls may not care. But people who read may be persuaded. 

The polls aren't fake. And if Trump doesn't adjust his strategy, they'll continue to decline, which will make him progressively less effective (and drive futher declines).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in this report. But he has to be losing at least some GOP support to get this low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just [leave this](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5rwoni/z/ddau0zt) for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to, but the Trump budget cut the government safety inspections so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America is getting tired of "winning." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you can use an automatic formula applied by a computer, but you still need someone to look at the taxes or other financial documents and verify that the self-reported number matches. Then you have people benefiting from understating their income to the IRS or purposely working less to remain eligible for benefits. And there's additional processing time. It's not impossible to run a means test that axtually saves money. My only point is that it saves *less* money than a simple reduction of benefits calculation would suggest, because the means-test entails several unavoidable burdens. This is fairly basic [public finance](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Public_finance) economics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The means-test needs to be enforced. If you have a graduated phase-out versus a hard cutoff (which you should, because hard cut-offs create perverse incentives), you have to calculate and periodically update the proportional reduction in the benefit. From experience, I can tell you that obtaining parents' tax returns can also be a huge hassle. And all of the additional paperwork needs to be processed, driving up administrative costs. As someone else pointed out, children estranged from their parents or whose parents simply don't want to provide the help can get screwed too.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Means-testing and enforcing restrictions cost money and resources. So you don't ever get the theoretical maximum savings from imposing the means-test. Plus, removing universal eligibility reduces buy-in from the people who are paying a disproprotional amount to fund the social programs. When we're all in it together, everyone wants to make it work better because we all use it. Go to a city where public transportation is used by everyone and compare it to one where it's only used by the pooryou'll instantly see what I mean. This is frequently the difference between something being seen as a public benefit that you pay for as compared to *welfare for those other people*. It's a large part of why Social Security and Medicare are so popular. They are *earned benefits*. These programs also represent an inter-generational pact that enhances solidarity and social cohesion. Working age people pay for their elders, who, in turn, paid for their elders when they were working. We need the same thing with younger people. We all pay for their education now so that they can pay for our dignified retirement later. These links between generations make our county stronger.

Also: 

This may be an unpopular opinion, but we have to raise **middle class taxes** to pay for this too. Although tax rates should probably be more progressive, raising taxes *only* on millionaires will lead to a much more volatile revenue stream (in addition to the lack of buy-in discussed above). If the idea is to have the government pay for higher education for everyone in order to create a more equal opportunity for anyone to go to college, everyone should pay a bit more. We're providing a social good so it doesn't depend on private ability to payso everyone in society should contribute to that. You get a bit less take home pay to use on whatever you want, but you and your kids can go to college without being saddled with debtand you don't have to save for college anymore. You can instead save to start a business or buy a house, or whatever else you want to do. 

           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. The customers are the donors who buy policies. This is the opposite of democracy, where each personrather than each dollaris supposed to get an equal say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. I get what Nate's saying about the AHCA's unpopularity, but the qualification "for Paul Ryan's agenda" is extraneous. Trump has no mandate period. We're in a legitimacy crisis that grows by the day.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd have to go a whole lot further than just the House Freedom Caucus; it's tough to see all but the most moderate of House and Senate Republicans voting for a single-payer plan. 

I recognize that there's a large gulf between Democrats and Republicans on the economic intervention dimension. 

These 2D models based on the DW-nominate score show it really well:

[House](https://twitter.com/bindersab/status/846092122763735042)

[Senate](https://twitter.com/bindersab/status/846092374996652033)

[House w/ Freedom Caucus highlighted](https://twitter.com/bindersab/status/846095467779969024)

The opportunity lies not so much in a new ideological consensus, but in the GOP's practical need to govern.

Republicans have a majority of 237-193, with 5 vacancies, but without the 31 members of the FC, the GOP can't pass legislation if Democrats oppose it as well.  But to keep the legislation palatable to moderate Republicans, the learship can't make the concessions necessary to get the HFC to go along (HFC members are ideological maximalists who won't compromise and take something at the policy midpoint of the overall Republican causus). 

This sets up future scenarios like the epic fail of the AHCA. But if this Congress gets nothing done despite unified control of DC, Republicans are fucked in 2018.

This gives the Democrats leverage if they maintain party loyalty. They can counter-propose something acceptable to their caucus and hold open an offer to negotiate in good faith from that starting position. If the GOP ask for too much, Democrats can credibly threaten to withdraw and leave Republicans with their original conundrum. 

Republicans will then have to choose whether they want to be the do nothing Congress that couldn't govern with a majority (Dems will have a laundry list of policies that the GOP rejected to run on) or they can be a bipartisan achievement Congress. 

Democrats likely gain less in 2018 under the latter scenario. But, in return, they can actually get some policies they favorlike fixing and depoliticizing the ACA, which would make it part of the consensus (like Social Security).

       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It very likely won't pass unless Trump decides to throw the HFC overboard. But it will make it harder to blame Democrats for the effects of Republican sabotage on the ACA and potentially work as a Contract with America style pledge for 2018.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With AHCA defeat, some Democrats see chance to push for universal coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He eats ~~steak~~ shoeleather well-done, with ketchup. 

That's unspeakable and is right up there on the list of his impeachable offenses with treason against the Republic and his emoluments clause violations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. But don't stop there. Vote out everyone with an R next to their name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This circular firing squad and inability to govern is just adding gasoline to the raging dumpster fire.

Republicans' blame game for their failure to pass a health-care bill is in full swing. And  in a sharp contrast from Friday, when he pointed the finger at Democrats  President Trump is turning his fire at his own party.

...

It's a mixed message, to say the least. On Saturday night, Trump took to Twitter to urge people to watch Fox News host Jeanine Pirro, who subsequently proceeded, on her show, to tear into House Speaker Paul D. Ryan (R-Wis.) and demand that he resign. (Both Pirro and Trump's top aides said there was no coordination on the matter.)

On Friday, as Republicans were pulling a bill they just couldn't build a coalition for, Trump didn't even mention his own party. Hey, we could have done this, he told WaPo's Bob Costa as he announced that the Republicans had pulled the bill. But we couldnt get one Democrat vote, not one.

Then, the New York Times Magazine reports Sunday that at one point during the negotiations, Trump told Rep. Charlie Dent (Pa.), the leader of the moderate GOP Tuesday Group caucus: I'm going to blame you if the bill fails. In an interview Sunday on NBC's Meet the Press, Dent did not deny the conversation.

But of all of Trump's finger-pointing, the one aimed at the conservative faction of his party feels the most notable.

Trump's admission that the hard-liners didn't come around suggests that he may be forced to recognize the limits of his dealmaking abilities. He spent the past few weeks courting these conservatives, hosting them at the White House several times. At one point, he even bragged that a lot of the no's had flipped to yes's.  

In the end, he didn't turn enough. Neither Trump nor Republican leaders could win over about a dozen of the 35-40 House Freedom Caucus members. Many of them wanted a repeal of Obamacare  something Republican leaders said they couldn't do under budget rules  or nothing at all.

Establishment Republicans' simmering frustration with the conservative wing of their party is nothing new. The caucus has successfully thwarted budget deals and immigration proposals.

...

But the fact that Republicans' frustration has broken out into open warfare is a new development  and a sign of just how much the party is smarting from their health-care loss.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is giving a lot of mixed messages about whom to blame on health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Subsume](https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/subsume):

:  to include or place within something larger or more comprehensive :  encompass as a subordinate or component element  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been dreading this for a while. How long till Trump's fearmongering rhetoric on the Muslim ban, combined with his attacks on the legitimacy of the judiciary, gets a judge killed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN reporter says Cincinnati police is ruling out terrorism:

https://twitter.com/IvanCNN/status/845929570616328192

Will post if I can get an official statement. 

-----

Local NBC affiliate   AP say police confirm multiple shooters:

https://twitter.com/WLWT/status/845929176846811136

https://twitter.com/AP/status/845937678940033024

----

Cincinnati police feed:

https://twitter.com/CincyPD/status/845934472289751041



      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tend to count those who survive these things as the lucky ones and rank the various shootings by the number killed. But being wounded, and possibly disabled or traumatized for life, is horrible in itself. There has to be a way to do *something* proportional to deal with these periodic mass shootings. We can't just accept this as part of normal life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. I'm so disheartened and sickened by these mass shootings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 people shot, 1 killed at Cincinnati nightclub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, and their other partner, if I recall correctly, was Lee Atwater. Yeah, *that* Lee Atwater, of Willie Horton fame.

It's veritable who's who of Republican fuckery and dirty tricks. 

Stone was heavily involved with the infamous Brooks Brothers Riot that shut down the Florida recount in 2000. But apparently that wasn't enough. Wanted to add some treason to their repertoire.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, going back 70 years to when we used to have World Wars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was subsumed within "indecent," but you're probably right that Trump's horrific crimes against steak warrant being specifically called out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had pretty much the same thought with that headline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardball political operative Roger Stone finds himself on the receiving end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unnecessary. The solution is *more*, not less democracy. The wisdom of the crowd actually got it right and rejected this buffoon. Under one person, one vote, he would have lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News host promoted by Trump calls on Paul Ryan to step dow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't acquiesce to this attack on the integrity of our elections because then, what's to stop it from happening again in 2018 or 2020? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extended remarks by Schiff on the rise of authoritarian populism and the attack on our democracy. Worth a watch over the weekend.

Here's a [Lawfare article adapted from these remarks](https://lawfareblog.com/rise-autocrats). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Rep. Adam SchiffRussian attack on U.S. democracy an unprecedented act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destruction evidence can be very serious for other reasons. You can, of course, bring charges based on the cover up itself. These are often easier to prove. But just as importantly, if destruction is proven, it can be the basis for an evidentiary sanction called an [adverse inference](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adverse_inference). 

Basically, when evidence has been destroyed and is no longer available, the fact finder is permitted to infer from the destruction that the evidence would have established the  damning fact it would have been introduced to prove. 

Also, if the evidence later turns up through data recovery or another source, destruction can establish intent and weigh in favor of a more culpable interpretation when ambiguous evidence is susceptible to multiple possible meanings.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine Trump going before the Democratic caucus to take questions, and not only defending specific policy features of the bill, but asking for their support and suggestions?  


Obama legitimately tried to get Republicans onboard. He made concessions that weakened the bill from what Democrats might have liked to be, only for Republicans (notably Sen. Grassley) to yank the football away and make more demands. Only when it became abundantly clear that they weren't negotiating in good faith did Democrats pass the bill on a party-line vote (without stripping out the concessions). 

There couldn't be a starker difference in the processes that produced the ACA vs. the AHCA. Ultimately, a better process produced a better product. That's a huge part of why the AHCA failed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe. Sure thing. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww. Poor wittle fascist fell down and hurt himself on separation of powers? Did it make a boo boo?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats have been talking about Medicare for all for a while. But there's also been talk of Medicaid for all, including in proposals that were floated to Trump as alternatives to the AHCA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't the first GOP President he's fucked either. Ryan was one of the principal architects of the failed Social Security privatization effort in 2005. That also didn't make it to a vote, and was a big factor in W's 2006 "thumping." Hopefully, 2018 will make that look mild. 

Ryan is not a technocratic policy wonk. He's an Ayn Rand cultist who beats off to the thought of shredding the safety net. We need to defeat him and this ideology again and again so that we can get responsible moderate Republicans who can compromise.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He signed a broad executive order designed to excuse agencies like HHS and the IRS from enforcing its provisions. Like the tax penalty/individual mandate. That could exacerbate adverse selection issues (healthy people not enrolling).
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that the law isn't going anywhere, Democrats should litigate the EO he signed on day 1 and to compel him to enforce the mandate. He and the GOP will own the sabotage, especially since he's made his intentions clear and isn't trying to make things better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like he's already chosen sabotage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Choice on Obamacare: Sabotage or Co-opt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even as he thrust himself and the trappings of his office into selling the health-care bill, Trump peppered his aides again and again with the same concern, usually after watching cable news reports chronicling the setbacks, according to two of his advisers: Is this really a good bill?

In the end, the answer was no  in part because the president himself seemed to doubt it.

...

For Trump, it was never supposed to be this hard. As a real estate mogul on the rise, he wrote Art of the Deal, and as a political candidate, he boasted that nobody could make deals as beautifully as he could. Replacing Obamacare, a Republican bogeyman since the day it was enacted seven years ago, was Trumps first chance to prove that he had the magic touch that he claimed eluded Washington.

But Trumps effort was plagued from the beginning. The bill itself would have violated a number of Trumps campaign promises, driving up premiums for millions of citizens and throwing millions more off health insurance  including many of the working-class voters who gravitated to his call to make America great again. Trump was unsure about the American Health Care Act, though he ultimately dug in for the win, as he put it.

There were other problems, too. Trump never made a real effort to reach out to Democrats, and was unable to pressure enough of his fellow Republicans. He did not speak fluently about bills details and focused his pitch in purely transactional terms. And he failed to appreciate the importance of replacing Obamacare to the Republican base; for the president, it was an obstacle to move past to get to taxes, trade and the rest of his agenda.

Trumps advisers thought he could nudge the bill over the finish line by sheer force of personality. He is the closer, White House press secretary Sean Spicer boasted on Wednesday.

**But by Friday it was clear that the closer could not close.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What a spectacular fail.**

This is what happens when you lack popular support for your policies and don't even try to build it by reaching out to the other side. When we say "Trump has no mandate," this is exactly what that means, in practice. 

Republicans have been the party of "no" for so longand internalized their own backrupt ideology and alternative fact universe to such an extentthat **they are no longer capable of governing, even when they have unified control the federal government**. 

They can't blame Democrats for this, because they can't even hold their own caucus together for their new President's first legislative initiative after he insisted on holding the vote and demanded their support. **Trump said take it or leave it, and they left it. If this were a parliamentary system, this rejection after yesterday's ultimatum would be the equivalent of a no-confidence vote.**

*Pay attention America*: this is what happens when you put these people behind the wheel. Seven years of bloviating, but no substance. 

Time to fire them and put the adults back in charge.

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The closer? The inside story of how Trump tried  and failed  to make a deal on health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's deliberate irony. Except the party that has the House Freedom Caucus and il Douche of Orange were never adults.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American political history suggests otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will try. But it rings hollow, and likely won't work given how accountability works in a Presidential-Congressional system. Dysfunction hurts the President's party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can and will try.  McConnell's law suggests it won't work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some are. Not the HFC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to his statement from the Oval Office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Trump is so full of shit. Democrats have no obligation to support your policy proposalespecially if it's bad policy. You couldn't even get enough of the Republican Party to support it. You have unified control of Washington. Stop pitying yourself and making excuses. It's pathetic.

And remember, with the ACA: you own what you sabotage. You are there and it's your obligation to improve things. That's what it means to govern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What a spectacular fail.**

This is what happens when you lack popular support for your policies and don't even try to build it by reaching out to the other side. When we say "Trump has no mandate," this is exactly what that means, in practice. 

Republicans have been the party of "no" for so longand internalized their own backrupt ideology and alternative fact universe to such an extentthat **they are no longer capable of governing, even when they have unified control the federal government**. 

They can't blame Democrats for this, because they can't even hold their own caucus together for their new President's first legislative initiative after he insisted on holding the vote and demanded their support. **Trump said take it or leave it, and they left it. If this were a parliamentary system, this rejection after yesterday's ultimatum would be the equivalent of a no-confidence vote.**

*Pay attention America*: this is what happens when you put these people behind the wheel. Seven years of bloviating, but no substance. 

Time to fire them and put the adults back in charge.

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've been the party of "no" for so longand internalized their own backrupt ideology and alternative facts to such an extentthat they are *no longer capable of governing*, even when they have unified control the federal government. 

Republicans can't blame Democrats for this, because they can't even hold their own caucus together for their new President's *first legislative initiative* after he insisted on the vote and demanded their support. Trump said take it or leave it,  and they left it. If this were a parliamentary system, this would be the equivalent of a no-confidence vote. 

Pay attention America: this is what happens when you put these people behind the wheel.  A lot of wind, but no substance. Time to fire them and put the adults back in charge. 

---

Edit: 

Here's why Trump's "blame the Democrats" strategy will likely fail.

[President Obama on McConnell's successful hack of the basic accountability mechanism under the American Presidential-Congressional system](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2016/11/28/obama-reckons-with-a-trump-presidency?mbid=social_twitter):

"Some of this is really simple and its the thing that **Mitch McConnell figured out on Day One of my Presidency**, which is **people arent paying that close attention to how Washington works**, he said. They know there are lobbyists, special interests, gridlock; that the powerful have more influence and access than they do. And **if things arent working, if theres gridlock, then the only guy that they actually know is supposed to be in charge and supposed to be helping them is the President.** And so the very deliberate strategy that Mitch **McConnell and the Republican Party** generally employed during the course of my Presidency was effective. What they **understood was that, if you embraced old-fashioned dealing, trading, horse-trading, bipartisan achievement, people feel better. And, if people feel better, then they feel better about the Presidents party, and the Presidents party continues. And, if it feels broken, stuck, and everybody is angry, then that hurts the President or the Presidents party.**"   

I like to call this **McConnell's Law**. 

It can be distilled as:

People who swing and decide elections don't pay as close attention to politics as those who read this sub. They will blame the President and his party when things don't work. The effect is magnified when the President's party controls Congress and when the President is unpopular. The exceptions are few and far between.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a spectacular fail. This is what happens when you lack popular support for your policies and *don't even try to build it* by reaching out to the other side. When we say "Trump has no mandate," this is what that means, in practice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. The opposition has been pretty goodeven if Trump hasn't made it very hard by commiting unforced errors.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if there's provable direct collusion, one way to take it out of the GOP's hands would be to go to federal court to seek to annul the election. If the election is held invalid, a court could order a re-vote. Here are [some re-vote scenarios](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/60yh2f/z/dfahwbv).

The unknown variable is public protest. If the  People take to the streets in Women's March numbers and stay there until our demands are met, we can make the country ungovernable and force Republicans to act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't necessarily have chosen that word either. It's not so much that it's strange, but rather that it's outrageous and unusual in it's insolence. It's become a clich to say that this would be rejected as too implausible if it were a script.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good and comprehensive timeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Long, Twisted, and Bizarre History of the Trump-Russia Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, hence my qualifying "if"  and "would mean." Lawyerspeak.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This bill is a cruel and ugly monstrocity without pork to lubricate its passage. I don't rule out the possibility that some form of it could still pass. So it's not quite yet time to gloat. But man, am I looking forward to the deranged tweetstorm if it does fail.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump the Dealmaker Projects Bravado, but Behind the Scenes, Faces Rare Self-Doubt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they could. If this rule was struck down under the Congressional Review Act, the permanent bar would be a purported consequence. That may be unconstitutional though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. I'm saying that this is what I personally would've advised him to do, in light of the political reality that he started off with an exceptionally weak mandate and desparate need to expand his minority coalition.  He thinks he won a tremendous victory and was robbed of a popular vote win by 3-5 million illegals. But he didn't. His first problem is earning popular support. 

Now, I'd never nominate Gorsuch. But if I did, it would be as my second move, to replace Ginsberg or Kennedy. Likewise, I'm not a populist or nationalist. I wouldn't push protectionism, mass deportations, border walls, or symbolic feelz over realz Muslim bans. But if I *did* want those things, I'd realize that I needed significant political capital to pull them off. The moves I suggested would build that up while dividing the opposition.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [See here](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/614lbp/schiff_new_evidence_shows_possible_trumprussia/dfc11lz). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are distinct and not related in any way. I'm not arguing that they are. Preponderance of the evidence is the standard for establishing civil liability. Probable cause is used in the investigatory and preliminary adjudicatory phases of criminal proceedings. It also potentially comes up with evidentiary exclusion during a criminal trial or appeal. It isn't a burden of proof for the accused's ultimate criminal liability. 

Yet, if you reason these standards through, it's pretty clear that a prosecutor shouldn't seek an indictment or continue to pursue a case where it isn't more likely than notat least in the prosecutor's mind, having considered all the evidence available (including exculpatory evidence)that a crime was committed by the accused. This is not so different than a fact-finder reviewing all the evidence presented by both a plaintiff and defendant during a civil trial, and concluding that the defendant is more likely liable than not. 

Again, I'm talking about logical valence and scope, *not* how prosecutors apply the standard in practice (especially when they're elected officials).      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with any of this. That's why I'm saying that probable cause as an abstract standard is a different thing than what it takes in practice to get a grand jury to indict the proverbial ham sandwich. 

Also, this is why burdens of proof are not expressed as percentages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're roughly congruent, but they're not exactly the same thing and I never said that they were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not advocating for that standard in connection with the death penaltyjust describing it.

Beyond a reasonable doubt means that it's still proper to convict if you haven't excluded every possible doubt, just the reasonable ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Administration Orders Tougher Screening of Visa Applicants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me push back just a bit. I agree that it's fairly easy--probably too easy--for a skilled prosecutor to get an indictment out of a grand jury. 

With that said, I'd take some issue with this:

It is not the task of a grand jury to determine whether someone is guilty, the task is to determine whether the prosecutor can demonstrate that the accused 'might be guilty', and that they're not unfairly being brought to trial by an overzealous prosecutor.

The evidence needed to convict in a Jury Trial is 'beyond a reasonable doubt'. This is much higher quality of evidence than 'probable cause'.

Regardless of whether "might be guilty" is the standard grand juries are *actually* applying, it certainly isn't probable cause. Probable cause is--or at least is supposed to be--a preponderance of evidence that convinces a reasonably prudent person that a crime was probably committed. To put it really crudely, it's being more than 50% certain. "Beyond a reasonable doubt" would be something like 90-95% certain. 

If Schiff is saying that there's *genuine* probable cause here--not just merely enough evidence for a prosecutor to manipulate a grand jury into indicting--it would mean that **the most reasonable interpretation of the evidence available is that there was collusion** (granting that other reasonable possibilities had not yet been excluded).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you sort of have a decent proxy for that. In principle, insurance premiums are supposed to cover risk. So compare the difference in premium subsidies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letter from CBO to Speaker Paul Ryan re: Updated Score for AHCA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. 

Trump blew a huge opportunity. He could've said: it's wrong to play political games with SCOTUS nominees, and renominated Garland. This would not only have disarmed the Democrats and won him moderate support, but it would have set up a powerful argument if there were another vacancy during his termwhich he could fill with anyone he wanted, including Gorsuch. And he'd likely have more goodwill going into his other agenda items, rather than a unified and mobilized Democratic Party. 

Same thing with the Trumpcare/Republicare bill. Trump campaigned on better coverage for less money. He could've outflanked the opposition from the left by proposing basic single-payer with private add-on coverage. He could then have called Obama on his promise to support something cheaper that covered more people. Obama has integrity and would likely support this plan, which would, in turn, free Dems to back it. He could then accomplish a full repeal and replace of the ACA, fulfilling a key campaign promise. The best part: Trumpcare wouldn't be an epithet.

If Trump had done these things, he'd be sitting on 55-60% approval, which would put him in a great position to pursue the rest of his agenda and fortify him against the Russia investigation. Instead, we have this rapidly sinking ship, with no one at the helm. 
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "His name was Merrick Garland." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Republican state Rep. Phil Covarrubias seemed to argue that the use of internment camps was justified.

We keep hearing about how things went down with the Japanese people. For anybody that has never been in the heat of combat, when the **Japanese attacked Pearl Harbor** and all of that was going on, **theres no time to ask questions and find out who's a citizen and whos not**," Covarrubias said. "You don't have that moment in time. You need to regroup. It's easy to sit up here and say this stuff now. But if you're in that moment, it looks a lot different than being able to be in a nice suit and tie."

He continued: *I hear people saying that we need to respect other peoples rights**, and I agree with that, **but what about them respecting our rights and our country and our laws**? Because I'm not hearing that up here.

Later on in the hearing, Covarrubias once again seemed to defend the mass internment of Japanese American citizens by pointing out that the Japanese had attacked Pearl Harbor. That attack, he said, was "what happened prior... that kicked all this off."

"I think we need to look at the Americans that are in fear from the terrorism and the things that weve seen over the last few years especially," Covarrubias said. "Everybody's talking about the immigrants being in fear or the other people being in fear. What about our own people? What about Florida? What about San Bernardino? ... We need to take care of our home here and realize that we have plenty of our own citizens  citizens  that are in fear."

Covarrubias did not immediately return a message left with his office Thursday morning. **His "them vs. our" arguments throughout the hearing appeared to ignore the fact that the majority of the people of Japanese descent forced into internment camps in the 1940s were U.S. citizens.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No time to ask questions: Lawmaker appears to defend use of WWII Japanese internment camps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, Clinton did nowhere close to the same thing. Accepting donations to the Clinton Foundationa highly rated charityis not the same as accepting illicit Russian assistance with *the election itself* in exchange for pro-Putin policies. 

[This fact check puts the whole thing in context](http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/article/2016/jul/07/fact-checking-donations-clinton-foundation/).

Yeah, there's a potential that such donations could create an apparent conflict of interest down the line if Clinton had to make decision adversely affecting Saudi Arabia. Even so, it would be an attenuated conflict, since it wasn't a contribution to Clinton or her campaign, and she did not solicit the donation.

With Putin-Trump affair, on the other hand, the allegation is of an explicit *quid pro quo*, where the Kremlin agrees to release the hacked DNC and Podesta emails to Wikileaks in exchange for Trump weakening the GOP platform on Ukraine, undermining NATO, and other pro-Putin commitmentspossibly even with some campaign funding or other bribes to sweeten the deal. 

This is totally illegal.

[52 U.S. Code  30121](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/52/30121-) (Contributions and donations by foreign nationals) provides:

------------

**(a) Prohibition**

**It shall be unlawful for**

**(1) a foreign national,** ***directly or indirectly,*** **to make**

**(A) a contribution or donation of money or other thing of value, or to make an express or implied promise to make a contribution or donation, in connection with a Federal, State, or local election;**

(B) a contribution or donation to a committee of a political party; or

**(C) an expenditure, independent expenditure, or disbursement for an electioneering communication (within the meaning of section 30104(f)(3) of this title)**; or

**(2) a person to solicit, accept, or receive a contribution or donation described in subparagraph (A) or (B) of paragraph (1) from a foreign national.**

----------


If proven, the allegation of direct collusion with Putin under a *quid pro quo* would be the biggest scandal in American history and would warrant annuling the entire tainted election.

Take a step back and think about what we're talking about here: soliciting or receiving from the Kremlin, in exchange for policies desired by Putin, material assistance in the form of unlawfully hacked information and/or illegal campaign contributions in furtherance of a plan to harm Clinton and aid Trump in an election for President of the United States. The policies desired by Putin allegedly include weakening of NATO, the U.S.'s principal military alliance, and an easing of U.S. sanctions for Putin's invasion of Crimea. 

I can scarcely think of a more serious charge.

The agreement to subvert our election would likely satisfy the "**adherence to the enemy**" element of treason (which could be further inferred from the delivery of pro-Putin policies detrimental to U.S. national security and use of the hacked information knowing that it was unlawfully obtained and disclosed under this illicit deal). Enacting pro-Putin policies and speaking favorably of Putin would likely establish the overt act of "**aid and comfort**". Russia has long been an adversarial power, and the act of subverting our democratic election to promote its objectives and weaken our principal defensive military alliance (and consequently, the U.S.' ability to "resist or to attack [its] enemies") would likely be sufficient to establish **emnity**. So if you had **two witnesses**, you might even be able to convict for treason in the strict [18 U.S.C.  2381](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/2381) sense. *See generally* [*Cramer v. United States*, 325 US 1 (1945)](https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=2809896451252158562 q="18+u.s.c.+2381" hl=en as_sdt=2006).             </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that it hinges on whether Russia can be considered an enemy. But I think there's [a colorable case to be made that subverting the election to benefit Russia could be treason](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/60yh2f/z/dfark64) even if there was no state of war.

The rarity of treason convictions since WWII may not come from the lack of a war. Rather, it likely stems from the relative procedural difficulty of proving treason in light of the two-witness requirement. Why would a prosecutor charge treason when they can obtain a conviction far more easily for something like espionage (as with the Rosenbergs) but still get the death penalty?

The only reason treason could be useful here is that it would make the person convicted ineligible to hold any federal office.

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, Trump is fucking up the governing part so badly that, once we start reaping the fruit of his policies, we'll see a backlash as bad if not worse than the one against George W. Bush. He's making opposition pretty easy. Democrats are in a good position to defeat him politically *without* a magic bullet that removes him from office.

I wouldn't be so dismissive of the scandal and the possibility of direct evidence of collusion emerging. This is actually progressing at an incredible pace relative to past scandals, like Watergate. We'll likely know soon enough.  


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be more political advantage for Democrats in letting Trump ruin the country and riding the backlash to power. But it's not worth it. Power shouldn't be treated as an end in itself. We should always try to make things the best we can right now.

I don't disagree that the Russian interference (and, above all, Comey) had adverse downballot effects that cost Democrats at least the Senate. But if a re-vote or special election is going to happen, even in theory, Republicans have to get something out of it. That something would basically be a chance to put country before party and throw Trump overboard in order to limit the lasting damage to their brand. A momentary loss of power at the Presidential level is not as bad as being permanently known as the "complicity in treason" Party. They'd also get to keep the downballot results of the tainted elections too, as part of the same compromise. 

We have to accept that some of the damage of 2016 is probably irreparable. The is no perfect remedy. The point is only to limit the damage as much as possible.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but there has to be a bone for the Republicans for going along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out [this TED talk by Erica Chenoweth](https://rationalinsurgent.com/2013/11/04/my-talk-at-tedxboulder-civil-resistance-and-the-3-5-rule/), where she pegs the critical threshold at about 3.5% of the population.

Less mobilization might be able to succeed as well. But I am erring on the conservative side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that, if direct collusion were established, Trump voters would continue to support him at the same levels. I mean, what kind of self-professed nationalists tolerate foreign subversion of their election? I think you'd have dead-enders, but the energy would mostly be on the other side. This is why an independent commission like for 9/11 is crucial. If this is what occured, it needs to be made public to the greatest extent possible so that people can examine the evidence and understand the conclusion.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sympathetic to what you're saying about not using the term treason loosely, but I actually think there's a colorable case of treason to be made on this fact pattern.

The Constitution sets the outer limit of what can be considered treason at [Article III, Section 3](https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/articleiii#section3), which provides:

----------

Treason against the United States, shall consist ***only*** in levying war against them, or in adhering to their enemies, giving them aid and comfort. **No person shall be convicted of treason unless on the testimony of two witnesses to the same overt act, or on confession in open court.**

The Congress shall have power to declare the punishment of treason, but no attainder of treason shall work corruption of blood, or forfeiture ***except*** during the life of the person attainted.

----------

The statutory definition of treason, codified at [18 U.S.C. 2381](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/2381) pursuant to Congress's constitutional power to punish treason, defines the offense as:

---

Whoever, owing allegiance to the United States, levies war against them or **adheres to their enemies, giving them aid and comfort within the United States or elsewhere**, is guilty of treason and shall suffer death, or shall be imprisoned not less than five years and fined under this title but not less than $10,000; and shall be incapable of holding any office under the United States.

---

Here, no one levied war against the U.S., so we're left "adherence to the enemy, giving them aid and comfort."

Note that the key phrase "aid and comfort"which appears in both definitionshas a narrow, restrictive meaning. But it doesn't necessarily require Russia to be a wartime enemy. In [*Cramer v. United States*, 325 US 1 (1945)](https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=2809896451252158562 q="18+u.s.c.+2381" hl=en as_sdt=2006), the U.S. Supreme Court explained that:

---

 Treason of adherence to an enemy was old in the law. It consisted of breaking allegiance to one's own king by forming an attachment to his enemy. Its scope was comprehensive, its requirements indeterminate. It might be predicated on intellectual or emotional sympathy with the foe, or merely lack of zeal in the cause of one's own country. That was not the kind of disloyalty the framers thought should constitute treason. They promptly accepted the proposal to restrict it to cases where also there was conduct which was "giving them aid and comfort."

**"Aid and comfort" was defined** by Lord Reading in the Casement trial comprehensively, as it should be, and yet probably with as much precision as the nature of the matter will permit: **". . . an act which strengthens or tends to strengthen the enemies of the King in the conduct of a war against the King, that is in law the giving of aid and comfort"** and **"an act which weakens or tends to weaken the power of the King and of the country to resist or to attack the enemies of the King and the country . . . is . . . giving of aid and comfort."** Lord Reading explained it, as we think one must, in terms of an "act." It is not easy, if indeed possible, to think of a way in which "aid and comfort" can be "given" to an enemy except by some kind of action. Its very nature partakes of a deed or physical activity as opposed to a mental operation.

**Thus the crime of treason consists of two elements: [1] adherence to the enemy; and [2] rendering him aid and comfort.** A citizen intellectually or emotionally may favor the enemy and harbor sympathies or convictions disloyal to this country's policy or interest, but so long as he commits no act of aid and comfort to the enemy, there is no treason. On the other hand, a citizen may take actions which do aid and comfort the enemy  making a speech critical of the government or opposing its measures, profiteering, striking in defense plants or essential work, and the hundred other things which impair our cohesion and diminish our strength  but if there is no adherence to the enemy in this, if there is no intent to betray, there is no treason. (*Numeration and emphasis added*.)

---

From this, it doesn't seem like a state of war is necessarily required, because aid and comfort also encompasses overt acts which "weake[n] or ten[d] to weaken the power of the ... of the country to resist or to attack the enemies of ... the country." 

Subverting an election for the highest federal office likely meets this test if there was an explicit *quid pro quo* to secure illicit Russian campaign assistance (and possibly funding) in exchange for U.S. foreign policies desired by Putinincluding a weakening of NATO, the U.S.'s principal military alliance, and consequent impairment of the U.S.' ability to "resist or to attack [its] enemies."

The agreement to subvert our election would likely satisfy the "**adherence to the enemy**" element of treason (which could be further inferred from the delivery of pro-Putin policies detrimental to U.S. national security and use of the hacked information knowing that it was unlawfully obtained and disclosed under this illicit deal). Enacting pro-Putin policies and speaking favorably of Putin would likely satisfy the overt act of "**aid and comfort**" element. Russia has long been an adversarial power, and the hostile act of subverting our democratic election to promote its objectives and weaken our principal defensive military alliance would likely be sufficient to establish **emnity**. So if you had **two witnesses**, you might even be able to convict for treason in the strict [18 U.S.C.  2381](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/2381) sense. 

Of course, there are easier charges to bring.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To a criminal jury.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the replies to my original post. There is something in the Constitution about succession when there's a dual vacancy. Congress is authorized to make provisions for that scenario. This authority is broad enough to enable a special election. 

I agree that there's no way for Democrats to force oneno more than they can force impeachment without Republican cooperation. But the People can by taking to the streets and demanding a re-vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no common law definition of treason. It's defined in the Constitution and by statute. What I meant was hostilities, since the definition of enemy depends on that. If it's up to the judge, I agree that subverting the election is a hostile act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree all of this requires GOP cooperation. 

The unknown variable is popular protest. If 3-5% of the population were to take to the streets and stay there, the country would become ungovernable. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't necessarily disagree. But do you happen to know how "hostilities" are defined?
Also, are you sure that this definition, as opposed to a common law or plain meaning definition, would control? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No wonder Trump likes it. He has experience with Trump University. Next: Trump Insurance Co.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that complicated actuallyjust politically difficult. 

I think we agree on the basic problem.

Impeachment would be fine if Trump were removed for something he did while in office, or for something that he did before the election that did not affect the election outcome directly. Pence would have a very strong constitutional claim to the Presidency in such a situation if he was not a culpable participant.

But if Trump is removed for collusion with the Kremlin to subvert the election, then Pence would be a product of the same tainted election and thus illegitimate even if he didn't know about the collusion (though he likely would have known). We agree (I think) that running the election again is the way to fix this.

Here are some ways to do that:

-----

1. The least complex is to impeach Pence and Trump (in that order) after amending the Presidential Succession Act (PSA) to require a special election within 90 days of a double vacancy. This would likely need to be done over Trump's veto. After Trump's impeachment, the amended PSA would be triggered. Paul Ryan serves as acting President during the campaign, then the election is held and the new President assumes office. This is totally constitutional and would resolve the legitimacy crisis. Technically, it wouldn't be a do-over, but a special election to fill a vacancy.

2. Another possibility is to wait for the findings of the Congressional committee investigations and file suit to annul the election with the committee reports (and supporting documentation) as evidence. If successful, this would vacate the Presidency and Vice-Presidency and could void any acts that Trump took as President (since the election would be invalid, he would have never have held the office legitimately). If the amended PSA is in place, that would trigger the special election to fill the vacancy. This latter possibility is [discussed at length here](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5tbwm5/intel_community_trump_administration_turning_on/ddlplwc/). Technically, this too would not be a do-over.

3. Alternatively, a federal court could annul the election and directly order a re-vote. This *would* be a do-over in the technical sense because it would be the same election being held again, as opposed to a special election to fill a vacancy. The equitable power exists for a court do this to address a tainted election. But the order would likely have to come from a solid SCOTUS majority to be perceived as legitimate. SCOTUS could order Congress to take a crack at it first under its supervision, but then step in if Congress failed to do so. Trump would likely resist, so it would be important to get Congress onboard with the credible threat of impeachment. Ideally, he and Pence would resign (avoiding the shame) and Ryan would become acting President until the judicially- or legislatively-ordered re-vote took place.

4. A final option would be to just pass a constitutional amendment annuling the 2016 election and ordering a re-vote. There's no question this would be valid, but it would be very difficult to do.            

(I think you skip the primaries and let the parties each do brokered conventions.)

------


For reference, [Article II, Section 1, Clauses 4 and 6](https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/articleii#section1) provide, respectively:

The **Congress may determine the time of choosing the electors, and the day on which they shall give their votes**; which day shall be the same throughout the United States.

and

**In case of the removal of the President from office, or of his death, resignation, or inability to discharge the powers and duties of the said office**, the same shall devolve on the Vice President, and the **Congress may by law provide for the case of removal, death, resignation or inability,** ***both*** **of the President and Vice President**, declaring what officer shall then ***act as President***, and such officer shall act accordingly, **until the disability be removed, or a President shall be elected.**      

This is broad enough to authorize a special election.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Constitution actually doesn't prohibit a special election, [as argued here](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5tbwm5/intel_community_trump_administration_turning_on/ddlplwc) and elsewhere in this thread in response to OP's comment. 

[TL:DR] Just amend the Presidential Succession Act to provide for a special election and then create a dual vacancy by (1) impeaching Pence and Trump in that order, or by (2) judicially annuling the election and vacating both offices.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You correctly identify why this is such a problem. But, respectfully, we *do* know how to deal with this problem as a democracy. It's not to give the second-place finisher a win by disqualification. But it's also not to allow *anyone* (like Pence) to benefit in any way from the tainted election.  **Rather, we annul the election and hold a new one.** 

Voting again would be the logical way to remove the taint of foreign interference and restore legitimacy to the Presidency. Other Western OECD countries--like Austria--[have done this recently](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Austrian_presidential_election,_2016), even in less extreme situations.

In a republic, [the people, collectively, are sovereign](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Popular_sovereignty). As Madison explained in [Federalist 39](http://avalon.law.yale.edu/18th_century/fed39.asp), our "government ... derives all its powers directly or indirectly from the great body of the people, and is administered by persons holding their offices during pleasure, for a limited period, or during good behavior." 

When we hold an election, we invest a portion of our sovereignty in persons whom we elect to hold public offices with various duties and powers. The Presidency is foremost among those. But the powers of the Presidency are derived, ultimately, from the American people (*i.e.*, consent of the governed). Here, the people's free choice may have been thwarted by a coordinated disinformation campaign in which Trump allegedly participated. This taints the election result. 

All a re-vote accomplishes is **measure the will of the People again** (as a way to moot the problems in the earlier measurement).  Since we're not a direct democracy, popular will doesn't get expressed continuously through direct choices about policy, but rather, indirectly through the People's chosen representatives including the President. Those representatives have to be chosen at some point in time. But there's nothing magical about *that particular time*. An election simply gauges who the people want to hold the office for the next term. This is where the common analogies between elections and competitive sports contests break down. The winner of an election gets no prize.  Rather, he (or she) is invested and entrusted with the People's power. This is a distinct honor. But in no way does the office *belong* to the office*holder*.  The People are not bestowing a permanent title on someone. A re-vote thus cannot deprive the winner of an annulled election of anything to which they'd be entitled independent of the People's will, as expressed in an election. 
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a private/incognito tab. Annoying but it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says "*choosing* the electors." So that part is *not* refering to the EC, but the general election. Then you have the part that says "and the day on which they [*i.e., the electors*] shall give their votes," which *is* the EC.

If you read this together with Clause 6, there doesn't seem to be any problem with scheduling a new special election to fill a dual vacancy:

In case of the removal of the President from office, or of his death, resignation, or inability to discharge the powers and duties of the said office, the same shall devolve on the Vice President, and **the Congress may by law provide for the case of removal, death, resignation or inability, both of the President and Vice President, declaring what officer shall then act as President, and such officer shall act accordingly, until the disability be removed, or a President shall be elected.**

Specifically, it doesn't say "until... a President shall *next be regularly* elected," it just says "until... a President shall be elected." That's broad enough to encompass a special election if Congress wants to authorize and schedule one (which it has the power to do under Clause 4). 


   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what he's saying though. Nixon sabotaging LBJ's peace talks and Reagan getting Iran to delay hostage release helped Nixon and Reagan get elected over Humphrey and Carter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he becomes President without a vote of the People, with large scale protests underway, and the basic legitimacy of the election called strongly into doubt, it would be a poisoned chalice.

It's not impossible that he would recognize this himself. 

But, more importantly, it can be demanded of him in order to raise the political cost of his refusal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Constitution authorizes Congress to provide for Presidential succession when there's no President and no VP. Ryan would "act" as President because of the Presidential Succession Act, which can be amended to instead provide for a special election with Ryan (or someone else) acting as a short term caretaker until the election is held.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the VP is fine if the motive for impeachment isn't directly related to the validity of the election itself. But if it was, or if you lose the President and VP, there should be a special election, with people in the line of succession acting as caretakers. The great thing is that the Constitution actually authorizes this.

Article II, Section 1, Clauses 4 and 6 provide:

    The Congress may determine the time of choosing the electors, and the day on which they shall give their votes; which day shall be the same throughout the United States.

and

    In case of the removal of the President from office, or of his death, resignation, or inability to discharge the powers and duties of the said office, the same shall devolve on the Vice President, and the Congress may by law provide for the case of removal, death, resignation or inability, both of the President and Vice President, declaring what officer shall then act as President, and such officer shall act accordingly, until the disability be removed, or a President shall be elected.

Thus, Congress could simply amend the Presidential Succession Act (PSA) to provide for a special election within some set time when the Presidency and Vice-Presidency are vacant, and specifying that the designated federal officer (Speaker Ryan or whomever would follow in the line of succession of the current or amended PSA) would "act" as an interim caretaker President. (*Acting* President Ryan would be finefor a few months at most.) Then you either annul the election judicially or impeach Pence and Trump in that order (or get them to resign). That would create the dual vacancy that would trigger the PSA.

After a short campaign, we hold a new election and the newly elected President serves until the next regularly-scheduled election.

Done.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard because the most plausible ways to do it all will require significant Republican cooperation19 votes in the Senate to convict Pence and Trump on articles of impeachment (assuming 100% Democratic support), 23 votes in the House to pass legislation amending the Presidential Succession Act (more likely 94 since you'd probably have to override Trump's veto).

But in principle it can be doneparticularly if Congress is facing [Tahrir Square on the National Mall](https://youtu.be/ASnaFc3oRQY) every day, with no end in sight.

Doing it without Republican cooperation would require the courts. But even SCOTUS can't enforce its decisions. So that's potentially a more difficult path.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's right. If you show the underlying agreement and *quid pro quo* by an agent coupled with Trump himself delivering the *quo*, that would be highly persuasive. Add in some financial transactions showing money changing hands, and they'd be fucked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it wouldn't. A special election  could be done by amending the Presidential Succession Act. Impeachment could be done by Congress. Annulment could be done judicially. As could a judicially-ordered re-vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we don't have to stand for the robbery.

 If there was coordination with an underlying agreement or understandingnamely, illicit campaign help or funding in exchange for policies benefiting the Kremlinthat's arguably treason. 

Even if not (or there aren't two witnesses), it's still potentially bribery, violation of election laws, conspiracy to commit (or aiding and abetting) computer fraud, as well as fraud on the electorate. Those charges are very serious and considerably easier to prove.

If this holds up, we should not settle for anything less than total annulment of the tainted election and removal of all of its rotten fruit. Only a re-vote or else a special election to fill the dual vacancy of Pence and Trump after impeachment can *even begin* to remedy the wrong and restore political legitimacy.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that comes when the actual substance of the coordination becomes public and is both inherently credible and highly damaging in and of itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actions taken by Trump campaign associates can potentially be imputed to Trump himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super vague, but this is probably what Schiff was referring to. It might also explain Nunes' actions as desperation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying but then I remember that nobody forced him to take the job. He's *literally* a paid shill for the Trump regime. If it *really* bothered him he could resign and write a tell-all book as an insider critic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Busy that day? It's OK. We can reschedule. It's no trouble. No, no, really, we insist. You're the guest of honor. We're flexible and will work around *your* busy schedule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are Black Block anarchists. If they are ideologically-driven, rather than just taking out generalized frustrations on property, they can point to a left-wing intellectual tradition going back to at least the French Revolution. 

So they'd be left, not *alt*-left.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, there's no alt-left. There's simply the left. ShareBlue is a Democrat-alligned site. The left and the Democratic Party aren't the same thingthough there's some overlap. ShareBlue is far from the most left-wing publication around, in any event.

Second, please cite to anything that you contend is factually inaccurate with this specific report so that we can discuss.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it isn't. This is false equivalence. InfoWars pushes wild tinfoil conspiracy theories. Shareblue reports factual information from a *disclosed* partisan viewpoint. For a good part of [our history, newspapers were explicitly partisan institutions](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_American_newspapers). That's why you see some older ones with *Democrat* or *Republican* right in the name.

Here, the information being reported is a video. So you can watch it yourself, draw your own conclusion, and ignore the partisan commentary if you wish. 
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's especially shocking given that they just had Flynn retroactively file disclosure forms *after* he was fired. Oh, and he also failed to sign the ethics pledge.  

So this admitted reliance on paperwork is... problematic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called vetting and due diligence, Spicey.

ALEXANDER: Can you say for certainty that right now, that theres nobody working for this White House that is presently working in the interest of a foreign government?

SPICER: **I can tell you that every form has been filled out**. That 

ALEXANDER: So you trust 

SPICER: Absolutely. Youve got to  people are filling out forms, so to sit here and ask me whether I can vouch for, whatever it is, a few hundred people, that have filled out everything, you know, that would be ridiculous to stand here and suggest that I possibly could.

-----


The administration  which insists on extreme vetting of refugees who already undergo a years-long vetting process  apparently believes they can keep foreign agents out of the White House by believing what people write on forms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're partisan Democrats and admit it. That doesn't mean the *information itself* is inaccurate.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch: Sean Spicer literally cant say no foreign agents are working in White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how it should be. 

The point is, the more authority you give to someone, the more you should be sure they can exercise it properly. 

If standards are too low *now*, then surely we.shouldn't be lowering them *even further*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. That's why the ACLU is filing a lawsuit on her behalf. Here, she's making public allegationswhich she's allowed to do. The CBP officer will have full due process protections, including the requirement that the plaintiff bear the burden of proof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the point of the suit she's filing against the officer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why vetting, credentials and training are important. But recall that Trump is proposing to lower the required qualifications to expedite hiring of his deportation force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't repost the description of the incident here (read victim's account of the alleged abuse at the link). The ACLU is representing her in a suit against the CBP agent.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Border Agent Took My Sister and Me Into a Closet and Sexually Assaulted Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration is asking a federal appeals court to expedite its review of President Donald Trump's revised travel ban executive order.

The Justice Department Wednesday asked the Richmond-based 4th Circuit Court of Appeals to speed up its handling of the federal government's effort to overturn an injunction a Maryland-based judge entered earlier this month, barring Trump from implementing a ban on issuance of visas to citizens of six majority-Muslim countries.

Justice Department attorneys also indicated they plan to ask the appeals court to stay U.S. District Court Judge Theodore Chuang's injunction while the appeal goes forward.

...

A federal judge in Hawaii handling a suit brought by the State of Hawaii issued an even broader injunction against Trump's revised travel ban order, blocking not only the six-country, 90-day visa ban but also a 120-day suspension of refugee admissions from across the globe as well as other provisions.

The Justice Department has not yet filed an appeal in that case, but is expected to. That appeal would go to another appeals court, the San Francisco-based 9th Circuit Court of Appeals.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration moves to expedite travel ban appeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Transcriptio erro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. I must have deleted it by accident while transcribing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only a safer play, but a *huge* job in its own righteven if he has no higher ambitions. U.S. Senator for California representing 40 million people. We need good legislators and he could fulfill that role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

Monday was a breakout moment for Schiff: 

The chair of the House Intelligence Committee, Rep. Devin Nunes (R-Calif.), gave Schiff a generous 15 minutes to make an opening statement in the committee's rare public hearing with FBI Director James B. Comey and National Security Agency chief Mike Rogers.

**Schiff used that time to launch a bold argument of why Democrats are suspicious Trump campaign associates colluded with Russia during the election.** Among the connections Schiff pointed out:

    One of Trump's national security advisers during the campaign, Carter Page, has ties to Russia and has praised its president, Vladimir Putin

    Former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort had been on the payroll for pro-Russian interests in Ukraine.

    Trump officials met with the Russian ambassador to Washington during the Republican National Convention. At that convention, Republicans changed their platform to remove a section that supported giving weapons to Ukraine as it battles Russia for territory.

    Former Trump adviser Roger Stone boasted in a speech that he knew of impending WikiLeaks documents related to Hillary Clinton's campaign before they were published.

    Former national security adviser Michael Flynn and current Attorney General Jeff Sessions would avoid disclosing their conversations with the Russian ambassador during or shortly after the campaign.

After laying that out, Schiff (rhetorically) asked:

    Is it possible that all of these events and reports are completely unrelated and nothing more than an entirely unhappy coincidence? Yes, it is possible. But it is also possible, **maybe more than possible, that they are not coincidental, not disconnected and not unrelated, and that the Russians use the same techniques to corrupt U.S. persons that they employed in Europe and elsewhere?** We simply don't know. Not yet. And we owe it to the country to find out.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. Or maybe he could run for Feinstein's Senate seat if she decides to retire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schiff was actually my representative back when he was a California State Senator and was initially elected to Congress. Does a great job not only in fighting for his constituents, but in keeping them informed. Very glad to see him gain national prominence.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Rep. Adam Schiff, the Democrat fast becoming the face of opposition to President Trum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Safe Spaces for Self-righteously Stupid Humans (SSSSH!) Act.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To troll and humiliate Mitt Romney, who actually did want the job, and publicly prostrated himself before the Orange One for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I hadn't seen that. Any links?

Generally speaking 

Money and assets are highly fungible. If I need and have $100 in non-blood money that I can use or transfer however I want, and I get an infusion of $100 in blood money that I can use for the thing I need $100 for but can't transfer, that frees me up to transfer the non-blood money. That doesn't mean the transferred money isn't tainted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If these are real, Andrea *admitted* that she knew.  Money is fungible, and in any event, she included herself among the "we" who had the money. 

Yet, if she knows in March 2015 that dear ol' dad is, in her own words, a "sick fucking tyrant" without a "legal or moral compass" who knowingly ordered the deaths of people in Ukraine to generate favorable political theater for the regimeand was handsomely compensated for these services with "blood money"then she's on notice when he offers to pay for her extravagant wedding held two months later, in May 2015. 

I credit her self-reflecton, and understand why she might be affraid to make this public (she didn'tit was hackedwhich I don't condone). But *even she* doesn't let herself off the hook so easily. She acknowledges that she keeps showing up and dancing for him, eating the lobster. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's extremely unlikely that he'd act as a check on Trump in a way that the current court can't or wouldn't. And even if he did, we would still get him for all the other issues the SCOTUS decides. If he does get on, this could well be Trump's most lasting and damaging legacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd argue that it gives the IC too much power. If they don't like a candidate/president they can open an investigation (even without merit) to derail an election or appointment. We shouldn't be willing to give law enforcement that much power. Now if an impeachment process were started I'd say wait, but investigation alone shouldn't be enough to hold them up.

I actually [tend to agree](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5ayble/the_fbi_is_trumpland_anticlinton_atmosphere/d9kctvb/), but we've already [crossed that bridge](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5nmxob/hillary_clinton_and_her_team_tried_to_warn_us/dcctqr2/?utm_content=permalink utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage). 

Norms have to be re-established and possibly statutorily codified. But right now, we need every tool at our disposal to contain the damage. The fact that this happened after the refusal to even consider Garland weighs heavily. It's not like a random vacancy. It's a vacancy that was basically stolen, which is only compounded by the taint of illegitimacy surrounding Trump until we get to the bottom of the Russia investigation. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
