<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama, the slide back to Iraq and the power of the Deep State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 04:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 04:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting article about where powers lies in Washington and why America is being pushed into another Iraq war, despite the fact no-one of it's previous wars of the last decade have really been successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama, the slide back to Iraq and the power of the Deep State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 04:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think you missed the point there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden Reveals U.S. Government Plans to Spy for Corporations, Despite Telling the Public Otherwise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 02:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kafka Revisited. Time to End the Scandal of Direct Provision in Ireland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 00:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intrusive thoughts are normal, they only become a problem when we (ocd suffers) over react to them and try and supress them.  I think your hypocondria may have just moved from schizophrenia to OCD, so don't worry.  I've suffered bad trips in the past and they can be very disturbing, not so easy to get over it, it's like a traumatic experience.  For now just focus on relieving your anxiety.  A healthy diet and exercise help and meditation is really the best thing I know for it.  You can find guided meditations online to help you.  Best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 03:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks quite beautiful, but I think a lot of it is the setting.  If it was crammed into Manhattan it wouldn't look that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 01:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some return he's looking for after only investing 22 million a mere 12 years ago. Alan Sugar must be sick as a dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Neville attacks Manchester United over Danny Welbeck sale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 00:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> QPR could be relegated to Conference unless they pay 40m FFP fine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 22:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 17:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he's into the OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Independent bookstores rising: They cant compete with Amazon, and dont have to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally, Wall Street gets put on trial: We can still hold the 0.1 percent responsible for tanking the economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 01:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally, Wall Street gets put on trial: We can still hold the 0.1 percent responsible for tanking the economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 01:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea's 2014 calendar is starting to look a bit out of date - Mr October is Juan Mata (now at Manchester United), Mr November is Fernando Torres (AC Milan), while Mr December is Manchester City's Frank Lampard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 01:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 22:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should watch [the power of nightmares](http://vimeo.com/84414208) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish emigrant sees his childhood home for the first time in 50 years on Google Maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 13:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 22:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with og's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40,000 year old Neanderthal abstract art found in Gibraltar cave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 01:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40,000 year old Neanderthal abstract art found in Gibraltar cave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 01:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40,000 year old Neanderthal abstract art found in Gibraltar cave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 01:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We cant let tech giants, like Facebook and Twitter, control our news values </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 15:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 14:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, man, you could also go explore, do a hike across a mountain, read an Alan Watts book, seek and you shall find and all that.  Go out in search of the person you want to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 03:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FAS in tralee have ayear long video production course, it's supposed to be very good.  St John's in Cork teaches filmmaking, but I've heard mixed reviews about their lectures.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 02:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's up to all of us to find a way to make our lives meaningful to us.  It's different for everyone.  For a while your girlfriend gave your life meaning, but the trouble with that is all your eggs are in one basket and if the relationship ends, as they do, you are left in your current situation.  Ask yourself, what would you like to do with your life if there was no obstacles?  What are you passionate about?  If you have something then set it as a goal and begin working towards making a reality.  If you can't think of anything, aside from getting back with your gf, make it your mission to find out what it is you love in this life.  Go explore, there are millions of things out there to try.  

Challenges are daunting but they can bring out the best in ourselves.  Try to seek out somethings that challenge you, you will get a great feeling of satisfaction from accomplishing something you weren't sure you could do, I think you are missing that in your life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang on in there, things can become very dark at times in this life, but if you keep going and keep trying it always passes.  Everything passes, it's the one constant in this life.  You may be a bit depressed, understandably.  Just try to do something, no matter how small, every day that makes you feel like you're making progress in life.  if you can't afford any therapy, try [7 cups of tea](http://www.7cupsoftea.com/) it's a website with trained listeners, it's free.  

There's a lot ups and downs in life, times when you just don't know how you're going to make through the day, but if you hold on to the belief that things will get better and keep going you'll make it.  To quote Winston Churchill 'when you're going through hell, keep going.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 02:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should post this in /r/changemyview  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 23:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louis Van Gaal - football genius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 16:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next thing the President will reveal he's a leprechaun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Insolvency tsunami on the way in afew years due to rising debts and inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 03:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic collapse on the horizon in just a few years due to debt and inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic collapse on the horizon in just a few years due to debt and inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic collapse on the horizon in just a few years due to debt and inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 02:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Island of Saints and Sadists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 01:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My plea to the people of Israel: Liberate yourselves by liberating Palestine - Archbishop Tutu's letter to Isreal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 01:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way politicians who are proven to be corrupt top the polls in their district in Elections.  Lowry, Pat 'The Stroke' Fahey and others.  What is with that?

Also, the way politicians, particularly ministers, rarely resign when shown to be incompetent or corrupt, eg James Reilly.  They hang on till the bitter end a la Shatter.  In England, they resign almost as soon as they are shown to act improperly, Mandelson resigned twice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Gov. Perry Indicted on Charge of Abuse of Power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 01:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 23:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll hazard a guess at what it could mean.  To dream you are being cheated on by your partner suggest a fear of not living up to the expectations of others.  Grandmothers represent nuturing and wisdom although seeing as you live with yours she obviously a big part of your life so you should ask what does she represent to me.  Shopping can mean trying to acquire the acceptence of others.  You spend too long shopping with your grandmother, so perhaps that suggest you lack self essteem and are trying to find it in the approval of authority figures such as you grandmother.  A car represents how you make progress in your life.  A child represents a part of you that is precious and pure that needs to be nurtured and protected.  So having found you have spent too looking seeking others approval you are determined to move forward as quickly as possible but in the process damage a part of you that is precious and needs to cherished.  So maybe you should focus on nurturing that child within yourself, even if you don't receive much encouragement from those whose approval you seek.  Does that make any sense to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 22:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you think reappointed Dunga as national team coach was a backwards step, he's not going to revive Samba football? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Dawkins: I once tried to commune with God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 23:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exclusive: Liverpool to Launch 20m Bid to Make Prolific Striker Guiseppe Rossi Their Ninth, and Final, Summer Signing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 02:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kolo Toure agrees terms to leave Anfield for Turkish side Trabzonspor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 01:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Authorizes Targeted Airstrikes, Humanitarian Aid In Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 03:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 02:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SuicideWatch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised he's gone to be a number two, might as well admit your career is over.  But he's a big wage bill off Liverpool's books which is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14-year-old girl reunited with her family after being swept away by tsunami 10 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uganda Anti-Gay Law Struck Down by Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 18:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 04:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to quit drinking, I know it sucks but it could save your life.  Your issues haven't gone away, you've just buried them and they're reemerging when you get drunk.  Get some counselling please and check /r/StopSelfHarm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aspirin could dramatically cut cancer risk, according to biggest study yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 02:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marianne Faithfull: My Ex-Boyfriend Killed Jim Morrison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 01:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marianne Faithfull: My Ex-Boyfriend Killed Jim Morrison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 01:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before and after: satellite images of destruction in Gaza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 16:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 05:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I'll get it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 17:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he had a few hellish years playing with Catona.  Things improved when he was with Sheringham but I don't think he ever fully recovered psychologically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 17:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andy Cole.  Signed for Utd in the middle of a goal drought and crumpled under the pressure to succeed at a bigger club.  Eventually recovered to a degree of respectability but never fully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 22:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I've found medication has helped dampen the anxiety quite a bit, you may want to discuss it with your doctor or a psychiatrist.  [This](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) is a link to some guided meditations I do, I mostly do the loving kindness one, it focuses your mind on love instead of fear.  I also learned at zen retreat not to try and battle your ocd but to accept your fears with love and compassion.  Just say 'I accept I fear xyz' it helps you to have a less hostile relationship with what is, after all, part of your own mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 16:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great! Meditation is something I find helps a lot as well, it gives your mind a break.  Also something like running is good.  Do they have you on any medication? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 04:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are performing a mental ritual to try and heal your mind, but it is the thing you need to heal.  Have you seen a psychiatrist about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 04:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't relate to the object of your fear but you are obviously obsessing, please seek a professional assessment of your condition.  There are medications to reduce anxiety and meditation helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 04:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you Lallana is a talented player, but I don't think he's 25 million worth of talented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes: See No Evil, Hear No Evil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes: See No Evil, Hear No Evil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes: See No Evil, Hear No Evil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 03:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinad OConnor Q A  very entertaining. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 22:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 00:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your fear of being gay ocd is a form of pure ocd known as hocd, h standing for homosexuality.   There's no sense to them, you just fear lsoing your identity as a straight man.   I have pure-o too.  I found tonglen meditation is very good for reducing anxiety.  Also, if you can learn to lightly embrace the anxious part of your mind with love and direct the loving kindness meditation of 'may you be happy, may you be well' towards it, that's also very helpful.  I discovered this on a buddhist retreat.  It is counter productive to have a hostile, adversial relationship with your ocd, try to view it and yourself compassionately.  It is a part of your mind, try and love it and forgive it.  Don't engage it with counter arguments etc, the content of your ocd thought is immaterial, it is nonsense, the less you react to it, the less power you will give it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 00:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has also begun to be used to mean inimpressed I've noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 17:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [link](http://www.dailydot.com/politics/israel-gaza-kidnap-false-inaccurate/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 17:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I just looked it up on the book depository, it was 30 bucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 16:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 16:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to have to get this now, you captured my curiosity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 15:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really sad and awful this has happened you.  Remember this person is a bully and their only goal is to cause you pain.  They can taunt you but can't do much else to harm you.  You are not a peadophile or a bad person in any way, you just suffer from a painful mental illness, which they are exploiting for kicks.  It just shows they are the truly damaged and sick party in this.  Keep you head held high, it may be this person becomes another object of fear for you, try to remember they can't really do anything to you except play on your fears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turns out Hamas did not kidnap the three Isreali teenagers after all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 15:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very insightful and in depth article that examines the power and influence of Rupert Murdoch over governments all over the world.  A power based on fear that rarely has to exercised, the threat of it is enough to bring many of the most powerful people in the world to heel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pervasive power of Rupert Murdoch: an extract from Hack Attack by Nick Davies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 21:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 04:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yes it is.  You want to see a therapist, someone who deals with ocd.  Medication helps, meditation helps, exercise helps.  It's a tough struggle but you can lessen the fear and the symptoms, just get as much help as you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Weird, Scary and Ingenious Brain of Maria Bamford </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 04:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fascinating story, always knew their was something up with that transfer, I thought Fergie had gotten greedy and lined his pockets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 21:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Samba football isn't going to return for another generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Video for Cork band Dissolutes, made by local crowd Epic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 23:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes -- Past Abandoned [Rock] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 22:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes -- Past Abandoned [Rock] (3:17) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 22:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 22:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wouldn't Sanchez be likely to score more goals than Giroud, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 20:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you hear the drums, Fernando? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 20:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - Past Abandoned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 17:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - Past Abandoned (new) [3:17] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 17:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - Past Abandoned [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - Past Abandoned [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New music video for Cork band Dissolutes, made by some mates of mine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 16:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 19:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painfully beautiful, images like this make think God is the greatest artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Natural Disasters including storms, floods and heatwaves have increased fivefold since the 1970s, UN finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 16:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Natural Disasters including storms, floods and heatwaves have increased fivefold since the 1970s, UN finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 16:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 02:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ENGLISH CLICHES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 03:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man was clearly a genius, how he doesn't have a hundred caps is beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis Calls Exploitation Of Nature Sin Of Our Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 23:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a horrible game of football, like watching a headache. I'd give up watching it football if it was like this normally. Persistent fouling now a tactic, referee was a disgrace. I hope they lose against Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 21:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we'll have a strong squad next year, but Suarez is irreplaceable.  Look at Spurs without Bale, although I believe we'll spend the money wiser, it's very rare to have a player who can consistently give you the bit of magic to win you games.  We'll miss that next season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 20:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Liverpool supporter I feel very sad, but that's football.  He nearly got us the title last year, I'll remember the good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joan Burton is the new leader of the Labour Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 16:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 00:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's the guy meant to be?  (Forgive my innocence). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 13:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, sounds god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 02:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's good advice, thanks, I needed to hear that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 02:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meditation is good for creating some peace of mind.  Nofap and other such strategies are just making concessions to your ocd.  Every teenage boy watches a lot of porn and jerks off a lot, it's not your fault you have OCD, it just finds a way to make you more and more fearful.  Don't try to fight or negotiate with your fears, just try to think 'this thought makes me fearful and thank ok, I accept my fears.'  You fear what you are not, not what you are.  You, we, all have a problem with obsessive, irrational fear, just accepting that and letting go is helpful to allow your mind to move on to other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 22:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the most perfectly excuted penalty I've ever seen and it seemed to do it so nonchalantly . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 03:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not trash, you are grieving and wounded, you took a little solace in someone who has been close to you.  It's just human, life is messy sometimes, it doesn't always work by the rules we try to impose on it.  Give yourself a little slack.  I would suggest having a frank conversation with Dave, explain you've had some feelings towards him and are feeling confused and guilty and don't want to rush into anything.  See how he feels.  Communication is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laurie Lee's life and work celebrated at centenary event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 00:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laurie Lee's life and work celebrated at centenary event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 23:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *also right about Obamacare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No more fillings as dentists reveal new tooth decay treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 13:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crowd funding effort to erect memorial at Tuam mother and baby home, please support if you can </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 07:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remember the good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 03:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try [these](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) guided meditations on self compassion.  You can learn to yourself and then life again.  I've been where you are (though I suffer from OCD) and I've learned you can get better from times of hopeless and pain.  Try and do one thing, no matter how small, that makes you feel like you're making progress in life.  Treat recovering from depression as your mission now, there will be set backs but don't give up. Or give up but don't give up for long.  Have hope, believe you can get better, there is always a way to healing even if you can't see what that way is at the moment.  Aim for fulfilling your dreams, however big or small they may be.  This will make your life feel meaningful and important to you, people need that.  Never give up, you are much stronger than you realize, you can overcome this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rumour] Liverpool 'to open talks over Firmino transfer' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 03:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 23:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor guy looked suicidal towards the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 01:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffer from ocd but I still related to what you said.  It is like you have an autonomous enemy within your own mind persecuting you.  I was recently at the Buddhist retreat and we practised loving/kindness medition towards the parts of our mind we reject or hate.  Basically you just say to that part of your mind 'may you be happy, may you well' over and over.  It has honestly given me more healing than 15 years of meds and I've reduced the amount of medication I need by about half.  It's about making friends with the parts of your mind you would rather not deal with, it really helps, you can't get rid of those parts of the psyche but if you can develop a less hostile relationship within them, it makes life a lot easier.  I hope this helps, [here](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) is a link to some guided meditations if you want to try it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sepp Blatter does U-turn over allowing video challenges in live play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 15:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rio Airport Workers Strike On Eve Of World Cup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 05:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 05:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the govt has a 90,000 waiting list for people waiting for social housing.  They could use these homes, some they'll own already through NAMA, others they could buy and finish very cheaply, and house people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 02:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are nice houses. How is there a housing crises when they are all these empty houses available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland's Suburban Ghost Towns Are Just. Plain. Creepy. (PHOTOS) (we made front page of the huffpo) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 02:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boyd Barrett: I was born in a mother-and-baby scheme. Im one of the lucky ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 01:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 23:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meditation has been the big thing for me, it creates a place of peace and calm in my mind.  Learning to accept my ocd with love instead of fighting it or trying to destroy it has lessened the conflict in my mind a lot as well. Believing that God unerstands I have ocd (i have a religious aspect to my ocd) and forgives me my ocd thoughts was a big help too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 02:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, you don't know, I thought you were refuting that, I thought that was the point of this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murakami Bingo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 01:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 00:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, can you clarify if the children were buried in a septic tank or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 23:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it's 4 times the normal infant fatality rate at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 20:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest skeptism, scientific skepticism. Not disingenious skeptism driven by the propaganda of greed and vested interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Call for inquiry into deaths at Tuam mother-and-baby home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 03:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't we all, brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German museum exhibits Van Gogh's ear replica grown from relative's cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German museum exhibits Van Gogh's ear replica grown from relative's cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 20:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 19:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally different from what I imagined when I read the title. There's something very lovely and very Irish about the image, thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 19:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is something I'm realizing myself and I think the guy in the post needs to learn.  It's not really her he needs to get over, it's the idealized person he believed her to be but she never was.  He allowed himself to invest all his dreams of what he could find in a partner in her, inevitably the relationship fell apart when reality intruded on the dream, but really the relationship could never work, because he never loved her for who she really was, only for who he wanted her to be.  He still misses the dream, because it was perfect, and for a moment he really believed he had it and it was beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 19:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's obviously got her own issues with self worth and depression, I would guess she's one of those girls who feeds off male attention make her feel like she's worthwhile, is addicted to the first rush of infatuation, keeps moving from one guy to the next.  Wounded people latch onto each other and then can't help themselves from wounding each other more.  I've been there man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 18:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't he have a gun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 01:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for much longer I suspect.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do Real get all the money?  I heard they were about 600 million in debt, but it never stops them dropping another 100mill in the market every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 01:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad Arsenal won the FA cup this year, just so journalists will stop repeating '8 years without a trophy' every time they mention them.  Like they're the only club to have ever gone through a lean spell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A poem by Michelangelo on painting the Sistine Chapel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 16:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful, you should try submitting it to /r/EarthPorn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roy Keane rules out Celtic job to stay with Republic of Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 16:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roy Keane rules out Celtic job to stay with Republic of Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 15:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nasa to test 'saucer' for Mars mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 02:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meriam Ibrahim 'to be freed' from death row in Sudan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 20:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida 6-year-old kills grandfather with AK-47 left unattended by boys uncle at family picnic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 22:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Pakistani man demanding justice after his pregnant wife was murdered outside Lahore's high court this week admitted on Thursday to strangling his first wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 21:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 00:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, when Torres was with us he was a fantastic striker.  I don't know what happened him at Chelsea, I read a rumour about a degenerative knee injury, certainly he didn't seem to have the same pace anymore, and he was sold at the last minute of the transfer window so Chelsea weren't able to do a thorough medical.  We did pretty well oput of the deal, got Saurez and Carroll for the price, although the last one was ill judged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Bruton: Ireland faces 10 more years of austerity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 20:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De Niro's TV tribute to his gay dad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 16:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De Niro's TV tribute to his gay dad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 16:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De Niro's TV tribute to his gay dad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More austerity is like putting an anorexic on a diet and expecting the body to strengthen - David MacWilliams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 15:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass grave of up to 800 dead babies exposed in County Galway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 17:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ross Barkley to Liverpool is a rumour I heard, mightn't lead to city wide peace though/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you have a congress with below 10% approval and at the same time an 80% encumbency rate you know democracy is failing.  People hate these guys but they keep getting re-elected, that's not democracy, that's a rigged game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Taoiseach met Maurice McCabe while canvassing in Mullingar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 01:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Controversial Answer To America's Heroin Surge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This world cup should be boycotted if it goes ahead in Qatar, the idea of multimillionaire running around in stadiums in which slaves died building is beyond horrible. Please take a moment to sign a petition calling for better treatment for workers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 21:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 15:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really good, man, I like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio Can't Name A Single Source Behind His Climate Denialism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 21:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio Can't Name A Single Source Behind His Climate Denialism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 21:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio Can't Name A Single Source Behind His Climate Denialism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 21:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio Can't Name A Single Source Behind His Climate Denialism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 21:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 18:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt the lads would be too happy with the music they put to it, totally inapropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 20:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.thebestshop.eu/shop/6-electronic-cigarettes-starter-kits) is a good site to get stuff on.  You need two batteries, a charger, an atomiser and some spare wicks.  Then you need some liquid, strongest strength is 24ml and they come in all different flavours.  I went from 25g of tobacco a day to nada on them, they've changed my life, much healthier and much, much cheaper.  Starting out to get all the kit is expensive but after that maintainence is quite cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 02:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had OCD for 15 years.  Recently I went on a buddhist retreat and I found the meditation practices very healing for me.  One which is good for dealing with suffering is [Tong Len](http://www.dharmaseed.org/talks/?search=tong+len+guided+meditation sort=-rec_date page_items=10), there are few guided meditations in that link.  Aso practicing loving kindness is great for creating a sense of love in the mind which relieves some of the fear and can rewire the mind somewhat with practise, here's a [link](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) to some.  Also Jeffrey Schwartz's book [Brain Lock](http://www.amazon.com/Brain-Lock-Yourself-Obsessive-Compulsive-Behavior/dp/0060987111) is a good book for your wife to read, he is the foremost psychiatrist on ocd and the book gives strategies to deal with it and lessen it's impact.  Cognitive behaviour therapy is supposed to be very good though I haven't tried it myself.  Good luck with this, it's a very difficult illness to cope with, your wife is lucky you care enough to research it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Editors Dont Belong in Courtrooms, and Cecily McMillan Doesnt Belong in Prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Editors Dont Belong in Courtrooms, and Cecily McMillan Doesnt Belong in Prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angelina Jolie to put acting on back burner for directing and UN work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking forward to Alan Shatter resuming his literary career, for those who missed it, here's some of his art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 13:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used be terrible with names, but I've gotten pretty good with them.  After I've been introduced to someone, once I've a moment to myself, I look at or picture their face and repeat their name three times in my head.  I've always been good with faces, I just try and tie a name to the face now.  It works for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama to make climate change case to weather forecasters - US president signs up for eight interviews with TV meteorologists to defend landmark climate impacts report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 12:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barack Obama to make climate change case to weather forecasters - US president signs up for eight interviews with TV meteorologists to defend landmark climate impacts report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 12:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 01:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Rodgers could allow for Gerrard's slip in the Chelsea game, changed everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 in 25 inmates sentenced to death are likely innocent, report finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 02:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 02:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to begin to view yourself with compassion, as if you were a dear friend of yours.  'We deserve compassion not because we are perfect but because we are suffering.'  I recently did a course on self compassion at a zen centre in Ireland.  It was very helpful in teaching me to accept myself flaws and all.  [Here's](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) a link to some guided meditations we were sent as a follow up.  It's a difficult journey to make to learn to love yourself but it is one of the most rewarding possible.  Pm me if you want to talk more about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 03:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was probably one of two footed on the shins tackles, Joey was good at those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liverpool rumoured to be in pole position to sign Lallana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 03:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir Alex Ferguson has thrown his weight behind Ryan Giggs to become the next manager of Manchester United </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 01:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 00:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating story of competeing desires for revenge and forgiveness.  I think the aspect of dreams of her son add an extra supernatural element to an already dramatic story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian mother who spared her son's killer: 'Vengeance has left my heart' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 00:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian mother who spared her son's killer: 'Vengeance has left my heart' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 00:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 16:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scratch a republican and you will find a racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, namaste! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Liverpool fan in Kosovo who vowed not to have his hair cut until Liverpool won the Premier League is so confident that the Reds will win the title that he has booked himself in to the hairdressers for the first time in 11 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 01:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your answer.  I'm confused between my Catholic beliefs and my interest in Buddhism and my conventional 'must strive and thrive' western mentality.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liverpool set to hand Anfield boss Brendan Rodgers 60m transfer war chest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 01:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 00:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting.  Can I ask, do you feel your life has a purpose or is it all trivial?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steven Soderbergh has done a 1hr 50min cut of Heaven's Gate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 23:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United players were telling friends that Moyes would be sacked before the 2-0 defeat away to Everton on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 03:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven of Paths Irish collection you need to see </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 17:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 03:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess quitting alcohol.  I had always been a heavy drinker, but after my sister died, I was grieving her and self medicating ocd and depression.  I drank every night for two years, I felt I was circling the drain in life, I felt I was powerless to stop it.  I didn't see drinking as part of the problem, I saw alcohol as helping me deal with my problems.  Denial, I guess, classic case.  I asked God to send me inspiration and always saw myself as a seeker of truth, but I didn't want to face the truth I was an alcoholic.  The day it finally dawned on me I got down on my knees and vowed not to drink for three years.  That was about 8 1/2 years ago, I haven't drank since.  It saved my life, saved my soul.  My life has been improving ever since, my depression's gone and my ocd has nearly gone.  If I'd known being sober was so much better than drinking I would have given up sooner.  Sometimes your crutch can become a ball and chain.  I thank God for saving me, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steven Gerrard - This may be my one shot at title glory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 00:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean FitzPatrick found not guilty at Anglo trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 18:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banksy artwork Mobile Lovers could raise 100,000 for Bristol youth club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 03:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Road to Chaos: Iraq is in danger of breaking apart, 2,500 dead since beginning of the year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 01:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are in great danger: Ex-banker details how mega-banks destroyed America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 01:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
