<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In space, no one can hear you cheech. 



PS. What if our first encounter was with alien police and earth as a planet gets charged with possession and trafficking? (7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 15:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Puerto Recon" sounds like knock-off Tom Clancy game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean would the excuse that im a good person be taken as a valid reason for not reporting a crime? Of course not, i would be labeled complicit in the crime by not reporting it when i had the chance. So why do the cops get to use that as an excuse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 21:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Increasing lean muscle mass increases resting metabolism at all times, exercise itself increases resting metabolism for the next 48 hours or so after (depending on the exercise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 21:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im pretty sure its 3500 cal = 1lb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 18:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point actually, we have seen evidence of some of the standards certain feminists want or at least what their opposed to (Sarkeesian, the Bayonetta backlash, GTA Vs banning etc) and seeing that rhetoric i can understand where the experiments coming from. However, whos to say if Galbrush was written and portrayed in the same way Guybrush was (and from what i hear monkey island is considered good game) it wouldnt be recieved well by female gamers as a whole. Its an interesting discussion honestly. 

So what do you think contributes to the lack of female protagonists? Do you feel there is a lack?  Do you think there is a lack of well written characters in general as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact, a snake (or dragon) depicted as eating its own tail is called an "Ouroborus" and is often a symbol of self-relflexivity, or constant reinventing of self. 


Source: http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ouroboros </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 15:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe today square-kun sempai will notice me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 17:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus who is that honestly going to sway? Maybe im wrong but i cant see someone neutral coming to the poll and going "im not sure whos right here but yes is a friendlier colour so ill press that one". On the other hand 40000+ people think Gta makes people hate women so maybe im too generous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 17:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listened to the creators of South Park talk about how much difficulty they had with the MPAA with regards to their independent movie "Orgasmo". Apparently when you submit a cut of your movie the MPAA can rate it whatever they want but they cant tell you why they rated it that way (or what to cut to get a lower rating), "because then they would be a censorship organization" (the words Matt and Trey). So in Orgasmos case it got an NC-17, and the solution the MPAA gave Matt and Trey was to send in more cuts, but since this was before South Park, it wasnt monetarily feasible for them. They eventually got the rating they wanted but couldnt believe the stuff they could leave in and the stuff they needed to cut, apparently its super arbitrary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did add first-person, which by all accounts that ive heard, does make it more visceral and brutal. But i doubt they knew that so it seems oppurtunistic to me. They just went for the big fish even if it isnt any different (content wise) from last year. GTA is just too much of an easy and gigantic target (no pun intended) to not go after it, everyone already associates GTA with violence and stuff your grandma wont like so they barely have to argue to the moral panic crowd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 15:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya "the fittest" doesnt mean the most physically strong it means the fittest to the environment, whatever is better suited to its environment will survive, however that may manifest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 16:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bans on talking about it in the beginning is what caused me to find out everything i can about it. I knew nothing until they told me i cant talk about it. I mean how naive do you have to be to think that banning a topic will do anything but cause people to fervently try to learn about said topic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 03:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would watch the adventures of a crime fighting otter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 18:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All hail the god of patriarchy, may you keep our mysogyny pure and our boners oppressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 01:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm as a 151-kin its really gross for me to hear people making fun of the original pokemon, please limit your hate to the rest of the pokedex and leave proud pocs (pokemon of color) alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 17:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has "Do Right" tatooed on his wrist. It was a phrase that our highschool football coach would always say and is some pretty simple yet solid advice. So sometimes its not a bad tattoo idea if it means a lot to you, but it still seems pretty unimaginative.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 14:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You monster! Those girls will never amount to anything because of that! Just like how beyonce never became anything after being called bossy. Oh... wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White hetero-patriarchy holding me down

A cis filled society, men holding the crown

And when i freebleed on the freeway i fear for my own safety 

So lets just teach men to stop. 

And bring it back to the patriarchy, the cis patriarchy

Everyones down for the white cis patriarchy 

- Quiet Mysogyny - Smashing the Patriarchy




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Rape' doesnt hurt anyone but the 'rapist' because their victim will label them a monster and ruin their social life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 18:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! How does she even justify that as an excuse? Its on her to arrive on time. This in itself could be grounds for not paying in full and shes saying it as if it should absolve her...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just in; Best Award Award Awarded Award for Best Award Award. More at 11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 00:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nothin says charm like an armored car

Taking the clone-farm tards to the arms bazaar"

Citronella - Aesop Rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 02:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found an article for you. The baby died a day later in his fathers arms. It didnt say how the fathers doing. This is so terrible, that man must be devestated :(

Source: http://www.fox10phoenix.com/story/27379288/father-sings-blackbird-to-dying-newborn-son-after-wifes-unexpected-death-video  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 18:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reek must remember his name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should know, in case youre new here, that jokes are not the point of this sub. In fact theyre against the rules and may lead to a ban. Just a heads up for why you are being downvoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 18:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Its bleeding well

Its bigger than a breadbox

It corrodes my leaky finance

Ill take my seat atop the brooklyn bridge 

With a coke and a bag of chips 

To watch a thousand lemmings plummet

Just because the first one slipped" 

(Nine to fiver anthem, Aesop Rock) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 19:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Politician" should never have been turned into a career option in my opinion, it should be something closer to a civic duty. But i dont know shit so make of that what you will. It just seems that having your life and success hinge on an election creates some major conflicts of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really are the queens of narrative, it would be impressive if it wasnt so infuriating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 17:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Im a woman trapped in a womans body! Can you not see how confusing this is for me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 18:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not even a theory its Newtons third law of motion and it applies  to all natural forces such as gravity. It isnt some grand philosophical theory to explain/justify human behaviour. It simply means that if something is struck with x amount of force the object that struck it will recieve an equal and opposite amount of force in return. I hate when these people bastardize things theyve heard in passing, especially scientific things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 18:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the fact that i actually got a little flash of anger when i read her name is testament to how effectively she was written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 18:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "These 2000 year-old, Ancient Greek, marble mammories are believed to be the work of Alexandros of Antioch" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 17:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Case-in-point: Dashcon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 00:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PO-TA-TO

PO-TA-TO

PO-TA-TO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 16:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Rock the vote or else im gonna stick a knife through your eye" - Sean "diddy" Combs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 00:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A sting operation is generally when police go undercover as criminals to gather evidence about criminal operations (usually drugs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 14:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse me? Us botani-kin are a proud people and by being "inb4" us u are literally speaking over us and erasing our identity


I am a proud hermaphrodite, trans-genic, aromatic, budding flower, slowly breaking down the planttreearchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 20:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This the funniest campaign because they're saying being called bossy discourages girls from being leaders and to show this they use a bunch of really successful women who claim to have been called bossy when they were kids ...which proves that being called bossy didn't hold them back... It's the same kind of doublespeak we see on tumblr "Women are powerful independent and free, but are totally helpless in the face of criticism, dissenting opinion and some shapeless structure that dictates their every move (patriarchy)!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 20:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really not a contest  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 21:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get that from? I said pot was easier to get than booze and smokes, not that smokes and booze are hard to get.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 21:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another little fact was that the photographer was explicitly told  not to touch any locals at all by the team who was providing aide. The chance of him passing on a virus that the locals had never been exposed too was really high. So he couldnt do anything to help directly without the risk of making things worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 20:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like grapes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 20:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people always use that as a comeback? I see it every time someone gets called out for not getting a joke and I don't get it, do they think humor is objective?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 16:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Theres no women in this class, its so sexist", "these guys want more women in this class, its so sexist", theres no winning is there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya it honestly feels more sexist to protect womens feelings rather than simply letting them defend themselves. To me it just seems to come from a need to protect women from everything and anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did Batman Begins at like 190lbs went down to 130lbs for The Machinist and then went up to 220lbs for The Dark Knight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 20:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i mean he did technically witness the murder as he was committing it, but your point still stands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 19:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "S-silly whitey onii-chan, it's not like i made this b-log for y-you or anything" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 01:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant they track the computers in the cop car? Maybe i just saw it on tv or something, but i thought that was a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 00:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I understand where you're coming from but when i talk about forgiveness I don't mean everyone says sorry, and goes on happily, i really mean accepting the past as it is and trying as best as u can to move on. Forgiveness might not be best word for it, but i honestly don't know what else to call it. 

  I don't know your situation, and im not saying i do, but in my case my dad doesn't feel bad, doesn't show remorse and probably believes that me and my mom are the actual problem. We don't talk or have a relationship but i've done my best to forgive him, for my own sake, and regardless of what he feels to be reality. It's very hard to live for the now when you have one foot in the past waiting for things to change or waiting for an apology that may never come (thats my own personal experience, im not saying thats what you're doing)

Basically my point is, what's done is done, but you can choose how to go on from now, so whatever you choose best of luck man, and I hope you come to terms with this (whatever that means for you) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 21:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right? 2nd largest country in the world and it has a smaller population than California, but whatever thats more land for us eh? aha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 21:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, my stepfather is a good guy and we get along great, so ya it gets better. Forgive as best you can and move on seems to be my motto atm aha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 21:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats actually higher than the population of Canada by about 3-4 million </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 21:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pretty shitty relationship with my dad (emotional/verbal abuse mostly) and seeing people with good relationships can feel pretty alien at times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its also a pretty big conflict of interest on top of that. I mean can you really trust anyone in that situation to not tell the story that paints their intentions or motivations in the best light possible? Even if he remembers it perfectly, I still think the natural inclination to cover your ass is incentive enough to change some details (especially if there's a family involved) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 23:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to take it a step further: Gawker raped me. How did a website rape me you ask? Well they did and they should have to prove they didn't, because rape is not a crime that people are capable of lying about. So i demand an apology from Gawker lest they admit their guilt by its absence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 23:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, no harm no foul i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 21:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My comment doesn't say fat is unhealthy, it says theres a point at which it isn't hurting your health but may hinder further progress and a point where it actually damages it. I mean I literally say that 20 - 30 lbs of extra weight is no big deal at the end of my comment, please read what i say before correcting me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 20:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ToJpKHYKkoA

This is certainly my favorite Gordan Ramsey moment. In case you don't want to watch it, he does a show where he teaches prison inmates to cook, and he challenges one to an onion cutting contest, the inmate wins and Gordon offers him a job when he gets out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's certainly a point where having excess weight doesn't help your health and a point where it actually hurts it. But you're right having 20-30 extra lbs isn't really a big deal depending on your height/age/gender etc. *especially if you eat right and exercise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 18:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think i remember reading a study (which means take this with a bucket of salt) that had a bunch of different people witness the same person commit a robbery. When questioned the people gave wildly varying descriptions of the perpetrator, there wasn't a consensus on even what race, age, height, or gender the criminal was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 18:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that people have a hard time coming to terms with that, it's understandable that they would, but it leads to an interesting place where death can be both humorous and/or entertaining (video games, movies), and somber and/or revered within the same culture. Just an observation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 21:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant make jokes about things you support? Im not saying go be a dick to gay people but can you seriously not support something and joke about it at the same time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 17:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just looked it up, it can apparently be spelled with or without the first "O". Which is just classic of cishet white males, they must have made English spelling so confusing so that slaves would have a harder time learning to read or write
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 19:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey did you just summon a bunch of monsters?" 

"Yah, so?"


"That's against the rules"


"Screw the rules, I have green hair!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 18:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any sources for that last statistic? Everything else you said is bang on and i couldnt agree more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 16:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valar dohaeris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 18:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya its a vaccine, not an amputation, how surprised can you honestly be that the doctor wants to give you vaccine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 01:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trigger Warning, it can be just a word but it can also be something like topics, or concepts (Eg Suicide, slurs etc).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 18:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what is the rest of feminism doing in the mean time? This comment pops up every time feminism is brought up and i would honestly like to know what theyre getting done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 16:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 - 20 lbs is the rule of thumb from what I hear. Perhaps your friend wasn't eating well or exercising on top of that, or maybe your judgement of her weight is off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 08:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Multiple Sclerosis](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiple_sclerosis) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 18:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always see that attitude when prison rape is brought up. Is this how we want to run our society? Criminal behavior makes you sub-human and thus makes it right to subject you to any matter of crime including rape and murder?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya If anything the fact that they're conducting raids based on the testimony of someone they caught committing crimes just shows how nonsensical the whole process is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 18:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but most arguments that life begins at conception are religious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 14:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same could be said about Hitler, he was still an asshole regardless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 01:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't misunderstand me, say whatever you want, discussion is a good thing. It's just a 2-way street, my disagreeing with your statement is not me saying you can't have input, it's simply the other half of discussion. Perhaps I wrote more harshly than I should have. I still think it was a redundant point, but I honestly wasn't trying to attack you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 00:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does someone always have to say one of these "Well not every X does Y" statements? Honestly I think most people can figure out that that not all of any group has the exact same mindset or behaves in the exact same way. It's just a redundant statement at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 23:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 19:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya apparently all domestic abuse is committed by asexual ghosts. Obviously the only logical course of action is to build proton packs and get bustin'. #BustAllGhosts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 04:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 04:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "An eye for an eye makes the whole world a better place" - Gandhi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it possible to be a misogynist and hate men?

Yep, but it's called misanthropy, the hatred of humans in general. I'd say it's more apt than misogyny, because he did hate both, perhaps not equally, but he clearly disliked humanity and human sexuality overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 03:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im fairly certain under federal law pot and crack are both schedule 1 whereas cocaine is only schedule 2, IE pot is as harmful and has as little medical value as crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly not sure if prison will help or hinder him at this point. Essentially my thinking is that since he's basically a child, prison would just surround him with the type of people he's already (mistakenly) looking up to; other killers and criminals. Prison certainly isn't a walk in the park, but I have to wonder if putting him with these people would have the opposite effect of teaching him a lesson and would instead just cement him into the life of being a criminal. However, there's also the severity of the crime and the necessity of some form of punishment that has to be factored in. But if it's at the cost of creating another career criminal then whats the point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 21:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, presenting yourself and your movement as hostile, irrational, and exclusive is the best way to garner support in the masses. Also alienating half the worlds population couldn't hurt as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 18:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuke it from orbit, It's the only way to be sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 18:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the informative response! Didn't know there was a UK equivalent to Affirmative Action, unfortunately there is. And i'm sorry but "Baa Baa Rainbow Sheep" just does not flow as lyrically well as "Baa Baa Black Sheep", it's alliteration, plus black sheep actually exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 17:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind getting started? I've never heard of this before and before I google it I wouldn't mind a first hand account. Again if you're willing aha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
