<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6932</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-Redditors of Reddit, what part of Reddit culture would you like explained to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm crying" awh, she sounds like she's having so much fun! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm no longer just a bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my SO and I decide to make the most of our little break from each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I couldn't get into Hogwarts and then my plumbing apprenticeship fell through but I'm still trying to be optimistic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW shits on the floor above the bathroom and for some reason we're looking down to see it but just ignore that part </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I jerked off early today but I meet a girl at a bar that wants to come home with me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone asks me to describe what Honey Nut Cheerios look and taste like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I've just come out of the closet and have no idea how gay bars work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone asks my advice on how to keep security from discovering their hidden marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I have a profanity exam and my friend asks me what grade I think I got </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I work border control and I catch someone sneaking in a lot of Monday Brew from Scotland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I see a fish's gills and they remind me of something important that I have to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone wired the focus knob to my seat back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I live in Australia and it's almost winter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friends and I go to our friend's speech but there are way more than just the twelve of us there watching him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone accuses me of being a shill for Big Aluminium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 14:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For some people, sandals are fetish wear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 08:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW it's the first sunny day of my vacation but it still rains all day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 18:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student describes how she became a Clinton plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm not a huge fan of Kurt Cobain but my friend will just not shut up about him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm trying to remember Right Hand Rule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm trying to remember how the Right Hand Rule works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I install a GFCI outlet and it works correctly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you feel like you should have done by now, but haven't for some reason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know how to do subassemblies? I can't figure out how to create new ones in this update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Micro-transactions are underrated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 19:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm the newborn child of a guy who like plain Jane kind of women but my dad can't spell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 08:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm watching porn while my roommate is out and then I realize my roommate is is actually just taking a nap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm North Korea's best spy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a really shitty extra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 07:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the broadcast crew won't stop switching camera feeds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 07:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a scrotum and it's even remotely warm outside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 05:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my anti-dandruff shampoo doesn't work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 05:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm at a steakhouse but I don't understand how steak works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone tells me my eyes don't close when I wink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm demoing a sex robot and it's just finished the foreplay routine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a really douchey robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my partner admits that they have a thing for watersports but I'm not okay with it at all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW it's time to have an intervention with my friend about his checkers addiction but he's so far gone I have to disguise myself as a checkerboard to approach him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I don't thank mr skeletal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I learn that the scoreboard is ticklish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 00:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I try to sneak out after a one night stand with OP's mom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my hat is a little too heavy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 01:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend doesn't know how to use a roundabout in England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 01:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I visit Australia and they've managed to combine a gun with a boomerang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 01:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most of my engineering education is not doing math, it's what math I can ignore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see a /r/physicslecturethoughts.

Also I should probably pay more attention in class. Otherwise I might do too much math than I need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the news comes out that Tidal is not doing well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I think that fighting fire with fire actually works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm an accountant for strippers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I really love fulfilling stereotypes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a clock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie's net worth is NOT $330k </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 09:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I learn that moderate conservatives like karate masters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I try to assemble your mom's bedframe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 03:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm into really alternative energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 03:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Lucius Fox and I have to rework my designs after Batman comes out as gay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 03:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my neighbor is having a really swanky party but I'm really tired after a shift in the coal mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW there are a lot of hoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I see that "Savage" is cool again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone asks me where I would put my doubloons if I didn't have pockets or bags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW when I'm cleaning off after a very successful bukakke scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I underestimate my opponent because I don't know that he's telekinetic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my boobs are too warm but then uncovering one makes it too cold so I give up and raise the temperature with my gesture-controlled thermostat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 23:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's amazing that this Jenkins guy is still employed, given how much stuff he seems to have fucked up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 23:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JDM bros are just automotive weaboos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I realize I upvoted a repost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I develop a formula to unshittify shitty tumblr gifs but then I realize that it will only be used by Vine stars and I hate Vine stars on principle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW Brutus hires a witch to turn me into a small bird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm trying to do my prayers but someone has hypnotized me into thinking that there's an earthquake happening and that I'm a duck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 17:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my roommate won't stop hosting raves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 17:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW it is exactly the perfect weather for a long-sleeve shirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 17:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW Frank, my Asian developer friend, needs his illustration license renewed so he can complete his vacuum-based masterpiece game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 03:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I have serious daddy issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm one of Sir Mix-a-Lot's bitches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a lizard person and my tailor did a bad job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend can't read English and he asks me what a 'trough' is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone asks me what they get if they make a sauce base that doesn't contain fat or flour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the guy talking to me says he has blond hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 18:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone tells me I should go back in time to protect my younger self from the dangers of selling meth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 15:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I find a woman who is accepting of my identity as an A-10 Thunderbolt II </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 06:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I wake up after a one night with someone I met at a T1000 pride parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I order a Coke and the waiter asks if Pepsi is okay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 23:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm having a tricky birth and I decide to use centrifugal force to help it along </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 23:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [House of Cards] Producers had Scalia killed to make the real world even more like the show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoilers ahead, as usual:

ICO, the terrorist organization seizing territory in the Middle East is clearly the show's version of ISIS the terrorist organization seizing territory in the Middle East. Petrov, President of the Russian Federation is clearly Putin, President of the Russian Federation. Clearly the writers of the show like it when the show's complications line up with those of reality.

So let's look at what happened in Season 3: the loss of a senior member of the Supreme Court. Jacobs, of course, retired because he knew he had Alzheimer's disease. This leaves a space on the bench during just before the election, something we have currently. But this happened in the show without any such counterpart in the real world, so the producers realized that in order to keep their complications in line with those of reality, a senior Justice had to leave.

Ruth Bader Ginsburg was the obvious choice, as she is the oldest current member of the Supreme Court and there has been some pressure for her to retire. But a liberal justice leaving the court would be much more complicated than a conservative justice, since a conservative justice's replacement can be fairly moderate which is easier than Ginsburg's replacement would be. So in order to allow the plot to move forward but still be reasonably correct, it would have to be a conservative justice in the real world.

Roberts is chief justice, so he's obviously out. Alito was nominated by W, so he's too new. That leaves Thomas, Kennedy, and Scalia. Thomas is, let's face it, not known for his wit and sharpness like Jacobs, so we're down to Kennedy and Scalia. Kennedy is more controversial than Scalia; yes Scalia is outspoken and witty, but he's consistent while Kennedy is a little more unpredictable. Kennedy isn't particularly conservative, so his replacement would be difficult just like Ginsburg's.

So it's Scalia. He's sharp like Jacobs, old like Jacobs, and has health issues like Jacobs (not the same issues, but issues nonetheless). We don't know how Jacobs leaned politically, but we know he was liked and respected by people on both sides of the aisle. And while Scalia was deeply conservative he was also well liked and respected.

So the producers offed Scalia. It wouldn't be that hard to make it look natural; he's old and fat and has a heart condition. And they get the biggest circus they could ever want. I'm not saying that it's canon yet, but nothing says it isn't possible and quite a lot of things say it is. Just something to think about.

TL;DR: The title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm trying to teach my kid to tie his shoes and he's an idiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I visit an outpost for an organization that helps closeted homosexuals and I've finished my work but they think they still need my help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I catch someone making a low quality gif </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm the star of Air Bud: Judgement Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 07:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone asks me which way my head is leaning and I'm stupid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 04:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I really hate Spongebob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 04:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm practicing the signal to summon one of my clone soldiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 16:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the receptionist doesn't understand that I need to schedule a rap battle with her boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 09:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm interviewing for a job writing math textbooks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 09:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm X but I'm tired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 09:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend doesn't know who N. Armstrong, B. Aldrin, M. Collins, P. Conrad, A. Bean, D. Gordon, J. Lovell, J. Swigert, F. Haise, A. Shepard, E. Mitchell, S. Roosa, D. Scott, J. Irwin, A. Worden, J. Young, C. Duke, K. Mattingly, E. Cernan, H. Schmitt, and R. Evans are and I can't spell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 09:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW Ami, my very tall girlfriend, is about to go on stage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 08:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend Crazy has an incredible voice and he doesn't understand why people phone him instead of texting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 08:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW a small black hole suddenly appears in front of me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 08:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend is a brass monkey and it's really cold outside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 08:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm on a really low-carb diet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 17:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the cure for paralysis is only 75% effective but I'm still pretty psyched about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 22:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I watch the RNC debate and I realize that Trump is talking more sense than the other four </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 04:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW he doesn't understand that "Netflix and chill" isn't literal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 22:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What songs are best played so loud that it hurts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OFFICIAL /R/FOUNTAINPENIS STYLE GUIDE: OXFORD COMMA IS MANDATORY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 03:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you don't want to, because who really cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMPORTANT: SATURDAY SHARK FIN SOUP DINNER POSTPONED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 03:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friends and I try three-way docking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 00:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my invisible car doesn't quite work when it's cold outside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 00:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a turbine and my friend is a fan and someone asks if we could be a perpetual motion machine if we tried </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ORW the seat warmers work way too well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my change machine isn't working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I don't see my boyfriend's ejaculation even though he told me it was about to happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my ring allows me to use my fingers to create time loops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend asks if I remember the spell to make my words appear in front of me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Chibuihem Amalaha justifying my position on homosexuality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm an immigrant in a bar and my buddy tells me not to go after a hot chick because she's xenophobic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 20:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I came here just to upvote Comcast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 04:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I see someone has just bombed the National Captioning Insitute's headquarters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my plan to stop my arch-nemesis' licorice factory is working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I think I've lost my sense of smell because I can't smell my normally fragrant knuckles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend and I spent years building enough muscle to force the magnets in our hands to touch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 13:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm in a lift and need to inform everybody to stay clear while I descend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 10:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a liar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 10:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And now I'll sticky that link because I forgot that you can only do that to self posts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 00:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://roosterteeth.com/post/51200515

I'm having way too much fun with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RT tweeted this and to be honest I'm mostly posting it because I'm way too pleased with myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 00:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW people are hating on my Hawkeye cosplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone tells me that a good mime should never talk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 21:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I install a dimmer switch in my eyebrows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 21:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my patient wants me to remove my mask during his surgury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 21:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Welsh and I start to hit puberty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 09:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm asked if tumblr gifs are any good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 07:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend doesn't know how to fix the synchronization on his old TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 06:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a very elaborate but still very shitty timer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 09:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I don't know what causes my brother's seizures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 09:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a train driving instructor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 09:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I learn that cameramen are attracted to sadness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 04:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I work out a lot and my friend doesn't understand why I'm not swole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my deafness is cured but I'm still not great at spoken English </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a donut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a penis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm delegating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a lizard person's tailor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 06:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend gets flattened and needs CPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 06:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I open the Ark of the Covenant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 06:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my neck contracts unevenly when it cools down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 06:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 08:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW people are talking about how terrible their student debt is but I was lucky enough to have a family that paid for nearly all of my tuition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my kid has can only count to one and wants to know how to get to eight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I manage to sneak a selfie stick onto a roller coaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I fuck up my tortellini and my boss keeps complaining about it but won't shut up and let me fix it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Stephen Hawking and I get a perm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a horse and someone asks me what we should do for dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I finally give a fuck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my coworkers exploit my fear of animation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the waiter brings a really good dish past and the nose on the front of my face is actually aesthetic and my real nose is on the back of my head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Italian and I watch something that wasn't recorded beforehand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW, after years of practice, I figure out how to smile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm dyslexic but that hasn't stopped me from making incredibly intricate diagrams of insects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW someone says they hate Pointillism as an art style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm having an argument about video games and the guy I'm arguing with loses his composure and tells me that frame rates don't matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The guy trying way too hard to be normal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 06:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I didn't realize how much Bruce Willis hates poptarts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 23:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I see that I've spent three years on Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 09:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I get reincarnated and to be honest it isn't brilliant but at least it's a step up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I need to get in my sidecar but I forgot that I don't have a sidecar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I have a kid after a one night stand with an Australian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW a friend of mine takes a role advertising a new line of hair straighteners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I see /r/sweden and /r/de conspiring to take over Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 20:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the couch starts talking shit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 05:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW she sends nudes but they're too hot to handle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW a tiny rainbow peacock farts right in my face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I change my mind about being born </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 04:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW somehow have the winning lotto ticket, but I accidentally eat it, but then when it comes out it's intact, but they won't take it if there's any trace of feces on it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 06:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my friend asks who Oedipus was </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 06:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I see this gif </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 23:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I want to try out my giant chrome cigar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 06:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 18:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 18:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Oscar the Grouch and my mobile home idea turns out to be really popular </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Oscar the Grouch and I decide to build a mobile home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 04:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 04:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I can't afford to lose the poop lottery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 00:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone in the porn industry is probably kicking themselves for not thinking of the name "RealD". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 07:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I take drumrolls very seriously </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 07:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The wrapper looks like it says "Obama Mama" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 03:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you get when you put a tiny umbrella in a supercar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Lambortini. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW it's opposite day and I need the cameraman to start panning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British currency has an emblem regardless of arrangement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 05:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] How much ass does the average toilet seat actually get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 23:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I go back in time but I forgot to bring a gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 19:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm an alien cowboy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I find turbulence entertaining </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 05:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I work for FedEx and it's nearly Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 05:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm a giant robot centipede from hell and I drop my contact lense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 05:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
