<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7770</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 00:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm well I think when my therapist diagnosed me with clinical depression I was clinically depressed. As for the the bleach,  it burned my throat for a weak.  The thing was that I was throwing up uncontrollably...  I still had to go to the emergency room...  It was class crazy experience because I just turned 18 when it happened and like they took me to a mental hospital full of grown ups...  I learned a lot in my week stay there. As for using my depression and suicide attempt as a way to get attention,  me and my ex girlfriend where doing great ... My depression didn't arise because of her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I confess that life is a bitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 18:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So where should I start? My life has taken a huge down fall in the past year. A year from.  Today I was dating what I thought would be the love of life, although I'm just 18 i feel like she's the only girl who will ever have loved me...
My life started spiraling out of control after February where I drank bleach until I passed out and realized that I had depression. Because of my suicide attempt and depression I missed a lot of school days and lost many friends including my bestfriend (let's name him narf) . Despite all of that I tried to keep my head high and try to overcome my depression. My ex girlfriend at the time was the only thing I had. As the year continued I felt that my depression was affecting her and I decided to break up with her, after that she was my best friend and my only friend she would come visit me on my down days and give me kisses...  Fast forward to a few month ago she tells me she doesn't love me and has feelings for my bestfriend (narf). I feel betrayed, lonely and helpless.  I really don't have any friends anymore. And when I try talking to someone they never reply to my messages.. She told me that doesn't see herself going out with me ever again....  It's hard to move on...  The nightmares of them being together just haunt me. Valentines will suck and life is a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 17:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol goodluck breaking even  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 04:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to get paid 7.25... When I started to make 9 an house I stated to pay for premium porn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 05:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend going to target online and buy target shirts there,  they even have target baseball tees,  sweaters, and cardigans!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 01:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow dude I'm sorry to hear that. Yeah,  it's not fun being depressed. It caused me and my first long term relationship to break.... It especially sucks because I'm 18 and everyone around me is in love atm..  As for your depression we gotta work through it man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
