<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never been mainstream here, to be fair. Hell, when there was a law institutinalizing that women could vote there were a big bunch of *women* protesting against it; on the overall, there's one thing Terpers are unfortunately right about some places from Latin America: the amount of traditionalist (on the mysoginistic sense of the word) women here is unusually high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to leave a small point here: I know it's not only an American thing. I see it everyday here and I'm not exactly what you'd call someone from the States :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny to read that, 'cause here it's the other way around when it comes to "libtard families/rightist kid": the most common set is right leaning families with a liberal kid suffering around that. I personally can fit into that description if you take the general position of my aunts and such, although I wouldn't call myself liberal (I'd say I'm more of *"can we just be hoomans and act as such"* line of thought, and my grandmother had a similar view... though she was pretty harsh with words, but eh, she was considered "out of her mind" back then if you take into consideration that she was born on 1934).

Either way, it's odd how different it is; while here a good 3/4 will boo you and call you a ton of names if you show a different view about gender roles (including, that woman who was punched in the face recently was being accused here and comments of the "she must have done something to deserve that, she's at guilt for that", "save that video/gif, it's not everyday we see equality about men and women" were thrown around like the most common thing in the world... and when a guy called the man who punched her a coward, everyone went to "call him out" on that and said it was "equality" to let her go through that) and such, where these guys live is the other way around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cellphone battery died, sorry.

'M not from the US either, and my country isn't on the "main targets" list. In fact, people are making memes out of the situation instead of worrying here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why "neomasculinity" is on rise and how did we end up this way? :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legit Question - part 2: Where did the sudden "change" come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As some of you probably saw before (and being fair, it appeared on News on both the Left and Right), on recent years more men started to agree on the "housewife + sole breadwinner husband" mentality along with the lines of "feeling emasculated by [thing]" appearing more. I mean, the studies shown on the News tend to show a sudden modification on the "criteria" cited (ie 1980-2000 there was a drop on the mentality mentioned along with a "broader" sense of masculinity when it came down to what was neutral/seen as not important to a "manly being", but then a sudden raise on 2000-2010ies and quick general changes), but still, where does that come from?

I've seen people pointing out that the "rise of the Right" brought that, but if it's rising and bringing these things along, where did this *rise* come from and why? Also, why inferiority complex went on a high again considering how the same people cited above started to feel intimidated by "independent women"?



Sidenote: by "masculinity" there I meant the general concept of Western nations, although some noticeable changes happened on the East too. Unfortunately, I cannot talk much about the East as I'm not exactly there nor see much about them generally speaking, but if you want to bring me a light about the East, too, I'll happily accept. ~The more you know~, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm legit laughing my ass off at this title.

SOMEONE PLS MAKE A MEME OUT OF IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been laughing at this comment for more than 3 minutes straight and I'm feeling dumb af for that, but bloody hell if it wasn't worth the laugh :'D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's simply breaking eye contact slowly when you do"

I know. That's also why I'd feel bothered considering that it was a complete stranger.

EDIT to add a few more stuff: my family and close friends don't have the "staring at you to show they're interested" kind of tactic. It's more of a "look at you a few times here and there between something else" because it can get *extremely* awkward. And to have me not feeling awkward over something like that, you'd have to live with me pretty much since I was born, so yeah, the only person that doesn't get me freaking out if they do that is *my mother*. I'm not exactly what you'd call common in that regard, I admit, but a freaky past and an entire life on the a dangerous and biggest city of your country (with over 10 million inhabitants) can do that.

Also, if a fucker I just met few minutes ago started to touch me, I'd probably back the fuck off and find a route to run away. If there's one thing I feel extremely bothered by, that'd be strangers touching me. Long story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticky eyes

That "technique" just would make me feel dirty, bothered and prone to hiding from whoever was giving me that look... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to prove this guy's point wrong: mine will only come up by the end of the month, ya fuckin' crabby-assed bastard :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to let you know, they probably won't answer.

No, not because "oh, you won the argument"; that's because it grows tiring to discuss/argue with a TRPer. 

You probably also find it tiring to discuss with us anyway.

EDIT: oh, wait, they did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but my head hurts even more when it simply "floats around" with no true meaning behind.

Even if that meaning is pointless and shitty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was as good as he put, wouldn't everyone, including men, want to be a house-something instead of working? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to love the comment I made because of these replies, y'all bloody geniuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. Which is also why I just felt like "WHERE THE FUCK DID YOUR COHESIVE THOUGHTS GO?" considering that he saw crying as unmanly during that transition... but eh, he "altered" history a buch of times to fit his views, so don't feel amazed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ey, sorry for the wait, it'll probably be a long reply (even though I can't remember every single detail) so I left it for later.

Right at the beginning of the relationship he actually felt happy that I wanted to work and all, but during his transition he tried to force the idea on me that I *needed* to be a housewife because "if you happen to have kids, they'll need a parent and your husband has to work". I mean, why does it need to be *me*? Also, personal experience here: one of my professors had a child recently; the first 6 months his wife took care of the kid. Now he's doing that so she'll be able to work on her common timing and while he's away she takes care of the kid as she finished the work for the day. It's just organization, not "ah, you'll have to give up your childhood dream because of children". I even blatantly told him that if there's one thing I wanted since I was 4, that'd be working. And now that I began, I can say for sure that I enjoy that. A lot. I probably was born to be an angry working class lass :v

Ah, and he did try to convince me to let my hair grow again. Not on an obvious manner, but by "boasting" a lot about it and "negging" around my actual cut (messy short cut. Nicknamed by a friendo of mine as "Liam Gallagher's SOTSOG cut", LOL). I didn't realize the negging at first... until he blurted out that I "didn't look very feminine". Then I just said I didn't care.

He'd often ask for full body pictures (not nudes because I left it obvious right from the beginning that I didn't send these because I didn't trust the internet) while he himself wouldn't send many of these. In a way, I like to think he was just shy around that, but I still have this gut feeling that he felt like it was a chore I *had* to do, so this point is not a "100% proven" one.

He'd boast about masculinity *a lot*. He'd often say the Romans and Greek (Athens) had the true perception around masculinity and that the "new one was lost". That point also went to the second part about the "women feeling entitled to what men had" and the first one: he saw working women as "huge turn offs" and as "trying to be men" (which, for him, meant that they were neglecting their true nature and "turning into monkeys"), that those who didn't have children were neglecting their true nature of "nurturers"... ehh long list you'll get tired of reading. To him, society started to fall after the Roman Empire fell, but boasted around the "castes" of Middle Age.

Anyway, as a final point 'cause I can't remember more for now (but if I do, I'll add on an EDIT), he'd also try to convince me to sexual stuff that were huge "no"s to me for a long time already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> singing in forests

I don't think singing on the Amazon rainforest is a good idea :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today on Our Daily "Women Don't Suffer Violence" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Biomedicine student was hit by a glass bottle during a party here. *On her genitalia*. She wasn't even alone when it happened.

And *SURPRISE*, it was a man who hit her...

I know, NAMALT, but seriously, this is getting out of hand on my country already...

EDIT: Oh, and I forgot to mention: a man also killed his girlfriend and commited suicide right after also today and it ended up on the news.

The "reality show" that's currently happening right now also removed one of its competitors because he hit his then-girlfriend this week.

A woman also suffered *violence* on a party last Sunday because she refused a guy who hit on her. He called her "slut" because of her clothings in front of the policemen.

And the police is also investigating a possible rape that happened on a spa recently.

I can even provide links to the news if you don't believe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. Just pointing out that here it's fortunately not a "only highschool thing" :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Awkward chads still get laid"

So, uh, what's your excuse to be incel again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here it's more of a 50/50 thing to both men and women: some want to share while others would rather have their partner paying for everything/they themselves paying for everything. There are also some (like my brother and his girlfriend) who do the share based on who is financially better at the moment, so... it's not even a "highschool" thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When I was what I think is myself and act like I was being gentle and then suddenly would flip, becoming a sadistic bloody asshat-wearing twatty fuckwit"

So you were mentally torturing her. 

*Psycho Killer plays on the background* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legit Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, since I ended my last relationship I've been wondering what my partner could've meant by that and still didn't get to a complete conclusion.

On one of our talks (which later became an argument, but that's not important) when he was transitioning to Terp-mode, he said he liked the fact that I'd like to share the restaurant bills and such instead of letting him pay for everything 'cause he surely met lots of women who didn't, calling that fact by "bad side of princess culture".

He said the bad side of "princess culture" was "women thinking they were entitled to everything men had" (making them pay for everything along with other stuff I later asked that proved his transition *and thus ended up in an argument*, but I'll keep the details because it still leaves me pretty amazed in a not-so-good-way that someone would think this way), so... what the fuck would be the "good side" according to this mindset? Yeah, I get the "delicate weak beings" part, but I believe there's more than that, so... halp pls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you "took" the underline here, but I didn't exactly apply it to every TRPer. Also, "Study on *A* TRPer", not exactly a study on the whole bunch; thing is, he's similar to the worst ones often shown here, or the ones that don't act that way but deeply believe they should turn to this side, you know?

Also, yeah, the worst ones *do* advocate for it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, we're together on that. I felt like Orwell was just saying the obvious we all already imagined at least once, and I didn't find anything that kept me going on the book. Couldn't finish it; not because it felt heavy, but because it felt like an extremely weak read to me.

EDIT: I went by the "it's a good book, read it!" people and actually became extremely disappointed. On the other hand, I'd suggest *We* from Zamyatin; this one was also a suggestion of this kind from a friend of mine (only one of the group who read that, everyone else went to 1984) and I agreed it felt more complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU FORGOT TO SCREECH

BEHOLD, THIS DEMON IS TOO STRONG TO STILL BE UP AFTER HOLY WATER AND NOT SCREECH IN PAIN ('CAUSE YOU KNOW, ADALT: ALL DEMONS ARE LIKE THAT)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illuminati Jewish satanic cult

Wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah. Especially because there are a lot of men from the baby boom and a few years later that weren't exactly what you'd call great at taking care of their children and *actually acting like a human being* instead of forcing themselves to not do certain things in fear of being seen as a(n) homosexual/gay/wanker/pooftah/whatever synonymous word related to that. My father was born on the actual baby boom era, close to its end, and back then it was usual of families here have 5-8 children (in fact, his family was him, his twin brother, two other brothers and an older sister)... and surprise surprise: his father thought his only service was working and getting money to the family. One thing his father/my grandpa differed from him, though: grandpa didn't try to pose off as "man of the house" (ie "I OWN THIS SHIT AND YOU BETTER OBEY ME", but eh, grandma was an angry Italian with an abnormal strength to a 1,40-something m tall person as well, so it'd probably be a fight) and actually incentivated his wife to get a college degree (it was her dream since childhood). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BEST MOMENT TO HAVE THIS BOT COMING BY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
