<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2527</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It runs pretty well for me. I used to play it on medium graphics on my laptop that had intel i3M and intel HD graphics 4000
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I meant EU maintaince time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I can't remember them from the beta. But that was a while ago.

I would like this type of cloaks. Kinda like traveling gear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, isn't nearly as effective as cup or two as coffee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 man zergs in cyro with everyone wearing capes would be really bad for fps. Doesn't the Breton Hero (from the trailer) costume have cape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maby as a light or medium shoulder pieces. Probably too hard to make well but I can dream can I? My rogue *needs* this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I had one wish to ZoS, it would be add cloaks like this to the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh since most people work 9-5 or 8-4 in europe, it makes sense to take the servers down during the morning. If the maintaince had gone according to plan, it would have been ready after people get from work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leveling happens pretty much by questing which is alot of fun. Mostly the quests are very well written. Then there are 4-man dungeons and solo delves which can be done at any level. PvP can be done from level 10 foward and it is only in Cyrodiil. There is a server for players who are under lvl 50 (max level).

12-man raids are mainly end game stuff. Thats where most PvE players get their gear. EU population is good imo. There is one mega server so no several servers. 

Crafting is lot of fun imo, easy to do on the side. You mostly gather mats in the world like mining, flower and pelts from mobs. Also you need to "research" traits which allow you to craft more powerfull gear sets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reminds me of this](https://www.reddit.com/r/elderscrollsonline/comments/4tvhhi/damn_lizards_amiright/?utm_content=comments utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ESO runs pretty great on lower ed pc's. I used to play it with my laptop that had 4gb ram, intel i3M and intel graphics HD4000. I wasn't really able to do raids or PvP because of fps but things like questing around and 4-man dungeons worked nicely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I go back in time 3 years? Beta was exactly this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That episode was great. I also really like Blair, I'm still waiting for my "Thick and refreshing" flair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into mobas for bit more serious team play (League of Legends, Dota 2, Smite) there also more fun shooters like Team Fortress 2 and Overload. And from mmorpg's I could recommend Path of Exile and Guild Wars 2. 

If you're interested in strategy games you might want to look for Civ V during sales. You can get  it under 10. Very fun game to play with friend/s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need dating websites. I have a tank so that gets me all the ladies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to say that I value you as a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mainbar is Fragments, Crushing shock, velicious curse, bound aegis, inner light

Second is Blockade of storms, liquid lighting, Mages wrath, Harness magica and bound aegis

I get around 20k-25k single target dps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish ZoS would do more to prevent things like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bangkorai public dungeon would be good place to do this, alot of imperials and it is fairly fast to clear them with AoE (It took me like 5-8 seconds to wipe 2 groups with my cp350 mag sorc)

This is going to become handy when I need money for homestead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using gold sellers/selling gold is a quick way to get yourself banned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His build can probably be found in www.alcasthq.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to try and simplify it a bit. There is alot of going on there, I see the ZMZ but it took me a while to see the skull(?) Also it is very hard to make out in smaller scale.

Otherwise it looks nice. A tattoo shop comes to mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we live in age of social media sharing, the person might have been filming it to post facebook/twitter/instagram/snapchat/whatever as some kind of challenge or just to show off how to get eggs from chickens. 

Or they found it first and then re-entered the coop while filming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 13:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fun fact, all [turtle color cats](https://c1.staticflickr.com/4/3688/13199110364_2f09912899_b.jpg) are female. Also (almost) all cats born deaf are white </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this doesn't break rule 9. 

This trailer is just great show of the progress they have made. I love this type of fan works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyblivion new trailer looks amazing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In CSGO bullshittery part 2, who makes the "killing bungalow" and "lvl 3 mage" jokes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Geralt of Rivia has left the library. Geralt of Rivia has been saved" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY WARDEN, FALLEN ON ANY SWORDS LATELY?

SAYING WE SHOULDN'T HELP THE DUNMER.. AS IF NORD WOULD EVER TURN DOWN A FIGHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A) Yes I do

B) No I sure don't

X) What are you asking me for?

Y) Sarcastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because to you don't like the lineup doesn't mean that it's shit or that zedd doesn't care for civil rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This style of illustration would be pretty hard to draw by hand, especially the shading. But it is very possible the artist drew this over a photo or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really adds to the game's replay value! And I did enjoy Roches path, he is very well written character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Gonna give it a try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that Saskia was such a small character on the Roche path. I really liked her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this style but I have no idea how to achieve it. This looks alot like they were done out of photographs but I kinda doubt this was drawn by hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are this type of illustrated images called? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> supercalifragilisticexpialidocious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know, the dude laughing does make this video funnier. But not exactly by this subs standards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 10:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you going to fit titles on that cover? Also you header might need some work, it was pretty much the last thing I noticed and IMO it should be the first because it's the name of the magazine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also liked Unity. It was bit of fresh air to old musty series that AC has become </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it wasn't Quenya. Quenya was based on Finnish which is very different language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swedish is like singing, Norwegian is like singing with potato in your mouth and Danish is like drunk deaf person singing with hot potato in his mouth. Or at least according to Swedish people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like either artist but man those replys were great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was around 7, I thought our cat had a tick in his fur but it turned out to be his nipple. I was not the smartest kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping it to be more flashy and bigger with scarves and stuff like how they look in most Morrowind fanart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I thought it was the Morag Tong symbol. I hope that add house armors in the games. I would love some Redoran or Telvanni robes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medium armour is great! I'm not really a fan of the light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was easier than the skeletons to me, I actually beat the Asylum demon on my first try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not the first boss, the first boss are the three fucking skeletons at the gravestones. Fuck those assholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I also really liked the robe design in morrowind 

The expanded bonemold armor mod for Skyrim is great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know yet, this was one of the ESO Morrowind screenshots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEDIA]This armor looks amazing, what dunmer style should have been </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If thinking what to do and organizing is helping you then do that. You just need to cry your eyes out first and scream into a pillow and punch a punchingbag and what ever helps you. Then it's easier to start actually thinking logically. 

I hope you have someone to talk to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me they looked more like mercenarys than slaves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well think about it how all morrowind players get PTSD when you charge into battle with your Cliffracer screaming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope eso's Morrowind questline will begin in Seyda Neen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh crap, I need to reboot morrowind today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I played Skyrim  Oblivion  Morrowind

And I think morrowind is the best rpg out of these three (most immersive IMO) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never knew Lion King was based on Hamlet. Then again, I've actually seen/read any versions of Hamlet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this a while after I got my hd598's and was listening to a song that had "knock on wood" sound in the middle of the song and I ran to the door 3 times and no one was there before I realized it was in the song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sooooo good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad ACLU is taking action, people with green cards should be let in to the country no matter what their country of origin is. Do they really fear that people with green cards are terrorists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yen actually references that in Skellige if you have beard she asks why did you suddenly decide to grow it out and then says she likes it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope this is not going to be dragons. We don't need dragons in this game. The embers make think this might be Vvardenfell teaser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was fast! Yeah I wonder if there is bigger/more active subreddit for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subreddit where you can link a song or a tv show or a movie you like and other redditors will link similiar ones or something they think you might like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is so scottish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I usually don't discuss religion in reddit but sure I could expand a bit.

I think that the idea of god or some other divine power can't be proven or disproven. When you look at the size of the universe and how infinitely small the chances are of earth exisisting in this exact spot with the exact properties so that life can thrive and evolve on the surface of our planet, I think it would be foolish to completely deny the possibility of some higher power. 

EDIT: A word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think religion is a wonderful thing. The fact that someone can find comfort in the idea of afterlife or god/s in hard times in their lives and that idea pushes you to be better person and be friendly and nice to everyone is just wonderful. Religion can be a beautiful thing if you let it be. As long as you can look for the deeper meaning and metaphors in the texts instead of taking them literally as 100% truths

Sure it can be bad too but what can I say, I'm an optimist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, I hate it when people shit on other peoples religions. I'm pretty much an atheist but I respect other peoples religious beliefs (as long as they aren't too extreme, i.e flat earthers)

EDIT: Well I'm not exactly and atheist, more like agnostic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definetly not! Apple has great graphic image and it makes it look very professional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gives it kinda "apple" like look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how it's simple and still carries out the meaning very well, even without the text. Not big fan of the typography. Even though I'm big fan of slim fonts, I think that is a trend that won't last too long and in a logo something more **bold** would work better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What an amazingly useful zooming feature (I hope this counts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that if you're a dunmer and ask about your race she says something like "Are you looking to be praised" or something like that IIRC

I play the game very similiar to you. I don't really roleplay, but all 3 of my characters (2 dunmers and an argonian) are very different and has backstories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finland. Putting sweet things on bread is pretty rare here, some people use Nutella but I don't get that either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toast with peanutbutter and jam. Like what the hell, that sounds so discustingly sweet. When I make toast, I put things like butter, salam,  cheese and maby some mayo, pickels and lettuce time to time. Putting sweet things on bread just sounds wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cin fit in a wee box

I don't know why that made me laugh so hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's green so you know it's good for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 11:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm late but how the hell isn't [Ingrid Bergman](http://wallpapercave.com/wp/lrjRjYr.png) mentioned yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a creator and I see your point. But it doesn't break any copyright laws and I would be extremely flattered if someone took some image I created and tattooed it in their body. Of course the tattoo artist is making money off it but it is not easy to recreate tattoo from image so the tattoo artist is also doing lot of work.  I wouldn't call it stealing. If it was stealing, getting a tattoo would be really difficult since you'd had to track down original artist on some image you saw online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically this game summarized in 4 words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 is just absolutely amazing. Tennant is teriffic actor and his doctor seems most "human" imo. 

Also his regeneration scene was absolutely amazing "I dont wanna go" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this post-murder meditation? Like he got angry, stabbed the other dude and then started meditating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a mexican man on the news yesterday who had wife and son in USA and he said that it doesn't matter if Trump builds a wall, he will get back to his wife and son no matter what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And mentally prepare for the fact that bug spray might not work. I spent summers in forests/swamps plating trees and I can tell you, there are some fuckers that don't give a shit about your bug sprays.

In the woods when eating, you basicly had to accept the fact that you are eating mosquitoes while eating your sandwich because the moment you open your mouth they fly in. Since your face is most exposed part of you body the mosquitoes fly around it alot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Finland we have similiar joke that goes "I went to the store, but then suddenly a spoon!" which means basicly a joke that makes zero sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the word "porn" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lion King is great movie, but Emperors New Groove is funnier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my favorite movie when I was a kid. When I was around 4-5 I walked around the house holding the vhs tape after I got it for christmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often do this I lock certain face features and then  randomize to find some I like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only answer. There isn't and never will be better Disney movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have programmer friends and one of them was once fixing a bug. Then I came to talk to him hour or two later and asked if he was still fixing the bug and he said "Well I fixed it but now I'm trying to find out how the hell did I fix it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stranger things, Peaky blinders and Game of Thrones are probably most anticipated on my list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont forget "Ploughing a troll" from the older, sillier stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I came from, now I can leave

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space is like the coolest thing ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
