<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6243</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VEGAN SPINACH GINGER SMOOTHIE BOWL (1024/1024) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 07:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Make the Most Perfect Indian Makhni Gravy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 06:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this on a blog, tried it and it's just perfect. 


**INGREDIENTS** 

Butter4 tablespoons 

Oil2 tablespoons 

Green Chili1 

Kashmiri Red Chilies4 

Ginger Paste2 tablespoons 

Garlic Paste1 tablespoon 

Bayleaves2 

Cinnamon Sticks2 

Cloves5-6 

Cardamoms2 

Peppercorns1 teaspoon 

Chopped Cashewnuts2 tablespoons 

Khus Khus or Poppy Seeds1 tablespoon 

Tomatoes, coarsely chopped14 large (1 1/2 Kg) 

Garam Masala Powder1 tablespoon 

Chili Powder1 teaspoon 

Turmeric Powder1/2 teaspoon 

Ketchup3 tablespoons 

Sugar or Jaggery (Optional)1 tablespoon 

Dry Kasuri Methi2 tablespoons 

Fresh Cream2 tablespoons 

Salt to taste 

**STEPS**

 In a large pan or kadhai, heat a tablespoon of butter and two tablespoons oil.  

Add green chili, red chillies, ginger, garlic paste and whole spices. Saute for a minute or two and add cashew nuts, poppy seeds and tomatoes. Mix well. 

Cover and cook this for ten to fifteen minutes till the tomatoes start breaking down. 

Switch off the flame and set aside to cool. 

Once cool enough to handle, fish out as many whole spices as possible, and grind the mixture to a smooth paste. 

In the same pan or kadhai, heat the remaining butter and add the tomato paste. 

Add garam masala powder, chili powder, turmeric, ketchup, salt and sugar or jaggery (if using) along with 1/2 cup water. Bring this to a boil.  

Once the curry comes to a boil, simmer and cook for 30 minutes, till the oil separates slightly. In another pan, dry roast the kasuri methi and grind it to a fine powder. 

Mix kasuri methi and fresh cream in the curry and switch off the flame. Let the curry cool completely before dividing it into smaller portions and freezing it in ziplock packs.

For full post click [here.](http://www.myfoodstory.in/how-to-make-indian-makhani-gravy-curry-recipe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Make The Most Perfect Indian Makhani Gravy (Curry) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 06:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad this helps!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goan Prwan Curry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 10:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> INGREDIENTS 

750 gms	Shelled and cleaned Prawns 

2 tbsps	Oil 

7-8	Curry Leaves 

1 large	Onion Chopped 

1/2 tsp	Turmeric 

2	Green chile 

2	Kokum pieces ( Optional) 

pinch of	Sugar 

to taste	Salt 

1 cup	 Fresh grated coconut 

2 tbsps	Coriander seeds 

1/2 tbsp	Cumin seeds 

4-5	Dry red red chillies 

4-5	Kashmiri red chillies 

5-6 pods	Garlic 

1/2 tbsp	Tamarind Pulp 

STEPS 

Clean prawns. Add little salt and turmeric. Mix well and keep aside. In a pan dry roast coriander seeds and Cumins seed till aromatic.  

In a blender add grated coconut, roasted Coriander, cumin, red chillies, garlic. Add enough water and make a very smooth paste. 

Heat a heavy bottom pan. Add 1 tbsp oil. Add prawns and Saute on high heat for not more than 3 minutes, stirring continuously.

Remove and keep aside. In the same pan add remaining oil. Add curry leaves. Add chopped onions. Saute till the onions are translucent and soft. 

 Add ground coconut paste and saute till the raw smell is gone. Add required amount of water to the pan. 

Season it with salt (Keep in mind that the prawn marination also had salt in it) and sugar .Bring the gravy to a boil. 

Once the gravy comes to a rolling boil add Kokum(If using) and sliced green chillies. Add sauteed prawns.  

Let it cook for about a minute or so. Switch of the gas.  


Note: 1.If you are using tamarind and Kokum both then adjust the quantities accordingly, as both contributes to the sourness. 2. The cooking time of prawn depends on its size,so judge it accordingly. Cooking prawns for too long results in rubbery prawns.

Find full recipe [here.](http://www.theflavoursofkitchen.com/goan-prawn-curry-recipe)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goan Prawn Curry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 10:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murgh Saagwala - Spinach Chicken Curry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 09:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 20:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank u. exactly why. Especially around this time of the year, even non vegetarians Hindus become vegetarian in large parts of the country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eggless Nutella Cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 08:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted a recipe for eggless nutella cake without cocoa powder or cooking chocolate. So here goes.
     These are Ingredients to serve 5

    1 1/2 cups All Purpose Flour
    1 1/2 teaspoons Baking Powder
    1 teaspoon Vanilla Powder
    4  tablespoons Nutella 
    3/4 cup Sugar
    1 cup Water
    100 gm Butter
    1 teaspoon Lemon Juice
    For Frosting
    
    2 teaspoons Caster sugar
    3 tablespoons Nutella
    Steps
        Sift together the flour and baking powder and keep aside.
        In a vessel, mix the water (Cold) and sugar till it dissolves.
        Preheat the oven to 200C.
        To the dissolved sugar add the 100 gm melted butter. Mix thoroughly.
        Now add the juice of the lemon and mix together.
        Then add the Vanilla powder and mix again.
        To this mixture add the sifted flour and baking powder mix. Whisk till no lumps remain.
        Add the Nutella to this and mix thoroughly. The final mix should not be thick. It should be a fairly thin consistency.
        Grease a 6 inch baking tray and pour this into that.
        Bake for 30 mins.
        Remove, allow to cool. Frost with some Nutella and top with castor sugar.

For the blog post and images. click [here](http://www.warandcheese.com/45-minute-eggless-nutella-cake-recipe). 
         </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eggless Nutella Cake Without Cocoa Powder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 08:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Festive Recipe Round Up, The Double Ds; Dussera and Durga Pooja  Cucumbertown Magazine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 08:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egg in Spicy Caramelised Onions Wrapped in Puff Pastry: Kerala Style Egg Puffs Recipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 08:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 08:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! It's just garlic bread stuffed with some mozzarella cheese and jalapenos and corn. But I'm guessing I wasn't very effective in communicating that. Total facepalm moment!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dominos Style Stuffed Garlic Bread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 10:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it's about as bad as bad can get. Something along the lines of how bad A Serbian Film is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we had to watch Salo as part of Psychology. Most messed up thing ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that movie was vile!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most messed up on screen couple that you can think of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mickey and Mallory of Natural Born Killers takes the cake in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Django Unchained, Chicago, Oceans Eleven, The Departed, amongst the good movies. One movie wit a stellar star cast which failed miserably has to be the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the things that go into making a successful blogger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 16:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanted to share this article on Medium about what are the things that makes a bloggers successful. It talks about consistent content creation, regular marketing through social media channels, monetisation through ad, affiliates etc. The article talks about food bloggers, but I suppose it can be extended into all aspects of blogging. [Full article here.](https://magazine.cucumbertown.com/what-it-takes-to-make-your-food-blog-a-success-5c0509ee121a)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 11:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be Shrek, especially cos I have a much younger sister, so we had to watch animation all the time! But I do love that movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 11:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casino Royale and Dr No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under 30 Minute Habanero Grilled Paneer Salad with Eggless Mayo Dressing Recipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 07:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under 30 minute Easy Mawa Kesar Peda (Milk Fudge with Saffron) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 18:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under 30 Minute Guli Appa/ Paddu (Spicy Dumplings Made from Rice Crepe Batter) Recipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 12:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 06:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is awesome! Love her work, and so easy to talk to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How this food blogger made a small change to her ad strategy and made enough money to quit two full time jobs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 17:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It talks about how Beth Moncel of the food blog Budget Bytes used optimised ads to get a lot more money than what she was making through ad sense. She talks about how exploring different ad networks and optimising ads worked best for her and why she doesn't believe ads are dead.  

[Full read here.](https://magazine.cucumbertown.com/how-i-used-ads-the-right-way-on-my-5-million-page-views-and-made-enough-money-to-quit-two-full-d1246a13af8f) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eggless Choco Cashew Cookies (Vegetarian Friendly Recipe) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 09:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The secret to absolutely delicious Masala Aloo Recipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 08:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
