<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> redditors like to make empty threats to quit the game, but statistically, protoss is still the most popular race </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broodwar would never succeed in this day and age. Players expect at least some amount of updates. They question is, how much is too much? I personally lean towards "more is better." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 09:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that popular will get it's share of edgy counter-culture haters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 09:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a fallacy. League is popular, among other reasons, because they shake up the meta with regular updates. The game always feels fresh and interesting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God forbid we learn anything from League of Legends. It's only the most successful competitive PC game in existence. They are totally ruining their game /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> new cyclone muh better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's essentially invulnerable for like a second </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that expensive for infinite range </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The resemblance is uncanny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that elves and dwarves, the two races subjected to most racial prejudice in the game, happen to also be white is conveniently omitted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit are you Lowko's long lost British twin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 shots to kill a zergling.. such buff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yandere nurse type sounds enticing indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLAGUU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flushing sodium down the toilet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 08:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> use the honeybee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same guy made a lego battlecruiser and thor as well

https://www.flickr.com/photos/31194766@N08/sets/72157628560420137/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> re mass turd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is way old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 23:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give back the mothership planet cracker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Witcher 3 PC: can you bind the same key to multiple actions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the default key bindings, left shift is context sensitive--it is used for both sprinting and for modifying attacks.  However, I cannot remap both of these actions to a different key.  For example, if I try to bind sprint to Alt, and then try to bind modify attack also to the Alt key, it will clear the sprint key binding.  It seems as though only the default key bindings allow for multiple actions to be bound to the same key.  Is there any way around this? Any insight would be appreciated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the first sentence, you were taught by Maeda-san.  In the second sentence, Maeda-san taught you.  Do you see the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I didn't know this.  That helps a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Godamn KSers are in FF too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parasitic bomb should help with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liberators take around 2 seconds to deploy, and they are even more exposed when transforming than Tempest, as the tempest has a cast range of 10.  And nobody considers liberators useless... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but even if I were to get a new mouse, this methodology seems awfully unwieldy.  Have to hit tab, point my cursor to the bombs, then flick the scroll wheel.  That's 3 actions to do something that ought to take one :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not more harassment, it's moving harassment to a later phase of the game where it belongs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got an incredibly powerful Tempest ability that is an AOE stun for 7 seconds.  How is that not a buff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see way more Protoss players crying that blink DT's are going to be useless than other races complaining about them being scary.  IMO its the protoss players that need to chill out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh weird. What if I don't have a scroll wheel on my mouse... I can't even find an option to remap this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a veteran player unfamiliar with the UI changes on PC. How do I switch between my 2 equipped bombs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've restarted this game after putting it down for more than a year.  I play on PC.  It looks like the UI has been significantly updated during my hiatus, and I can't figure out how to switch between my equipped bombs anymore.  I equip two types of bombs in the inventory, but when I hit tab, it only shows one of the bombs.  How do I switch between these bombs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the protoss players realize just how powerful the new Tempest ability is.  4 second cast time, but 7 second complete stun AOE.  It's nothing like the original Disruption Blast idea that just hurt enemies slowly over 30 seconds.  Being stunned for 7 seconds is as good as dead.  It's like a mini liberation zone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And no early review copies I presume lol.  Scumbag tactics.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on guys, blink DT's are freaking cool.  It fits the lore, the effect looks nice, and while it may not be the most efficient upgrade, it definitely has potential for skillful plays.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I totally, genuinely, really believed Portugal had a bunch of original NES's sitting on store shelves. You sure educated me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah that escalated fast.  I think your sarcasm detector might need to get checked out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there pressure in the porn industry to get breast implants? What made you decide to stay natural? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are just original NES's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really not so hard to imagine DT blink being useful. One good scan used to be a death sentence; now the DT can escape and re engage later.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shades were never meant to be used for scouting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit i saw this way before it was posted.  That karma could have been mine...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you give back the mothership vortex? xDDD PLEASE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 20:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This awesome change to Hunter Seeker Missile slipped under the radar:

Seeker Missile: Added new upgrade Recalibrated Explosives

Increase Seeker Missile tracking range by 50%

Increase Seeker Missile damage by 30%

xDDD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 20:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This awesome change to Hunter Seeker Missile slipped under the radar:

Seeker Missile: Added new upgrade Recalibrated Explosives

Increase Seeker Missile tracking range by 50%

Increase Seeker Missile damage by 30%

xDDD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 20:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will come a time when seeing your mom in porn won't be that bad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he put high tariffs on all imports from any foreign country, wouldn't that force them to come back to the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump threatens to curtail the influx of Chinese imports, and China responds by threatening to do the same?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that explicitly stating that you are neutral would be interpreted as a negative by Japanese people.  If you said, "I neither like or hate dogs," Japanese people will take that to mean you don't like dogs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ass-ass-inated more like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> make avilo great again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know how long she can hold onto that title with a Trump presidency.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 00:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need for snark. When it comes to language learning, every question has been asked by someone already. Repetition, in this case, is a good thing IMO.  

You are correct, in this context it means "stuff like."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's impossible to feel good about getting promoted without feeling bad for being demoted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's Nina?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we slightly buff cyclone AA to compensate for +armor nerf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should just air it anyway tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this has got to be the dumbest thing i've read all week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps the one thing we can all agree on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very appealing idea if you execute it well.  Very appealing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard you can equip more types of bombs/potions at a time, is that true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has changed since the game was first release? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys.  So I played the Witcher 3 for about a month when it first came out on PC.  Now I am considering getting back into it.  I've heard that with all the patches, the game has changed considerably, including things like the user interface, sign balancing, and quests. For example, I heard the Igni sign was heavily nerfed. It is nearly impossible for me to dig through the patch notes of all the updates, each with hundreds of bullet points.  Would you guys be able to explain some of the biggest differences between the game when it was originally released, versus the game in its current state? Would very much appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really helpful!  I feel he's speaking a bit too slowly (feels a little patronizing) but the grammar points are still useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the old dislocated shoulder around-the-backfist. Classic technique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have been announcing a new album for years now. Why should the fans believe you this time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 week repost?  Do people really have this short memory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much this.  VA work does not come cheap
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even think there is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 MacBook Pros not compatible with many Thunderbolt 3 devices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no amount of dongles could fix this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Macbook Pros not compatible with many Thunderbolt 3 devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know, there is no way.  It's really infuriating and stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  I had been saying  but it's good to know the more precise ways!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much, this is all very helpful!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Counter for music notes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in a touring band that does shows in Japan. I am somewhat conversational in Japanese but lack a lot of precise technical terminology.  For example, I don't know how to say "Raise the key by 3 notes" because I don't know the counter for semitones.  Does anyone know how to say this?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you tried pressing alt-` (alt-tilde)? that is the hotkey for switching between romaji and kana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People should do the right thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Wait for the game to come out, see if it's good, then buy.  Stop encouraging publishers to overhype their games while failing to deliver. No Man's Lie would have never happened if people hadn't preordered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how the roaches are like, "o-oh..guess I'll go home now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit that was like a nuke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razer apologizes for "S my D" tweet; angers more people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razer apologizes for "S my D" tweet, angers even more people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the bone of my mop

Soap is my body and lysol is my blood 

I have cleaned over a thousand floors

Unknown to dirty, nor known to clean

Have withstood pain to disinfect many stains

Yet, those hands will never hold anything 

So as I spray, unlimited janitor works! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said heterosexual sex must be accompanied by two witnesses and a notarized affidavit /s

how the hell could you even prove you had sex a man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or simply lakes or rivers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong, but I believe when the US government itself is filing the lawsuit, the case cannot be settled out of court for some undisclosed monetary amount. So if this case goes through, someone is going to come out taking the blame. I really hope AT T gets served its humble pie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOJ sues AT T for colluding with competitors over Dodgers games' broadcasting rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steam game listings FINALLY required to include in-game screenshots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prior to this, I think devs could get away with just promotional images </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Steam games now required to have in-game screenshots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeleton believed to be that of Amelia Earhart discovered on remote Pacific Island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screengrab:

https://gyazo.com/71676095f3fa0e7fea32618888eaa902

https://gyazo.com/b63146325b149bc7435bbc09973f47dd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I can still see all the tweets, but here you are : )

https://gyazo.com/71676095f3fa0e7fea32618888eaa902

https://gyazo.com/b63146325b149bc7435bbc09973f47dd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screengrab:

https://gyazo.com/71676095f3fa0e7fea32618888eaa902

https://gyazo.com/b63146325b149bc7435bbc09973f47dd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screengrabs for when it inevitably gets deleted:

https://gyazo.com/71676095f3fa0e7fea32618888eaa902

https://gyazo.com/b63146325b149bc7435bbc09973f47dd
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I can still see all the tweets. But ask and you shall receive:

https://gyazo.com/71676095f3fa0e7fea32618888eaa902

https://gyazo.com/b63146325b149bc7435bbc09973f47dd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razer to Apple: "S my D" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look in my history, I posted this in PCMasterRace several minutes before him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SJW goes nuts over Razer marketing tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razer's "S my D" tweet triggers SJW shitstorm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My original title was sarcastic, but nobody could tell so I changed the title for clarity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razor's "S my D" tweet sets off SJW rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He technically doesn't have to buy anyone copies because he didn't get 100 upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fourth person in that video is Suyra Bonaly... and she remains the only skater to land a backflip on one foot...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's her.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fourth one is Surya Bonaly.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies for the slightly inaccurate title.  She is actually the only skater to land a backflip on one foot, which is far more challenging than landing on two feet.  At one point, they tried to ban backflips by making a rule that all jumps had to be landed on one foot, so she skirted the rules by doing this in defiance.  Of course, subsequently all backflips were banned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, she is the only person to land it on one foot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surya Bonaly performing a backflip at the 1998 figure skating Olympics. She is the only skater ever to land one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  Wow that's really interesting, never would have thought
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh.... doesn't look smug to me at all... He just seems tired or lazy... Maybe that's why I'm so confused </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but can you explain the joke? 9 times out of 10 when i see Pepe used in a political context, I don't get the joke, or what makes it a meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 how Pepe the frog went from "feels good man" to a conservative political symbol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
