<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject723</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he'd been a Catholic Priest he could have just gone on a nice long sabbatical instead of prison!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Van Jones sounds like a damn moron.  Trump was the one that got the guy killed in the first place!!!  The guys Dad wouldn't even deign to meet Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abuse survivor quits pope's commission citing 'shameful' resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It is a reflection of how this whole abuse crisis in the Church has been handled: with fine words in public and contrary actions behind closed doors," she said.

Read the entire article here.  Don't worry, it's short.

https://www.google.com/amp/mobile.reuters.com/article/amp/idUSKBN1684GI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narrow is the way are few there are who find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is righteous.  False conditions for your argument.  The real question is why anyone is let into heaven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't argue about Revelations.  It's likely you both misunderstand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither.  The pope is a fallible man, just like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God chooses us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God is good!  Praise God! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YUH HUH!  (This is exactly the level
of debate I've come to expect from Trump supporters) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little-noticed addendum-he is legally required to grab them all by the pu$$y now.  Just the 7+ ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO. YOU DID TOO!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those Duke boys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYONE LOST!  THERES A RETARD RUNNING THE COUNTRY AND WE ARE ALL YELLING!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Wheeler Peak in Great Basin National Park? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a lady.  That very pose explains everything I've been wondering about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get better sources.  I hear the Bible is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who shall bring any charge against Gods elect? It is God who justifies. (Romans 8:33) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Above God, there are no higher courts. If God is the one who acquits you  declares you righteous in his sight  no one can appeal; no one claim a technicality; no one can call for a mistrial; no one can look for other counts against you. Gods sentence is final and total."
Piper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow-what kind of Christ follower would downvote what you just posted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saved by grace, through faith.  It is the gift of God! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, is your goal to get like Christ or just get off?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He made fun sexual acts NOT a sin too.  

What you need to realize is that marriage and sex are awesome, AND are pictures that point to greater truths about Christ and the Church.  

Just looking at your most recent posts, you seem to be very young, involved in a lot of internet pornography, and no almost zero about mutually gratifying, God-glorifying sex.  Sex is designed for the marriage bed.  What you are seeing on the screen is called perversion and is really about domination and power.  Christ could dominate the Church, but He doesn't.  He's gentle and lowly of spirit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys gotta get your Theology from somewhere other than google.  Sex outside of marriage-before,bedridden,between, whatever, is fornication.  Read the Sermon on the Mount and tell me how you can justify premarital sex when Jesus says even LOOKING at a woman lustfully us wrong.
I am praying judgment right now on all the blind guides leading people off the cliff in this thread right now.  I pray God stops your mouths and causes you to repent publicly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he'll find out he's wrong very soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't really talking to you, I was kind of guffawing.  I think that's also the first time I've ever used that word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was a goddess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They gave that  tree an erection...dare I say a woody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to lean toward illogical opinions and allow my bias to sway me.  Was that not the most self-inflated intro to a post you've ever read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good post!  Lets continue to value the truth by calling out lies wherever they may come from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bout you put some Trump quotes in the projector in you church?  Flash some of his statements up for everyone to see?  
Rather than "being a Daniel", how bout I think like Jesus and value holiness and the truth?  Out of the overflow of the heart the mouth speaks.
There are MANY conservatives and many Christians who are opposed to Trump because he is a WICKED, WICKED man.  You are  not opposed to him because he happens to have an "R" on his jersey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spleen vented.  Feel better?  Reality just texted me, he says he's gonna keep happening even if you don't like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he's ever heard of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Missler.  He knows his Bible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More on Catholic Pedophile Priests-Politics and Secrecy at the Highest Level </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ is humble Trump is not.  Christ is meek Trump is not.  Christ is loving Trump is not.  Christ sacrificed Trump does not. Christ is welcoming Trump is not. Christ was poor Trump is rich.  Christ is self-controlled Trump lacks anything resembling self-control.  Christ is the Truth Trump is a liar. Christ is faithful Trump is a serial adulterer and admitted sexual assaulter.  Christ points to the Father Trump points to himself.  Christ wants unity Trump revels in division. Christ divested himself of power Trump grasps for more and more power. Christ protects the weak Trump exploits them. Christ healed the sick and Trump makes us all sick.
You are going to say , "Well yeah, no one looks good compared to Christ!"  And I will agree with you, no one is perfect, that's why He came.  However, for someone who claims to be a Christian (he eats his little cracker and drinks his little juice, he tries to not get God involved and has never repented) he shows zero Christian virtue (at the age of 70, I might add).  His administration has already coined the term "alternative facts" and made up on the fly several massacres that never happened!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll pray for you right now too.  Then I'm going to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you personally opened yourself up.  I'm glad it freaked you out enough to make you repent of doing  it again, though.  Concentrate on Christ, pray, read your Bible, stay involved with your church, and serve people.  Be a Christian-we are more than conquerors and have zero to fear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's all a ploy to sell more Blue Apron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the Duke boys just ran shine..I had no idea they were involved in murder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God was there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus is not a trickster, Satan is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus talks a great deal about hell.  If you want a clear idea of what the Person who actually made hell thinks of hell then read His words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus was welcoming, especially to the outcasts and rejected.

Come to me, all who labor and are heavy laden, and I will give you rest. Take my yoke upon you, and learn from me, for I am gentle and lowly in heart, and you will find rest for your souls. For my yoke is easy, and my burden is light.
Matthew 11:28-30 ESV

Graham, in embracing Trump, is turning his back on this ethos that Christ Himself encouraged.  A Pharisee focuses on the sin, a Christian focuses on the sinner and pulls him in with arms open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I simply disagree with you.  He was on the timeline and acting strange (a dozen phone calls, the business card) around the time of her disappearance.  You are obviously upset-I just don't understand why.
Do you think if HD had it to do over again he'd have an affair with her?  Hell no!  That affair ruined his reputation and his life.  He has been looked at sideways for years-way before this podcast came out.  There was always the question hanging out there.  
If you have a problem with the podcast then don't listen.  That was easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've debated soteriology many times.  This particular opponent in this specific post hold no interest for me.  Mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just chill.  Realistically a lot of murders have to do with sex.  So to catch the killer you look at people who they've had sex with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know from experience!  God bless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read that as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP-I'm SB and I've read that book.  It's pretty interesting.  Chick Missler has some interesting things to say about demons and fallen angels over at K House.  
Just a caution-I'm sure unnecessary in your case-but this line of interest can easily become a distraction from the real Mission.  Don't classify it as time in the Word or as your Bible Study because it's focus is not on God, but on our enemy.  I guess what I'm saying is that this type of study takes away from your real study.  Focus on God and that's where your real power will come from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be a deist and not a Christian then.  Deists will be going to hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one guy knows how to do a Bible search?  It takes like 11 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good grief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pride is really the enemy of faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  God has established it.  It is a transcendent reflection of His character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are proud, argumentative, and sad.  Each of your posts reveals more about your sorry spiritual state that whatever issue you are flailing to elucidate.  I won't be responding to anything else you post-so feel free to further demonstrate your spiritual immaturity to the rest of the board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pray for the martyrs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a measure of your heart that you take a post about our brothers being killed and driven from their homes to grind a theological axe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure.  You'd do well to keep reading, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look.  You'll need to grow up and accept that the denominations have differences that they hold for good reasons.  God is Sovereign and Jesus is Lord and Savior.  The only safe space is in His hand, and you can be in that place on a number of denominations.
I will say that the churches that bear with and are gracious are closer to the heart of Christ (Eph 4), and those that value the Word and teach it are closer as well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other side of this is that the White House isn't Trumps house, it's the people's house.  He shouldn't be able to pick and choose who gets to come to the briefings.  What an infant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is just throwing a tantrum like the child he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure HD was like "you better solve this sh!t" to his GBI buddies. From another perspective, if he was not committing adultery with her he'd have never been as big a suspect-so he made his own bed there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $10?  I bet it cost 12 cents to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible describes the path to sainthood as believing in  Jesus.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow-it makes our little persecutions pale in comparison.  Pray for the persecuted Church! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love watching rich kids wreck the toys their daddies paid for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is just trying to establish dominance like the Neanderthal he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to Christian to be anti-Trump.  You just need taste, a smidge  of discernment, and at least one lobe  of a functioning brain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no leftist even by your alt-definition of the word.  I've voted Republican for 20 years until this election.  The man is a vain pathological liar, adulterer megalomaniac and a danger.  Gloat that he won-that's fine.  But own the chaos that his very obvious personality disorders are going to wreak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that Payne's work, even though he never even mentions Duke, has pushed the GBI into committing to an arrest and prosecution where they otherwise might have just let the status quo ride.  Maybe it resulted in new information being given to them, maybe it simply forces the to look again at what they already had, maybe it was bringing heat on them indirectly in that some members of law enforcement were suspects and were pushing people behind the scenes to clear them due to the added attention.  
What is very clear is that UAV has been a real catalyst to getting this thing solved.  Good job Payne! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow-I guess I have to eat crow.  Payne's work looks to have been effective in pushing the GBI into making an arrest and look where we are now!  Amazed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's exactly how I'd expect a Trump supporter to respond.  Reactive and thin-skinned with zero creativity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  Perfect answer!  
I think the more simply you live the better.  You do have to be conscious that austerity and self-denial can become points of pride and idols in-and-of-themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Praise God! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be happy today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 11:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blessed is the one whose transgression is forgiven, whose sin is covered.
Psalms 32:1 ESV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone listened to the History of Rome podcast?  I just finished the episode on this battle today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a retard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's all take a deep breath and not be offended together.  When did conservatives become such a pack of whining, menstruating, pack of pansies?  
That's a rhetorical question-it happened the same time we elected a President who whined that the whole system was rigged and "not fair".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame.  Your post.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate anyone.  I check outlets from left to right.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't snozzberry a euphemism for penis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be patient.  Until you are married be  celibate.  Don't do "long-term" relationships that aren't marriage.
Who knows what God has in store for you?  Not me and not you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relationship with God is what we were designed for.  Every person in every society in every time  needs to be connected with God their maker.  He programmed this need into each of us.
Some people's relationship with Him is petulant rejection and pride( Atheists),  some people's relationship is grasping and searching, but rejecting the Way ( pagans-as a descriptor, not a pejorative), and a few peoples relationship is as children of God; those elected, called, Justified, Sanctified, and ultimately Glorified (Christians).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I guess I should have believed what You wrote in the Bible!"

And then you accept that you are forgiven, His blood paid your penalty, and you are exalted with Him to glorify Him for all eternity.  Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't think any direct harm will come of your prediction, I'd be very careful trying to put God's timeline in a box.  It might be 3000 years from now!  Who knows?  Only God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you.  Cycles.  This planet is so amazing an incubator for humans in so many ways!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely do not support a corrupt administration-speak out against out, like John the Baptist.  Jesus called him the greatest man born of a woman.  Everything done in the dark will  be revealed by the light-we are called to be that light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot on.  Trump has drawn many strange bedfellows together, hasn't he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is as alt-right as he can be.  He's a Breitbart darling!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be kind of strange-Graham is going to see this as persecution of him for sharing the Gospel ( although clearly it is a renunciation of his political and policy stances), and this will likely cement his status as the martyr in his own mind and encourage the Trump Christians (should be an oxymoron) to just entrench.
I think a more effective strategy than just silencing him would be to publicly challenge his views-make him justify himself from scripture and if he can't, then he is discredited.  Ultimately, I hope he will repent of his associating the Church with this godless leader, Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A happy demand then.  Very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an immature little tantrum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a prophet-a false one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are real differences in theology involved-most are secondary and tertiary, which would cause legitimate disruption in practice-but a few, as a Protestant, I would consider of primary import or at least close enough to make me very uneasy.  That's why I'm not Roman Catholic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fighters, take your corners... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
