<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Link between climate change and armed conflict is exaggerated. Researchers examined the "conflict potential" of the sort of droughts that will become increasingly common under global warming. The researchers effectively combined three sets of data to look for any links. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surge of volcanic eruptions between 320k and 170k years ago changed the course of human evolution. Scientists say this pulse of activity along the East African Rift System would have drastically altered the environment for the Homo sapiens arriving in Ethiopia, forcing them out of Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research is shedding light on how leukaemia cells can survive cancer treatment. They don't sit and hide near bone marrow. Instead, to the researchers' surprise, the cells were scattered throughout the mouse bone marrow both before and after treatment, and they were moving around rapidly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 11:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selling AMD FX 6100 and MoBo ASUS M5A78L-M/USB3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See here:

http://imgur.com/a/SfTck

Used (by me) but perfectly working. I updated my desktop, so selling my old parts.

I sell CPU and Mobo together.

I am asking 60 pounds. On ebay the same just sold for 72 pounds (67+5): http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/ASUS-M5A78L-motherboard-AMD-FX6100-processor-6-core-/302102796591?hash=item4656bad92f:g:iLkAAOSw8w1X-9fB

I can swap for N2DS or New nintendo 3ds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minix 2 vs Minix 3, which is best to write an OS from scratch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 12:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to do it as a personal project, just for fun. I did OS courses back in the day as part of my degree, but I always wanted to write one from scratch.

Minix 3 seems the perfect option, because it is newer, but I have read it is bloated with code, and that you are not really coding one from scratch, just learning from the book. Is that right?

If that is the case, would you then recommend minix 2?

I know there are projects out there which aims to do this, but I find in most of their cases the documentation is lacking. I prefer just to read a book (I like reading books more than scroll through documentation). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In search of a N2DS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 11:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am willing to pay 40 for one in good condition (no scratches). No games included. Bag and sd card favoured. This is more or less all the deals I can see in Gumtree. Theres a guy selling one like this in Stirling at the moment, but I dont have a car.

thanks for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anti-Muslim "bias" is apparent in attitudes towards asylum seekers among Europeans, a new study suggests. Researchers found that people were more likely to "accept" Christian asylum seekers, while those with higher employability and severe vulnerabilities were also said to be favoured. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Glasgow have a mice problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just asking here. I was speaking now with a few friends, all of them in the west end, and all of them had mice in their flat. I don't have yet, and I am crossing my finger because I am always unlucky with these things.

Is this very common? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fan control of new mobo doesn't seem to autoregulate but just run at a specific constant speed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 13:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new motherboard ASRock H61M-VG4 Motherboard (Socket 1155, H61/Micro ATX, DDR3, PC-1600)  (this is a LGA1155, so it is a new mobo from amazon, but an old model), doesnt seem to auto regulate, but it runs at a constant speed. The CPU is an i5 3470s (I just bought it 2nd hand on ebay), so it runs under low temps (it seems to give me around 33-34 C under normal workload).

When I installed the motherboard initially, the fans were running full blast (it has 3, one connected to the CPU, and the other 3 from the case connected to another fan socket in the mobo). It was very noisy. I didnt know what was going on, I thought it was just a noisy fan (I bought the cpu fan from amazon, it was not a stock fan, it is Akasa AK-CC7117EP01 K32 High Performance Intel Cooler for LGA775, LGA1156 and LGA1155 ).

Then I went to the bios, and I saw that there are 2 options for fan control, temperature (which I set to 50 degrees) and fan speed (which was set to 9). I also installed the mobo software, that lets me change these parameters from windows.

The only thing that seems to change the fan speed is the "fan speed option". The temperature threshold does nothing, and when I change the fan speed (from 1 to 9) it just keeps a constant speed, whatever I set.

My understanding was that the fans would auto regulate themselves based on the temperature, but in my case, they dont seem to care. The temps are very low as said (low 30s) so I would expect the fans to go at low speed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google creates AI program that uses reasoning to navigate the London tube. Combining external memory and deep learning, DeepMinds program learns how to do tasks independently, and could pave the way for sophisticated AI assistants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 12:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fan control of new mobo doesn't seem to autoregulate but just run at a specific constant speed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new motherboard (this is a LGA1155, so it is a new mobo from amazon, but an old model), doesnt seem to auto regulate, but it runs at a constant speed. The CPU is an i5 3470s, so it runs under low temps (it seems to give me around 33-34 C under normal workload).

When I installed the motherboard initially, the fans were running full blast (it has 3, one connected to the CPU, and the other 3 from the case connected to another fan socket in the mobo). It was very noisy. I didnt know what was going on, I thought it was just a noisy fan (I bought the cpu fan from amazon, it was not a stock fan).

Then I went to the bios, and I saw that there are 2 options for fan control, temperature (which I set to 50 degrees) and fan speed (which was set to 9). I also installed the mobo software, that lets me change these parameters from windows.

The only thing that seems to change the fan speed is the "fan speed option". The temperature threshold does nothing, and when I change the fan speed (from 1 to 9) it just keeps a constant speed, whatever I set.

My understanding was that the fans would auto regulate themselves based on the temperature, but in my case, they dont seem to care.  The temps are very low as said (low 30s) so I would expect the fans to go at low speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can Puppey be so good barely playing the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on EE, puppey barely plays or cares about the game. No pubs, no scrims, it seems he only plays pro games. 

On the other hand he is an outstanding player. I remember like 2 years ago when he only played terrorblade (terror being shit back then), he had like a 70% win rate. 

It does surprise me how someone can be so good playing so little. When I stop playing for a week I feel very rusty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three scots have won the nobel prize this year (in different disciplines, chemistry and physics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fraser Stoddart in chemistry. 

David J. Thouless and J. Michael Kosterlitz in physics.

Quite amazing for such an small country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last year a study suggested the majority of cancers are down to bad luck - random DNA mutations in stem cells that are not caused by lifestyle factors. New study contradicts this claim; while bad luck does play a role cancer development, researchers find it is unlikely to be the primary contributor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 11:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists manage to examine at atomic resolution how nicotine achieves these cognitive and addictive effects. The protein alpha-4-beta-2 nicotinic receptor, sits on nerve cells in the brain. Nicotine binds to the receptor when someone smokes opening a path for ions to enter the cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 11:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paella recommendations in Barcelona or rodalies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 19:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research suggesting that the planet might be committed to vastly greater warming than previously thought is being dismissed as flawed by climate scientists. A study published today offers the most complete reconstruction to date of global sea-surface temperatures for the past two million years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 10:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I cannot see 3D, which Nintendo 3DS (or 2DS) should I buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lazy eye, which means I cannot see 3D. Like I cannot see it on movies, or when I tested a Nintendo 3DS in a shopping center.

I have been playing a lot of emulation lately in Android (classic gbc games), and I want to buy a new 3DS and get new ones.

I don't know if I should buy the 2DS because I cannot see 3D, or if it even with that going with the 3DS is a better option. The 2DS is very cheap, so I don't know.

Also, I don't know if I should go for an XL, and for one of the newer models, or one of the old ones. I see the new ones have a more powerful CPU, but I don't know if that has any real effect.

Probably this has been asked here a lot, I am sorry for repeating it.

I will mostly play at home. I am an old guy, and I spend most of my day at work, where I cannot play.

thanks for the info !
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I cannot see 3D, which Nintendo 3DS (or 2DS) should I buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prestwick airport car park, any cheaper place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was checking it now the car park for prestwick airport, and it is around 50 pounds for a week.

This is extremelly expensive compared to what you pay in Glasgow main airport or Edinburgh, because in those airports there are unofficial parks which are much cheaper.

I cannot find anything similar in Prestwick, and only the official park is offered.

No idea is someone has any experience?

The reason why I need to park a car, is because the flight arrives very late at night, and I cannot take the train. Otherwise I would very gladly take the train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Potato laptop with HD4000 benchmark (tldr use dx9) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 19:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My laptop uses a hd4000, the cpu is a i5 3320m and the resolution is an amazing 1366 x 768. It has 8gb of RAM, and it uses a standard HDD. It runs Windows 10 64b.

I have tested Dota2 for the 4 default video profiles (min, med, high, very high), and a extra one, which I will call "extra med", where when compared to med, it puts high textures and med shadows (med uses med textures and high shadows).

First of all, in Windows 10, gl failed. it loaded the game, but then it became frozen. So I tried it for vulkan, dx9 and dx11.

So now, the average FPS on laning phases, the order will be min, med, high, very high, extra med

vulkan: 75 - 34 - 21 - 20 - 36

dx9: 80 - 37 - 22 - 21 - 43

dx11: 70 - 26 - 17 - 17 - 34

I also tried Linux. On Linux I use Arch Linux, and my DE is i3wm, so the cpu / memory usage is minimum. And I don't have anything runing in the background. I used the intel drivers. Vulkan did not worked, so only opengl:

linux_gl: 70 - 26 - 17 - 17 - 34

So yeah, on Linux it is way worse than Windows.

Using the minimum setting the game gets easy 70 FPS, so it is very playable, but if you want it to look better, you need to set for like 30 FPS.

DX9 is the way to go, on medium settings it gives 3-5 more frames than the other options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help choosing a LGA1155 motherboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 12:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yesterday I bought a new CPU, I bought a i5-3470s to update my FX 6100. I know this might seem old and crapy here, but it is the best I can afford, and the FX 6100 was giving me problems with 1080 videos.

Anyway I am now in the search of a LGA1155 mobo. And I see them with a big different range of prices.

I don't plan to OC, or SLI (my gpu is a 750ti), the mobo needs to be mini micro, because my case is not full size.

I am a bit confused, I dont want to spend much, something like 50, and I dont know if that range will give me crap or decent stuff.

I dont know how decent something like this would be:

http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/like/111617728437?lpid=122 chn=ps adgroupid=27378760866 rlsatarget=pla-181484360946 adtype=pla poi= googleloc=1007326 device=c campaignid=620865095 crdt=0

or something like this:

http://www.kikatek.com/P296252/H61M-DGS-ASRock-H61M-DGS-Motherboard-Core-i7-i5?source=froogle gclid=COrNtsPfp88CFbYW0woduYQE4A

I dont know if these ones are decent, horrible, or if theres better stuff for the money

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zidane FK against Las Palmas 15 years ago. You just cannot place it better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 11:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mourinho: "Florentino asked me to return and clean the team from Casillas, Pepe, Ramos, Marcelo,..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 11:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I dispose of single use alkaline batteries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 14:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I am from almost every supermarket has a special bin for used batteries. I am talking about old school alkaline batteries.

I use them a lot because my keyboard uses them (it it wireless). I have around my house like 20 used batteries at the moment.

Where can I dispose them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Filipe Luis' foot after Luis Suarez tackle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 11:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several studies published today concur that all current global human populations stem from a single wave of expansion out of Africa. Yet one has found 2% of the genome in Papuan populations points to an earlier separate event  and an extinct lineage that made it to the islands of Southeast Asia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change drove early humans out of Africa over 125,000 years. Shifts in the Earth's rotation led to wetter climate that influenced population movements out of Africa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best fighting book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to buy a fighting book for a friend who loves MMA, but the book doesn't need to be about MMA, it can be about fighting.

I was going to buy the Mark Hunt book, but it is 30, which is out of my pocket. My budget is around 10 pounds.

Seeing through Amazon I can see a lot of books based on fighters, like Ronda, Conor,... no idea if they are any good.

Any recommendation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robbie Lawler cam (UFC 201) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the world only had 100 countries but all of them with a similar population (around 75m each) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 13:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the world only had 100 countries but all of them with a similar population (around 75m each) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 11:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have presented a statistical model that describes the process of mate selection in online dating. The researchers, who looked at 1,855 users of an online dating site, analyzed why cyber singles choose to look at and message certain potential partners. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 11:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breast cancer cells found to switch molecular characteristics. Spontaneous interconversion between HER2-positive and HER2-negative states could contribute to progression, treatment resistance in breast cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 11:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study adds more evidence supporting the anti-aging effect of caloric restriction. It compared the physiology of mice on restricted diets and mice that could eat whatever they wanted. Cutting calories appeared to affect the brain and neuromuscular system, slowing changes associates with aging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 11:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good curry place, decent price, for big group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will be around 20-40, I don't have the exact number, somewhere around that.

We don't want a cheap, "eat as much as you can" curry place. But we also don't want the other extreme when it is 20 pounds per head.

last time we went to ashoka west end, and I was very disappointed. They also wanted to charge us for 4 people who were reserved but did not appear. Mind you, we were 46 instead of 50, it's not that a big difference in terms of service.

Anywhere in Glasgow is good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers used fMRI with representational similarity analysis to search for a neural code consistent with semantic false memory. They found clear evidence that false memories emerge from a similarity-based neural code in the temporal pole - region that has been called the semantic hub of the brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 10:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UFC 202 PPV is now up for free on Fight Pass (only on certain countries) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 10:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not buy the PPV because I cannot. Today I received a letter at 4am saying that it is up on Fight pass, and hell it is really there.

It seems that now they are uploading the fights with only 48h. That's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland. bite me deep, difficult to remove. 5mm size. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 10:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spammed movie continues to top r/movies and r/all. I guess they need to sell more DVDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lack of oxygen in tumor cells changes the cells gene expression, thereby contributing to the growth of cancer. New research shows that maintaining proper oxygen supply in tumors could be key factor to stop progression of cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new King's College London study reveals that a gene called TRPM2 initiates a 'warm' signal in mice that drives them to seek cooler environments. When this gene is removed, the mice are unable to distinguish between cool and warm temperatures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to open from term an app in a different workspace? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I open something from term, it opens in the same workspace splitting the screen. That is fine as standard behaviour, but sometimes I would like to open the new window in a different workspace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to donate books to public libraries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 11:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything I find is about people who want to donate "collections", but I just want to donate 2-3 normal books that you can buy from anywhere. Just novels.

I don't want to donate them to charities, because I don't agree with how they operate. I'd rather it to be to a public library, university library or something similar. Where I am from there's a place you can leave books, and anyone can take them (I am not speaking about a market, it's a public place). I don't know if this exists in Glasgow.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pulling consecutive all-nighters makes some brain areas groggier than others. Regions involved with problem solving and concentration become sluggish when sleep-deprived, a new study using brain scans reveals. Other areas keep ticking along, appearing to be less affected by a mounting sleep debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers reprogram brain cells in mice with thin beam of light demonstrating that a set of neurons trained to fire in unison could be reactivated as much as a day later if just one neuron was stimulated. Their findings suggest that groups neurons may form the basic building blocks of learning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have uncovered previously hidden sources of ocean pollution along more than 20% of America's coastlines. it offers the first-ever map of underground drainage systems connecting groundwater and seawater, and also pinpoints sites where drinking water is most vulnerable to saltwater </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 11:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warming oceans may be boosting levels of dangerous bacteria in northern seas, possibly explaining why more people are getting sickened by tainted seafood and seawater, new research suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how to get temp in an thinkpad x230? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 19:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am tring i3 status to show my temperature. I followed the guide, and it just says "cant read temp"

I guess the path I put is wrong. I wonder if anyone knows what's the correct path for a thinkpad x230 (or similar models) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered what causes a switch to flip in our brains and wake us up. The team studied the sleep homeostat in the brain of fruit flies. Each fly has around two dozen sleep-control neurons: If the neurons are electrically active, the fly is asleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have discovered that birds can sleep in flight. They measured the brain activity of frigatebirds and found that they sleep in flight with either one cerebral hemisphere at a time or both hemispheres simultaneously </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a new study, researchers zapped a main component of rocky planets with a laser and discovered something unexpected: Instead of simply melting under suddenly high temperature and pressure, crystals form in liquid as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Increased activity in frontal motor cortex compensates impaired speech perception in older adults. Relative to young adults, older adults show higher activation of frontal speech motor areas as measured by functional MRI during a syllable identification task at varying signal-to-noise ratios. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study show that relational exchange, where healthy people fill in for sick ones temporarily inherit their social contacts, can actually spread the epidemic to more peoplejust before an epidemic peaks, the team calculates, leading to an exponential increase in the number of new cases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 10:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about card readers and gratuity tips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has happened to me lately in a few restaurants (both small restaurants but also popular chains), that when I go to pay with my card, the machine asks me if I want to give a gratuity tip.

At first I thought this was a great idea because that means I don't need to search for coins in my pocket.

But then, the question is, are the workers really getting my tip? How much of it are they getting?

With classic cash tips, workers put them in a jar or similar, and then divide at the end of the day. Some dodgy bosses take a cut. I wonder if this gratuity tip thing is a scam for workers. I understand it might work in small restaurants where the person serving you is also the owners, but I don't know about big chain.

So my question is simple, to those working in a place with automated gratuity tip, are you getting the money? Or should I ignore the option and leave my tip in cash.

PD: Please avoid the discussion about if we should leave tips or not. That's another topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comparisons of oral nongender-blind tests with written gender-blind tests for about 100,000 individuals observed in 11 different fields over the period 20062013 reveal a bias in favor of women that is strongly increasing with the extent of a fields male-domination. (study done in France) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaching accreditation exams reveal grading biases favor women in male-dominated disciplines. Comparisons of oral nongender-blind tests with written gender-blind tests for about 100,000 individuals reveal a bias in favor of women that is increasing with the extent of a fields male-domination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 10:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the stranges fights ever, Nick Diaz vs Koji Oishi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers have discovered a new type of binary star, in which a rapidly-spinning white dwarf star sweeps powerful beams of particles and radiation over its companion red dwarf star, causing it to pulse across almost the entire electromagnetic spectrum from the UV to radio. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only way to stop Nate Diaz is to literally bat his head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ceres should be riddled with craters, but it is relatively smooth. Now researchers think that the "peculiar composition and internal evolution" of Ceres must have erased larger impact basins somehow. They found signs of multiple large craters hiding below a surface smoothed with smaller impacts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 11:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great hammerhead sharks swim on their side to reduce transport costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 10:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the step dad said at first that it wasn't her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 12:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is something that surprised me. But then he said it was her. I think the pictures were very clear.

What if the dead girl was not actually her step daughter but just someone who went into the house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you like the way TNO approaches the law / jail system, I recommend you the french movie "A Prophet" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 12:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Prophet

97% in rotten tomatoes.

In particular the first 30 minutes or so from "A Prophet" are very similar to how Nasir is protrayed in prison in TNO. Same kind of cold approach without much drama.

A prophet is a hard movie though. There's a scene in the first 30 minutes which is one of the hardest I have seen in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have mapped the structural changes that occur in teenagers' brains as they develop, showing how these changes may help explain why the first signs of mental health problems often arise during late adolescence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 11:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new global study has found that one in three large cities spend 50 percent more on water treatment costs as a result of damage to the ecological quality of their watersheds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 11:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yale physicists have created something similar to a Moebius strip of moving energy between two vibrating objects, opening the door to novel forms of control over waves in acoustics, laser optics, and quantum mechanics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 10:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research improves the 2014 Chemistry Nobel prize about super-resolution fluorescence microscopy by making it faster, simpler, less expensive, and increasing its resolution by four fold. Spectroscopic photon localization microscopy (SPLM) can analyze individual molecules with sub-nm resolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 10:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An anti-malaria drug could help radiotherapy destroy tumours according to new study. It slows down the rate at which cancer cells use oxygen by targeting the mitochondria, the powerhouses of the cell that make energy, a process that uses oxygen. Tested on tumours with low oxygen levels in mice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 10:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Zika case in Europe happened in Barcelona (Spain) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The day the hardest kicker in the game, Jose Aldo, won a fight by soccer kicks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question to Three mobile users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 11:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this is the wrong subreddit to ask, you are welcome to point me in the right direction.

I have been with Three for 4 years. Recently, as with everyone, my bill went up 6.5 pounds a month. I am paying now 20 pounds a month.

I have seen lately they have this offer about six months half price. I wonder if I could call and get it, or if it is only for new clients. In which case, I wonder if I can say "ok I leave you" and then get it, or if there's no way at all to get it.

20 pounds a month is quite a lof for what I do with my phone (wi fi all the time). My data use is around 1gb a month. I never call, and I never send texts. So I plan to change my tariff and get something cheaper, and I wonder if I could get the 50% discount.

thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A serious childhood cancer takes advantage of a quality control mechanism that usually protects cells from stress-induced damage to propel tumor growth. By blocking that mechanism, the scientists were able to kill cells derived from patients with rhabdomyosarcoma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 11:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> W10 takes a lot to boot (around 2 minutes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 11:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The computer is a Thinkpad x230, 8gb of ram and the cpu is i5 3320m. It is not a powerhouse, but it is a decent computer. The hard disk is just HDD (not SSD).

I disabled the fastboot option because I have Linux dual booting here (Linux boots in 25 seconds)

It takes around 2:10 from power button to getting the windows sound. The desktop appears at 1:30, but most of the things in the start bar are empty.

I have tried to remove as many things as I could from the start, like I don't even start Dropbox. Based on the Task manager, everything left starting is "low" (basically audio and usb), and the bios startup is 4.6 seconds.

I don't know if this is normal. The only "strange" thing I have done is changing my user name. It is a fresh w10 installation (it was a w7 fresh, updated to w10).

There were no pending updates or anything like that, and I have just booted the laptop like 5 times in a a row, always the same result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers report that cyclin, an enzyme that is highly expressed by neurons in many brain cancers, may dampen the ability of T cells to reject tumors. In a mouse model of medulloblastoma, if tumors were cyclin deficient, T cells were able to remove them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 11:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a step toward devising complex cellular circuits, MIT engineers have programmed cells to remember and respond to a series of events. These cells can remember, in the correct order, up to three different inputs, but this approach should be scalable to incorporate many more stimuli </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 11:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European football: Goals change crowd air chemistry. The emission rates of particular chemicals in the audience's breath vary sharply  apparently in response to events on the football pitch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 12:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineers program E. coli to destroy tumor cells. They programmed harmless strains of bacteria to deliver toxic payloads. When deployed together with a traditional cancer drug, the bacteria shrank aggressive liver tumors in mice much more effectively than either treatment alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 11:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New electrochemical cells use a aluminium as the anode and co2 and oxygen as cathode. It sequesters the carbon dioxide into carbon-rich compounds while also producing electricity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 11:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Duffy slick boxing tagging Dustin Poirier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti piracy tools during the 80s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti piracy tools during the 80s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eruptions from supervolcanoes may be controlled by large, dense magma reservoirs, which keep magma stored away beneath a thick overlying crust until an eruption takes place. These findings stem from a new seismic model of the magma paths beneath the Toba supervolcano in Indonesia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [help] GPS enabled (and draining battery) even when it should be disabled (cm13, motog 4g) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the name says, the GPS seems to be enabled, even when I have disabled it. In particular, I don't remember using it in the last 24h, and the maps app (which I havent used) has consumed a 33% of my battery through GPS.

the gps is actually consuming battery now, even though I have double check it is disabled everywhere. And the only apps I am using at the moment are reddit is fun, whatsapp, email. None of them are supposed to be using my gps.

By the way, I don't play Pokemon Go or anything similar
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [help] GPS enabled (and draining battery) even when it should be disabled (cm13, motog) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the name says, the GPS seems to be enabled, even when I have disabled it. In particular, I don't remember using it in the last 24h, and the maps app (which I havent used) has consumed a 33% of my battery through GPS.

the gps is actually consuming battery now, even though I have double check it is disabled everywhere. And the only apps I am using at the moment are reddit is fun, whatsapp, email. None of them are supposed to be using my gps.

By the way, I don't play Pokemon Go or anything similar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 37-year-old man has stabbed a mother and her three daughters at a vacation center in southeast France for being dressed too lightly, local authorities said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [help] Firefox crashing constantly (Linux) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been happening since yesterday in 2 different computers connected to different networks. It has just been crashing constantly, and after a while it tells me that some script is blocking the execution, so I can stop it, but that doesn't really fixes anything.

It has happened in very different websites, so I cannot pinpoint where is the problem coming from.

Checking top Firefox is using 2.2g of memory, 8 tabs opened, the only one there that can be memory/cpu consuming is youtube.

Writting this from Chrome :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists discover how proteins in the brain build-up rapidly in Alzheimer's using a combination of computer simulations and laboratory experiments to identify the necessary requirements for the build-up of the disease-causing 'plaques' that are characteristic of Alzheimer's disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physicists have just invented a zero-knowledge warhead inspection system using physical encryption that allows warhead scanning without revealing too much. Inspectors would send a high-energy x-ray beam through a warhead in which some of the x-ray photons would be absorbed by nuclear materials. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Investigators have discovered that cells from HIV-infected people whose virus is suppressed with treatment harbor defective HIV DNA that can nevertheless be transcribed into a template for producing HIV-related proteins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nate toying with Cowboy's head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Continental breakup is still not understood. New research shows that the continents initially stretch very slowly along the future splitting zone, but then move apart very quickly before the onset of rupture. The final speed can be up to 20 times faster than in the first slow extension phase. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 17:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't a huge conflict of interests that the new owners of UFC are also managing fighters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 21:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see this going wrong in so many way:

* Favourable match making or title shots to their own fighters. I mean, their manager, who happens to be the same as the ufc, will only renew is the fighter gets a title shot. Ronda for example is managed by them. I don't think Ronda deserves a title shot now, after two different belt fights while she was resting. 

* Forcing fighters to be managed by them. "If you let us manage you we will offer you a better deal".

* Forcing fighters to agree to worse deals once they are inside.  As manager and owner, the fighter would be completely isolated.

In case you think points 2 and 3 are the opposite, this is what supermarkets do when they open a new one in a new area: big chain opens supermarket, lowers the prices to the point that all the other supermarkets need to close, once they are alone the put the prices high.

Considering that IMG by owning UFC what they are basically owning are the contracts and the library, I see this like the boss being also the union. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New material made of carbon nanotubes supports the growth of nerve fibers, bridging segregated neural explants and providing a functional re-connection. Implanting it into the brain of small rodents did not marked immune response. It could be evaluated for prosthetic nervous system applications. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 12:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about battery lifespan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 12:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a macbook, and there are a lot of theories there about how to maximize your battery lifespan, to calibrate it,... My battery was dead after 3 years.

I just bought a Thinkpad x230 second hand, and so far I love it. The capacity of the battery is 86.74% (I think this is pretty good for second hand). Also, I am a Linux user (with i3) and I am getting 9h of battery, which is quite good.

I wonder if there is there any tips about how to maximizing the battery. I've looked around, and basically the common tip is "remove the battery when you are at home". Does this really help? If the battery is at 100% and connected to the AC, does it make a difference or is the battery permanently charging / discharging?

Do you do full cycles at least once a month? Do you calibrate your battery?

I am just interested to see what Thinkpad users do. As everyone, I'd like to maximize the lifespan of my battery, I don't want it to be dead after 3 years.

thanks !

So far I love this x230. best keyboard I have had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 68% of porguese people would like a political union with Spain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 15:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists recruited 48 trained amateur cyclists and gave them either EPO or a placebo for 8 weeks. Participants were subjected to seven endurance tests. The researchers are still analyzing results but have already shared one key outcome: Riders on EPO weren't faster than those on placebo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 10:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists recruited 48 trained amateur cyclists and gave them either EPO or a placebo for 8 weeks. Participants were subjected to seven endurance tests. The researchers are still analyzing results but have already shared one key outcome: Riders on EPO weren't faster than those on placebo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 10:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Before joining the UFC, Lineker had 24 fights in 3 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 16:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised by his "bad" record, 28 and 7. (27-7 before yesterday), because they said he was on a 4 win streak, and he is only 26 years old. 

He lost 5 fights between August and December 2009

During 2009 he had 9 fights in 10 months for a record of 4-5.

From 2010 onwards his record is 21-2.

Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Lineker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James (RMadrid) doesn't appear on his hearing for speed limit violation (200kmh) because he was in Miami celebrating his birthday party. The judge just asked him to come on another date. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 11:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor nutrition during pregnancy stunts the growth of young mice by modifying their gene expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 11:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a new method of creating human pluripotent stem by cells in a minimal medium without the need for costly and time-consuming biological substrates using a protein derived from human blood called Inter-alpha inhibitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have developed a system that generates electricity from osmosis with unparalleled efficiency. Their work, featured in Nature, uses seawater, fresh water, and a new type of membrane just 3 atoms thick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to list installed apps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just starting with i3wm, until no I have been using gnome3 for like 5 years. In Gnome when you go to the up left corner you see your main apps installed (like firefox, libreoffice, texstudio,...).

I want the same kind of funcitonality in i3.

So far I am using "dmenu", but it basically lists everything, and if you don't remember the name of an app you are done.

thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In half of Europe it is impossible to walk more than 1.5km without finding some kind of transportation infrastructure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 11:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research from offers a more complete picture of the genes responsible for type 2 diabetes, demonstrating that previously identified common alleles shared by many in the world are the biggest culprits-not the less common variants scientists thought might play a large role in who gets the disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 11:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dana White: "We have plans for Dan Henderson" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second week Fight Pass replay is a disaster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 12:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same stuff happened to me with the card Wonderboy vs Rory. Both cards after the update.

Watching the replay of the fights the next day is almost impossible.

The markers are completely off, all of them in 1 mm at the start. They are useless.

There is no way to navigate through the fights. Clicking anywhere in the status bar is useless, clicking directly in a fight is useless, clicking in the "fight card" button and choosing a fight is useless.

The only way to do it is to click +10 seconds. In a fight card that is 335 minutes this is a joke. If I want to watch RDA's fight I need to click +10 second for 20 minutes. But wait wait, at some point it will always go back to minute 0. Also, if I press full screen, it goes back to minute 0.

This happened during Wonderboy vs Rory and I had to torrent the fight because it was impossible to watch in Fight Pass. Same crap is happening now 3 weeks later.

All this used to work perfectly with the previous fight pass.

Fix this shit goofs or I am stopping my monthly fee.

PD: UFC reads more this forum than the emails sent to them.

EDIT: Great, after 10 minutes of clicking +10s it just logged me out so I have to do it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freed in Madrid (Spain) a 19 years old teen who had been locked in his room for 2 years by his father </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 11:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have come up with a mathematical equation that when solved is meant to offer a means for estimating how often life begins on other planets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 21:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit's parent company puts into top /r/pics and /r/all one of their other products </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 21:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I am speaking about:

https://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4r7ki0/antipaparazzi_scarf_that_ruins_photos_by/?st=iq8fbtgq sh=4a93c100

Obviously one of the comments tells you how to buy it:

https://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4r7ki0/antipaparazzi_scarf_that_ruins_photos_by/d4yyxrk

In the on-line shop you can even click to the Conde Nast review.

You can see the review they did in their own magazine here: http://www.cntraveler.com/stories/2016-06-30/the-ishu-privacy-scarf-is-hollywoods-new-favorite-travel-accessory

I guess nowadays as part of the package you can get a top Reddit link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Union asks 7 spanish clubs to return 69 millions ruled as illegal help from the government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the cross between St Vicent St and W Nile St need 4 burger joints? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was walking today around that area, and it's a big shocking. Especially the fact that Handmade Burger Co and Gourmet Burger Kitchen are one against the other and they seem to focus on the same style of cooking burgers. At first I actually thought it was the same company, but no.

Exactly besides Gourmet Burger you have Fives guys, and 20 seconds away you have Bread Meats Bread. Five Guys is the only one that is a bit different. Because it is less "gourmer" and more "american dirty".

It seems a bit crazy. It made me remember when in the TV series Deadwood they open a pub in front of his pub.

Have you visit any of them? Any good?

I've tried a Five Guys but in another city. it was OK but I wouldn't go again. I am not a big fan of bugers, though. I tried years ago ketchup in the West End and it was OK, but the last time I went it was vomitive. I also enjoyed the ones in Bruadar, but I guess no one else enjoyed them, because the place closed.

I don't really understand all this thing about burgers. It is something you can easily cook at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spains jobless claims show biggest June drop in a decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 11:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Scotland gets independent and joins the EU, can Michael Gove still be an english PM without being an english citizen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 23:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gove is born in Edinburgh. He is a British citizen. If Scotland gets independent we can assume he would be an Scottish citizen. He can later on apply for the English citizenship, but there will probably be a small period of just paper work and bureaucracy. Yes, he has been living in England for something like 30 years, but he never applied for the citizenship.

I just wonder what would happen if he was the PM of a country he is not even citizen. 

Considering how the Tories are turning into Game of Thrones, my call is Theresa May will call for the Scottish referendum just to get rid of Gove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panama canal amplification in 2 minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 18:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During spanish GE this Sunday, at least 2000 votes were considered spoilt because the ballot had a slightly different logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 15:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reserachers have developed and tested in mice a technique for packaging antigens that induce an immune response in vaccines, which combines E. coli bacteria and a biocompatible polymer material. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 11:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real Madrid told by EU to repay millions in illegal state support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 10:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 month old SD card giving me problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 21:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, my phone is a XT1309. And my SO is CM 13.0, just updated today.

A month and a half ago I bought the sd card "SanDisk Ultra Android 32 GB microSDHC Class 10". It is supposed to be good. I decided to use it as local disk, so everything now is installed there. It has been working fine, but yesterday the phone told me the card was missing. After rebooting it, it was fine. But today it is doing the same constantly. After 30 minutes or so it tells me that the card is missing, and the only thing I can do is to update it. I cannot take pictures or see my gallery or do anything. Removing and inserting the card doesnt work, only reboot works.

Everything seems to point to my SD card being defective, but I want to rule out first a phone / software problem. This is the first card I use. And it is also strange that after booting it works fine, so I don't know if it has a RAM / swap problem, or if it becomes corrupted after some use or something similar.

The card is almost new, just a month and a half. And it was working fine until yesterday. I don't really remember doing anything yesterday that could have stopped my card. It failed just after waking up.

I am not a heavy user. I dont install many apps, I don't take many pictures.

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> problems with e3d v6 after a good working year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sorry if the title is all in capitals, I cannot change it.

I have been using the e3d v6 for like a year with very good results. Something like 2 weeks ago I tried a new filament (always PLA) and there is when the problems started. I tried for a day, but I couldn't print anything. Every time it looked fine, and then at some point it stopped extruding.

I've gone back now to my working filament (verbatim), and the problems persists.

See album attached: http://imgur.com/a/lnwtE

I thought it was more a problem with the motor and the hobbed bolt, but while it is printing the bad layers, it seems to move as usual. if I pause it, I cannot really extrude pusing it manually, but if I pull it, and push it, then it works fine again (until it stops printing).

When I pull the filament it doesn't look strange. It's not like folding or anything.

I also tried cleaning the nozzle inserting a needle through it.

I don't really know where the problem is.

thanks !

EDIT: I have replaced the nozzle and the motor driver, and the problem persists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on with the racist incidents appearing everywhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 15:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The six EU founding members ask the UK to leave asap and no "cat and mouse" game. "The people have spoken and we need to implement this decision." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 15:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From an EU citizien living in Scotland: Thank you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been living in Scotland for some years. It is the third european country where I have lived (I work in academia, researcher, high mobility), and the one I liked the most. I love its cities, its character, its landscape, and especially its people.

I remember the first time I went to a pub here, my first week in. While I was waiting to order something an old man near me started to chat with me. That had never happened to me before. We started to talk about football, which was a mistake, because at some point he asked me if I prefer Celtic or Rangers, and I said that I don't care. An answer he didn't like, so we almost had a fight, but at the end everything was cool and he paid me a pint, although when I left I said "see you later" and he said "I don't think so". 

I never knew what my future would be, but a few years ago I considered staying in Scotland in a more permanent way, and work together with you to make this, your country, a better place. I always felt welcome. That's why when the whole referendum initiated the situation started to be grim. Nothing really happened in real life, quite the opposite, every person I met was 100% remain, but the debate here in Reddit or in the main media websites was quite toxic. As a EU citizen I felt offended a few times, and the few times I ask them to tone down their debate, I was told I don't even have the right to feel offended. I started to feel paranoid and I tried to minimise social interaction with strangers, just in case.

That's why I say thank you, Scotland, for trusting us all. For making us feel welcome. I don't know what's going to happen, maybe I will need to leave your country in 2 years. Maybe I am out of a job in a year and I need to go somewhere. I don't know. Meanwhile I will try my best to pay you back. I don't want to make a politicial statement, but I really hope you get a second indyref.

From your average random EU migrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French President Hollande: "All the procedures required to exit should be made as soon as possible" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French President Hollande: "All the procedures required to exit should be made as soon as possible" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found that planes passing through clouds make them brighter and cause them to reflect more sunlight back into space. It wont make up for all the CO2 emissions, but this discovery assists the general cooling effect of contrails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 11:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientist discovered that by running liquid chocolate through an electric field, they were able to remove up to 20% of the fat while making the end product tastier. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refugees can offer economic boost to their host countries. Research indicates that refugees receiving aidespecially in the form of cashcan give their host country's economy a substantial boost.The researchers found that these economic benefits significantly exceeded the amount of the donated aid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Based on observational field work, patients who heard their surgeon explicitly disclose specialty bias had higher likelihoods of choosing surgery than patients who did not hear their surgeons disclose bias (RR 2.07, 95% CI 1.47-2.92). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers found that the amount of DNA methylation that is hard wired into the production of each individual's oxytocin plays a dramatic role in the persons social skills and adaptability to social situations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Torbe (De Gea prostitution scandal): "There are many more football players involved, but the police doesn't want to know their names" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Del Bosque: "Pedro is sorry. He didn't want to insult anyone" (5 minutes later) Pedro: "I am not sorry. I don't think I should be sorry for what I said" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favourite baked beans and sausage tin ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 15:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering, I've never had them before but a friend recommended them to me. She said best ones are from Asda, but probably my first try will be Heinz because I already like their soups. 

Any recommendation for brand or tinned food in general ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [spoiler] Dana's reaction to Fedor's fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 15:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have developed a hybrid photodetector capable of attaining concomitantly better performance features in terms of speed, quantum efficiency and linear dynamic range, operating not only in the visible but also in the near infrared (NIR: 700-1400nm) and SWIR range (1400-3000nm) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 13:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered the cause of a mass extinction of sea-floor marine organisms 800,000 years ago. They tested various possible causes and were able to discount others such as ocean cooling. They discovered that it was caused by a global change in plankton at the surface of the ocean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 13:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carrots and sticks fail to change behaviour in cocaine addiction. People who are addicted to cocaine are particularly prone to developing habits that render their behaviour resistant to change, regardless of the potentially devastating consequences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 12:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study published today in Science, shows that boreal forests in far-northern latitudes may one day act as a climate refuge for black spruce, the foundational tree for the northwoods ecosystem; home to caribou, snowshoe hare, lynx, and sable; and nesting site for dozens of migratory bird species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 12:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [wanted] laptop 13 or 14 inches max </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a budget of around 200-300 pounds.

I want an i5 (although  an i3 would be ok in some cases). 4-8g of ram. Intel HD graphic card.

I don't care much about the HDD (or SSD).

Preferably IBM or Lenovo or one of the likes (avoid stuff like acer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> scientists have combined biology and 3-D printing to create the first reactor that can continuously produce methanol from methane at room temperature and pressure. They removed enzymes from methanotrophs and mixed them with polymers that they printed or molded into innovative reactors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boon or burden: what has the EU ever done for science? Ahead of a possible Brexit, "Nature" examines five core ways that the EU shapes the course of research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers demonstrated new technique to find "ligands" (binding partners) for many proteins previously thought to bind poorly to small molecules that can be used to determine the functions of their protein targets and can serve as starting compounds for the development of drugs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1979 World Disco dancing finals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new equation showing how our happiness depends not only on what happens to us but also how this compares to other people, has been developed. The study found that inequality reduced happiness on average.This was true whether people were doing better or worse than another person they had just met. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 11:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers report that infant monkeys who engaged in more neonatal face-to-face interactions with mothers have increased social interactions at 2 and 5 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 11:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phylogenetic comparative methods and a sample of over 500 mammalian species show that mammals in which males carry the offspring have shorter lactation periods, which leads to more frequent breeding events. Provisioning the female is associated with larger litters and shorter lactation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 11:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study shows that the final grades that college students received in a second-language class were predicted by a combination of genetic and brain factors. Genetic variations of the COMT gene white matter accounted for 46 percent of the reason for why some students performed better than others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers measured heart and electrical activity of the brain during sleep. They found that the beat-to-beat variation in heart rate accounted for much of the previously unexplained variation in how well people performed on memory and creativity tests following a nap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An all-UC San Diego team is reporting that it has found out how to more accurately detect single-nucleotide variations in DNA using nanoelectronics. It could lead to more reliable DNA-based diagnostics, such as miniaturized, implantable sequencing biosensors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liquid drops on soft solid surfaces interact by an 'inverted Cheerios effect', which can be tweaked so that the droplets move towards or away from each other, according to an international group of scientists publishing in the journal PNAS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a new essential sequence within bacterial genomes required for DNA replication - the second ever to be discovered and the first for 30 years. The "DnaA-trio" is described as a core element of bacterial replication origins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A second protected under 18 declares Torbe recorded her naked for De Gea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A second protected witness under 18 declares Torbe recorded her naked for De Gea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New longitudinal data sets from offline and online operational networks [for example, ISIS (Islamic State)] shows that although men dominate numerically, women emerge with superior network connectivity that can benefit the underlying systems robustness and survival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 13:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fedor vs Maldonado epic promo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 14:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have made the first autonomous chemically powered synthetic small-molecule motor. The new device, which is very much like the protein motors found in biological cells, might be used to design artificial molecular machines similar to those found in nature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using laboratory techniques to mimic the conditions (900,000 times normal atmospheric pressure and 3200F) found deep inside the Earth, scientists have identified a form of iron oxide that they believe could explain seismic and geothermal signatures in the deep mantle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK government slammed for losing track of its own research. Government can't say how many policy studies it paid for or published, report reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 11:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iconic Willow Tea Rooms brewing move to Watt Brothers department store as Trust revamp historic Mackintosh building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 18:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enrique Wasabi (who will fight next against Sage Northcutt) last fight in the TUF house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have developed rice crops with an improved ability to manage their own pH levels, enabling them to take up significantly more nitrogen, iron and phosphorous from soil and increase yield by up to 54 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Novel imaging model helps reveal new therapeutic target for pancreatic cancer. New study describes new model that not only allowed to track drug resistance in vivo, but also revealed a new therapeutic target, which early testing suggests could provide a strategy to arrest pancreatic cancer growth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A toxin isolated from the Togo starburst tarantula provides new insights into pain mechanisms and could lead to new treatments for irritable bowel syndrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long-term memory test could aid earlier Alzheimer's diagnosis. Scientists say testing memory over a long timescale reveals early deficits in the brains ability to remember. These are not detected by checks for short-term forgetfulness, which is the current practice for diagnosis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 11:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out there for 10p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 19:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.miclos.google.games.outthere

I cannot send the link because it was already submitted. But this is a great offer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decades of college-educated singles marrying each other hasn't changed our genetic makeup: study shows there were no changes in the presence of genes linked to educational attainment. There also was no association towards genes influencing their offspring's height, BMI, or depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple exercises to help incoming students understand the challenges that they would face in college substantially improved the success achieved by first generation and minority students. Interventions could help close persistent achievement gaps occurring in higher education institutions nationwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Facebook forcing messenger to browser users ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK voters leaning towards Brexit, Guardian poll reveals. Phone and online survey shows a 52-48 split in favour of leaving the EU as referendum campaign gathers steam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK voters leaning towards Brexit, Guardian poll reveals. Phone and online survey shows a 52-48 split in favour of leaving the EU as referendum campaign gathers steam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who voted no during indyref, if the UK leaves, would that change your opinion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 11:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember one of the big points of the referendum was about Scotland being part (or not) of the EU. People who went for the NO said that Scotland won't be able to be part of the EU short term, or even long term saying that some countries will always veto it.

Sorry if this has already been discussed here before. I used the search engine, and although the next referendum has been discussed a lot, I could not find anything about no voters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berkeley researchers report a major advance in understanding how oxygen oxidation creates extra capacity in such lithium-rich cathodes, opening the door to batteries with far higher energy density, meaning your phone or electric vehicle will be able to run for much longer between charges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barao as BW pre USADA, BW USADA, and FW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please UFC TV, do not spoil the results at least for 24h (as you usually do) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 22:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mazzagatti destroys the GOAT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atmospheric aerosols, particles once thought to need human-generated sulfur dioxide to form, can form from other, naturally occurring compounds alone, according to a series of new reports. The discovery has significant implications for modeling the effects of these particles on climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Results from laboratory experiments and mouse studies suggest that small doses of drugs from a specific class of approved cancer medications called topoisomerase 1 (top1) inhibitors may protect against the overwhelming immune response to infection that sometimes leads to sepsis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frankie Edgar: "That was one of the nastiest KOs I have seen in my life" (TUF19) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 14:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Although a fruit fly is only a few millimeters long, its sperm reach an impressive length of almost six centimeters. The longer the sperm become the fewer of them can be produced and transferred. Females have to mate more frequently to ensure fertilization of their eggs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 11:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have uncovered a new class of galaxies, called "red geysers," with supermassive black hole winds so hot and energetic that stars can't form. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A team of MIT researchers has discovered that light can "heal" defects in certain solar cells. The materials healed in the study are perovskites, which can be used to create thin films with numerous electronic and optical properties and have the potential to be used in solar cell applications. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 11:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changes in neural circuitry during adolescence are associated with persistent attenuation of fear memories. Findings identify new strategies to leverage neurodevelopmental changes during adolescence to extinguish pathological fears implicated in anxiety and stress-related disorders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 11:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find cellular changes precede ovarian cancer development. Early changes in fallopian tube cells increase risk for ovarian cancer in more than half of women with BRCA 1 and BRCA 2 mutations, which researchers say could lead to a non-invasive test to predict the disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 11:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audio from DJ's corner during UFC197. His team said to someone from UFC they were totally behind TUF. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a miniature microscope that opens a window into the brain, UCLA neuroscientists have identified in mice how the brain links different memories over time. While aging weakens these connections, the team devised a way for the middle-aged brain to reconnect separate memories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineers have developed a flexible wearable device capable of monitoring biochemical and electric signals in the human body. The patch records electrocardiogram heart signals and tracks levels of lactate in real time. It communicates wirelessly with a smartphone, smart watch or laptop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 12:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reserachers discover how a key biochemical enables bacteria to repair otherwise fatal damage to their DNA, including that caused by antibiotics. Adjusting the action of the molecule ppGpp with future treatments may disable DNA repair in microbes to make them more vulnerable to existing antibiotics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 12:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repeated large-scale retreat and advance of Totten Glacier indicated by inland bed erosion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have designed a potential cancer therapy that uses a unique strategy to block mTOR, a molecule that helps drive the growth of many tumors. In animal experiments, the drug reduces the size of tumors that are resistant to earlier-generation mTOR inhibitors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover how antibodies access neurons to fight infection. In response to herpes infection, CD4 T cells entered the nerve tissue, secreted signaling proteins, and allowed antibody access to infected sites. Combined, CD4 T cells and antibodies limited viral spread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have been looking at the breeding habits of fish to test the theory that bigger genitals make males more attractive or successful in fathering offspring. They found that females don't find males with big genitals any more attractive than those with normal or smaller genitals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kharitonov vs Semmy Schilt - brutal ground and pound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New analysis by Stanford computer scientists shows that it is possible to identify a persons private information  such as health details  from telephone metadata alone. Additionally, following metadata hops from one persons communications can involve thousands of other people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statins could protect the hearts of babies in the womb from the adverse effects of their mother's stress, research suggests. Scientists have discovered that the widely-prescribed drugs help to counteract the negative impact of stress hormones on fetal growth and heart development in mice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study indicates that when we act unethically, were more likely to remember these actions less clearly. Researchers coined the term unethical amnesia to describe this phenomenon, which they believe stems from the fact that memories of ourselves acting in ways we shouldnt are uncomfortable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 11:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboy Cerrone accepted the McGregor fight, and was even fighting for 2 days with the camera crew. He also accepted 155. Dana told him to watch SportCenter to be updated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 15:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> clash royale, how much money you need to spend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 13:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to try the game, but I don't like spending money on F2P. Is it possible to play it without paying anything? Otherwise, what would be the minimum investment to make the game playable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Diaz goes to war against Paul Daley in one of the best WW fights ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have created a chip for the nano-manipulation of light, paving the way for next gen optical technologies and enabling deeper understanding of black holes.They designed an integrated nanophotonic chip that can achieve unparalleled levels of control over the angular momentum of light. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 12:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
