<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 22:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know what your point is but drinking age in Alberta, where I reside, is 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 22:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Canada, so it was free (technically). I'm not sure how that would work, to be honest. It could depend on the doctor. Does anyone have more insight into this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hyperbolic speech is a thing, ya know. I have no intention of trying to destroy this man's life, but that being said there needs to be some kind of action taken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even slightly bothered by the hate mail. The supportive messages quadruple the rude ones, and most of the rude ones are so obviously people trying to upset me that it's more humorous than anything. Thanks for the kind words!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know where in the post it says anything about his skin colour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I definitely am not fazed by the rude PMs I've been getting, the positive ones and the supportive comments have 100% overthrown all the grumps that want to make me feel bad about speaking out. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so sweet. I'm going to look into the other two gynos, but a couple of people have mentioned that sometimes GPs can put an IUD in, so I'm gonna check around for that. I definitely won't be seeing this doctor again, so no need to worry! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, a couple people have also PMd me asking what his name was, but I'm not going to tell anybody. Not only for his privacy, but for mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 08:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like ITT: women supporting women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an angel! I appreciate this so much. I'm definitely going to use this when I'm filing my report. Thank you so so much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I searched his name. There are tons of reviews, and they're not good. Thanks for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's one thing to be a jackass about patients when you're in the break room, but it's another to be horrible right to their face! I read his reviews on ratemds and a bunch of people said he's really rough during exams and inserts IUDs incorrectly. I'm going to find a different doctor. Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 06:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Alberta but that sucks that there's more than one of him :( maybe it's like having an evil twin except they're both the evil one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
