<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 04:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have eaten Pho in a couple of dozen places in Australia and it has always been served with lemon. That is probably because limes are much more expensive here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have eaten fresh Maine lobster in the US.  Admittedly it was at red lobster...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have 3 lime trees and 0.5 lemon trees in my garden. I think I belong here... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Limes are insanely expensive in Perth shops ($1-2 each; lemons are about 30-50c ea), but the climate is great for growing them, so as a result I have 2 tahitian lime trees and 1 kaffir lime. 
If you are wondering about the 0.5 lemon, it is a cumquat tree that has sprouted from the root stock (rough/bush lemon). They are not bad as lemons go, a bit similar to a meyer lemon, and can be peeled easily like a mandarin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roasted/Grilled garlic is delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and I did. See my edit in the top comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we paid NZ$50/kg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 01:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We call everything a BBQ here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you search the comments you will see I posted a youtube link to the original (B52s) a few hours ago... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were staying in TeAnau and just bought the ingredients locally and cooked it ourselves. We tried to buy crays off the boats but they didn't have any. We eventually got directions to the processing factory where they sold us some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a couple of times. Ours is much better of course...  
Seriously though, the texture is similar but the flesh of the southern rock lobster is sweeter. Where I live there are 3 crayfish/lobster species that are commonly eaten, but this one is by far the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is probably the cutest baby animal gif I have seen. I feel bad for having posted a picture of venison now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything was cooked on the barbecue/grill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's "fookin potatos" precious???
if this had been posted by u/precious that would have worked much better... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I responded to this below. Where I come from we call them a "Southern Rock Lobster" https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jasus_edwardsii
Get back to me when family guy do some cool songs about crayfish and I might reconsider...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Yes, most definitely.
2. Lamb is one of the most commonly eaten meats in both Australia and NZ. Generally much less expensive than beef.
3. Venison seemed common in NZ, every farm we passed had some deer, however we were told this was wild not farmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We normally prefer red, but the lobster took precedence... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One person who has done lots of hiking and kayaking... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I usually cut my sprouts in half and grill them without foil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sorry. It was all rare or medium-rare though. I was cooking on a guesthouse BBQ though, so it is not as good a job as I would have done at home... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was after a day of hiking (tramping as the Kiwis call it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=szhJzX0UgDM
Will this do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the link was going to be this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f31mB6apCoE
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 15:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.huntaway.co.nz/Range/Huntaway-Reserve-Gisborne-Pinot-Gris-750ml
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 14:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can always change their name to Russell Crowefish if it makes you happier...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
