<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3387</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 17:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a strange one. Like the bridge in osaka is "nippon bashi" whereas a bridge in Tokyo of the same kanji is "nihon bashi". I really think it just goes with whatever is generally accepted in society. In sports or politics you hear "nippon" being used by supporters so maybe it has a stronger feel to the word. 

Generally nihon is used in speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 11:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although  or  is just the  form of . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 11:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either you guys are right or my or my japanese teacher is poor at explaining. I'm sticking with what I was taught until I double check this with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 01:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the case of  or , it is the latter, with the meaning "the speaker receives the favor (from the listener) of being able to take a picture."

Exactly my point.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 00:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is a loan word. It's the japanese version of "tobacco". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 00:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kutsu too I think? I recall my korean friend saying that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 23:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have it backwards. 
...... - "is it ok to take a picture"
...... - "is it ok to get you to take a picture" 

 is a causative verb form of "toru" (to take a picture or film). Causative verbs can be translated as "to make/to have somebody do something".

For example -  (seito ni eigo wo benkyou sasete mo ii desu ka) would be something like "is it OK if I make the students study english?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 13:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with meteor. I pay 10 euro a month for unlimited data. 

All my texts are sent through WhatsApp or Viber.

For calls I used credit that I bought on Viber. I bought 5 last October and i still have 1 left. I rarely make calls however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 13:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on context using . 

In addition to the above, it was also be used to soften the blow when asking a question. 

Example: . "Could impossible get you to take a picture". The  makes it less of a direct question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 00:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R$1500 isn't bad compared to European prices. Thank you for your help again. I will look into these areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 00:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, thanks for the offer. Unfortunately I am looking for somewhere furnished. I need somewhere with at least a bed. Thanks though.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 00:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is not really a problem. Compared to Europe, rent is cheaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 23:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're not brazillian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be the safest, cheapest option. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I wasnt expecting such a big response. Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this very detailed response. I really appreciate it. Ill check out all these places. 

Generally is the bus safe to ride at night around the city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link, I will check this out. It could be ok temporarily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say "money to spend", what can I expect for an apartment in Bela Vista or Moinhos de Vento? R$700 as the above comment says for appartments near PUCRS?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nightmare? That sounds bad. She moved there by choice as an exchange student from Europe for 1 year. I am also from Europe and plan to visit for 90 days (the length my tourist visa will allow). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats good to know. My girlfriend is there at the moment and I'm really concerned for her safety. This is a relief!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice. I heard that it's not a good idea to walk at night. I'll be careful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your help and your offer for PM. Ill check out some places near Praa da Encol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question, I never thought about this. I think maybe we might prefer to have our own accommodation and space?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Safe place to live near PUCRS, Porto Alegre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 10:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, my girlfriend just moved to Porto Alegre to study in PUCRS. I am going to visit her for 3 months soon. Can anybody recommend any safe areas near PUCRS? Somewhere where it is safe to walk to visit her. I'm concerned about security.

Some people recommended Moinhos de Vento and Auxiliadora, but these seem very far away. Thank you in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2:1 in biological science.  Didn't do shit with it. Travelled and taught English for a while. Went back and did a h.dip in business with a language - beginning to do something with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost English man confused by Welsh language. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
