<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone with experience help me with Nioh questions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck do I pull off killing the guys at the top of hill? It's 1 playing bait, 2 on the left, and the big guy on the right. 


If I play a different game, is my progress gone? 


If I summon my pet to the shrine, will I lose the cash I had on my corpse?


What are the numbers in the bottom? I get that the bottom left is cash, what is above that, and to the right. 


What does summoning a visitor do? 


Thanks for any answers!

Edit: so it seems going left at the second village (2 guys are farming on the left, and there's a guy in the house on the right) gives you a bow if you manage to make it alive. I'll work back to the building soon and update. This is a phenomenal game so far, if you're willing to take on a challenge and repeat your path a LOT.

Update: killed em all in 1 attempt. I can PM  you about how I went about it if you want, but the bow is incredible help.

Huh... So it now turns out what I expected to be the demo boss is actually a common enemy. Seems like I just found my first pre-order of 2016.

Found the boss of bosses. It's also 11pm and I'm nodding off... Quite the predicament I've got here. 6 hours of my life into this run. Gotta finish now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are some of the stronger champs when it comes to higher ranked tiers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 11:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: God, not champ, sorry, bad habit. 

So I'm level 14 right now, and coming from League, I know that everyone who is easy to stomp with now, may not be the same later on. So instead of fucking over casual with Loki, I'd rather settle back into my Support role, although I'd like to learn general top tier champs too. So who should I be looking to learn, so I ready for ranked when I get 30? 

Also, I understand how this comes off, but Guardians are the only supports in this game, right? Or can I support as a few mages, or even warrior.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for a first time pitcher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm rocking default settings, which is pulse I believe. Is this okay? I heard someone mention meter but I'm not a fan of it. 

My 3 selected pitchers were: 4 seam fb, sinker, and curve ball. I'll be honest and say I'm not sure about the difference between sinker and curve ball but I chose them and I'm not sure if I can go back.

With that said, I'm starting a game so I'll end the post here. Thanks for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I start? (New to both baseball, and the show 16) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have it installing, although after 2 games of the royals v Mets, I decided to kick it into rest mode and decided I'd ask for some help.

Just gonna do it in a bullet point style so I don't rant on like this.

What is the best position for a new guy doing a pro-career? 

What game mode should I start off with? Like, I should stay away from online for quite a while, yeah? Then along with that, how hard is manager mode for someone who doesn't know the sport too well?

After playing 18 innings with the default beginner settings, would you suggest changing anything to try it out? 

That's the main reason for this post, but if you have any thoughts that might help, I'd appreciate them.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You get to travel to the furthest point from _____, what/where do you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 00:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does hearts of stone work in new game+ (spoilers for main game) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 00:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm fighting Eredin right now and I'm guessing that means I'm nearing the end. I also have HoS downloading. 
Once I wrap this up, I plan on going for ng+ on death march. How will HoS work with that? If it starts you off at 30 in the original game, but new game+ starts you at 30, would that put HoS at 60 on ng+ ? Also, is it an instant quest or do I need to reach a certain point in the game for the quest to show up? 

Thanks for any help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some help with HoS setup. [Spoilers for late game] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 10:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just got to Kaer Morhen, and I'm loving it so far. But I also realized I'm coming up on 30 (level 27 right now) and I just realized I can look to get the DLC now. I don't really know what it's about or anything, if it's a new zone, I'm guessing new storylines, new monsters etc. But do they just install into my current world? Would I be okay to install it once I wrap up this Kaer quest, or am I too far into the game for that to work well? I'll be doing ng+ on Death March so if I'm right, I'll be keeping my level and whatnot going through. So would I be better off waiting for a new game, then installing, and just going to the dlc, if that's even an option, I'm not sure how it works. 

Any advice on this matter would be great. Thanks!

EDIT: I put spoilers in the title just for location, but I'd rather not know exactly hwo many missions are left, but rather what percentage of the main quest I've done, just so I know whether or not I should start collecting ?s and side quests. With that, how does late game work after completing? Do we go back to roaming depending on the ending we get? I'd rather not get specifics but I'd appreciate some kind of help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you support the team you support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 14:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Why do you support the team you support?* 

So I tried to get into the sport last season, but I joined in around mid June, so I was lost as all hell and had nothing to do outside watching the games (In Ireland). Now, with the release of the game, and I'd guess the season just started, so I'd be looking for a team to support. I don't know where to start though. 

So why do you support the team you support? I'd love to find a team to settle down with, and last year the suggestions were to watch a game, and feel out the teams but being honest, I really couldn't figure it out. 

Thanks!

EDIT 2: I also feel I should say this. I don't want to choose a team who are always on top. When I got into soccer in the early 2000s I was a Chelsea fan. When I got into the NFL, I was a Pats fan. Although neither of them are not exactly year by year winners, I feel they're easy to jump on to and be tagged as a bandwagon fan. I refuse to be that. I want a team people believe to be a great team, not in skill or winning, but to support. Although winning is nice. 

EDIT 3: I may also look into being a Dodgers fan. I loved watching those videos from the Dodgers guy a while back, but I heard he got taken down. (Just checked out his channel, turns out he's still active!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youtube may be one of the greatest inventions in babysitting history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 12:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] As much as this ep has destroyed the show... I was an emotional wreck. (very much a rant) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 21:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I  knew she was dying as I went into this ep. I had to know when I woke up, and only finished the ep now. 

I am furious with the writers, I truly can't believe Guggenheim had the balls to kill off Oliver's better half, and one of her last lines were that she was not the love of his life, but rather the fanfic was.. Gah. 

But Katie Cassidy in this episode man.. SHE HAD SO MUCH FUCKING POTENTIAL. She was incredible in this episode. From deciding on the DA position, to talking to Oliver, to the final scene. If she were given actual writing, I'd honestly imagine there would be enough fans of her to get Guggenslime away from Tumblr. 

Hearing her say "one last time" though... It broke me. Along with the photo.. I was genuinely crying to the point of my lip wobbling like a child with no ice cream. Why did they have to bow down to Tumblr? This episode is real proof that Oliver should have been hers, as she was his, and it also shows that Felicity is an incredibly unnecessary character. Who also gave out the most bullshit gasp ever when Laurel was confirmed dead. Hiding her face because she couldn't pull together a real tear. 

I just don't know what to do. What was the secret? Did the container have some bullshit toxin in it, and she pulled a Roy? The writers aren't smart enough for that, are they? Was it simply the picture? (Heartbreaking too)

I'm so lost right now. Arrow is the reason I started reading comics. Props to Amell though. That shot of him leaving the room and looking truly lost in life.. Holy shit. Along with Lance dropping to the ground. A guy who has legitimately been fucked over throughout the show more than anyone. 

It's.. I don't want to let go but I have to. I'm genuinely heartbroken over a show, in a way I've never felt before due to a show. A real sense of loss, not for a character, but for an experience. A brand. A family. An adventure. 

I'm done.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] I guess it's time to say goodbye. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 09:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've dropped one show ever. Gotham. Arrow is now my second. And I was glad to drop Gotham. That shit was like dropping a shit after a long day at work. But I'm upset right now about Arrow. I've given fucking 4 years of my life to this show only for it to be taken from me by some 40 year old tumblrinas.

The writers are useless and disrespectul, and it genuinely gets me annoyed just thinking about how they came to that result. I can't say anything that hasn't been said, but I felt it is right to say goodbye. The Arrow writers deserve to know they destroyed a show with incredible potential, and not only spit in our faces, but rubbed it in. 

Fuck the writers. Fuck Tumblr. Fuck Olicity. I'm out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who are missing one of the 5 senses, or know someone who is missing one, how does it affect your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 08:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What have I missed? Been gone since about a month after TTK. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 07:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved TTK. However, was on 360. Upgraded to ps4, and the amount of time I put in after TTK release, it killed me to level again, so I dropped the game and moved on for a while.

Now here I am, logging back on, just used my shard on a hunter. 

What are some things I've missed? I know emotes seem to be huge now. I had a load of coins/motes in my post when I logged on. Why?

EDIT: I thought I'd add in this though, hearing the sound of a drop being revealed by the cryptarch.. Such a great feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woody and Taylor have hockey. Taylor and Kyle have Age of Mythology. What do Woody and Kyle have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 07:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking guns, but Taylor holds some opinions on the matter. Any ideas?

EDIT: I mean it that when the two examples are brought up, there is a host pushed from the topic, albeit unintentionally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] How do you plan on watching? (Europe) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 00:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many version of the Justice League, Justice Society, JLA, do we have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 21:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I read the main JL run. I know the characters. I also know Constantine has his own Justice squad, and then in the GA run, he is on the JLA or the JSA? Now, as I take up Alex Ross' Justice, they're being called the JLA, but in reality, it's the current JL we know. 

So basically, what's the deal with all the titles? Justice League. Justice League of America. Justice Society. Justice League Dark is Constantine's run, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How realistic is aiming for a job in the comic book industry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let's be honest for a second. We've all thought about it at some point. Going for the art. Going for the writing. Maybe even going for the business side of it, but in the end, we've all thought about it.

With that said, considering I was 18 when I picked up reading, and only really draw in phases every few months, I had the idea for a while, but then life hit and realized I'm from Ireland, 19, and there are people younger than me with way more talent. So I shifted. I'm going for a realistic job and just aiming to enjoy the stories from the consumer side.

With that said, I've never actually looked into it. And of course, instead of doing any research, I thought why not ask reddit. So here I am.

TLDR; We've all thought about going for the DC jobs, but how realistic are those thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is Batman written in Earth One? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 12:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read vol 1 of Superman's Earth One, and loved it. He is definitely the most human version I've seen. 

Is Batman the same? Will I be seeing a more emotional version of him? I'd love a few notes before I buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most basic healer for new healers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 11:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I played a while back. Like a year and a half ago, if not more. I had a healing monk around 60. Logged back on today. Have absolutely no idea how to play it. I've got all these tumbles and whatnot. Quite frankly, the class seems to mobile for my liking.

Considering my mmo skills are that of a toaster, I'd much rather be able to stand and spam, rather than jumping around, dropping down totems and shit. 

I'd love some opinions on what is the easiest healer to get into. I may come back to monk one day, but getting back into the game, I'd like help having an easy start.

EDIT: So a pally and priest are getting reworked for Legion.. while druid and shaman can't be played by human. Fuck me I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easiest event to jump into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 08:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd try Civil war, but I've heard it's not really that great, and you need to be reading before the actual event to feel the weight of it, along with out of character heroes and whatnot.

So what other events can I read? I'd be willing to try anything.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just some thoughts about a theory going around regarding BVS. [spoilers] (Nightmare related) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 02:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geoff Johns talking to IGN about Rebirth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 03:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Props to Woody this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 04:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just about to wrap up this weeks episode, and as I actually watch the cameras, it's clear this problem ruined Woody's mood. With that though, he stuck with the show, added when he could, and dealt with it as best he could I'm guessing. 

That's all really. I feel whenever I'm on this sub I'm getting on his back for something, but damn this must have been a rough 4 hours for him. 

Hope you find the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone here have a problem with Skype? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 22:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying the guys aren't trying or anything, but I'm curious as to why it would be skype. I use it every day for anywhere from 3 hours to 9 depending on the day. Yet I've never really had any bugs. I may be lucky, but I'd be curious to know how the sub has dealt with the program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can recommend one story, and one only. What do you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I understand we have the sidebar, but I'm not looking for just one character. Most of my reading is Batman. I've read New52 JL, but anything pre-52 is a Batman read. 

However, I feel I've missed out on some of the epic reads. I haven't read Kingdom Come, but I'd imagine that is one. Then I'm thinking Flashpoint, because of course that story went big enough to reset time. Then I feel All Star Supes fits in there too. 

That is as far as my list reaches though. And I'd love some other opinions, because next week I'll be picking up the three stories I've mentioned above, to read most likely within the weekend, and I'd love some more suggestions on where to go next. Thanks!

EDIT: Here. As of right now, this is my [collection] (http://i.imgur.com/QA5akN1.jpg) The book just above GL is Superman Unchained.  I'm also only about 300 pages into the GL run. Hal just got back talking to the guys at the airbase if I recall it correctly. 

EDIT 2: I should point out I'm caught up with the entire Justice League run. I'm missing most of the books but I blame the store for that. Same for the Killing Joke, and Omega Men, and American Alien. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best series currently running? (In your opinion of course) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm curious about trying Marvel. I tried a while back, but it was overwhelming, simply because I don't remember there being a starting point, in the way DC has New52. 

I really do want to get into the world though. I'm just unsure where to start.  I don't have a preference for characters because I'm honestly not sure if the characters in the movies are the same tone of those in the comics. 

With that said, instead of grabbing a random series and being turned off, I'd rather start off strong and work from there.

Thanks for any opinions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would we be able to get some kind of banner for spoilers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 22:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Dardevil is spoiled this week, and it has me thinking about GoT now. I've also been watching TotalBiscuit's Secret Hitler series lately, and I feel what he does really manages to keep away spoilers. 

Just a simple overlay for when the topic is there, and drop it when it's not. It doesn't need to be some fullscreen banner, because that'd take away the faces and sponsors. I'm just looking for somethign in one of the blank areas, or under the sponsors. 

Thoughts as always, are welcomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite love story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I of course know the basics, Lois/Clark, Diana/Steve, Bruce/Talia, Dick/Babs, but apart from the names, I'm not very well versed in the actual best stories. 

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4E16] So how long do we give the relationship before they are back together? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking about it, as we approach the end of the season.. There is a slight, a very very slight change this is the writers listening, and dropping the relationship, and setting Ollie up for a blast of a final season. 

With that said, there's also a very loud noise that I call Facebook and Twitter, really shutting my hopes down for my theory. 

Thoughts are welcomed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to check what junk breaks down into, without opening the store every time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 16:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spoiler-free thought for going to BvS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 04:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is The Dark Knight Strikes Again worth reading, so you can read DKIII? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wrapped up TDKR, but I've heard Strikes Again is genuinely awful. 

With that said, I'm also not sure how good DKIII is, but I'd love some thoughts on that too. If DKIII is great, is it worth reading SA to get to DKIII? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So.. Um.. How are they going to explain Barry being in Supergirl's universe next week on the Flash? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 00:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the final clip of him running was going to be him breaking the dimensional barrier again, but ending up on the wrong earth. It was just him shouting. 

So next week, we have Barry going to Kara's show and spending a night there. A night, which of course falls before the next Flash episode. If someone could help explain this to me it would be great. I'd hope they didn't skip over it when it comes to the Flash episode afterwards, but I can't see how they will explain his jump between episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old is Oliver in Lemire's run? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 20:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just picked up GA Volume 4 (which is a lot of fun so far), and I'm a bit confused.

I know Oliver from the show, and that guy is in his late 20's at this point. But in Lemire's run, he is drawn to be someone just entering his 20s, or at least that is what it seems like to me. 

I'm sure one of the earlier issues covered it, but I'll take the warning and stay away from that mess. Thanks for any feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right now may be the riskiest time in history for a 19 year old guy to make a move on a girl he meets in public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 18:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What story could do the best as a novel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 17:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be real. The art is an equal to writing, when it comes to what makes a normal comic release, into an all time great.

With that said, I've been wondering lately, which story, could you remove the art, and make it a legit novel, while keeping the quality and storytelling up to par. 

I'm not sure if it's been done before, and I'd imagine it has. Of course it's no longer a comic, but I'd imagine someone, at some point in time, has tried to take one of our beloved heroes, and took a swing at a story without the art or the speech bubbles. 

So, I'll ask for both, stories that have already been done, and stories that you feel could pull it off.

Thoughts are always welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would the clothes I get in Vizima sell for more in a nicer part of the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've heard selecting where you sell something really matters. How if you sell fish to a shore city, you'd get maybe 5, but if you sell it to an inland city, you could get 10 (just example numbers).

So now that I have these clothes from the vizima trip, would I be better off selling them to a small village in White Orchard, or a bigger store in Novigrad? 

Any thoughts are welcome, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is first time Death March suicide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just made a post about armor, but quickly deleted it because I realized something. 

So I played a while back, got to Skellige, lost my data. Had to start again, fell out of love due to how into that run I was. Now I'm back, and trying on Death March. Although it's a struggle, I feel it can be handled well, but still, it takes me a full 2-3 minutes to take out a pack of wolves, and that's if I time everything perfectly, and due to it being such a challenge, I feel I need to right mindset before playing. So I ask you guys. 

Should I continue on Death March? Should I drop down one, or even two difficulties on a first time run, and come back to DM when I've finished the game at least once?

Thoughts are welcome. Thanks!

EDIT: So after a bit of googling, it seems it gets easier. With that said, I'd love some tips for how to go about it. Do i hoard everything? Do I sell everything etc. What type of armor. Character upgrades. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite scene in Season 2? [Spoilers of course] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 16:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the mortal instruments Netflix series like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browsing past it, the show image looks awful, but the concept seems decent. If someone has watched it, I'd love some opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Seth Rogen's new movie picks up enough steam, there are going to be a lot of people asking "One for Sausage party at 8 please" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 00:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This may be the most jam packed year in history when it comes to being a nerd. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 12:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain the dark zone area setup for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hit 22, and thought I'd give the DZ a go. When I got in, it of course said the normal level for the area was 21-24, but the dz level was 19-22 or something. I was level 1. I was being killed by rogues level 20. Why am I with them?

I understand we may have the same normal level, but the gap was very, very noticeable, and when trying to kill a rogue, it was close to impossible. 

Should I just wait until 30 now? I'd guess I'm too late to start in the dz, and should come back when geared up, but I also feel a bit lost on why that is happening. Thanks!

EDIT: I'll add this in. I have 10k primary DPS, 13k health, and 7.5k skill power. (Going for the healing role of the group) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a thought about this whole hate thing Woody has for flying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 00:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole reason he seems to hate flying as a superpower, seems to be because he can fly wherever he wants, and flying would be cold. 

Can I just throw out that it's not actually a shit power, rather a useless one for you, because as someone who is not really set when it comes to money, I'd wear a few extra layers of clothes to fly. 

So yeah, that's just it. 

Woody: Doesn't need to fly due to money, passport. Finds it to be cold and irritating.

My point: Flights are expensive as fuck when it comes to flying outside Europe, and I'd be willing to wear some clothes to deal with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The phone recording "Week Two: 08"... What the... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 22:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on my way to collect a side mission to finish the area, stumbled across it. 

I now have tears in my eyes. The phone recordings have been interesting to listen to, but this one is just terrifying. Great job kid. Great job.

EDIT: It's in Hudson Yards, between 36th and 38th, around the building beside the intersection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if I fail to negotiate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 14:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying my hand at taking a bit extra lately, but I've also played it super safe and not taken too much. What happens when I fill the bar? Does the deal just cancel? Do I get the minimum price?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is focusing Skill Power crazy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 03:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember back in the beta, the easy way to win the DZ was stack armor. By the end of beta, I had maybe 7-8k hp. 

Now though, with the actual game, I am going to focus a lot more on my stats, and considering I'll be the guy with all the heals, I feel power should be where I aim all my gear. 

Is it crazy though? Should I be going hybrid as a healer, or is it safe to lack a bit of health, if my skill power is above everything else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we're going to stick with the soundboard, try find a way for Kyle and Taylor to hear it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 21 minutes in, and I've probably heard 4 soundbites so far, and honestly, they're not very good, but at the same time, this is of course the first time. 

With that, I feel it is pointless if the guys can't hear it. If, after every soundbite, all we hear is a chuckle from Woody due to him believing it's well timed or a zinger, and all the while, Kyle and Taylor continue the talk. 

With that, I of course haven't reached the end of the show yet, although while writing this, I've heard two poorly timed Wings bites, that straight up clashed with Taylor's talking. 

Hopefully something can come from this, although if I recall it correctly, didn't we have soundboard talk within the last 15 eps or so, and how it didn't work very well, and every 1 in 10 was actually funny? 

I'd love your thoughts.

EDIT: Chiz is now adding to the show. I'm all for this idea of a background guy googling and researching, but he needs to cut off earlier. He's getting carried away in this steak thing and throwing out his opinion. Sounds kinda harsh, but just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extremely simple questions in regards to cooking chicken fillets, and rice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So some time in the next few weeks, I am going to put my fitness act in play. I'll be eating chicken, rice, and depending on the day, something like carrots, broccoli, baked potatoes, etc. 

With that said, I rarely, if ever, cook the food I eat. So here are my questions. 

How long do I boil the chicken for, and I do boil it right? Just a sauce pan full of water, still the chicken in, and boil, right? 

Then, the same for the rice, right? 

Once both are done, how long can I store it for? If I were to use clingfilm, could I store say, 10 chicken fillets, for a week, or would I have to cook 2 a day, and keep on top of it? The same applies for rice. 

If I can store both, I'd be fine microwaving them back to edible temperature, right? 

I understand these questions may truly be below a lot of you, considering this is a cooking sub, and I have never cooked, but I can honestly say I appreciate the art, and would love some help on getting started. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has a team ever been as good as the Red Army 5? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got done watching that.. Truly incredible documentary, and it seems like when the 5 of them played together, they were absolutely unstoppable. 

Has a team ever come close to the level of play, that those 5 guys played at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often, if ever, do we see evil win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a big part of Tolkien's memory, would be, in my opinion, that he set the ground work for what a true fantasy piece is, by simply writing a battle of true good vs evil. 

With that though, I wonder now, with all of the history he wrote, when does evil actually win? 

Don't quote me on it, because I'm foggy on the events that lead up to it, but would we consider Fingolfin's suicide by combat a loss in the good vs evil fight? I'm not sure how he came to be the last of his kind, and of course he never stood a chance against Morgoth, but I feel it does seem like a genuine loss in some way. 

Are there any others? There has to be, right? 

I'd love to hear your thoughts and opinions on the matter. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which fictional character had the greatest end? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 23:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I change the version of the game, to match older mods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what Kony has been up to in the last few years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 02:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly is Galadriel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 17:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we know she's not a Maia, or at least I believe she's not.

But she has an incredible level of power. I don't really know what else to say without getting a lot mixed up, so I'd just love an answer. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Helm's Deep the most powerful example of true Elven skill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 16:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual, I've been watching clips from the movies, and I've seen how incredibly talented Jackson made the elves. How the men of Rohan shot arrows, but they were all kind of bogey shots, and wobbly when holding the bows, yet when it came to the elves, nothing would faze them. They stared down the army, and they even had the accuracy to shoot from behind the wall, through the gaps in each soldier. 

To me, at least, this really does seem like the biggest example of elven warriors being some of the best in Middle Earth. That being said, of course it's now a cliche that elves are the best archers in any selected universe.

Thoughts are welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I look when it comes to reading about any mythological gods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the Norse gods, the Greek gods, Egyptian gods, so on and so forth. Modern writings, or older writing from actual followers of the pantheons. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I look when it comes to reading about any mythological gods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit and social media has really tilted my hype for this movie.. But dear god I'm emotional right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be the lack of sleep. It may be a long week. It may just be my naivety.. But we're now in the same month as the Batman Vs Superman movie. 

We are legitimately going to see Batman take on Superman. We are going to see Lex before he becomes the maniacal Lex we all know and love/hate. An introduction to one of the strongest female characters in storytelling history. Aquaman! Maybe the Flash. 

All of this will be on our screens in 3 weeks. I just can't believe it managed to creep it's way into my calendar so quickly. And then we have the JL movie next year.

I'm sorry if this post is pointless, but I just felt like venting, because the hype is getting to me now. Thoughts of course are welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best sports movie on Netflix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 23:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for something to watch, and I rarely watch sports movies, so I thought I'd try them out.

That being said, a lot of them are 30 for 30 situations, which I'm guessing is kind of a documentary styled movie? There's also a lot of god awful stuff like "Dad's a soccer mom". There also seem to be a lot of super cliche fighting movies.

I'd just love some input. Are the 30 for 30 movies worth watching, no matter the subject? I don't have a love for a sport, nor a hate for one, just an interest in a movie. 

Thanks!

EDIT: I should probably say this too, I'm looking for either a true, word for word telling of events of someone's history.. Or just a great story put on the screen. Not something in middle, that has a few truths, but is also covered in lies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not sure if this has happened before his time on stage this week, but Andy Serkis is going to receive some kind of award in the coming years for what he has given to motion capture, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 21:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just thinking out loud, but when I saw those clips of him show up on stage a few days ago, I was expecting to see him receive some kind of award. Then it had me wondering, and I looked into it a bit, and apparently there was some talk about him being nominated for Caesar in Dawn Of The Planet Of The Apes. I can not sign off on that, as I am yet to see it for some reason, and have a copy in my cart on Amazon. (Please, please don't spoil it.)

With that, I feel this guy really does need some recognition on the main stage. It may be because I've had some kind of nerd love for him ever since Gollum, but yeah, I'd love to hear your thoughts.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Netflix started it's war vs everyone outside the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back, I heard news that they'd destroy any dreams for those of us looking to use the US Netflix by blocking any client with a vpn on it. 

I just tried to log in.. And, well, it seems it has begun. Is anyone else suffering the same loss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who, in your opinion, is the best working rapper today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 09:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was watching that clip of snoop and 50 talking about rap these days and how it's all the same shit.

Who breaks that, and is above and beyond the rest? Is it Kendrick? Is it Drake? Both just examples, because I really don't know the rap game too well, but damn am I looking for some modern shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite piece of art that you can buy online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 12:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking maps, concept art, original art, sketches from Tolkien himself, etc. 

If a link could be provided too, that would be great, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a chance we could get less political talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 01:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, before we start, this is not hate, I feel it's genuine criticism. 

In this weeks PKA, the first 40 minutes or so of the show was all political talk, and then about 30 minutes after that they worked back around to it somehow. 

Now I'll admit I don't mind it that much, but I feel for that amount of time to be taken from a show we only get once a week, seems a bit much. Especially for those of us outside the US. 

Along with that, I feel it's easily said that shows that have a heavy amount of current-events talk, tend to age poorly. An odd example, but something I noticed nonetheless. In PKA 145, we hear that Ben Affleck is announced as Batman. And with that, is a barrage of hate for the casting choice, and it's said that he has no chops, how we need a stronger Batman, and it won't work. Now.. Well I'd imagine opinions have changed on that.

Although that is more around opinions, I feel that because it was so long ago, and things have changed, the hate for the casting choice has faded away, that whole topic didn't do very well. 

I get the same thing with bootcamp talk, considering the outcome we saw, and the current Wings we know. 

So yeah, I'm not asking for it to be wiped out, because of course that's not going to happen with the year we have ahead of ourselves, I just thought I'd give my thoughts before heading to bed. I'd just like to see PKA age better than I expect it to when it comes to this time-frame. (the presidential race)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else outside the US feel Jap's eye is a fairly common thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 02:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Terrible title. I mean do you guys feel it's a common phrase in regards to the pee hole. 

I'm not saying it's a friendly expression and should be used everywhere, because I see the offensiveness of it. 

That being said, I also grew up knowing my dick hole as a japs eye. I thought it was a fairly common thing, everyone that I'd ever talk to regarding it, would call it a japs eye. 

Curious to see if this is a common thing outside the US, or what, because we heard it from an Australian, and I'm here in Ireland (And I've known a few guys from England use it), so I'd love some thoughts.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How good, or bad, is Chicken and Rice when it comes to replacing your daily meals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 00:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, I don't know if this can be a breakfest and dinner type scenario, or if there is more to it. I've tried looking at the getting started section, but it's incredibly overwhelming for someone who doesn't really keep up with weight, what is in his food, his daily intake etc.

That being said, I've seen it mentioned a few times among groups I talk to, that a person or two is only eating chicken and rice for whatever amount of time.

Is this a good idea? A bad idea? Of course it's boring, but I feel it may also take a whole lot of bad stuff away from your day to day eating, along with the chicken bringing in protein.

Like I said, this is the first time in my life that I'm paying attention to my weight, the ingredients in my food, and just general healthiness, so tips would be great. Thanks.

EDIT: Also, I'm guessing it's one of the cheapest diets out there, considering you can pick up 6-8 fillets for like 5 euro in some butchers. 

EDIT 2: Would it make sense to add some kind of powdered shake into the mix for gain? I understand what I'm looking for here is weight loss, but it's more about dropping the wasteful weight, and turning what I had into muscle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The internet has destroyed a fun evening for those of us that actually want to watch Netflix with a friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 22:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why have I never heard of Tomorrowland? [No spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 22:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm looking for a movie to watch, and I spotted tomorrowland. I'm not sure how I know the girl from it, but I like the actress. It also have Clooney, and what seems to be a pretty fun adventure story..

So why have I never heard of it? Did it go straight to dvd after a week cinema release? Did it straight up bomb? 

Any thoughts on it would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4E15] This was a great episode of Arrow.. If you removed every scene with Felicity. [Emotional rant] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 00:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Emily Bett Rickards, and I can say I'm sorry for how I feel about her character, and that she should leave the show..

But lets be real. You remove the opening walk scene, the yet again crying Felicity, the search description scene, and then the final scene. You know what you have? An action packed, emotional episode. 

I understand the writers pander to Tumblr, and I would leave the show, but I care too much for this character. Please. Writers, if you ever read this. Fuck Tumblr. You are absolutely destroying what could be an amazing, action packed show, simply to please a few fan fictions spammers on a website that is known for shipping characters. 

Please. I really don't want to give up this show, but you're making it so fucking hard. I'm in tears here because I know it's coming. I know Felicity is still close to Oliver come to funeral scene. I saw the tweet or whatever it was of them in the wedding. I'm not sure what it meant, but dear god if it's a shot from a future episode I'll be done. 

You may not care about your characters, but please care about the fans that do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It took me 3 years to realize this, but Thresh is a Guardian, because he controls a Green Lantern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 20:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, I get the Jay joke..But can someone actually fill me in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 15:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we have our Jay, who "lost" the speed supposedly. 

We have the Jay in the cage, who I'm guessing is the actual Jay, the real speedster.

Then we have Zoom Jay. Is that Hunter Zolomon? And if so, can someone explain it to me? Why are they twins/clones? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woody, I'm not sure how you're reacting to this Whiteboy thing, and I know you're a vet, but leave it here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 02:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, I watched 3 minutes of it and left. It seems he's taking the good old "I'll speak loudly to be perceived as correct" strategy. 

That being said, I also feel that nothing positive can come from this for you. If you "win" this drama, you gain nothing. If you "lose" this drama, we of course know Keem is already working up a vid and whatever else. 

Along with that, and this is honestly just me speaking, but I'm done with drama. I watch you for you. You're a 40+ year old dad. I don't watch you to get caught up in something like this. I can.. And naive as it may come off, say that I feel you're better than this. 

So if there is a video or Reddit/twitter post coming, don't?

EDIT: So I'm listening to his video now on like 10% volume... Did he just pimp a coupon code mid "fuck you" rant?

EDIT 2: Restraining order.. Huh. 

EDIT 3: Just a few notes. That fucking shock collar thing was a scummy thing to say. He shouted quite a lot that he's done with Woody, while making a video about Woody. That payment idea he has for Wings on PKA is fucking idiotic. And there is the threat for following up on the recording..

That was interesting. That being said, we now have both sides. Leave it there please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A person's reaction to the term "I'm getting a facial later" can really tell a lot about them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 00:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the Netflix show "Love" like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 23:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even sure if that's the actual name. 

It's at the top of Netflix when you log in. Has the chic from Community, and seems pretty fun. So can someone who watched it, tell me what it's like? 

A lot of humor? Actually plot or just series of events? Worth the watch in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So how do you guys feel about The Division? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 11:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to say the beta is over, because if I recall it ended on Sunday, but I wasn't sure on the time and I'm work now. 

With that... I went in very, very wary because it was of course a Ubisoft beta. And because of that, I can honestly say I was blown away.

I loved the beta, I really did. I'm considering now if I should grab a physical copy at 9am on the 8th, or just go digital so I can go big at midnight on the 7th. 

If you enjoyed Destiny, and love the city feeling this game sets, you should definitely look into buying this game. 

Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the map an actual clone of current New York? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 11:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not from the US. I live in Ireland, and, as someone who plans on travelling to the US one day, I have a love/hate thing with New York. On one hand, it's New York, an incredible piece of culture with millions of people packing the streets every day. There is also the shitty part of too, with traffic, and of course with that many people, there are a lot of assholes..

Back to my point though. How good is the mapping? Is the post office actually across from MSG or is that just for convenience? If I'm walking down 34th in Division, would I see the same buildings along 34th? 

Odd, and most likely asked already, but thanks for any answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has an episode ever been as widely loved as this one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching the show again, and browsing through the posts on here. I don't think I've ever seen a more positive version of this sub than right now. It's all just posts about the great guest, the reactions, trips that could go down now, and just general good vibes. (lacking a term right now. Only awake)

Thoughts are welcome of course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This episode was an interesting one.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a lot of great humor and Prison Break jokes, but at the same time.. They totally had Savage cornered and he told her to leave. There was no reasoning behind it at all, and a few minutes before it, we even heard them say she's the only one who can kill him..

That being said, I was expecting Old Man Oliver at the finale.. And damn was I in awe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What video do you watch when you're down or in a rut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4] [EU] Looking for people to play with when it opens up tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a mic, I'm a fairly strong player when it comes to shooters.

With that, I'd like to see whats up with the Dead Zone, although I also want to complete some PVE. The missions and whatever else we get. 

Although, with all this, I'm not one to put my PSN name on here, so if you could leave your name below I'd appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie has the best directors commentary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 03:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title.

Also, does Lord of the Rings have one? It seems too long, but it would also be '1 on my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4E14] Please tell me there is a way we can group together and tell the writers of the show we're done with drama surrounding romance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 01:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done my very bets to defend this show for most of it. I wasn't on this sub when I watched the first 2 seasons or so, and I rarely, rarely came here before mid season 4, but when I have, I've done my best to defend that which is Olicity. I was just a big fan of the actress at the time, and Laurel was very much drunk/mopey/angry Laurel so I never saw her with Ollie.

That being said.. Why the fuck do we have scenes now that are dedicated to the relationship of Lance/felicity's mom? What the fuck is this show turning into?

I understand Tumblr has a foothold in the show's working for some reason, but dear fucking christ is it ruining this show. 

I've never been one to post about how angry or annoyed I am at an episode, but this episode was a joke. 

I'll give the positives of it. The fight scene in the courthouse (if that was where the debate was held) was badass. Diggle deflecting the swing? Yes please. Diggle finishing the guy off? Yes please. Thea swinging from the chain, only to save Laurel? Yes.  Thea's line about learning the fire alarm trick in school? I chuckled. The Oliver line about bringing the house down was pretty funny. Then the finale. Darhk straight up killed Samantha. I understand something would come of it due to Malcolm, and the screen time with Thea. But dear god, he just took the child. 

That is some drama I can appreciate. The Green Arrow has a son, and now he is in danger that no kid should ever be in. I don't want to hear about how Felicity's mom has met liars before, when Darhk is kidnapping children at the same time. 

Sorry if this came off a bit ranty, and I understand I've probably said nothing new, but I had to vent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first real image of a certain character to soon appear on Legends of Tomorrow [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 01:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harley Morenstein's House Tour (The main face of Epic Meal Time) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 14:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] What is the book like compared to the show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 20:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'll be honest, I'm new to this sub. I only started the show like 4 days ago but I'm caught up. With that, I just found out it's based on a book. And that book is a trilogy. 

So is the show just based upon the characters, with a vastly different story? Does the show take place at the same time as the books, but events unfold differently? Are the characters the same for the most part? Is it one book to one season? 

I'd like to look into reading them, but I'd also like some help before starting. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any show suggestions for someone who just binged 3 seasons of The 100? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 15:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else having a problem with licenses lately? (Digital, specifically) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 14:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I bought a BF4/Bf Hardline bundle a while back. BF Hardline told me to re-buy it to play. I asked PS Support, they said reset the licenses or whatever the setting was.

Ever since I did that, I've been getting a notification about the game I'm playing. Something about not having a real license, so the game will suspend in 15 minutes. Something like that, I'm sorry I can't think of the real quote. 

Any help would be great. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here you go guys, Game of Thrones Season 6 Teaser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 6] Official Game of Thrones season 6 Teaser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official Game of Thrones Season 6 Teaser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] [Shitpost] This is the last time I go to sleep without knowing what is coming next season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most disgusting thing you would do for $631,592 ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who does Deadpool actually like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 21:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I saw the movie today, and I loved the jabs at X-men, and the whole "movie rights" area. That being said, after the movie, I went to see what Deadpool stories my local book store had, and I'll be honest. There was one Deadpool Collection, but then there were 4-5 "Deadpool vs" sets. Deadpool vs SHIELD. Deadpool vs hawkeye. It goes on, but I can't remember the others.

So who does this guy team up with? If he even does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you guys think of Batman 44? [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 23:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got done with it, and.. I'm not sure. The art is definitely an interesting take. I'm not a big fan, but I felt it did the message of a flashback well. The writing however.. This is the first time I haven't been a fan of Snyder. The whole 'third-person' Batman thing didn't do well with me.

That being said, I am also still new enough to the point of this being the only issue I actually left disappointed with.

I'd love to hear your thoughts on it though, because it's clear a lot of you understand the choice of art or writing better than me. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] When did you realize you were depressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 00:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much of the current Flash run is worth reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 22:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I find it odd that I have never read Flash, due to how much I love the show, but this week I think I'll pick it up.

That being said, I'm not sure where to start. I know with Batman, the entire run is worth reading, but with something like Green Arrow, you only read Volume 4 and up. Ignore 1-3 completely.

So. Where do I start with Flash? Is the entire run worth reading?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone versed in the world of Green Lantern help me with something?[GL Omnibus spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 22:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two questions I have.

1) Why are the Lanterns forbidden from the Vega zone? I understand it is part of a pact made long ago, but do we know why?

2) What is the extent of the color yellow's power? I understand that Sinestro is Yellow for fear, along with Parallax, but I felt at the start of my read (Currently about 250 pages into Geoff's Omnibus), that it was just a thing for art. Green bounces of yellow, in the way blue does off red, and black does off white... But now OA is under attack by these Spiders, and they have to retreat with a lot of the new trainees because they are straight up weak against the spiders because they are golden in color. Is it strictly to do with "Yellow=Fear", and once they overcome so called parallax equation, the actual color isn't a problem anymore?

Thanks for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it okay to just pick up Infinity War? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't read much Marvel, I'll be honest. I was starting my read on Civil War, but got caught up in a DC run, so never picked it back up. (Right now, however, I'm reading the current Old Man Logan run. Incredible.)

Then in the store the other day, I saw this cool 2 piece collection for Infinity War. But I didn't buy it, because I'm not sure what I need before hand.

So I knew to ask you guys on here, before buying. So can I just go ahead and buy those two collections? Or is there a bigger read before hand that is a literal must-read? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the NFL Network be showing the normal Superbowl ads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 19:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll most likely be watching the game on the NFL network tonight, but a big part of the channel I choose, has to do with them showing the ads.

I would have watched on CBS, but they have the stream blocked outside the US (although a VPN blocker would fix that right up).

if anyone has knowledge about this topic, I'd appreciate it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we all need to thank Boogie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 19:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He legit took in the criticism of weight talk, and gave maybe 40 seconds of the show to bring it up, and then finished it, because he knew we aren't big fans of it.

That being said, I can only speak for myself I guess, but I know we don't really beat around the bush when it comes to problems we find with the show or guests, but thanks for taking our thoughts into consideration!

Can't wait for the next time your on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone on here have experience with the DC Universe Online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 18:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just installed it on to my PS4, and it seems okay so far. That being said, I know MMOs are all about late game. 

So can anyone on here fill me in a bit about how the game plays late game, the DLCs, some tips for beginners etc.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with the BATMAN VS SUPERMAN graphic novel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 01:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I spotted [this] (http://www.dccomics.com/graphic-novels/batman-vs-superman) earlier and was curious about it, but didn't pick it up.

What exactly is this meant to be? Is it basically just a collection of Batman fighting Superman, or is there an actual story throughout the collection? It seems a bit odd to have #612, with Batman 35-36, with Batman/Superman #32 and #78, and the Dark Knight Returns #4.

Also, is it worth picking up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we get Grayson added to the 'Other Characters' section of recommended reads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 00:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm browsing the new comers section for ideas on what to buy, and honestly, for all the love I see Nightwing/Grayson get, I'm amazed it's not on the list.

Hasn't Grayson been top tier since it kicked off? I myself have only read 1 or 2 issues, but for all the love it gets on here, I'd love to see it be recommended beside Nightwing/Dick Grayson, especially considering he straight up has no titles beside his name.

Thoughts as always are welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there somewhere I can buy a stream for the entire Superbowl 50? [Ireland/UK] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do people feel about Superman For Tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 16:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised because the cover art is probably my favorite shot of Superman 'posing' if we call it that, and it's of course, by Jim Lee.

So why is there a lack of talk on it when Superman is brought up? Is it a forgettable book? Is it under-rated, even over-rated? 

I'd love to hear your thoughts on it, because I picked it up today, knowing nothing about it and was curious why.

Also, if you're going to discuss moments, a spoiler tag would be great. Thanks!

EDIT: This saddens me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After all of last week's drama on videos, I will be very interested in the next Youtubers React. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 18:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are people feeling about Farcry Primal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'll be honest. Until about a week ago, I had no idea this game existed. And of course, it isn't released just yet, but I'd like to hear the thoughts of those that kept up with pre-release.

Seeing as it's Primal, we can expect a whole lot of Wildlife, right? And a massive world, due to the size of some of the animals.. But is there quicktravel? Considering there can't vehicles. Or can there be? Can we ride a mammoth?!? Also, what can we expect in story? I haven't played the other farcry games, but I understand 3 is something of an incredible story/game.

I'd just love to hear what we're in for, and if I should into buying it, or avoid it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look! Look! [American Alien '1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 22:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Superman should I be reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I wrapped up Unchained a while back, and damn did I enjoy that. I've read Volume 1 of Earth One, too, which is also amazing. 

But I now have to wait for Volume 2-3 to come back in stock for Earth One, and I thought I'd try a few digital issues of the various Superman runs we have right now.

Superman. Action Comics. Batman/Superman. Superman/Wonder Woman. Lois and Clark. American Alien.. It's quite a list, so if you could point me towards the best run, or even the best timeframe of a certain run (as people tend to do for GA, which is around Volume 4), I'd really appreciate it. 

Thanks!

EDIT: There is also the Justice League/ Justice League 3000 version of him, if we want to count that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well this is an interesting Sam moment [Latest Bloopers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get a TLDR on Old Man Logan's setting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I understand that he is an alternate universe version of Logan, who is old, duh..

But the world he just got thrown into is the basic Marvel world, in which the avengers are superheros and beloved by all, right? So, having come from the world where the hulk gang, which I'm guessing is run by a super villain version of Hulk, Logan is going to find the good guy Hulk and believe him to be a villain, right? He simply feels he's a few years in the past of his world, and the actual one he is in right now is a different past than his, right?

That is the main problem I'm having, but I also understand a big event just happened, so something could have taken place in that event that actually leads Hulk to be a villain, I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Actor Fluff] So Stephen just put this up on his Facebook page. (Legends of Tomorrow spoilers, I guess?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 23:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way we could get a recommended list for the animated movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a though, but I think a few people, newcomer or veteran, would find it useful to know where to start in regards to the animated universe, and what to avoid. Even a list, giving you an idea of what the movie is about and how it feels.

Like I said, this is just a thought, so it could be a terrible idea, but I'd like to hear what you guys have to think about this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S4E11] So, that line from Ollie about Felicity's new name.. It was incredible, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be the first the first to say it. I hate what they have been doing in terms of baiting her death, only for her to go full Oracle on us... But damn when they actually mentioned her. What was it? "I was going with Oracle but it's taken".. God damnit, I can get behind that.

The fact that they know she's basically Arrow's Oracle at this point is amazing to me. It's even better because, well, THEY MENTIONED BATMAN. I remember a few weeks back we got the "I've seen Men of steel break, and Dark knights fall" or whatever it was, and damn did it feel good.

But with the mention of Oracle, it shows so much.. The existence of Batman. The fact that Barbara isn't Batgirl, and has already become the Oracle we know from post-killing joke..

I'm sure I've thought about this more than I should, but being the Batman fan I am, I thought I'd share my thoughts here. And with that, I'd like to hear yours!

Guys,, I thought I'd add this in.

I do not expect any Batman/Gotham in the show. I just appreciate that the show runners made it noticeable, to those of us that care, that there is in fact other heroes in this universe they made, even if we never see them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I'll be shopping again this week, and I feel like I should look outside, and stop planning what I buy. Who should I keep an eye out for? (writers and artists) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 22:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds weird, but stick with me.

So I've been looking for Superman Earth One Volume 2-3. 3/4 comic stores about 50 minutes away have replied saying they don't have it, the 4th is yet to reply.

So instead of letting myself get annoyed at missing out, I have a better idea. I'm going to shop for writers this week. All I really know so far is Snyder's Batman. Snyder's Superman Unchained. Then whoever wrote Trinity War (forgive me).

So the two names I hear most often are Geoff Johns, and Grant Morrison. Would I be doing it right by buying any 'big title' they have? As in, not a volume 4 of a run, but something like Batman RIP. It can be read without previous reading and whatnot.

Any other names would be great, or even artists, because i have the same tunnel vision for Capullo (which.. Isn't too bad IMO, but it feels wrong to only know one artists style).

Heck, even massive titles would be great. I am nearly caught up on Batman, but after reading Unchained a few nights ago (in one sitting..), I can't help but feel I'm missing out on something. Jim Lee is his name, right? Are there any titles you guys would suggest that is packed with his work? 

Once again, thanks for any help you give, I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Just an idea, but the trailer may be tomorrow (26th) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 01:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been refreshing the YT page since Saturday night because of a theory I heard, and it hasn't been any use so far.. Then I was checking the Facebook page.

We have the Stark teaser on the 23rd. The Targaryen on the 24th. The Lannister on the 25th..

And seeing as last year, we got those raven visions to hype us up before, can we assume that..

THE TRAILER IS TOMORROW?!? If you are like me, and have a lot of spare time, I'd check the GOT Facebook page, between 3-7pm on the 26th. Two of the house teasers were released around 5pm, while the Lannister one dropped 3:30 today, which was the earliest of the lot.

Good luck hunting guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you guys for suggesting that I continue with Zero Year.. I am now an emotional wreck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll admit it took me maybe a month and a half to go from buying V4-V7, and starting to read them. I found the art style odd quite a lot, and I love Capullo's work. But now on to it.

So I just got done with Dark City, after starting it yesterday. It was... Quite a ride. It really was. Especially the flashback scenes. 

The final battle was awesome too, and how he just stopped caring about the bots. Then, even though I knew nothing would happen to the city any further, I was still panicking as I read about the jets flying in. The bat-signal was also touching.

I'll just give these two points and then end the post because I'm not very good at reviewing or sharing my thoughts.

That 2-3 page spread of Bruce settling down with Julie.. I legit closed the book after realizing it was Alfred's dream, and just sobbed for a few minutes. Snyder why?!? Along with quite a lot of other pages in the arc, this really hit me hard with the fact that Bruce, will never truly be free of the Bat, and as much as it destroys him, it is the only way he'll be happy. 

Then, we have the pages that are after "the end". I only know of Harper from Volume 1 of Eternal, but after reading this, I realized I'm going to buy V2-V3 when I get the chance because I really like her character. That being said, I found everything post- her dad shutting the door, to be a wave of emotions coming towards me. The shot of Batman with all the other heroes around the page. Her then fixing the light, while giving the speech about believing in those that we cannot see. 

Dear god, that was just an incredible experience, and I was considering skipping it not so long ago, until I chatted with a few of you on here and got convinced to read it. 

So thank you guys. I really appreciate you as a community, and more so, thank you Snyder/Capullo.. What a ride you guys sent me/us on.

EDIT: Also, [this] (https://i.gyazo.com/75336f3b792db1608766df82b0b6561f.png) look by Alfred.. I'm done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reading Zero Year.. Does Bruce actually deserve Alfred? [Zero Year-Dark City] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 23:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that studied some kind of art in college, how did that work out for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 19:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Woody's schedule is flexible enough to go to Wings' house, and Spain.. Why is there such a lack of PKA plays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 23:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a thought I'm having. Isn't the reason PKA Plays stopped being a thing, was due to Woody and his work schedule. How he could some nights be up for most of the night, only to be up early the next morning for the same thing.

So it seems this has changed, right? Maybe he picked up more staff or something, but if he has time for travelling to S Carolina, and to Spain for some 'jetpacking' in the water, is it crazy to ask for a few hours whenever to get PKA Zombies out? More Mount your friends, etc. 

Of course it can't just be a 'lets do it today' type deal, but seeing that they guys are up for something like this, and the fact that Taylor/Kyle/Chiz tend to play BO3 a lot, I feel like we could reasonably ask for PKA plays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite dc-focused channels/series on Youtube? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 15:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have more than one, I'd love to hear them, because I come from the gaming side of Youtube, so I'm not really sure where I'd look for DC content, besides the actual DC channel.

EDIT: So I just found Variant. I'm enjoying the 'every version' series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the consensus of both Blackest Night, and Brightest Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 20:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm looking to start picking up random comics and reading, instead of sticking to Batman, and only Batman. 

Today I was looking, and one two that stood out, were of course the Blackest Night, and Brightest Day set.(I went with Superman: Earth One, in the end). It may be because I was reading Omega Men last night and Rayner says it in that, or it could be because of how highly it's praised on here, I'm really not sure. 

So that's what I'm here to ask. I looked in the recommended section and it's not on the GL list, but it does seem interesting, because it both holds the GL oath, and it has undead. 

If you could share your thoughts on the set, I'd very much appreciate it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite video of a crowd singing at an event? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 18:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capullo... You never cease to leave me in awe. [Batman Zero Year:Secret City] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 21:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait, so if Bad Blood is released today, why is it so hard to find? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been seeing a few posts regarding this release, and I saw a picture of a certain character, along with a post saying how incredible it is..

But looking on Amazon, it says pre-order for the 2nd of Feb. While the release date says 19th of Jan.. So is this an actual cinema release in the US? I don't mean to sound so shocked, it just doesn't seem like a thing that happens. 

I've also heard people praise it, so it's clear it's somewhere.. And being the investigative type I am, it may be on less-than-legal sites.(which confuses me due to the lack of sites I can find a purchase on)

If anyone could even link me to somewhere that I can buy a digital copy, I'd greatly appreciate it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most damage heavy DH build? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just hit 70, and I've been feeling like I lack a whole lot of damage as I play.

So right now I caltrops, the leap, sentry, and vengeance (just because I feel OP in it). Also, Hungering arrow (piercing rune), and elemental arrow, the one that is a lightning orb. 

So what do I change, in your opinion? I've tried looking for guides, but they all require items that I get from t6 drops or something. I'm new to this whole late game thing, sorry. 

Any advice would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it okay to skip Snyder's Zero Year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 13:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll be honest. I bought volumes 4-7 back in early December. And.. I really haven't got the love for reading it like I had with Death of the Family, or any of the first 20 issues in general. Heck, even the later parts of Batman Eternal really had me on the edge and flying trough it, although not loved by all. 

So then I got to Zero Year, and I kind of have an idea about hsi origins, but I also understand that Frank Miller's is the one and true definite version of his origins, so Snyder tried to give his own take on it I guess? 

So seeing as I'd like to get around to Miller's version in the coming weeks, along with reading TDKR, I'm just looking to ask you guys. Can I skip volume 4-5 and go to Graveyard shift and Endgame?

Or should I grind through the two issues of Zero Year? 

Thanks for any help you give!

EDIT: Also, I know at some point, I'm guessing after Zero Year, it says that the events that follow are taking place after Eternal. Should I grab Eternal Volume two before continuing the normal run? I enjoy it, but it's also 40 euro.. So yeah. Kind of expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TV] Now that there are no more books to follow, there won't be as many reaction videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 11:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole thing behind reactions like the red wedding, jon snow's death, purple wedding etc, is that people knew when it was coming, even if they only noticed a minute or two beforehand. 

Now they only way we can get a reaction is if someone were to watch it, then watch it again later with someone who is on the first viewing. 

Just a little thought I had. Feedback is welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a warning for those of you that watch the show while in bed.. Watch out for the condom explosion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 03:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 2am right now, they are talking about the different types of fuel for the flame thrower right now.. The talk went on.. I was fading out, in my own thoughts.. 

AND BOOM. That fucking explosion scared the absolute shit out of me. I legitimately thought something went off downstairs. 

I'm guessing this is an exaggerated thought for most of you, but for those of us that watch it in bed, be careful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Ruffalo is absolutely incredible in Spotlight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 01:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been putting this movie off for some time now, but I finally decided to watch it today, and I won't get into how I feel about it, because I still have a disgusting feel in my stomach. ESPECIALLY after seeing that my city was on the list at the end.

But on to my point, this cast was great, it really was. But Mark Ruffalo.. Wow did he stand out. For the first half of the movie, I found his performance very refreshing. Something about character really set him apart from his other characters, although I haven't seen much of his work.

Then when he wants to publish it and get's told no.. That shouting was some of the best shooting I've seen on screen in a while. Just the passion. The belief what he was saying. You could tell he himself was truly fucking horrified of what has been happening, and he channeled it into his character perfectly. 

I also just looked up the Oscars, and he's a supporting role in this movie? I understand we had Michael Keaton playing the head of the office, but I really feel Ruffalo was the lead in this. That being said, I just hope he gets the recognition he deserves for this role. 

Phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you under 21, what is the age of the youngest person you would consider to be your friend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 14:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being new to Marvel, should I read just the 7 issues of Civil War, or the entire series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 10:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So back when I started reading DC, I read absolutely everything when it came to a crossover or tie-in, and due to doing that, I didn't enjoy certain stories as much because I didn't like the characters, or the store for said characters.

But now I'm looking at Marvel. And seeing as this is an older arc, I'm sure some of you guys know what's good and bad, but here's my thought. 

Should I read just the main 1-7 CIVIL WAR issues, or should I start off before Civil War, with Spiderman, Fantastic Four, and New Avengers, Illuminati.

Instead of listing the reading list I found, I'll leave this here. [List] (Ihttp://www.howtolovecomics.com/2014/11/30/marvel-civil-war-reading-order-guide/)

So if you guys have any experience in reading this I'd appreciate it. I'll most likely start off by reading at least one issue of different titles, and if I don't enjoy it, I guess I'll leave it. 

Although, if there are standout issues or titles I should keep up with for this, I'd love to know. Thanks! 

EDIT: So.... Looking into it further, apparently there are 107 issues? I'm not saying that's insane, but I also feel not every one of those are necessary. That being said, I'll start off by trying them all, any input is welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Jennifer Lawrence cursed with being too big a star? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 16:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just a thought I had watching the Golden Globes but hear me out. 

So when you watch a movie, the goal is to care about, or hate the characters, right? To get into the world, and forget your one. The whole point of entertainment really. 

But here we have Jennifer Lawrence. And actress who went from an unknown, to one of the biggest names on the planet.

But.. When I hear her name at this point, I'm no longer excited. I may be alone in this thought, but when I hear she's in a movie, I don't expect to be blown away, or even grabbed by her character. For example, Joy. I watched this trailer a few times to grasp what the movie is about (and I still don't get it), but while doing so.. I realized I'm now just seeing Lawrence on screen. I'm not seeing her character. I have the same feeling for x-men. You hear her talk about 'this is war' in Apocalypse, but something just doesn't feel right. And I feel it's due to her sweeping the world around the time of Hunger Games. 

Of course stars hit it big all the time, or they stay relevant across a period of time (which she is doing too, of course).. 

For example, Leo DiCaprio. He is one of the best actors on the planet, and we all know it, right? You hear he's in a movie, you watch it, or least most of the time. He is a star on the same level, if not bigger than Lawrence (for you to decide I guess), yet, watching him, I see his character. I don't see him. I'll be going to the see Revenant next week, and I really doubt I'll see Jordan Belfort trekking across the woods. 

So I'd like to hear how guys feel about this. Do you feel I'm just looking at it wrong, or if she is too big for his shoes. Even writing this, I may be burned alive, but I feel.. For the star level that she's at, I don't think her acting is keeping up with her. Of course there are different examples to prove me wrong on that, but I can't put a finger on the problem I'm talking about here, so if you guys have input, I'd love to hear it.

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where should I start with Marvel unlimited? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 16:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm gonna take the leap and buy Marvel Unlimited, or at least for a month to try it.

But, seeing the kind of library they have, I have a feeling I'm going to be overwhelmed straight out of the gate.

So I'd be looking to start with more recent stuff. I will read an older arc, if it's one of the top tier reads. For example, when reading DC, I tend to read all New52, but I've also read The Killing Joke, and All Star Superman. 

So if you guys could suggest some newer runs that are good, along with some of the must reads of Marvel, I'd appreciate it. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milo was wonderful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 18:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was excited to get him on the show after watching a few videos of his, and damn did he do a great job. 

Everything from politics (which is something I rarely care for, not being American) to whatever section of sex talk they were in. He is a captivating person, even if you disagree with his opinions. 

I'd love to have him on again some day, and feel he is a great friend for the show to have. It may not be the same the second time he appears, due to us knowing his take on it all now, but I also feel it would be nice to see him come back on again just as a friend of the show, and we skip past the interviewing section, straight to the typical PKA banter we usually get.

All in all, this episode really was great. (IMO of course)

I'd love to hear your take on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could I buy Hearts of Stone before starting my main journey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just killed the Griffin, and I'll be heading off to Yen soon, but I'm also hearing incredible things about Hearts of Stone, and I must know. Could I play this alongside the main game, without anything being ruined?

Or is Hearts of Stone, in itself, a separate part of the game, and I open that OR the main game? 

Any help would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aside from all those awesome gifs, what is this game actually like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 23:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious about this game, and I have the money for it right now..

But I'm very wary, because all I've actually seen of the game is the gliding shots of people fitting through gaps in buildings and whatnot.

So what is the game actually like? The story, the world, the side-quests, gunplay, weapon options, vehicle options, customization (if any). 

Any help on the matter would be great because I'm not sure if this is worth 55 euro right now. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Wish is just getting better and better.. [Spoilers up until the end of The Lesser Evil] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 22:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I post here quite a bit regarding the books, but I also have to discuss what I read..

So Geralt of Rivia, the Butcher of Blaviken. I always guessed he got that name for slaughtering a shit ton of people, as you'd expect with Butcher, but oh my.. You would expect when he wins that you'd be happy for him. That you would feel relief. But you don't, do you? You feel, or at least I do, genuinely sorry for Geralt because of what he had to do. 

You know he's a monster hunter for hire, and he tries to stay out of man on man affairs, like he did this time, but for someone that believes all evil is evil, and he deals with evil.. You can really feel his struggle this time due his belief that she wasn't a monster like the rest he kills. The best part of the 100 pages I've read so far is definitely the last few paragraphs after that fight. (and also the attic scene before hand)

So those of you that read it, I'd love to hear your thoughts, because I, being new to this world, could be very wrong about how I imagine Geralt feels in certain moment, so some outside opinions would be nice. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I insane for picking up a tablet with very little training before hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 20:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much has this game changed since the month of TTK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was playing back when TTK dropped, but a few weeks after release, I saw the chance to pick up a PS4 for way cheaper than normal, but having been on xbox 360 before hand, nothing I achieved carried over, so after trying to level for a few days, it felt like death. Having nobody to play with, having no gear, none of my achievements.. Basically all that is Destiny, and I had none of it. 

So back to my point. How is the game now? I saw they added in some kind of in game currency you can buy, and now you can buy character levels. Is there more to it? Has the silver ruined the game or helped it? 

How is the game lasting due to TTK being the only release for this year? (instead of how year one had content split up)

Overall, I'd appreciate some keynotes on the game's state right now, and where you see it going. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Civil War be read on it's own, without any previous reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 00:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What fantasy books should every writer read at least once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 23:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to copy/paste what I wrote in /r/books. Here you go: 


I'd like your opinions on the matter of course, because I'm not that well read if I must be honest, and feel I should vastly expand my current collection.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New year, new game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4] Is there anything wrong with not doing quests if they are somewhat illegal or morally wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 15:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious about this, because ESO is of course of MMORPG, right? 

So if I am offered a quest by a sleazy looking individual, and the mission is to steal a bottle of fine alcohol from a tavern owner, only because Mr. Sleazy wants to sell it, and he believes the tavern owner would never drink such a collectible so he could easily replace the bottle. 

If I just hit goodbye, and leave the guy there forever offering me that quest, I don't lose out on anything right? Apart from XP of course, but if I feel I should ignore such a quest, is there anything else that comes of it? 

Also, if I were to do the quest, and seeing as 

it's stealing, if I were caught I'd get a strike on my justice bar, right? 

I'd appreciate the help on the matter because I'm not too sure about the extent of the RP side of this game. 

Thanks!

EDIT: I'll also add this in, although it's completely irrelevant to the other question. How do I fish in this game? I have the bait, I've seen some fishing spots. How do I do it? Do I need to learn it from someone? Do I need to buy a rod somewhere? etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you forgot to make a resolution, why not do what I plan to, and read for an hour a day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 03:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care much for the excitement surrounding the new year, so I completely forgot that resolutions were a thing. That being said, I may not care for the event that it is, I'll still use it to try better myself. 

I don't read often, yet when I do I love it, so to fix that problem I've found my resolution.

No matter what I'm reading, or where I am, I'll be making sure I read for at least an hour a day, for the year or further.

Of course for some people an hour may be a bit, so start off at 30 minutes a day? Even just find the book you want a do a chapter a day if you can. 

All in all, I'd like to say a happy new year to everyone on this sub, or anyone who reads this. 

EDIT: Duke Paul mentioned it below, and I forgot to put it here first but here it is. It doesn't even have to be a 'real book' for lack of a better term, but could be poetry, it could be a childrens book that you're reading to a younger sibling, it could be a comic, short stories, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syndicate's reply to all this drama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 01:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This shaving video seems to be getting a very mixed reaction. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 00:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the deal with the books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 00:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far I understand, they are originally Polish books, right?

So basically, I'd just like to know how many there are, if they've been translated, if there is further translating to do, are the books still being released? 

If there are 5 books in Polish, and only 3 in English, is it still a good idea to read them? (Just random numbers of course, it's just in case some of the books are Polish only due to language barriers)

Any help on the matter would be great! thanks!

EDIT: Also, it may be a bias place to ask, but I'd like to know if they're legitimately worth reading and good books. Although they most likely are due to a video game series spawning from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you play Geralt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm trying to figure out how I should play him. 

My first time around, I did a pretty typical run of the mill guy. Now I'm picking it back up and starting again, and I feel my Geralt is way too human. I don't take the coin that is offered when I save someone. I'm helping strangers for free, and I just feel like I'm playing a much more emotional Geralt than most would. 

That being said, I understand the game is meant to be played how you choose, and for that, I'll stick to my emotional Geralt, but at the same time, I'm very curious to hear what you guys have to say on the matter.

Do you play a heartless witcher, or a for the people witcher?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone pitch me the faults and merits of both the Northern states, and the Nilfgaardians? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm coming back to Witcher after a few months away, but I have to start my game again due to loss of save, which I don't mind. 

So going into it this time, I want to know all there is of the world pre-W3. I've read up on Yen, Triss, Dandelion, a few other characters, and state of the world. Along with the first 2 game's plot. 

But when it comes to the armies, I'm struggling here. 

Apparently the north are free folk, but in saying that, they are also heavily racist, inbred, and siding with them could result in a whole lot of war among states, but the game is also seen from a Northern perspective. 

Then the Nilfgaards come along to conquer it all, and you have a past with their leader. They are wealthy, resourceful, and they have pure peace in their section of the world. But then they are also brutally strict and allow slavery. 

So can someone help me clear it up and a bit and give me some more perspective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeing how into fantasy Kyle is, and how much he loves Fallout, do you guys feel he'd fucking love Witcher 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 01:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing for about 3 hours, and remembered how incredible it feels, and that it may just be the closest we ever get to a Game of Thrones game, in terms of sex/violence/plot/ world style. 

Just a thought, but if someone with a Twitter could recommend this to him, or even if Woody/Taylor see it. 

The game is phenomenal, and knowing that he sinks hours at a time into the game he is playing, I'd be curious to see what he thinks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far through the game was I? [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 00:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So here's the deal. I had the game a while back, but it broke. Then I got it about a week ago, but due to the holidays and everything, I only got to pick it back up today. 

So when I had it, I believe the last part of the main quest, if it even was that, was when I was with Yen in Skellige and I told her I loved her. That not be the main quest, but that's all I can remember from that late in the game. 

I don't mind having to restart though, there are choices I made that I'd like to take back this time around. And in saying that, I've heard there are something like 36 endings, right? When it comes to other choices in the game, lets say something like the Baron's fate, how many outcomes are there? 1-2? 3+? 

I'd love some help on the matter, but I only put the spoiler tag up for the moments I give away. I'd rather not learn the other fates of the Baron, just a number on how many ways it could go, if we even know. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is wrong with James? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 14:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there an easier way to add custom playlists/races to my list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 12:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I thought I'd add this in, I'm only returning now, after a break since the heist release) 

So I love to race in GTA. It's probably my favorite part of the game aside from the first time heists I did when they released. 

I've also ran that highway race maybe 150 times too many. So when I look to get the custom built races, I'm not really sure how to go about it. 

I know you do it on the Rockstar website, but when I looked to add races way back when, it was always such a hassle of having to add the race, then load the new option, then add the race, and so on, and so on. 

Is this the only way to go about it, or can I just kind of mass-add the a set of races? I'm not sure if I can add playlists in general in, but if I can I'd appreciate being told how. 

Any help regarding this matter in general would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For a site that is based heavily around the anonymity of it's users, I find the lack of a 'delete everything' button terrifying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 22:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Batwoman is not a part of the Batfamily, why did she choose the name Batwoman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm just thinking about something I read in Batman Eternal a few weeks ago. 

There is a point in it when Batgirl, Batwoman, and Red Hood, are all together in Brazil or something like it. They are both hunting the same guy, and decide to teamup, but at one point, Batwoman says she's not part of the family dynamic, and to my knowledge, this is the first I've seen of her in 24 issues of Batman and a few early tie-ins to Death of the Family. 

So why did she choose that name? Also, upon googling, it says Batman is her significant other. Is that simply because of the Batman-Batwoman name, or is there some kind of connection that has been left of Batman? It seems odd, but I'll ask just to be sure. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would one go about making a Batman class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 15:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on the face now, but in terms of stats and perks, I really have no idea. 

Of course I go melee and full stealth, but I can't decide on the amount I'll put in each SPECIAL slot. 

Any help on this would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there some kind of path I should be following? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 22:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I decided to pick up Bloodborne today, and I'm really, really enjoying it. I have 4 deaths in about 90 minutes of gameplay, so I'd like to think I'm doing good. 

But I can't for the life of me figure out where the fuck I'm meant to go. I'd be going one way, then find a ledge I can drop down from, which brings me to a gate I can't open, that puts me up against a monster I can't fight yet, only to see me returning to the lantern at the start of the game. 

Right now I'm down fighting what seem to be were-people and birds. There's also a pit of pretty large zombie like creatures further down. Am I going the right way?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys have any tips for reading Tolkien? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll be honest. I'm yet to read LOTR. The only way I could do the Hobbit was by audiobook (partly because I picked it up between the movie releases, so I struggled a bit more because I thought I knew what had already happened, which was of course wrong).

But I've tried to read LOTR a few times throughout my life. I've been a die hard fan of the movies since release, and find myself watching them in the background in the same way someone would listen to the radio in a car. 

Yet I can't read the books.. I absolutely love Tolkien too. I know of Eru, I know of Bombadil, I know of Fingolfin and Feanor. Yet whenever I try to read LOTR, I always get distracted and find myself doing something else instead of continuing to read. 

So is there something I can do to remedy this? If you guys have any help I'd really appreciate it, because as you can probably see, I really do want to read it but I need help regarding how I go about reading it or the setting in which I try to read it.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some fun builds I could try out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 22:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll be honest here. I'm looking for a new build, because the generic one I've been trying just isn't working for me, and because of it, I really don't play the game as much as I should. 

Right now I'm doing the somewhat stealthy rifle tactic, then when I'm caught I go guns blazing with a pistol or shotgun. My highest 'trait' (if you'd call it that) is that I can lockpick master locks (or the one bellow it). 

So with that, I'd really appreciate some setups or guides that could make the game more interesting. Whether it be a public speaking type deal, an idiot that is max luck, a full stealth melee character (which I've heard is great but I don't see how it works in a few cases). 

So yeah, any suggestions would be great. Thanks!

EDIT: Fallout 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else absolutely terrified of going on to something that has anonymity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about Reddit inbox, Twitter, Youtube comments..

Even, as a gamer, I'm fucking terrified of playing a game of League or CSGO right now, because I know the type of people that use chat in those games. 

This is going to be the longest 45 hours of my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hearing about spoilers being around.. This is the scariest thing I've seen in a very long time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be very careful checking your inbox now folks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 11:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most valuable piece of DC material you own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 14:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So how does the world feel about Scott Snyder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as someone who has only been reading for 4-5 months, keeping up with all the writers and artists, who at points I guess are called pencillers? 

But so far, here's what I know. 

Geoff Johns is pretty liked, but I forget why. I'm a fan of Justice League, although I've heard people aren't a fan of his WW, and how he shits on Batman a lot in the early issues. 

Grant Morrison is loved for his GL run, and I guess loved in general? 

Frank Miller.. Wrote one of the greatest Batman stories of all time, but he's so off the deep end at this point that the world just accept's the fact he's a crazy supremacist.

But I came to a realization today. My favorite writer, is accidentally Scott Snyder, because I have Superman Unchained, the Vol 1-7 of Batman. And I love it. (Although I'm only starting 4 now, after finishing vol 1 of Eternal).

So how do you guys feel about him? While you're at it, if I got any of the majority opinions wrong, or you have a differing opinion, I'd love to hear it, because I feel I should start learning more about the writers I like/dislike, the artists I should look out for/ avoid, etc. 

Also, the only artist I know is Greg Capullo, for his Batman. Although Eternal seemed to have a whole lot of varying artists, so that was an interesting read. Even some of the covers were 3d, which felt weird, but in a good way.

So yeah, I'd love to hear your opinion if you feel like sharing!

EDIT: So Geoff Johns is the guy who wrote the GL run, and not Morrison. My bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just gonna throw this out there as kind of a psa, but if you don't get to see this movie on release, you may want to stay off Reddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 23:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not because the posts will be spoilers in there titles, although there will be the few that don't understand their wrong doing.

But more of the fact that there are people out there, who will make accounts, just to pm other users that browse certain subs, and spoil the thing they loved enough to be on that sub for. 

For example, two days after the release of Fallout, I was maybe 15 hours in, and bang. I opened my inbox to see what people had to say to me, and it was just sitting there. In all caps, for maybe 15 lines, the ending to Fallout 4. 

So that's it really. Be very, very careful come 1-2 days before release, on what you post/say. It may just get the movie ruined for you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's the deal with Superman Unchained? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked for some suggestions a few days ago, and somehow came up with Superman: Earth one. 

But that wasn't in stock. Well the first volume was, and so was the third, but I didn't pick them up because.. Well. I got sucked in. I bought the hardcover version of Superman Unchained. 

I honestly know nothing about this story other than it's Superman. Did I just buy the whole thing as a hardcover? Is there another hardcover I should pick up after this? 

It was a legit blind purchase, but the hardback/art style combo.... I'm not that great with money. 

So if anyone could help me with this matter, I'd appreciate it. Thanks! (If you could also give me a rating out of 10 on it, I'd appreciate that too)

EDIT: This praise.. Oh wow it seems I chose well. Thanks for the input guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I have a 3 hour train ride in a few days, and what better to do it than reading? Can you guys suggest anything you'd find in the average bookstore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll just list off what I've read so you have something to work off I guess. 

Batman 1-20

The Killing Joke

Justice League 1-34

Nightwing 1-8

Injustice 1-13 (or so)

Grayson 1-3

Supergirl 1-2

Green Lantern Rebirth (I just don't have the time or money to get through that entire read, no matter how incredible it is)

I've also watched All Star, Under the Red Hood, and some Young Justice. Oh, and The Dark Knight of course.

Just thought I'd add these in to give some kind of idea as to what I'd enjoy, and maybe you guy point me in the direction? 

I was thinking, maybe Death of Superman, or maybe even read The Dark Knight, although reading something I've watched already tends to be a problem, when I could read new content instead. I'm also unsure where to start for Superman, because I've heard Action Comics gets a lot of praise, but then there's the actual Superman run.. So yeah, any help with that would be great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They both totally know. [BvS trailer 2 spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 14:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A very different side of Bill Burr (A story about his dad) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has the best on screen chemistry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So before we start, these are the ones I already know of, at least off the top of my head. 

Simon Pegg and Nick Frost. 

Emma Stand and Andrew Garfield. 

Jennifer Lawrence and Bradley Cooper. Although it's been a while since I've watched them together, I just think of Cooper when I hear Lawrence, and think Lawrence when I hear Cooper. 

So any other suggestions would be great. As I just watched The First Time, and damn did the two leads in that work well together. 

EDIT: Just gonna throw it out there, I'd prefer male on female suggestions. I understand Jonah Hill and Tatum are amazing, but I'm looking for a good lovestory. And not the bromance kind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I buy a game from the US store, on my Paypal, even though I'm in the EU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 17:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the EU black Friday sale is on right now.. And it's below par if anything. Of course it is though, it's a US holiday, so I expected nothing more from it over here.
But looking on my NA account, Shadow of Mordor is 24 dollars right now, as opposed to 70 on EU. So if I try to buy that with my paypal, it'll work, right?
|EDIT: So here's another thing. If it says 23.99 (dollars), can I just use the xe.com/ucc website to find out what that costs in Euro or does it fuck me over? Because looking now, Witcher 3 was 34 on EU, but only 25 on NA. So would it self adjust or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I buy a game from the US store, on my Paypal, even though I'm in the EU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 17:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the EU black Friday sale is on right now.. And it's below par if anything. Of course it is though, it's a US holiday, so I expected nothing more from it over here. 

But looking on my NA account, Shadow of Mordor is 24 dollars right now, as opposed to 70 on EU. So if I try to buy that with my paypal, it'll work, right?

|EDIT: So here's another thing. If it says 23.99 (dollars), can I just use the xe.com/ucc website to find out what that costs in Euro or does it fuck me over? Because looking now, Witcher 3 was 34 on EU, but only 25 on NA. So would it self adjust or what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I rent or buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 11:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm at a real crossroads right now. 

I have 70 euro. And when I woke up today, I had the intention of renting it for 3 days, and getting a haircut, with some new clothes. (both of which I can just as easily pick up next week instead)(I'd also note my hair is nothing crazy, just a bit longer than it normally gets)

But now that I'm getting excited for it.. There is that chance I get real hooked. But there's also a chance I regret it and fall into the 'no content' mindset. But if I don't, then I'll hate bringing it back. 

Those of you that have played it, and you most likely have, being on this sub, I need some advice from you guys. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is renting the way to go when looking at Battlefront? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 01:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm just thinking out loud here. Should I drive like 40 minutes away, make an account at a rental store, and pick up Battlefront for 3 days? 

I've seen how much shit it gets, but it seems that it gets all the shit because it lacks long term content, and gets the feeling of emptiness after a while. But renting, at least in my eyes, seems like the perfect way to counteract that problem. 

Should I do it? Or pick up something older like Arkham Knight? (A game I've watched a playthrough of, but I'm mid dc-game-craving right now) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best romance movies/love stories released in the last 10 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 23:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone on PS4 struggling to find a game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 20:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just loaded up the game, went to play casual, and I've been sitting at the "Finding Teammates" screen for like 15 minutes. 

Is there a pre-requisite to playing or is there just struggle for games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me in regards to Batman Endgame? (And Eternal) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 00:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've found my love for reading again, after a long and difficult Autumn. So I just have a few questions. 

I was talking to someone a few days back and they adviced that once I read up to 20 (I was on 18 at the time), that I should skip ahead to 34 and avoid Zero Year until I'm caught up, just because it's set in the past and I guess would serve as an origin story? 

So I took his advice and got 34 to 40. But when I started it, it said the setting that is about to take place, is post Eternal. And now Jim Gordon is in prison, something about Catwoman hitting it big?  So should I go back and pick up where I left off Eternal? 

Also, my other odd question. What's up with the artstyle? I'm only a few pages in, but the change in Bruce's stature between 20 and 34 seems odd. I've only seen a few shots of him, but there is one specifically when he is about to get into the Batmobile and straight up looks lean. Way more than he should at least. So is this a change in artist or something? I'm not good with names just yet so I thought I'd ask here. 

Thanks for any help you can give.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just saw the Star Wars VII trailer in a cinema for the first time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can honestly say I cried. I never had the pleasure to watch 4-6 in cinema, and I was but a child when 1-3 came out. 

But when I heard John Williams' score kick in as "THIS CHRISTMAS" showed up on screen... I have no words for it, other than the true and real meaning of awesome. 

I may not be a massive fan who has been following since the beginning (because I literally wasn't alive), but I'll be damned if I miss out on this movie. 

Gonna be a 3 weeks guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I just pick up at the start of Darkseid War? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 10:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I finished Forever Evil a while back, and read a few issues after. But I also have no idea what issue it was. So is there an issue I can skip to in order to pick up at Darkseid War? 

I'm also not so sure how it ties-in with other series like Batman, Superman, Aquaman etc. (As it did with that Throne of Atlantis tie -in to a bigger extent) 

EDIT: I'm just going to ask for a guide to read it. 

EDIT 2: I just found where I recently was, which was issue 30. So it's still a while away, but once again, if you could share some insight surrounding how to read the event and all tie in issues, I'd much appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever been fucked over by not reading the terms and conditions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 10:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How up to date is Marvel Unlimited? (New to Marvel) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 17:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'll admit I'm new to all this. I'm not sure how you guys feel about DC, but I started reading DC a few months back and loved it, having never read comics before. 

But I never really thought about Marvel, because in my mind, for some ignorant reason, I thought all Marvel to fit the feeling of the movies, in which it's all happy and family friendly. I'm going to take a wild guess and say I'm wrong. 

But another reason I went with DC is because of the New 52. It gave me a starting ground on where to read and it was pretty simply. Is there a Marvel version of that? Or can I jump in whenever, or is it a certain event I should start reading after?

But a big draw to it right now, is Unlimited. Although I'm questioning it. Will it give me all the older comics? Because without sounding ungrateful, I want the recent stuff, and right now I don't care much for the older stuff, or at least until I get a foothold in the current run and what's what. 

Also, Star Wars.. So I'm not willing to buy Battlefront, but need my Star Wars fix until the movie. So how recent is Unlimited? Because I know this Star Wars run only started this year, does it have it on there? Or is Unlimited on the type of system in which an issue releases, then 6 months later I get that issue on Unlimited? 

This is all incredibly new to me so any help on the matter would be great. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is everyone destroying EA for a 50 dollar season pass, when Activision have been doing it for years with Cod? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 02:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before you downvote me to hell and abuse me, I am not defending EA here. I haven't bought Battlefront, a game I would really love to, but I don't see enough content there for me to spend 60 dollars or whatever it is, only a few weeks before Christmas.

So why is it that this is happening? Is it because of the whole EA hate circlejerk? Is it because it's a beloved franchise like Star Wars? Is it because of the content in the game right now? 

It was just a thought I had while listening to a podcast on the matter. Hearing that after the season pass is complete, the game will have like 30 maps and however many weapons/vehicles/heroes etc. 

Any thoughts on the matter would be great, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the beta ever hit consoles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't have a pc capable of running this game, but I do however, own a ps4. That will be the platform I'm getting the game on, so I'm really wondering here, will they be testing the ps4/xbone systems before release?

EDIT: Downvoted 3 times for asking a question.. Interesting first time on the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you guys played DC Universe Online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to give it a try on PS4, seeing as I don't have the cash for Arkham Knight right now, but I'm not so sure.. 

What is it like? Is it pay to win? Can I play solely for free, without ever buying anything or does it get to a point of making me pay? 

What is the gameplay like? The character customization. The leveling system. The characters you meet in the world.

Any help on the matter would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a CSGO equivalent of "Free to Play" or "Legends Rising"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 17:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new here, and I'm a big fan of a good documentary. 

So as someone who enjoyed both Legends Rising and Free To Play, is there something like that for CSGO? I don't know much about when the season takes place, or the main tournament of the year and whatnot, but I'd love a good look at the whole 'scene' in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What cases would you guys recommend to someone who can't really tell the difference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 01:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm new here. I've been playing like 6 days now after getting a new laptop, and my account is allowed to trade in like 4 hours. 

So what cases would you guys suggest? I can see they're all just preference, but seeing as I don't know what to look for, is there one case that has a better selection than another, in terms of skins for 'main weapons'.

Like, as of now, these are my main weapons: AK, M4A1, AWP, Deagle, and on occasion a Galil/M4A4. 

So is there a case with a bigger chance of getting a skin for one of said guns, or should I just pick up the cheaper cases/keys. 

Honestly I'm still learning my way around the market and whatnot so any help on the matter would be great. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just read The Killing Joke for the first time, after hearing the rumor of the R rated movie... Holy fu.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 13:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I knew it was highly proclaimed. And I knew he shot Barbara.. But I expected it to be at the end of the story, and seeing as the rest of it was unknown to me...

I don't know what to say. 

It took me a few pages to adjust to the older artstyle due to the fact that I've only read some New 52 stuff, a bit of Injustice and as of last night, GL Rebirth. 

It was also fascinating seeing, what I guess the one and true Joker origin. It shows he was an anxious, loving husband, who was forced to do one bad thing and suddenly becomes the most haunting villain in the history of DC comics. Also, as far as I remember it, Jason Todd got the Red Hood look from Joker, or pre-Joker I guess. So who is the other Red Hood guy they're pretending to be? 

Then Gordon.. I was sad to see what he went through, but his surroundings caught my attention way more. Those shots of Barbara... Fucking hell. I've heard before that some people believe rape was implied. But I've also heard it was just simply to take pictures for Gordon. And after reading, I can see where people get the idea, but I don't believe it. 

Now.. The last 4 pages of the story.. I've thought about it a bit, thinking about saying it might be my favorite.. But it is. Those 4 pages are truly my favorite piece of writing across any platform. Comic, book, music, movie, tv.. All of it. It was fucking incredible. 

He finally made him break. He made Batman, the embodiment of fear, laugh, and finally lose it. Not only the writing, but the style of it.. Oh the [style] (http://images.sequart.org/images/killing-joke-final-page.png). How it fades to rain. How he grins. How he grabs Joker during his laugh. 

It was a true 10/10 in my mind. That being said, I'd appreciate it if  you could share your opinion on it too, as my 10/10 may be a decimal or two too high. 

Now on to the story that took place after TKJ. We had an un-named guy just telling a story a story to a camera. Which was in fact very, very creepy. But it also felt real. We see this man, this shadow, this idea. He fights villain after villain. We get story after story.. But one day, he could just no longer exist. It's pretty haunting. 

All in all.. What a read. What a truly wonderful read. Thank you /r/Dccomics for helping me into this universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my.. Can someone help me wrap my head around the GL world so far? (Rebirth spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 02:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I made a post earlier about WW and Rebirth, but after reading 3 issues of it I only have more questions. 

So Hal was evil because Parallax poisoned his mind, and in the process he killed Sinestro by snapping his neck. Now we have the spirit version of Hal walking around, doing Spectre's vengeance work, because Spectre took control of his soul due to him being evil earlier.. All the while, Hal is still a good guy on his own, but is being torn apart by Spectre because he's committing all of these awful orders, right? But then we see Hal with grey hair go off and do all that awful stuff as he slowly loses his mind, and all the while we see these 3 shots. [1] (https://gyazo.com/9933c7449ab8a2ca6aaf7aafbb4991be) [2]  (https://gyazo.com/cfe670e3561c40a160dacc4fb0387a0e) [3] (https://gyazo.com/b5f593b1cc4c8af00bf3be44adfaf980).. Like this is all him just battling with himself right? The grey haired one is the poisoned, Parallax side of him, while the jacket wearing guy is true Hal, and hooded figure is Spectre? There was also the shot of him walking back to Coast City, after the John flip out I'm guessing.. But that's destroyed, so supposedly, according to grey haired Hal, he rebuilt the city? 

Then we have Guy. A once-was lantern who is now some kind of Warrior. But now he is back to being a lantern after a ring Kyle had went searching for him, but making him an insane person.. And I'm not exactly sure where he went after fucking up the watchtower. 

John is someone who clearly cares for Hal, and seems like another strong lantern with good in his heart, but he flipped out and started destroying the area the JL were in with ghost Hal..? And why exactly? Is the battery that his power source comes from being tainted by Parallax back on Oa? 

Kyle for some reason crash lands on Earth, searching for Guy, or at least the ring was, right? And he for some reason isn't being affected by the madness from the battery? Is it because he is rejecting the power all together, as we see him not want to use it, or is it because he admits to feeling fear, therefore fear has no sway over him and his ring? 

Then at the end of issue 3, we see Sinestro, and it seems like he admitted to freeing Parallax? Or at least woke it.. But Sinestro got his neck snapped. So how is he walking about? Or is it some GL magic that brought him back? 

That seems to be everything on my mind. Apart from wondering if there was meant to be pre-reading before this, but after Kyle explaining to someone what happened (or one of the GL's right now) I seem to have.. Actually I have nothing. I just know that Hal is corrupted as shit right now and Kyle is the savior. Apart from that I'm lost.. And damn would I appreciate some guidance. 

Anyone who made it this far, thank you. I just hope to read what I keep hearing is Geoff John's best run, right? Either way. Thank you. Any help that will untangle the mess I've stepped into would be great.  


EDIT: Okay. The guys were right. Reading the rest of Rebirth cleared it up.. And oh my fuck. That was amazing. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Wonder Woman actually have a weakness? She has to right? (Also, I'm including a question in regards to Green Lantern Rebirth) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 00:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So instead of making two posts I thought I'd do them both here.

So in the JL shot on the thread from like a day or two ago, Bruce was warning Clark about Diana having no weakness, and that he should be careful. So what is her weakness? 

Then Green Lantern...

Due to the movie, I've never really held an interest in the Green Lantern series, until I heard about Coast City lighting up in support of him during Sinestro Wars and thought I'd pick up the series.

But the only GL I know is Hal.. But I've heard whispers of John Stewart, Kyle Rayner.. I may even be listing names that aren't Lanterns, but just in the GL bubble. 

So who are the GL's? And if the opening to rebirth is one of the GL's talking about him being the last.. And the lady whiping dust off a plane to see Jordan on the side of it, meaning he was there at one point.. But then we have John above a baseball stadium?

If someone could help me into this world it'd be great. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So.. Ronda Rousey just lost her belt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 06:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as it was a topic this week I though I'd post it here. 

Ronda Rousey just got fucking destroyed. Thoughts from those who watched it? 

EDIT: [Here's the knockout clip ladies and gentleman] (https://streamable.com/gbg5)

EDIT 2: I just had to add in this [dodge] (https://streamable.com/qxyl)  {Credit to u/RazerSyndi}  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to buy keys without 'adding funds'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I of course know I need to spend money and do it through steam, but I found the question hard to put in the title.

So when you're buying a key and need to add funds, you're set to a list of 5, 10, 20, 50, 100 euro etc. options. 

But what I'm looking for is just adding the required funds. I only have like 3 euro in paypal, but if I had 5 I'd add the 5 to Steam. But in this case I can only really add enough for the key. 

Is there a way to do this or will I just have to wait it out? 

EDIT: I should add in that I can't use the public market because I'm on a new pc as of yesterday, so Steam are shutting down any trades I try to do due to some "new device" protocol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my.. Injustice really knows how to kick off guns blazing. (Year One Issue 1-2 spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 11:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (UPDATE: I'm updating this post with edits at the bottom so the spoilers will go past issue 1 and 2 now. So just a warning, the edits are now spoilers from Year One in general, seeing as I'm binge reading right now.)

I just had to make this post, and it may even be a shitpost but you be the judge, because I just thought I'd share my thoughts.

So straight off the *bat* I'm enjoying it. Seeing Bruce tell Clark that Lois is pregnant, minutes after found out is hilarious to me. How protective Clark is shows a side to him I haven't seen yet (Justice League is my only source of Superman so far). Then they kill off Jimmy. Right in the first issue. I've heard Injustice has a way of killing off anyone they can, and I know of a few deaths but I'd rather not say.

But by far, my favorite part of this two issue rollercoaster I've been on is seeing Batman call everyone to arms for Lois. 

It may not be much to reading veterans, but seeing him call every justice league member, and everyone in the area, for one missing person, is incredible to me. And knowing the tend to kill off people... With the cover of badass superman.. I'm quite scared being honest. 

I'll most likely update my thoughts when I finish year one, because damn this seems like my kind of writing/art style. Although I've heard it's not the greatest writing out there.. I don't really know the difference just yet, so it seems like I'll be just fine.

I'd love to hear your thoughts on the series though, good or bad. Thanks!

EDIT: OH MY FUCK?!? THAT CHAPTER THREE ENDING WHAAAAAAAAT!?!?!

EDIT 2: Chapter 4 was pretty touching.. But Chapter 5 was pretty fucking hilarious. Also, if this is a series that stands on it's own, who are they referring to in regards to Green Arrows last 3 of 4 women?

EDIT 3: Issue 6 shows a side of Superman I've wanted to see since I started reading back in the summer. It may be dark and wrong, because he's superman of course, but I'm just curious to see how it goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the Gun Game leaderboard is completely broken. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 14:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's nothing major to a lot of people, but after I prestiged I turned to Gun Game just about every time I logged on. Then I thought, with like a 28-4 win loss in it, I'd check the leaderboard.. 

It doesn't have a working leaderboard. Like I'm fine with this gamemode being taken as a joke or just a laugh, but if you're going to give it a leaderboard you should probably make it work. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your most emotional read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 01:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a big fan of emotional moments when reading or watching something. But seeing as I'm still fairly new to this whole comic world, I only really have a few examples.

I watched All Star Superman, that was heartbreaking. Of course it wasn't reading, like I asked in the title, but at the time I just couldn't spend close to 50 euro on a book with an art style I wasn't a fan of. 

Now I'm reading Batman. I'm on issue 20 right now.. And by god. 18 was heartwrenching. It was Requiem for anyone wondering. It involved a whole lot of Harper, and because of it, was very, very tear jerking IMO. 

That being said, it was the first time I got truly emotional over a comic (Or at least I believe it is, because I may have way back in the Summer and I just don't remember it, but that's neither here nor there).

So my question to you is, what read hit you the hardest. Whether it be with sadness. With joy. With sorrow. With excitement. With triumph. The list could go on but it's 1am and I'm off to bed. 

I'd love to hear your thoughts. Have a good night folks. 

Oh, and if it's a one shot in the way All star Superman was (right?), and you don't 100% need to spoil it, and believe it's worth reading, I'd appreciate that too because I'm always looking for new reads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does storage work when it comes to crafting tables? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 21:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I stored some stuff in the weapon table at Sanctuary. Ran down to the Rocket garage, found some stuff in the armor table there. Went back to my weapon table, it was empty, so I assumed my gear from the weapon table moved over.. But then after emptying out the weapon table, I found new shit in the armor table close to me. 

Has anyone figured out how they all work? Are they all in sync, or should I be transferring with every table I find, for loot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apart from running slower, are there any disadvantages to doing everything in the power suit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 15:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I, like the rest of us, had a pretty fun time in the power armor at the start fighting vs the deathclaw. But after that, I just parked it in Sanctuary and left it there, because I'm never sure when I need it, or what I can do with it, compared to what I can't. 

So should it only be brought it out for main quests, or should I be roaming the land in it? Can I fast travel in it? Can I do everything that I could normally do, in it? Or are there drastic changes when you get in it apart from speed? 

Thanks for any help you give. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please god. Someone tell me how he beats Zoom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 12:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time in the CW universe that I've actually felt fear. Of course he wasn't going to kill him, but how does he beat him?!

Unless Jay gets his power back. Unless they pull in every hero from the CW universe. Unless Zoom somehow loses a leg. I just can't see how Barry wins.

*THE MAN CAUGHT LIGHTNING FOR FUCK SAKE.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
