<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is mostly the frame rate and resolution - 2x 1080p at 90FPS is typical, I believe, whereas most gaming PCs are 1x 1080p at 60FPS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hired to rob a boat

Drill hole in boat and take stuff

Now we have the stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smackdown: Dean Ambrose vs Samoa Joe
 
Raw: Finn Balor vs HHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no such thing as unbiased news. Any news source will, at minimum, introduce [selection bias](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Selection_bias), consciously or unconsciously, when they decide what to report on. It's also important to get biased, opinionated content too, because it's impossible for a layperson to do all of their own analysis - the insights of smart people like Paul Krugmen and Charles Krauthammer can go along way. 

So best to get your news from a variety of different sources, and to avoid extremely biased sources like Salon and Brietbart. The best news sources have a full editorial staff and separate their news and opinion sections. I recommend: 

**Soft Paywall:**

[The New York Times](https://www.nytimes.com/) - hard news, centre-left editorial content

[The Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/) - hard, mostly political news, various (mostly leftist) editorial content

[The Wall Street Journal](http://www.wsj.com/) - economic news, various (mostly right-wing/libertarian) editorial content 

**Free**

[BBC News](http://www.bbc.com/news) - hard news

[CBC News](http://www.cbc.ca/news) - hard news, mostly liberal editorial content

[NPR News](http://www.npr.org/sections/news/) - hard news

[Vox](http://www.vox.com/) - leftist editorial content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wrong. Minorities vote overwhelmingly liberal, whites overwhelmingly conservative. If you ever want another conservative elected ever again then you need to deport the illegals.

And the username is CATHOLIC_EXTREMIST, which apparently isn't a dedicated troll account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Goldberg tells them to hit the music, then he opens the door.

Tells them to hit the music by headbutting he door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  - How it works

 - Who the money goes to

The US borrows money mainly by issuing treasury bonds -- fixed-term, low-interest loans. [Much of this debt](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_debt_of_the_United_States#/media/File:Estimated_ownership_of_treasury_securities_by_year.gif) is held by governments, foreign citizens, and banks or mutual funds - anybody who needs to securely invest a large number of US dollars. Famously, the government of China owns many treasury notes, because they tend to have an excess of US dollars from trade, but exchanging these dollars for renminbi would increase the value of renminbi relative to dollars, making it more expensive for the US to import Chinese goods. 

 How much is healthy or not healthy

Typically, a debt-to-GDP ratio below 100% is considered "safe," although there is no hard-and-fast rule. It is obviously not sustainable for the debt to grow faster than the economy, and sustainable economic growth rates and interest rates typically hover around 2%. The US has the advantage of borrowing in a currency it controls, so it is unlikely to face a debt crisis like Venezuela (who borrows in US dollars) or Greece (who borrows in Euros) so it they can borrow quite safely. Whenever borrowing money can stimulate GDP growth at a faster rate than interest on the loan accumulates, it makes sense to do so. 

 - What it would mean if we were "positive" (as in, instead of being $20T in debt, if we had a positive balance. If that makes sense?)

Your question makes sense, but it does not make sense to maintain a cash surplus. It would make more sense to decide how best to spend this money - by improving infrastructure or education, funding scientific research, etc. Cash sitting in a vault somewhere does nobody any good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I just assumed people liked AJ more than Dean during the feud?

Some people did. They both got mixtures of boos and cheers at TLC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are right you could make some good money betting on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty sure Alexa was going to go full KKK when she said "who do you think you are."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naomi's entrance is sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I forgot Ender's Game and Snow Crash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shocking Affront of Donald Trumps C.I.A. Stunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also the co2 theory doesn't work when you consider that the living can cover themselves in blood/guts and be left alone by the walkers. The live people would still be producing the co2.


True. Maybe they hunt by sound + smell? They seem to be able to "cooperate" and gather into herds.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But they did kill stormtroopers while in disguise so it is still perfidy.

No, it isn't. Luke and Han were 

a) Not combatants, and 

b) Were engaged in, *at most,* espionage. 

It is murder, not perfidy, for a spy to kill soldiers while disguised in pursuit of other aims, and regardless, Luke and Han were civilians unaffiliated with the Rebel Alliance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AJ and Dean are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People need to stop blaming third party voters. If nothing else, they vote. They can be worked with and bridges can be built moving forward.

This is hogwash. Third-party voters essentially **don't vote.**

Sure, they can be worked with, but there is nothing wrong with acknowledging that they are partially responsible for this dumpster fire.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Perhaps walkers are attracted by the carbon dioxide we exhale. 

Decaying flesh also produces CO2 though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luke and Han were not combatants. Their ship was impounded (arguably arbitrarily,) and they disguised themselves (first) to prevent themselves from being detained and allow themselves to escape, and (second) to rescue a prisoner. They did not disguise themselves to allow them to kill stormtroopers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - William Gibson: **Neuromancer**, Virtual Light, Count Zero

- Paolo Bacigalupi: **The Wind-up Girl**

- Kim Stanley Robinson: **Red Mars**

- Robert Heinlein: **The Moon is a Harsh Mistress**, Starship Troopers

- Larry Niven   Jerry Pournelle: **The Mote in God's Eye**

-  Mary Shelley: **Frankenstein**

- Frank Herbert: Dune

- Phillip K. Dick: A Scanner Darkly, Do Android's Dream of Electric Sheep?

- Stannislaw Lem: ~~Polaris~~ Solaris

- Arthur C. Clarke: Rendesvous with Rama, Childhood's End

- Ursula le Guin: The Left Hand of Darkness, the Dispossessed
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Numerous counts of perfidy

This example is definitely espionage, which is [not a war crime.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Espionage#Military_conflicts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem was not realizing which areas were key. Clinton was polling nearly as well in Wisconsin as Trump was in Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ah alright I wasn't aware it was a D D spell as well!

An awesome D D spell at that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perkins desperately needs a new gimmick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  On being told by the woman hopes to resume her employment, the judge said her employer has been very fortunate to date to have an employee as good as you".

The copy-editors were all on break?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd need a pick to get through rock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was HP Lovecraft. Must be something in the water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the IP eh! phase. 

There area tonne of craft breweries in Vancouver, but most only really nail the IPAs. I went through a brief Belgian phase but that terminated when I got back from France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. The point I was trying to make is that Mozilla is correct, and the number of native English speakers is much lower than 2%%, not much higher. 

In fact, [25% is a very generous estimate.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/English-speaking_world) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a language barrier because it isn't yet practical to develop for a minuscule demographic, but the demographic is minuscule because of the language barrier.

Look at the fourth figure. Chinese, Arabic, and Spanish internet-users are relatively under-served.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What is should be comparing is what percentage of the internet using population speaks English.

This is exactly what they demonstrated in the fourth figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken/Egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not to mention many many MANY people speak English as a second or third language so I doubt the validity of that statement.

Mozilla is correct. [~~Nine~~  Five percent of the global population speaks English as a first language, 25% speaks English at all.](https://www.reference.com/world-view/percentage-world-speaks-english-859e211be5634567) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "My game library spans about 30 linear feet of games:" rpgument over why GMs would want to deceive their players </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Lightning Colt** will soon grow into a champion racehorse.

**Math to Exile** happens when somebody flunks calculus and gets kicked out of college.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What would happen?

It would pulverize one of your atoms (probably carbon or oxygen.) You wouldn't light on fire or anything - a teraelectron volt is a lot of energy for an proton - about a million times it's rest mass energy - but it's still not much energy, about enough to lift 1.6 x 10^-5 grams up one metre, or (amusingly) almost exactly the kinetic energy carried by a mosquito. 

However, cosmic radiation does pose health risks. It can damage DNA molecules, either directly or by creating free radicals from other molecules which can go on to attack DNA. Damaged DNA can lead to cancer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I completely agree that Nixon's methods were horribly unethical, "beyond reproach" means the opposite of what you seem to think it does ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How? Surely if it's physical it has to come into contact with... everything, no matter how small..? Please help me science.

Cosmic rays are atomic nuclei (mostly just protons actually,) so they are very small. Nuclei make up about .000000000000001% of the volume of their atoms, so direct collisions between cosmic rays and other nuclei are not that common. They also have immense energies, ranging from .1 GeV up to TeVs, so interactions with magnetic fields, electrons, etc. don't do much to slow them down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead seriously, Nixon was arguably an improvement over both LBJ and Kennedy. Kennedy and LBJ entered the Vietnam War and escalated the Cold War, while Nixon left the Vietnam War and normalized relations with China. (He also, unforgivably, sabotaged peace talks during LBJ's administration.) 

On the domestic front, LBJ passed the Voting Rights and Civil Rights acts, while Nixon established the EPA, expanded social security, and forced unions to commit to diversifying their membership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Creatures with strong ETB effects are important and allow good removal to exist without being oppressive. 

- Stoneforge Mystic and Bloodbraid Elf should be unbanned in Modern.

- Planeswalkers were an OK idea, but the ones that see Modern play are extremely unfun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately a large percentage of the cost of batteries and solar cells are materials, not manufacturing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  nearly useless 

Nearly useless? Bad data is worse than no data! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be already familiar with them but Dimmu Borgir is pretty well-produced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in both cases the interestion was empty when they ran it, and then someone else enters and gets hit. 

Probably. If you cause an accident by running a red light, you are probably driving recklessly. I guess I should have said "quiet" or "deserted" - I didn't mean nobody was *in* in the intersection, I meant nobody was *at* the intersection. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Would it be reckless though? Or just running a red light and failure to avoid an accident.

Running a red light through a busy intersection is reckless driving. Running a red light through ~~an empty~~ a *quiet* intersection is running a red light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This assumes that he doesn't spend any money though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Oliver ran that bit because Trump had done a similar thing to John Stewart. He was parodying Trump.

I'd have assumed a bit more good faith if he he didn't constantly make fun of people's accents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House Tanstoffel

Symbol: A blue djinni on a white field

Words: In Kind

Lord: Darian Tanstoffel

Heir: Mortimer Tanstoffel

Ancestral Weapon: Mist, a pale blue greatsword </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I have always admired British television/BBC shows for ending on a high note

The Misfits is also an exception to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Than you very much, kind Internet stranger. 

 Maybe the stock market isn't as bad as I thought. It is a popular mode of investment, and I wish people would more diligent in investing in it. However, it does seem a reliable way to participate in economic growth of a company and even a country itself.

You are correct. Before investing in a company, you should convince yourself it is under good, honest management. Alternatively, you can invest in a mutual or index fund, which will spread your money throughout many different stocks and offer you a slow, reliable return on your investment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a thing called preferred stock. Can the everyday person buy preferred stock? No.

Preferred stock is often issued by a company at risk of going insolvent or having a long period with little cash flow. There are also strict restrictions on which companies can issue preferred stocks - in the US, [mainly banks.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Preferred_stock#United_States) 

These people get paid dividends first. Even if an amount can pay everybody.

This isn't exactly true. It's more like they get "first dibs" at money, up to a point guaranteed by their shares. Edit: Preferred stocks are more like a mortgage than traditional stocks - they usually allow the company selling them to buy them back at a fixed price, in exchange for "guaranteed" dividend payments that can be deferred once money is available or in the case of insolvency.

Regardless, employees of a company acting against the interests of their stockholders is usually a crime. This obviously happens, but it is not the norm. As somebody else in this thread posted, the value of stocks increase by about 4% per year on average. The stock exchange is an important vehicle that allows people to invest their capital in companies and, on average, make a return on their investment. What would change your view? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I do believe you explain it out well, but it still seems to me like this is all an elaborate way to get money from people.

Thank you.

It it is a way *for the company* to get money.  But it is not a scam, as you are buying a percentage of a real company that does real things. 

 A company can issue my shares with no compensation, all with the hope of profiting from other people in purchasing these "shares."

No direct compensation to you, but the value of your shares haven't changed. They money doesn't go into the voting stockholder's pockets, it goes onto the companies balance sheet. It would be [embezzlement](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Embezzlement) to directly route it to employees or individual stockholders.

 All with the hope of profiting from other people in purchasing these "shares".

Could you explain who you believe is profiting here? Stock offers add new cash to a company by allowing new stockholders to buy in. Cash leaves the company through spending, which is geared towards making the company profits in the future, or through stock buybacks or dividends, which you will be party too if you are an investor, even if you don't have voting rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, because there are literally millions of shares of large, publicly traded companies. Selling additional shares is simply one of the millions of management decisions that are made every day during the operation of a large company. You agreed to leave the oversight of the company to the board of directors, and the oversight of the board to the voting shareholders, when you bought the stock. It would be impossible to manage the company if each of the millions of individual shareholders had to be consulted. 

And again, the value of your shares haven't changed. If you own a 1% of a $5 million mine, and we double the amount of shares in the company, you now own .5% of a five million dollar mine and .5% of five million dollars. The voting stockholders own stock just like you do, they are doing the best job they can to make you money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a little bit more complicated. 

If I originally found a company I own one hundred per cent of it. If it needs more cash, I could sell half of it two my sister, and then we would each own half of the company. If it needs even more money, we could publicly incorporate it, and initially offer fifty per cent of the company, lets say five hundred thousand shares, at a fixed initial value, keeping 250,000 shares each for ourselves. Now my sister and I own 25% of the company (125,000 shares) each, and people such as yourself own the remaining fifty per cent.

Now, lets say the company has a good opportunity to expand. The company could borrow the money, or we could sell more stock, let's say another 500,000 shares for ten dollars each. Now, this would dilute both our 25% shares, and the 50% that you and other members of the public own, down to 12.5% and 25%. 

But! The company we own will become more valuable, because it will have another five million dollars under its control, which it will  spend expanding itself. If the ten dollars/share we sold this stock for isn't significantly misvaluing the company (that is, if before the dilution, the company wasn't worth 500,000 shares * $10/share = $5 million dollar company,) the value of a single share should not change much when this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So I don't profit from the value of the company's operations itself, rather value of having a "share" in the company then?

This is correct. Until such a time as Google doesn't need all of its cash to maintain or expand it's operations. It is actually better for you - a successful company expanding typically brings you much more value a stable but profitable company (that pays dividends) would. 

 Isn't it similar to a pyramid scheme, where I rely on others to participate as well?

No. Google actually produces something valuable. You own a percentage of Google, and *Google is valuable.* Non-voting stock, like yours, is typically sold to the general public to avoid needing to consult with a large number of shareholders on corporate decisions, such as managing the board of directors. You still own a percentage of the company.

Let's think of it this way - pretend Google is a mine that sells a valuable ore, and you are one of one hundred and three stockholders. Three major stockholders, who together own 50% of the company, run the business, you are one of a hundred guys who own the rest. 

It is calculated that the mine can run at a small profit, equal to $6000 per thousand tonnes of ore it produces, and the mine produces a million tonnes of ore per year. The three bosses could each get a million dollars, and you and all of your friends could each get $30,000, and everybody would be pretty happy.

However, the bosses also work out that they could double the size of their mine in two years at a cost of twelve million dollars. The owners decide this is a better idea, so that in two years, they can each make $2 million (and you and your ninety-nine buddies can make $60,000) per year. 

This is essentially how Google is operating right now, except they are planning to keep expanding their mine indefinitely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I have google stock, right? What did I buy exactly?

You bought a percentage of Alphabet, Google's parent company. You own a small percentage of Google. If Google continues to perform well, the value of Google, and your shares, will increase. 

  I don't get any share of the profit even though I am an "owner"?

Google is not paying any dividends - it's using it's cash to service its debt (about $4 billion, I believe,) perform R D, and expand it's services. If Google ever matures (unlikely) and stops expanding, it may pay dividends in the future. If you want your share of Google's success now, cash out and sell your stock.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I also enjoy Sonny Boy Williamson, John Lee Hooker, and Lightning Hopkins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Music] [IIL] The Black Keys, Howlin' Wolf, Clutch [WEWIL?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for gritty electric blues rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate the Young Turks, but yeah. They definitely rank far ahead of Brietbart on the "being real news" scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 08:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number one is Shawn Michaels ( "I'm just a sexy boy!" )


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Vampyre" and "the Burial: A Fragment." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They way they finally beat him was normalizing him and attacking him on the issues, which is what Bernie wants to do against Trump. 

This did not work well for Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  TBH I genuinely enjoy using dumb terms like "comrades" and "gulags" when talking about their stupid drama.

Sure, but there's a difference between using the term 'gulag' ironically and being sincerely worried about the reactionary counterrevolutionaries of Reddit subverting your discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ I hate the way they talk about "reactionaries" and "outside elements."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  r/socialism is run by nazimods

No, it's run by Bolshevik mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So the FX-6300 isn't really a hexacore CPU?

Sort of. [This is a Bulldozer module,](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/AMD_Bulldozer_block_diagram_%28CPU_core_bloack%29.PNG) with two 'cores' that share a single floating-point unit. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And democratic centralism dissolves into bureaucratic dictatorship once again.

I swear it normally goes better than this. Last time we had this whole Union and everything.

lol

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 09:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, I think you're an assblasted vegan that's bitching about **"muh holocaust"** because you don't like the fact that the article is shitting on an annoying vegan.

...

 ...complaining about something that happened so long ago

... Jesus Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Owens looks like the kind of fat guy you don't want to fight. 

I think he definitely could pull off this look, but I wish he would buff up a bit and and change up his ring gear a little. 

People obviously like him though, so this is just my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So you are saying that Comcast could charge data hogs like Netflix and pass the savings to consumers?

I'm suggesting it's possible. [Netflix paid Virizon for a direct line in 2014,](http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/10/since-netflix-paid-verizon-video-speed-on-fios-has-doubled/) which resulted in significantly better performance (not lower prices) for consumers. Netflix greatly benefits from net neutrality laws, obviously, as they are responsible for a huge amount of web traffic. 

  I feel it's theoretically possible, but wouldn't the far more likely outcome be that Netflix increases their prices?

These aren't mutually exclusive. Netflix could pass the cost onto their consumers, and Comcast could pass their savings onto theirs.

The point I'm trying to make is that I see strict net neutrality as a stifling band-aid solution to the larger problem of poor competition in the ISP space. It is [extremely, extremely difficult](http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/04/one-big-reason-we-lack-internet-competition-starting-an-isp-is-really-hard/) to start up an ISP, and unfortunately all current ISPs have additional obligations - they are also cable TV companies, and cable is struggling. These are large, unwieldly beasts not in a position to compete aggressively. However, excessive regulation that tells them how to do their job will not likely make things better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are companies like Comcast, Verizon, and AT T truly this.evil? 

No. That's silly (and I think you realize that.) They are for-profit corporations doing their best to make their shareholders money. Just like Tesla, EA, and every other company out there.

That being said, I do not think their campaign against internet regulation is necessarily anti-consumer. Capitalism isn't a zero-sum game, and what is good for Comcast is not necessarily bad for you. 

For example, allowing providers to charge extreme bandwidth hogs like Netflix and Google extra could potentially lower costs to consumers, and allowing providers to prioritize data based on it's data type could be transformative - critical tasks could be done remotely, safe from lag spikes, for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   He said it 12 years ago as a joke and did not know that microphones were around

No, he bragged about committing sexual assault twelve years ago, when he didn't know he was being recorded (not that that matters.)

He objectifies women [constantly.](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/politics/donald-trump-sexism-tracker-every-offensive-comment-in-one-place/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite theory is that irregardless is [a portmanteau of 'irrespective' and 'regardless,'](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irregardless#Origin) giving it a slightly different shade of meaning than 'regardless.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Contranym" means a word that can be it's own antonym (like "dust," "stone," or "table,") which is close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He definitely didn't have a "traditional WWE look," but I'm quite sure he was aware of and put effort into his appearance, and his appearance had a positive effect on his career.

Styles rocks the redneck biker look, Punk rocked the straight-edge punk rock look, Wyatt rocks the swamp cultist look. Not everybody has to look like Orton or Triple H.

Owens, on the other hand, looks sloppy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Punk.

Huh? I mean, he's not 220 lbs of muscle or anything, but he's got a unique appearance and it's not like he's not in shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Canadian PhD student, paying about $7000/year in tuition.I receive with about $28000/year in financial support from the school, in line with most of the science department students. I feel that my tuition and financial support are reasonable. 

I would not support dramatically increasing tuition, however. A glut of so-called 'useless' degrees could much more effectively averted by strengthening admission standards. Why discriminate against students without rich parents when you can discriminate against students without aptitude for academics instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, why on earth would you bring that to a conference like that? 

The same reason he brings steaks to campaign rallies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, man I have just the scene in mind, too... if only I weren't a starving university student... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks like a bad rendition of a coked-out Rich Swann. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If she was following orders, then why on earth isn't she still minister of democratic institutions?

Either Trudeau is stalling until the next election, or Monsef is taking the blame for trying to back out of the campaign promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The cultural cues of the characters is that they were all East Asian (except the Water Tribe which was Inuit), and should've been portrayed with actors of East Asian ethnicity.

I imagined them as [Siberian Yupik.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Siberian_Yupik_people) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The transistor sizes are the same (14nm,)  but the die sizes may not be (though they are likely to be similar.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/daduntsh.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 06:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palin was not "party line." Especially in 2008. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's been **golden,** he's been **shower**ed with praise...

I see what you did there! ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never liked Nikki, but I have to admit that was a solid brawl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/SquaredCircle debates how much work visiting dying children is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noob question here:

I bought a Lynnwood AV-405 amplifier with a Rotel RTC-965 preamp and some speakers on Craigslist for cheap. 

~~The system was demo'd working, but I can't get audio from any input on the Rotel except "Phono," and sound through "Phono" sounds extremely bassy and distorted. As I primarily want to use the setup with my existing speakers and an MP3 player, so it's not a huge deal that I can't get the Rotel working, I'd like to try anyways, as I may want to connect additional components in the future and I'd like the volume control. I have no screen connected to the system, so I cannot see the menu - how to I force it to use the analogue CD input?~~

Edit: I am retarded, volume was set very low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you do Robert Pickton next please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can WWE please decide whether Steph is a heel or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sasha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The French Revolution was rebelling against the government that had supported the American Revolution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate Enzo   Cass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know you are not a [brain in a vat,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brain_in_a_vat) connected not to a body, but to a computer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, no? He didn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nowhere in your link does it say you can get a license for a domestic deer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Meltzer is the Wikileaks of pro wrestling.

Uh, so he secretly works for a Russian pro wrestling company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm not sure what the difference is in raising the bottom or inflating the middle.

"Raising the bottom," via negative income tax, greater unemployment insurance, welfare, or something else, helps the people who need help the most.

Creating additional middle-class jobs, particularly unskilled, unionized manufacturing jobs, expands an existing privileged class. The working poor and the unemployed are still fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is not true. ](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Social_class#The_common_three-stratum_model) Upper-class refers to the very wealthy, middle-class refers to professionals, and lower-class to wage-earning workers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because all college educated people should be upper class not middle. Only the unemployed should be lower class.

While I don't entirely disagree with you, traditionally middle-class refers to people [advantaged relative to the "working class."](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Middle_class) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Supporting jobs for people who are themselves racist, or who have union jobs under a union that is racist is not racist . Are doctors now racist when they want to cure the disease affecting a racist?

I don't follow your analogy. Supporting the expansion of a system that disproportionately benefits an already-advantaged racial group at others' expense is racist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   What steps could the government take to make engineering fields more accessible to minorities?

Better anti-discrimination laws, better primary and secondary education in minority areas, and targeted scholarships.

A significant number of factory jobs in the Midwest have been held by racial minorities.

Do you have a source with stats? (I'm not saying your wrong, I'm interested.)

Also, despite their flaws, there is no evidence that labor unions have made income inequality worse. 

Unions exist to give their in-group as much money as possible. Do you really not think they increase income inequality between union members and non-members?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I think Sanders position on higher education would have the raising up effect you are talking about.

I don't think so. While it is certainly important to make sure  that college is affordable, college-educated jobs are typically already middle- and upper-class earning. It's more important to raise the bottom than to inflate the middle.

(I think this should be done through scholarships rather than simply waiving tuition, but that's neither here nor there.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Your plan to increase engineering, science, and entrepreneurship doesn't help Joe Six Pack who has a high school degree and does not do well in college.

Why does "Joe" Six-pack need to be in the middle class? Why is it so important that he have somebody to look down upon? 

I'm not saying he shouldn't have a job or anything - I'm just saying that it's more important to make the lives of people without "successful careers" fulfilling, rather than bending over backwards to ensure a select few less-qualified people have better jobs than their peers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks proposes tracking verified Twitter users homes, families and finances </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks proposes tracking verified Twitter users homes, families and finances </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken - egg problem. Adults who aren't interested in moe/loli/etc perceive that anime is either for children or creepy, so they don't buy anime, so unsexualized adult-oriented anime isn't made, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have any of your own territory in America? Not even developing colonies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always assumed they got a decision popup like "border tension" or something like that, where they have an option of sending an insult or losing prestige, a core, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Banks are just greedy.. the above is easily solved. Run 2 security system, first one will take normal crappy footage and when a teller get held up, she pressed THE BUTTON! - and another system kicks in and start recording in 1080p.

Something similar happens actually. The cameras obviously don't record at 1080p, but I believe the panic button increases the frame rate they record at in some banks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen one of those, but where I worked the drive-thru was run entirely by highschoolers and college students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It confuses the sensors in the drive-thru. If they blow through without making an order and the staff don't immediately understand what happened, it misaligns the orders with the cars in the drive-thru.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Who would wait in line to throw something out in a bin where there is a bin by the door?

People who don't want to get out of their car? I may not "own businesses here" but I worked at a Timmies while I was in high school and this happened all the time, and it was annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some sort of UI that shows you the names of the fields filled might be the best option. Even that has problems.

This requires a click to confirm the fill or it may be too late unfortunately, but is probably the only possible solution. 

 Is u/ScrewAttackThis a reference to "You don't know Jack", "Gurren Lagann", or "Sonic"?

Metroid, I believe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Knowingly is the word they should have used.

I would have gone with "clearly," but there was obviously no reason to tilt off like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's how he explained it. He said if John Cena vs CM Punk at MiTB 2011 is a 5, and this match is much better than that, then it deserves to be a 6.

That makes no fucking sense. Ebert didn't break his scale because he thought Eastern Promises was better than Scarface or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
