<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you also believe that your 1st Amendment right to free speech gives you the right to threaten violence against others?  That is, after all, the exact parallel to your argument.

Obviously, both statements are stupid, juvenile examples of extremist talking points, but if that's what you believe, then that's what you believe, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the question, at its heart, is what is efficiency?  If efficiency is defined strictly at creating the greatest output with the least effort, then I would agree that automation and a UBI would be the way to go.

On the other hand, what is the purpose of automation and of work?  Are we as a species ready to detach ourselves from the concept that effort equals return?  I may sound a bit primitive or old testament, but I believe that having purpose helps most of us find fulfillment with our lives.  By reducing the number of jobs too much, we end up questioning our purpose and this would likely lead to reaching out for something to fill that gap.  That kind of worries me.

That's not to say that I see no purpose in automation, but I think that with we can create a better world when we work with automation, instead of letting it do all the work for us.

There's also the worry that if we create a society in which a few extremely wealthy individuals have the power to create vast power structures based on automation, there would likely come a point in which they ask what the rest of us are here for and why they should foot the bill for our survival.  Aren't we already seeing the beginnings of this with the constant attacks on medicare, food stamps, the ACA, and other social safety nets?

As such, I believe that efficiency without purpose leads down a frightening path, while moderating efficiency with the promise of a healthy society, one in which people have purpose, is our best bet.

Thanks for a great discussion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I won't try to make your decision for you, but I will point out if your partner's life is ruined, it will be his doing, not yours.  Try very hard not to let guilt over someone else's actions deprive you of experiencing happiness or fulfillment.  He has made his own choices going through life and now it's time for you to do the same.  He should respect that, no matter what you decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the dilemmas I read about here, yours is the possibly the toughest.  To help ensure a happy future, you have to hurt the person you love and make the present miserable.

I'd suggest that your parents likely already know you're living with your partner and their offer of help isn't as altruistic as it seems.  I'm guessing they figure this is the best way to break the two of you up, and they could be right.

Your partner, on the other hand, isn't offering to make a change that would support your future and that says something about him.  People with cold weather dogs and health issues move all the time in the 21st century.  That shouldn't be too much of an issue.

So, based on not knowing many facts about your family and relationship dynamics, I think you have two parties wanting to control your future for their own satisfaction.  From everything you've written, it appears you tend to put other people's needs before your own and that others use your generosity to manipulate your actions for their own benefit.  Your parents want you to live the life they imagined for your, but don't respect your need to forge your own path.  Your partner cries and manipulates you to abandon your possible future so you don't leave him alone.  Are these people really looking out for you?

With all that said, I don't have a recommendation as to whether you should go to San Diego or not.  Instead, I'd suggest you take a good long break from everyone and use the time to ask what's best for you, and for once, you alone.  If these people really love and support you, they will do what it takes to keep you in their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been taking about this for years as a better option than universal basic income, for the very reasons promoted in this article.  Thanks for posting this, u/s-d-p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay.  You've convinced me. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that convinced me.  Thanks for the detailed and cogent discussion. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you are as entitled to a stupid opinion as anyone else, and I'm not trying to take that away from you.  You're even allowed to be wildly wrong and hateful toward people because right wingers have taught you to be afraid of your own shadow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize you needed a safe-space to talk about tweets, but I do appreciate you telling me where I can post and where I can't.  That doesn't sound like the political culture you're crying about at all /s.

As for looking bad, it seems to me you're doing a fine job of that by running around caving to alt-right talking points and smearing people who may be misguided, but deserve the same freedom of speech as Marr or yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I didn't write anything specifically about "those tweets," so you should probably take a deep breath or two than ask yourself if you're the one of those wanting the right to talk shit about others without them being able to say anything back.

Are you a delicate flower?  It kind of sounds like you are right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no such thing as "PC culture" outside the rancid, frightened imaginations of racists and bigots who want the freedom to spew hatred without being called out on it.

Cultural appropriation is fine and those who scream about it are just as bigoted as the other idiots.  And those who go along with it aren't "PC," they're morons who don't have the courage of their own convictions.  

There are brain dead followers on the left as well as the right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleese is free to say what he likes when he's in the US and anyone he offends here is free to say what they think about what he's said.  That's how the 1st amendment works.

I won't speak to what goes on in Britain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Marr should have speech without consequence while others needs to be sensitive to his feelings and keep their mouths closed.  Got it. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you nearly lost your job because of that, I'm guessing there was more on your file than you're telling us about.

Now you can rant about how you were teacher of the year for 17 years running and all the other kids bring you donuts and come to you for life advice.  I'll call bullshit now because if you're in a teaching position and can't figure out that actions have consequences, you shouldn't be in your field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so Damned sick of idiots crying about "political correctness!"  Those who complain about not being able to say exactly what they want are really trying to force every decent person to listen to their bigotry and hatred without repercussion.

In other words whining about 'PC culture' is nothing more than saying, "I want to say something hateful about you but I'm too delicate to hear something bad about myself." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree to an extent.  If all water froze the moment it hit 0, it would be hard to live in winter.  However, I don't know anyplace that has flowing fresh water and trees where the temperature is 0 degrees or below at all times.  There has to be some ability for seeds to sprout and for water to be above freezing to move from one area to the next.  This is why there comes a point going north where there are no trees, not even evergreens. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tree_line#Arctic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty definitive. So the hunt for Coldhands goes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If answers were easy, we wouldn't be debating these small points.  I think it adds to the enjoyment of it all since the books take forever to come out.

Raiding and scavenging doesn't seem like it would be enough to supplement the dietary needs of an entire population and I don't think trees grow or water would flow if the temperature was always below 0 Celsius.  And we know that there are tons of trees and flowing water as far north as the Fist of the First Men, since it has to be brought from the base of the hill.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably right.  I did some googling and found a quote in which Leaf, a child of the forest, says, "They killed him long ago," referring to Coldhands.  That would exclude Benjen.  It would also suggest Benjen, not Coldhands, buried the dragonglass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a possibility, but if the earth didn't thaw in the summer, the Wildlings wouldn't be able to grow crops of any sort, which would negate the need for creating settlements.  Although there is evidence of some trade, it probably wouldn't be enough to supplement the dietary needs of the populace.

Also, the Wall is supposedly kept frozen in summers by magic, not cold weather.  It weeps but never shrinks in size that I know of.

I agree that the rope being frayed is a clue; however, fraying isn't necessarily a sign of aging, but of being pulled apart by stress instead of cut with a knife.  I think the question to ask is why would it have been frayed and not cut.  It could be due to age or perhaps it was severed by someone who couldn't use sharp implements.  Is there any word on whether the Children use sharp weapons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough, I just re-read this chapter and was thinking about it as well.

To get to the answer, I think we need to look at the possible players as well as their motivations and opportunities.

At this point the only player we know of north of the Wall are the Wildlings, the Night's Watch, Bloodraven, the Children of the Forest, Benjen, Coldhands, and the Others.  Of these players, the Others can likely be ruled out because they wouldn't likely give the NW effective weapons and they probably wouldn't be able to even touch dragonglass.  The Wildlings are likewise unlikely to give away weapons they could use.  And of course, the NW didn't bury them to give them back to themselves and didn't know of their power to begin with.

So that leaves the Children, Benjen, and Coldhands.  Benjen and Coldhands could be the same person, but either way, he/they are probably dead and reanimated by the power of the Children or the Others, or simply dead and lying under the snow.  It is also very unlikely that Benjen would have known about the power of dragonglass without the Children, and its not very plausible to believe he would have been able to discover their power and gather a sack-full of weapons over the course of the months he was in hostile territory while at the same time trying to avoid Wildlings and Walkiers and find enough food/water/shelter to survive.  Bloodraven is known to be working with the Children and Coldhands is strongly implied to be doing so.  As I wrote above, the Others wouldn't use either Benjen or Coldhands to give weapons to the enemy, so that leaves only the Children/Bloodraven.  

The NW cloak that the weapons were wrapped in wasn't rotted so that indicates it was a newer cloak that would have probably come from a recently killed or still living crow, which strongly suggests Benjen.  

Regardless, I'd say every indication points to the Children leaving the weapons although they could have done it directly or through an intermediary.

If the series is ever completed, we'll see if GRRM came to the same conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the Westminster area and feel like I got the best of small town America along with the ability to hit the city when I want to experience culture and events.  

My home is on a country lane with a farmette next door but I can get to downtown Westminster within 10-15 minutes, which has many shops and great restaurants while keeping that small town feel.  Or I can get to downtown Baltimore in about 35-40 minutes for the harbor, Fells Point, Mt. Vernon, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I didn't realize I was "debating" with a child.  When you grow up, maybe you'll learn to form a cogent point on this subject.

Until that time, you'll have to throw your little tantrums without my help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its fine when you blame Sanders and his supporters but not cool when directed back at you, yet you don't see the entitlement or privilege in your posts.  Classic!

Personally, I doubt you did any of the things you claim.  The entitled rarely actually do much, they just like to brag about what they want us to think they did.

Now that you and your three remaining 'pure' friends have chased the vast majority out of your party, you come online to bitch and cry about being left alone.  Too bad for you.  Those of us who actually care about what happens to the people of this country have moved on without you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bernie and his loudmouthed supporters..."

That statement confirms everything I've posted here.  You want empathy when you write that kind of shit?

You talk about being a lifelong, loyal Democrat but you never bothered to read up on what the party stands for or who it was meant to represent.  It was meant to represent those dirty loudmouths who are so beneath you.  

And Sanders supporters weren't the flaming assholes screeching about things like how it was her turn and he was merely an interloper.  That was you and your entitled crew.  Hell, you're still doing it.

And now we have Trump who will make very sure to nominate justices who are against everything actual Democrats stand for.  Pat yourself on the back for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm... Yes.

Everything you write drips with exclusion and self-entitlement.  Sander's was running on a Democratic platform but you want to focus on how long he was a Democrat.  

Some of us care far more for policy than party.  But you keep pushing center-right, pro-corporate candidates who are despised by the majority and see how that does for you. 

And enjoy the four years of Trump your privilege gave us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
