<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.
I got WMC for free with Windows 7 professional. Then I upgraded to Windows 8. WMC was gone but could be purchased. So I bought it. When I upgraded to Win 10 it was gone. Something I OWN(Purchased) was gone and not able to be installed and used. I downgraded back to 8 because WMC is the only way I can use my tuner. I don't want another program(I've tried a few). I like WMC. I bought it. I should be able to use it. This is what sent me over the edge for Win10. That and I have a Windows Phone. A pretty high end one, Lumia 1020, and after having winphone 10 brick my phone twice I was told by users, not microsoft, that my hardware is not compatible. Thanks MS. Way to think of your users needs.../s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in middle school, 11-13, I started calling my friends cause now I was allowed to use the phone. What I didn't know was how collect calling worked. So, if I wanted to call my friend from the library, or the local pool, or wherever I happened to be, I'd use the pay phone and make a collect call.

One day, one of my friends parents called my house and left a very angry and loud message saying I need to stop calling them collect because it was costing them a lot of money. I deleted the message before my parents heard it but very slyly asked my parents to explain collect calling to me at dinner. They basically told me never to use it unless it was an emergency. A few years later enough people had cell phones that it wasn't an issue.

But yeah...collect calling...whoops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In college I went over to a classmates dorm to work on a project. His roommate was a friend from home. I noticed when I got into the room that there was just one giant bed. They had pushed the beds together. I don't think they were gay cause I thought the roommate had a GF. So, just two straight college dudes sharing two twins. They thought it was normal. No one else I talked to about it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish I had done a PhD in Econ after getting my undergrad in Econ. I really love the subject in general, especially labor economics. Maybe I'll go back at some point, but after 2 undergrads and a masters, I'm kinda done with school for now. I'm thinking of having business cards printed up that read "armchair economist". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As they have told me. But they still regret not just stopping with a Masters and joining the workforce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My undergrad was in Econ? I took all the grad Econ classes even though they weren't required? I really like Econ? But I didn't get it so I must not have been qualified. I'm not saying I was fully qualified, but the response I got was relevant to the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got my MBA and applied to teach grad level Econ. They told me I couldn't without a PhD. So...maybe apply to teach at Grad school? 

I'm also looking at teaching online. Seems like an efficient use of time. I can "teach" 3 sections without leaving the house. I hate online education but if I can make a buck...why not? You're essentially a moderator of a forum(class participation) and then need to grade assignments which in many cases is done automatically. I haven't heard back but I hope to start this fall.

I have family that went for PhDs in the sciences. All but one regrets it. The one that landed a sweet Phama job. The others are stuck doing bench work as Post-Docs hoping they can publish and get out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 00:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hot is the skillet? I wanna do this but children reaching into a hot cast iron skillet sounds...risky. We have only so much burn cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 19:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, I'm not allowed to tell Executives that there is a process and that skipping the process is a disregard for any security and inventory controls we have in place. You know, for the safety of the organization... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 01:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illway the amay on the anceday orflay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can he donate some money to all the Craigs in the world who have had to put up with some sort of joke related to craigslist? Shits getting old... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Man's Sky please.

Just had to shell out $2500 to get my car fixed after getting in an accident on my way back from my best friends wedding where I had to buy a $500 tux and spend 3 nights in Cleveland. Could really use a win, and a game to play this summer! Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 16:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't the norm, but the only time I called a mechanic a crook was when I went in for an oil change and when I came back three hours later all four wheels are off and I'm being told I need new brakes and they already started the work. While I have zero confidence when it comes to car maintenance, hence why I pay someone to change my oil, I'm not a moron and I know signs for when I need brakes. There was no screeching, or issue with stopping distance. I told the mechanic that heads up would have been nice, and that he really should have asked permission before he did something like that. I insisted he put everything back together, to which he bitched and moaned and said it would be unsafe for me to drive away in the condition the car was in. Saying things like "I'm not allowed to put it back," or "I won't be able to get it done until tomorrow," pissed me off even more. I gave him the $30 he wanted for the oil change, waited an hour+ for him to put the brakes and wheels on, drove right to another shop where they told me I had at least 4000 miles left on my brakes. He also told me that the oil filter wasn't new. And now I go to that guy for everything and have for 3 years. 

All I want is a person I can trust and rely on. I don't care if it costs me a little more. The problem is, when you do run into a crook, what are you going to do about it? They know how to get you into an uncomfortable position. I can call the BBB or tell everyone I know but I'd rather put up a billboard over the highway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is happening over at r/2007escape? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no one has actually tried it? Is there anything wrong with a bodyweight workout? I want to get into shape but obviously am pretty lazy and a workout "plan" seems like a good way to stay on track and stay motivated.

Thanks for the comments so far. Suggestions are welcome. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foundation Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person I know is circulating the Foundation and Foundation-Light 30 days workout plans.
Does anyone have any experience with this? Does it "work"? 

In case this isn't well known information here's a link, hopefully it doesn't break any rules. http://darebee.com/programs/foundation-program.html

EDIT: There are also nutrition guides. I understand that weight is lost in the kitchen and muscle is built in the gym. The menus are paired with goals. Are they worth using as a framework for a diet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Czech mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Young MC - Bust a Move](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xy4FXhkm6Nw)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was on the desk(the service desk) we'd get calls like this all the time. BUT there was one guy who started calling in every morning at about 7:55am because he couldn't log in. I used to help him when I was a Desktop tech(I went from Desktop Tech to Senior Tech at the Desk) so we knew each other and I almost was delighted to get his call every morning. Started me off right. After about...a yearish of this going on he started getting really irritated and seemed to forget who he was talking to. He would say things like, "I never used to have this problem," followed by, "there's a guy that always fixes this for me." I never really thought anything of it. At some point, we get a resignation notice for him. We all notice it and have sentiments of sadness since our favorite inside joke would be gone soon. He was retiring at 76 after 35 or so years with the company.

Two days after he retired, at like 2:30 in the afternoon, we get a call. It's him. And he wants to reset his password. This time his account has been disabled. He had left the firm. We weren't sure what to do exactly. 
We had been trained to never tell someone they had been removed the the company. Someone calls in and we've termed them, we tell them to go talk to their supervisor. We say nothing about the disabled account, or that we got notice from HR to remove their rights.

So, armed with this training, we tell the guy, "you need to go talk to your supervisor." He hangs up, frustrated. We all think it's weird but we all have other work to do. We noted he called form his office, but how did he get in there? He must have turned in his badge upon his retirement. How did he get in the building even? He'd have to go through security who gets the same HR termination notices we do.

I call a desktop tech to go check on him and to swing by his supervisors office on his way. I later hear through the tech and a buddy in security about what happened:

Desktop tech and the supervisor show up. The supervisor asks him what he's doing there. He days he's trying to log into his computer. He notices the desktop tech and saying something to the order of "good thing you're here this fucking thing never works right." After some discussion, Security gets called. He is physically removed from the building and his wife is called.

Luckily this guy couldn't find his car in the parking lot before she showed up. Turns out he had dementia. Some days were better than others. This was a bad day.

I know, long story. But I'll never forget what happened and just remind myself when I have a frustrating call, maybe they have dementia and it's not my fault.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 16:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got shingles when I was in 10th grade. And since shingles are an "old person" issue, everyone just thought they were bug bites or something. For 2 weeks I felt like something was trying to eat its way out of the left side of my body. 

Went to the doctor, he asked 2 questions and was like "yeah, its shingles, here's a prescription." 3 days later(maybe longer?) the pain stopped.

I'm going to assume im lucky here though. No broken bones or major bodily damage. No exploding organs or surgery. I want to say I'm lucky but I know one day I'll get hit with it all at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here except it was my grandfathers pipe tobacco. I still love the smell.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for doing this! Yay community!
I'm looking forward to No Man's Sky cause it looks amazing. I haven't pre-ordered but have requested June 24th off from work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 16:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone playing with the O/Us today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Web Site and App not updating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 04:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this happening to anyone else? It is now 10:30pm EST and the front page of espn.com says there's 8:51 left in the Cavs game. The app seems to be stuck there too. All the games seem to have frozen then. Weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 03:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any basic, step by step, idiot proof directions out there? Everything I've found has been intimidating. Also, I'd love to build one that is as large or larger than yours and I'm struggling to find a tv worth destroying. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 17:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to take this opportunity to thank everyone involved with this sub, especially the mods.

I got into sports betting a few months ago and knew nothing about...well anything. Thanks to some very informative posts, stickies, and other useful links, I've learned so much that I almost feel like a pro now!

At least I know the lingo and can keep up with my friends as well as make some informative, yet pussy, bets.

Keep the picks and information coming everyone! I really appreciate the community and all that it provides.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up from the meadows Rich with Corn
clear in cool september morn
The clustered spires of fredrick stand
green walled by the hills of Maryland
round about them orchards sweep
Apple and peach tree fruited deep
fair as a garden of the lord
to the eyes of famished rebel hoard...

4th grade history class, had to memorize a civil war poem. There's more but that's all I can remember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 17:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WaterFox has frozen...

FYI: WaterFox is the 64-bit version of firefox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
