<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject943</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babysitting for the Fitzwillys (Part 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Part 1**: https://redd.it/691whw

*"Rock-a-bye baby, in the treetop*

*When the wind blows, the cradle will rock*

*When the bough breaks, the cradle will fall*

*And down will come baby, cradle and all . . ."*

I must have sung that one a thousand times, Margery joining in with no small amount of gusto. 

That was my first task. 

Put precious Jaime to bed. And Jaime loves nursery rhymes, so I was forced to sing to him as I rocked him in my arms and Margery danced to the tune, eyes closed, arms whirling. Lionel and Bosworth were nowhere to be found. Dylan took it all without so much as a minuscule shift in his expression. I studied his face as I held him, trying to gage his thoughts, trying to peer into his state of mind and wordlessly ask him about the horrors he had endured in the last decade. 

There was nothing. I had prayed to see anger in those brown depths, hatred toward his captors maybe, embers of resolve but it was as if all the fight had gone out of him. He seemed . . . defeated. Dead. My heart clenched. 

Eventually, Dylans eyes began to droop and he nestled into my chest as though he were a real baby. For the briefest of moments I thought I could feel him squeeze my arms quickly a sign of recognition or a plea for help. But my fleeting hope disappeared once I realized he had actually fallen asleep. 

Hed been a chubby kid, but there was so little of him now that I knew I wouldnt need help lifting him. He was so malnourished that I barely struggled to carry him to his crib. It was marginally bigger than a regular one and my heart broke at the thought of him lying here for years, the implications for not only his physical health but his psyche as well. 

This was humiliating. 

What were they playing at? Forcing a grown man to pretend to be a baby? 

After I put him down, I felt Margerys claw-like hand clasp my shoulder. 

He is so precious, my little boy. I can see that youve grown attached to him already. There is a bond. Her overly-animated voice chirped in my ear, her mouth so close to my face I could smell something rancid on her breath. She giggled in that creepy way of hers, a sound that bore no trace of happiness or joy, but rather seemed to slowly scrape away at my sanity. Like nails on a chalkboard. 

You have been the only nanny so far who has been so helpful. 

She placed her chin on my neck, its boniness digging into my skin. Revulsion washed over me in waves and I had to force myself not to shake off her grip. 

You are the only one that seems to connect with our little Jaime. The others were all so . . . Here she sighed dramatically, her impossibly wide grin tilting downwards. Naughty. She giggled again, squeezing my shoulder. But youre a good little girlie, arent you? Youre not going to disappoint us like they did. You are going to stay with us, become part of our family. Were so excited to have you here. 

I could hear the blood pound in my ears. 

What . . . what happened to the other nannies? I asked quietly. 

Margerys smile grew even wider, more malicious. 

Oh, we had to let them go. But theyre safe, theyre sorry, theyre so, so beautiful now. She pinched my cheek. Lovely rose of a young woman, you are. 

Then she practically leaped away from me and began chanting Ring-Around-The-Rosie, winking at me before skipping out of the nursery. Only once she left did I release the breath Id been holding. 

I had to stay sane, strong.

I couldnt fall apart.

I couldnt cry.

I couldnt freak out. I needed to keep my head if I was going to get us both out of here. 

I was offered a guest bedroom but told them Id rather sleep in the babys room, in case he woke in the middle of the night or something. Margery assured me that Jaime never did that, he was not one of those naughty toddlers. I spent the entire day scoping out the room, looking for hidden cameras as subtly as I could. I found two, one hidden between the knickknacks of a shelf and the other in the button of a teddy bear. I pretended to check on him as he slept, but I was actually poking at Dylan, trying to wake him. 

I wasnt sure how I was going to get rid of the cameras without them noticing, but I couldnt wait until Id come up with a good enough idea to talk to him. 

He was practically comatose. He didnt budge, not an inch, not even when I pinched him so hard his skin bruised. It was almost as if theyd drugged him. 

I was invited to have supper with them a few hours later. It was one of the hardest things I have ever had to endure, sitting opposite them, watching them eat and carry on as though they had not destroyed the life of my best friend. I thought of his parents, how heartbroken they were when their sons case was closed. A lump formed in my throat. 

No.

I couldnt be sentimental. I couldnt be weak, not if I wanted to survive. If I wanted to get out of this, I had to be calm and I had to be clever. 

I dragged my fork through the mashed potato on my plate, not intending to eat anything these monsters were serving me. I didnt drink anything, either. I went to the bathroom or kitchen and drank water from the tap if I got thirsty. I cleared my throat politely. Margery stopped her singing and looked at me expectantly, food crested around her mouth which still hung open mid-song. 

That damn woman could never stop singing.

Um, I had a thought.

She smiled encouragingly at me. 

I continued. If I am going to take on this job, you expect me to be here full-time, right? 

She nodded slowly, her head lolling to the side. Lionel remained quiet, polishing off the steak on his plate. Bosworth, whod been lurking in the corner of the room, looked as nervous as ever. 

I took a deep breath. Well, thats not going to work. I mean, you took my phone, right? If I just stay here and skip all of my classes and not let anyone know that Im ok, then theyre going to worry and call the police. Theyll look for me, thinking Im unsafe or being hurt and if they find me here, which they will, then they 

Margery suddenly let out a loud, inhuman-sounding screech, covering both of her ears as she shook her head violently. The sudden display chased my planned speech right back down my throat and I nearly pissed my pants right then and there. 

Then suddenly, she stopped. Just like that, as though she could turn off her craziness with a switch. She smiled at me, spittle glistening on the sides of her mouth, dripping down her chin. She cocked her head to the side again. 

Youre not planning on disappointing us, are you? Her voice had returned to its normal, chirpy cadence as she singsong-ed the words, but there was a very evident threat beneath the sugar. 

I shook my head no. No, no, of course not. I want to be here. I want to be part of this family. 

That seemed to steady her mood. She straightened her head. I was learning the outlines of their insanity, learning where to tread and where to sidestep. 

All I was trying to say was that I should let at least one person know that Im safe. If I could call someone, they would make sure that no one informs the police or gets the wrong idea. 

For what must have been a full minute she said nothing, just stared at me, smiling. I never thought a smile could make me feel as sickened as I did then. 

But there was something worse than Margery Fitzwillys smile. 

Finally, finally, she answered. I suppose that makes sense, dear. Though, you must understand, weve had so many girls and boys who said they wanted to be a part of our family too. They disappointed us. They tried to get away from us, tried to get us in trouble. I like you, girl. I really, really do. I would hate for you to be just another disappointment. She flattened her veined, weathered hands on the table. But I do see your point. We shall need to trust you first. Trust must be earned. 

Then she stood, as did Lionel. They both left without another word to me. 

Bosworth escorted me to the nursery. Dylan was still asleep. I tried talking to Bosworth but he simply shut me in the nursery and bolted the door from the outside. I sank into the rocking chair beside the crib and just sat there for what felt like hours, stewing over what I could possibly do to earn their trust. 

Only once the idea began to form in my mind, did I allow myself the luxury of falling asleep. 

The next morning brought a fresh sense of determination. When I woke up, Dylan was on his knees and leaning against the bars of his crib, looking at me. I couldnt say anything to him just yet. I knew we were being watched and listened to. So I got him out and dressed him in day clothes. I could hear his hollow stomach rumbling, so I carried him downstairs. The door had been unlocked in the early hours. I had to put him in a giant high-chair and then feed him a bottle of formula. Something made me feel vaguely uneasy about the white liquid, but he drank it greedily, and I made a mental note to try and replace it with something else. 

Margery made me play with him, flying toys through the air and making all the sound effects as well. I tried moving through the house under the guise of our little games, trying to spot my phone, but of course it was never in plain sight. Dylan remained as quiet as death, but still tried to grab the toys I teased him with, acting out the role so faithfully I wondered if he had started to lose his real identity through the years. Nothing overtly strange happened until about mid-afternoon. 

I had taken a bathroom break and when I came back, Margery was waiting for me outside. She tilted her head to the side in her regular, creepy fashion, and pointed to where Dylan lay sniffling.

The baby needs changing. 

My stomach dropped. 

Oh god. 

No, they werent going to make me do this. 

Yes, they were. I was forced to change Dylans diaper.

Hed shit himself quit badly, and there was something different about his demeanour, a fracture in his previous monotony. I was more concerned about the humiliation this guy must have felt than having to clean up his shit. This was the regular pattern of events for about a week. 

I fed him, burped him, changed him, played with him, sang to him, put him to sleep. 

The initial bubble of hysterical laughter that had accompanied nearly every routine had long since vanished by the third day of this. I was getting angrier, wearier, more pissed off. I had to try and gain their trust by making them think I was being compliant but I didnt know how much more of this I could take. I still couldnt communicate with Dylan safely, for someone was always watching us. I eventually memorised the layout of the bottom floor as I was never allowed up the stairs.

But I knew the living areas and kitchen and library and nursery quite well, even discovered a crawlspace hidden in the back of the nursery, though it lay in one of the cameras line of vision.

The day eventually came when Margery allowed me my phone call, after I managed to convince her that people would definitely be starting to worry now. I had put Dylan down for his nap. It was late afternoon, early evening. I was called into the kitchen and handed my phone, the Fitzwillys and Bosworth facing me, waiting to listen to make sure I didnt say anything I shouldnt. Lionel leaned over my shoulder, watching me select the number.

Shit. I couldnt call the police.

The only person who was in my city right now, who Id known for a long time and who might believe the insanity of my situation was Zander. So I clicked on his contact. Lionel nodded. 

Zander, to my eternal shock and everlasting gratitude, actually picked up on the forth ring.

Teresa? his voice was distorted and there was a ton of noise in the background. He was obviously busy, at some event or other.

Yeah, um, hi. My voice was surprisingly even. 

I shifted my gaze to take in all of the three people around me. Lionel still waited behind me, Margery stood to my left and Bosworth to my right. The counter stood in front of me. From the sound of his voice, I was probably the last person on this planet Zander would ever imagine calling him. I could practically hear him raising his eyebrows. 

Uh, how have you been?

Im good, Ive been good, thanks. Yourself?

Im fine. Look, Teresa, not that Im being an asshole or anything, but why are you calling me?

I cant say hi to an old friend? I laughed the fakest laugh I had ever emitted in my life. 

Youre hilarious. Okay, Im gonna need you to listen to me very carefully, okay?

Teresa, whats going 

I shoved Lionel as hard as I could, careful to not end the call. I dove over the counter and felt Margery grab onto my foot. I lifted my other leg and kicked her hard in the face. She fell back with a scream and I ran like hell to the nursery. I grabbed the key from the outside lock, shut the doors and bolted it. 

Dylan was still asleep, still put out by whatever shit they put in his formula before every nap and sleep session. I put the phone to my ear, heart beating out of control. Zander was still in mid-sentence.

 iously, what the fuck is going on over there? The background noise had faded to a murmur. He must have gone somewhere quieter. His voice was angry but there was concern as well. 

I could already hear Margerys banshee-like screams, I could hear the thundering of footsteps down the hall. 

Listen, please! I begged. Im with Dylan right now and were in a trouble. You need to get the cops to come over here and now! The people were with might kill us! 

Bosworths heavy blows began shaking the door. I moved to take Dylan out of the crib and hide him, just in case theyd try to hurt him.

Zander, please, youre the only one who can help us.

What, did you just say 'Dylan'? I dont 

I SWEAR TO GOD THIS ISN'T A JOKE! PLEASE JUST GET HELP! 

I screamed out the address at him several times before my phone died. I rushed around the room looking for the cameras, then covered them. I turned off the light and began dragging Dylan to the crawlspace Id mapped out in my head. 

We had just reached it when the door came flying off its hinges. I quickly laid Dylan inside as comfortably as I could in my haste and left the door semi-open, moving a chair in front of it.

The light came on and then Bosworth was picking me up by the arms. I kicked out, as hard as I could, catching him once in the groin and he barely flinched. That was . . . not normal. He threw me to the floor and when I looked up, I looked up into the most horrific sight I had ever seen in my life. 

I thought Margery Fitzwillys smiles were unsettling. 

But they was nothing compared to the long, long frown she wore that dipped past her sagging jowls. 

Her face was bloody from the kick my boot had delivered, thick blood pouring out of her nose. Her eyes had gone dark, something vicious and evil barely restrained behind them. Lionel wasnt there.

Just Margery, in her terrifying glory. 

She leaned down until her bleeding nose nearly touched mine. 

Naughty, naughty girl. Why did you do that? 

She tilted her head to the side, several degrees further than what looked comfortable or natural. I felt a dread unlike any other I had ever experienced before begin to seep into my very soul. 

Take her. She straightened herself and Bosworth picked me up again, dragging me by the arms out of the nursery. She sang as I was carried screaming across the floors of the house and down a flight of stairs, her voice the same eerie chirrup that only fed my terror and panic.

*Ring-a-round the rosie,*

*A pocket full of posies,*

*Ashes! Ashes!*

*We all fall down . . . *

**Final**: https://redd.it/69gtqq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't think of any interesting question but this sounds pretty good . . . waiting for the next update.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
