<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1580</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did this happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! The developer shared a lot of stuff with me, and I have a reason to believe that nothing shady is happening (from a privacy standpoint) -- which is why I chose not to report it on the site. But still, data usage is a thing that Talon users should keep an eye on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I have been looking for a Twitter app that makes sense to me. I have literally tried a dozen of them, and I don't know, for whatever reason, the official app just seems the best. I also find the "night mode" awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, 

The developer and owner of the app has since responded to me, here's the statement he provided:

"I made changes, and released an update, last night that will forcefully restart the app if it detects random data spikes, to close the data connection. I had about 5 reports this week of anywhere from 600 MB - 4 GB spikes. I saw your tweet toward me this morning, nothing like that will happen again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talon for Android is consuming a lot of data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 14:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, this is Manish Singh, freelancer with CNET. For the past two days, I have been noticing that my Nexus 6's battery was dying every 5-6 hours of moderate usage. After doing some investigation, I found that Talon app had used [more than 96GB of data during the same period](https://twitter.com/refsrc/status/761201948628389888). I thought maybe it's an isolated case, but turns out some other users [have also complained](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B6B4X7fZNYOlZEhiXzBlUUUyWVU/view?usp=sharing) about it on Talon's Google Play listing. I am awaiting Talon's response, but in the meantime, if you use this app, I would urge you to go to Settings and see if anything weird is happening at your end as well.

Note: I'm identifying myself only to ensure that people know I don't work for a rival app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project Hosting Service Fosshub Compromised, Embedding Malware Inside Hosted Files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of the "journalism" the majority of tech reporters/bloggers do these days? For many of them, writing press-release esque launch posts of new mobile phones and tablets is all what journalism is. Do you think people -- who mostly do this kind of work -- stand a chance to survive in the industry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomis first laptop is a Macbook Air rival thats as cheap as $540 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 09:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple to open retail stores in India, says CEO Tim Cook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 08:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's largest seaplane unveiled by Chinese state company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Orders Yahoo to Explain How It Recovered Deleted Emails in Drugs Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking: Verizon Nears Deal to Acquire Yahoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking: Verizon Nears Deal to Acquire Yahoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except I don't live in the States, and have a carrier that offers 250GB plan + I buy more data when I need more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 21:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would usually consume 120-150GB of data in a month. (I stream a lot of YouTube and Netflix).  But thanks to the Xbox One, my monthly data consumption has been between 200-250GBGB for the last couple of months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon to disconnect unlimited data customers who use over 100GB/month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EFF is suing the US government to invalidate the DMCA's DRM provisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden's New Research Aims To Keep Smartphones From Betraying Their Owners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
