<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, with only 9 teams you become a lot more accustomed to playing the same guys every other night or so. Also they had a lot of 3-nights in a row playing games. But yeah, context is key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iman Shumpert and Scott Brooks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are we gonna throw up an asterisk like Barry Bonds and 73? There's no evidence that Oscar didn't do the same thing in 1962... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he has the chance to do something that hasn't been done since 1962...can you blame him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're so annoying. That seven-game series between the Bulls and Knicks in 1994 should reinforce the idea that it was a great era with many exciting playoff series. Whether or not Jordan was there at the time doesn't have anything to do with the luster of the decade you fartsniffer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D2: Team USA forgets the value of teamwork at the Junior Goodwill Games while Team Iceland (the good guys) go back home to train after kicking the snot out of the Americans in a poetically just rematch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crashing, hit a wall...right now i need a miracle... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this makes shit posts look like dissertations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao, like I said, this is pointless. You seem to think that basketball is played on paper and the actual games don't matter, which just makes me sad as a fan of the sport. The '90s were a great era, and I'm sorry you can't appreciate them because you haven't watched anything pre-2003. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also spent a lot of time guarding PG's before Shaq left: Stoudamire, Mark Jackson, Kidd, McKie, Bibby, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dan Majerle. This is pointless, I remember your username bc we got into this about a month ago. Michael Jordan is the GOAT, you jerk off to LBJ every night, and nothing either of us says will convince the other. Good day sir/madam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Heat gentleman-swept the Thunder because Harden forgot how to bball and Perkins couldn't handle the small ball, there's nothing in that series to suggest it was a challenge. The 2013 and 2016 series were both great, but LeBron was spanked in 2014 and 2015 (once the Warriors went small). But you're probably one of those guys who thinks the 1993 Suns were scrubs, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one on the Celtics or Pistons retired, they just got old. Same thing that happened to the 2000s Celtics and Lakers. And LeBron's path got exponentially easier when he left to build his Big 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> always second </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible to learn how to rebound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, so what about the 2007 Heat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Love a good defender when he has the worst DBPM of his career at -1.1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year's Finals showed us regular season wins don't mean shit when you get to the playoffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your first sentence makes no sense. And you're still ignoring my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texas isn't bad:
Bradley - Tucker - Durant - Aldridge - Turner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty impressive that he dropped 63 points on the eventual champion Celtics, a team that until 1996 was considered the greatest ever. What does "fucking dip" mean? Or are you that frustrated that you can only resort to cursing me out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess there's no established time-frame for when we can start forgetting about spoiling it...obviously things like "Snape kills Dumbeldore" and "I am your father" happened so long ago they're mainstream now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again you're completely ignoring my point. 

"LeBron never lost in the first round" is supposed to be some great feat according to you, even though he has never played anyone of the 86/87 Celtics' caliber in that round. 

If you're going to knock MJ for taking a lottery team to the 8th seed as a rookie and losing in the first round his first three years, then I get to knock LBJ for missing the playoffs in both of his first two seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read and watched the whole series, speaking for others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoilers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need someone on the bench waving a towel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you've never seen Jon Snow's turnaround J </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raptors are the North, DeRozan = Jon Snow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> giant obstruction after tennis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> figure skating. he's too thick to look small and dainty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not 12, not 13, not 14... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this u/BigEarl139 guy has to be all of 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you dense? You really think LeBron beats the 1986 or 1987 Celtics in a best of five series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not addressing my point. After overcoming the Celtics and Pistons (two teams who repeated as champions and are regarded as some of the greatest teams ever), Michael never lost again in the playoffs in a full season. 

LeBron never lost in the first round because he got to play cupcakes like the Wizards from 2006-2008, the 39-win Pistons in 2009, and the 41-win Bulls before leaving for Miami. 

I'm not sure if you are understanding that LeBron had far weaker first round opponents during his first stint with Cleveland.

EDIT: Also worth noting that, no, LeBron never played a 67 win team. In 2006 they won 64 games. And apparently KG was in his prime from 2008-2012 lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farther as in still lost the series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To All-Time great teams! LeBron never played anyone as good as the 1986-87 Celtics in the playoffs until his fourth trip to the Finals in 2013 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying he wouldn't, but he wouldn't have beat the Celtics in 1986/1987 or the Pistons 1988/1989/1990 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the point. Dude said MJ didn't start winning chips until the Pistons and Celtics were gone. Same thing with LeBron, couldn't win from 2008-2010 until Celtics and Lakers were gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he got to play scrubs like the Wizards and Bulls in the first round every year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jordan has never lost in the Finals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the same thing didn't happen with LeBron and the Celtics/Lakers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take the actual GOAT (MJ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which show are you going to? I'm going to Hollywood April 15th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vol. 1 is my favorite album of all-time. So stoked for the Neverender in less than a month!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someday, my friend. Someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like any genre it's evolved/branched off over the decades. Every existing subgenre has similarities and differences to original punk rock (which, obviously also diverges from original rock and roll)...pop punk, hardcore punk, post punk, emo punk, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote about Black Flag, The Clash, Sex Pistols, Ramones, etc. Insomniac is certainly their hardest, rawest, purest iteration of punk rock (Geek Stink Breath, Brain Stew, etc.) but it still has sing-along, poppy songs like Stuck With Me and 86. The main distinction between them and older punk rock outfits is commercial success, but it also has to do with their target audience. 22 years later they're still trying to attract the same demographic "misfit" teens. No disrespect, if you have a working formula then by all means, but I've certainly outgrown that demographic by now which is why I prefer their early stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk why you were downvoted. Manu was the FMVP in 2005 through the first few games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote my senior thesis on punk rock...GD has always been pop punk. I don't disagree with writing new stuff, but their recent albums just don't do the job for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X-Kid is my favorite song of the three albums so I'd definitely include that. Still Breathing just sounds like recycled pop, kinda reminds me of Lifehouse to be honest. Does not remind me at all of GD or their earlier stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John's supposed to jump in the air and celebrate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The break started with Uno, Dos, Tre...I felt like it was way over-hyped and there was maybe one album's worth of good material between the three. RR is all the same. There's no punk edge to it. We already went through the whole rebel/revolt/revolution themes with AI and 21CB. I'll always love them because they got me into music, but I can't support their product anymore when it is just supbar/bad to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coheed   Cambria - Good Apollo, Vol. 1: From Fear Through the Eyes of Madness

...actually pretty much all C C  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you said goodbye to me tonight... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't listen to GD anymore because of RR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lacrosse? I think he'd be a beast at lacrosse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phil is synonymous with the triangle because he won 11 championships while running it, even though Tex Winter is the architect. Honestly, the Knicks don't need to run it, but given that Melo is a strong iso player, you would expect him to be able to work out of the post like Kobe/MJ/Shaq. The problem is he isn't as willing a passer, and Rose can't shoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then Newman fixed a divot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MJ winning the championship in 1996 on Father's Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> purple for royalty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FULL COURT PRESS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I'll take Mavs by 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean people can say LBJ, MJ, KAJ, but they'd be wrong. Not necessarily a hot take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP you skipped Warriors vs Mavs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Count of Monte Cristo - first read </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> vet minimums. works for the cavs /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll add D-Lo for ONE SPECIFIC PLAY in 1984. Sub him in for Worthy for the last seconds of game 2 and he doesn't throw that ball away to Henderson because he can shoot FT's. We go up 2-0 and probably win the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll dispense with the "f you's" if you can dispense with the condescending tone. You're not Jerry West, and there's no gold star next to your name that says you know any more about basketball than anyone else here. I actually like the direction we're going with this so here's my rebuttal.

I am familiar with the idea of Positionless Basketball, having played in a HS system that was set up that way and written at length about its place in the future of basketball. The first problem, however, is that to be truly "positionless" we'd have to dispense with the idea of G-F-C. This may be the case in 20-30 years when everyone has the same skill-set and is between 6'6" and 6'8", but for the time being it makes no sense when Rondo and Klay have decidedly different skill-sets. We're just not there yet.

Second, this has more to do with the sentimental side of the game, but if you've played you know that the PG is considered the QB of the offense. No, this does not mean you make every assist or drive every time you have the ball. It means you're the vocal/motivational leader.  If the coach needs something done, he goes to his point guard, regardless of whether he is 5'9" or 6'9". It's a title, an honorary position.

Third, I'm a basketball historian, and even if the game moves in a certain direction in the future, we still need a frame of reference to compare players. I'm not going to lump Iverson in with Bob Cousy just because they were the same height or both guards, we need to be more specific and that's why AI was a SG and Cousy was one of the first true PG's. Hence my reference to 1954, because skilled players were so rare back then that it would be moot to call anyone a PG vs. SG.

If we're going to dispense with PG/SG distinctions, then we better do the same for SF and PF. But clearly T-Mac and Duncan did not play the same position. There have been hundreds of multi-skilled players over the course of the league's 70 years, but they still need to be categorized for history's sake. Far be it from us -- mostly fans -- to determine when and where we stop using specific terminology. 

EDIT: One last thing, if playing off the ball is one of two unique skill-sets required of guards, then literally all four players without the ball are non-guards for the split second they don't have the ball. Sounds awful pointless, which is why you're clearly oversimplifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next time I'll say go fuck yourself and call my beloved Point Guard that which I please. Kobe and MJ had all the skills of a PG too but historical accuracy calls for us to recognize them as SG's. This isn't 1954. All guards aren't within three inches of each other. 

The role of a PG is to facilitate the offense. The role of a SG is to shoot the basketball. No one ever said players can't fulfill both roles, but for the sake of consistency, we call someone like Russell a PG because Nick Young can't facilitate the offense. Russell is also a better shooter than Clarkson, ergo we call him the SG when the two are on the floor together. 

His ability to drop 40 points isn't mitigated by what position he is listed at in the box score, so it shouldn't matter to you what I or other fans call him. He is my Point Guard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then Stacy's mom drives up in a white convertible and a sundress... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, where's your Pistons flair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a nightmare to try to read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually say "That's my Point Guard," but he played SG yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there was always at least 5 wings better than him in the East during his prime: LeBron, Wade, Pierce, Carter, Allen, T-Mac, Joe Johnson, AI, etc.

EDIT: I'm gonna swap PG for AI, PG didn't come along until after his prime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk...you should probably get that validated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a bunch of them are covered up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got ours wrong, should be Nwaba/Zubac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has to be a Terminator/NBA reference for this that I'm blanking on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one said it was far superior, it's just that KD was competing with LeBron that year and the MVP race was neck and neck. With his team winning 73 games last year there was no real competition for the MVP for Steph.

What's more, statistics alone never tell you the whole story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP did you even watch Steph play last year or are you just throwing out numbers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "17 seconds...17 seconds from game 7 or from championship number 6." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dddjdd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol thanks, I'll work on my "tv-watching" skills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeBronnie and the Cavs, by Elton John </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. Ironically I was downvoted in another thread for pointing out how far they'll go to ignore that he has flaws. I can understand admiring him but by god they actually think he is the human embodiment of perfection, and that's just so sad to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying he wasn't a good fit on the team, I'm saying the guy (who I love as a coach) was so marginally average as a player that I honestly have no idea when you think his "prime" occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bench:

Chris Farley

Chris Crawford

Chris Anderson

Chris Gatling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs a center, Olowokandi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardly trying...you think this guy goes into a professional basketballl game thinking "yeah lets half-ass this one""? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he kinda is putting in crazy minutes already... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did I, at first. After 20 an hour though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did him on the right side in 2015, now it's time for the left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this ever in question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point I'll take anything that interrupts that god awful "I Don't Wanna Miss A Thing" parody commercial  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why Jamaal matters, but Mike was never even All-NBA or an All-Star, bro. It's the Hall of Fame, not the Hall of Pretty Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make him a Hall of Famer, just a very good player for a short period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Bibby? Lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you lost me at prime Luke Walton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Aristotle, not the Big Copernicus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnson had a very long career mostly coming off the bench, so this doesn't really surprise me. He only started regularly for four years -- three with the Kings and one with the Suns -- and none of those teams were flashy enough to warrant an All-Star selection. 1989 6MOY  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And LeBron stans will bend over backwards to ignore that he is mortal and has flaws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Archie Manning did a shit job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idgaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's go Zephyrs!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
