<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1258</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 21:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're right! A dietician would be helpful! I'll definitely bring it up when I take him to his physical in August! Thanks! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 20:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depo provera is a shit she can take every three months. It's a great form of birth control and very easy! Just remember, If you aren't using condoms, no other method will prevent STDs. It's important to get checked if you haven't already!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesss my life! Why can't my curls just all be one same pattern each day!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 15:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU. This page helped A LOT. I never thought about seeds!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 15:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's an  idea!! Mixing with meat!! Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some high fiber easy meals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 00:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello r/cooking!!

My little brother has aspergers. His social and common sense cues are really not on target. Anyway, he's been having a lot of trouble getting fiber into his meals.  My  parents aren't really around too much and he can't make anything complicated but is VERY picky. So, people who love to cook, what are some easy high fiber foods or snacks that don't include??

    fruit and most veggies. 

All i can think of hear is pita chips and hummus. Popcorn too. But the kid really needs meals too. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calculating Lattice energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 00:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you can use the born-haber cycle, but I am just really struggling. Could someone go with me step by step, if possible?

Mg (s) + 1/2 O2 = MgO (s) + light

The energy change that accompanies this reaction is -602 Kj/mol MgO. Calculate the lattice energy of MgO from the following energy changes. 

Given:
Mg (s) -- Mg (g) = enthalpy change of 150

O2 (g) -- O2 (g) = enthalpy change of 499

Mg(g) -- Mg2+ (g) + 2e- = enthalpy change of 2188

O(g) + 2e- -- O2- (g)

I just don't even know what to do here...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> first two days of class are infuriatingly warm and I wear long sleeves and jeans. Third day of class I wear shorts and a tank top and it's the North Pole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 21:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is methanol less viscous and lower tension than water? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 00:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 07:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can make a sound in my ear that sounds like static or a click. What the eff is this!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 07:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's when I tweeze my eye brows. *pluck, sneeze,pluck, pluck, pluck, sneeze. Pluck, sneeze, sneeze.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 01:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg me too. Just reading your comment got my eyes all watery. I cried SO hard.

That and the ending of rooftop prince. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 18:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,
This is the problem I have with lexapro as well. I've been taking it for...a year now and it has also done wonders for me in terms of anxiety and depression. I'm a pretty small person. Before lexapro I was a very small eater.  I weighed around...82 pounds (i'm 5'2" btw). But once i started taking lexapro and the pill combined, I suddenly got a huge appetite and I didn't know what to do. And i HATE being hungry.

My solution:
All foods don't have to be bad. I started eating smaller meals more frequently instead of 3 big meals through out the day, so I would stay full. If i wanted a snack between  my 4-5 meals a day I made SURE (on most days) that it is healthy and low calorie. Some of my favorite options:
1. pita chips   hummus
2. Frozen Blueberries (great in summer)
3. A hot pocket
4. salted edamame beans
5. half an avacado with sea salt and olive oil.

changing my diet stopped me from packing on pounds and having an increase of fatty foods. 

If you ever want to talk about other symptoms or have questions about lexapro, feel free to message me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take magnesium supplements as well...but i take it for hand tremors! Maybe it was helping with my palpitations too!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 18:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how  much does this usually cost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My jealousy knows no bounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sensitive tooth not a result of filling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 01:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, excuse me for using pleb language here b/c i have no idea what certain teeth are called: my second farthermost left upper molar is extremely sensitive to cold. I've had no fillings and my dentist has triple checked for cavities there- there aren't any. Why is it so sensitive?! What can I do? Is there a special toothpaste I can use that won't hurt my other teeth?

Thanks guys :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 21:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not even brocode. it's fucking decent human obligation. DEF tell him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 20:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this made me awww so hard :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my Indian parents named me Hetal. (pronounced hey-thul.) Americans pronounce it hate-all or he-tall For some god knows why reason they can't  pronounce the "th" sound. anyway, it's all very sad because  my name actually means loving. Not Hate :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 20:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 21, I went to my doctor. We talked about getting my first papsmear and she said "I know you haven't had sex." I promptly open my mouth to tell her I have. But then she continues " I know you haven't had sex, because you're a good girl and wouldn't do that. You know better. So we can just do the papsmear next year since you aren't sexually active."  I promptly shut my mouth.
Damn you for making me feel terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 02:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was once a participant in a hypnotizing show. It was in a trance, but i wasn't hypnotized. Iknow that for sure. Like I'd have to think of my answers and knew what i was doing, but i couldn't get up and leave and say HEY I'M NOT HYPNOTIZED. When i finally went back to my seat, it all seemed like a distant memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 04:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now i'm curious. What was the ethnicity of the baby and parents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 02:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 02:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a great idea. Thank goodness I moved out 4 years ago. But i am DEFINITELY doing this every time i come home. What an easy solution! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 21:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, she really gave me a lot more freedom than most parents would give there girls when I was young. I  never had a curfew growing up. Was allowed to have co-ed sleepovers in high school. My mom trusted me in any situation...it's just THIS that's driving me crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: There is no Such Thing as a Slut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 20:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 20:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's right on the mark. My mother is Indian and was always raised on the the perception that you are useless without your virginity. "he took it away from me." That's not true. We talked about it- no peer pressure at all- and I actively made the decision that this was something I wanted for myself. Also, I'm 22 and not getting any younger :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I be in charge of my body? [rant] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 18:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently had a talk with my mother, again. After deciding to have my first boyfriend, EVERY single time I go home, it's always: "Have you had sex yet?" I got fed up and told her it wasn't her business what I chose to do. Just that she should know that whatever I chose to do, she should trust me enough to know that I'll always take precautions and be safe. 
She responded with "That's bullshit. You're my daughter. I have a right to know whatever you are doing and goes on with your body. It came from me and if you are having sex, I need to know every detail of when you become unpure."
That really hurt. I thought my body was my own. 

Then, when my boyfriend and i got into a fight, all my mom cared about was whether I had sex. "I just need to know that your body is still pure." As long as it is pure, your father and I will be ok." What about me? What about my heartbreak? What about how I feel about my virginity? WHY DO YOU THINK YOU OWN MY BODY. WHY DO YOU THINK MY SEXUAL BUSINESS IS SOMETHING YOU HAVE RIGHTS TO? It's hurtful.
 [End Rant] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 07:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, I tried epilating my plane strip once. Like 3 hairs in it was bleed city :'(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 03:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this topic is so overly complicated when it doesn't need to be. What's wrong with Virgin men? NOTHING. What's wrong with not Virgin women? Also nothing. It should be that easy, but instead it's virgin men aren't real men. Virgin women, are prude. Non Virgin women are unpure. WHY IS THERE NO WINNING? Something that is a personal choice, no matter what your age, has become such a shameful and humiliating thing to so many in our societies. It's just sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 06:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think it really depends on how traditional of a family your parents came from.
For example: my father came from a pretty strict and traditional family. He can get seriously angry and violent. No funny business around him when I grew up. My dad always thought i should bow down and listen to my elders.

My mother on the other hand, came from a non traditional family who raised her with a lot of patience and love. All the funny business around her. My mom always  told me to respect my elders, but to stand up for myself and respect myself no matter what.

The two came together and my dad was always pretty angry and strict with us. Adhered to tough love. My  mother raised us with a  lot of unconditional love and forgiveness. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 06:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm tipsy and i cried over this. No shame. Humans don't deserve to be treated like this. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 05:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please tell me someone remembers Bean from the show Even Stevens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 03:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By George, I think you've got it!! No wonder zoo animals hate me so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 22:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> firstly can I just say you are a beast? WAY TO GO STRONG!!
Second, you  need a hug. Even if it is from an internet stranger. *hug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 22:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  monkeys have stolen my ice cream twice...in two separate zoos. In two separate countries. 
WHAT DID I EVER DO TO THEM TO DESERVE THAT!?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 21:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh my goodness, thank you SO much. I was missing the part that ln(e) = 1 and thatw tas just messing me up. I understand how it all comes down now! Thank you!!
As for the second one, hat one makes a lot more sense too. 
Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [College Level] Pre Calc - Solving equations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for the life of me cannot figure out how to solve these 2 equations:

How on earth do i solve when there is an exponent such as 3x-2? How do i bring it down? Would someone take me step by step?
Solve for x. Find the exact solution to the equation below. (Do not give a decimal approximation

54e^(2x+3)=28.

#2: exact same instructions...how am i opening it out to solve for x? How am i getting x alone here?
log(2x)log(3+x)=2.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 06:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Books by Eva Ibbotson are great!

1. Which Witch
2. Island of the Aunts (my personal fave)
3. Journey to the River Sea

Almost Anything by Bruce Coville, but I highly recommend:

1. Jeremy Thatcher Dragon Hatcher
2. My Teacher is an Alien
3. Into the Land of the Unicorns (if you want a slightly girly book)


I also argue that the first 3 Harry Potter books are good for all ages.

1.Junie B Jones series
2.Captain Underpants series
3.The Boxcar kids series
4.Magic Tree House series
5.Chronicles of Narnia series
6. Encyclopedia Brown series

Stand alone books:

1.Where the wild things are
2.Frindle
3.The Doll People
4.Howliday Inn

I really like reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My curly hair actually got complimented. Felt the need to post it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 04:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 07:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> explaining some of what Aarena52 said:

Bailaban b/c dancing is a continuous activity. It's not something *BAM* and done.

**Llevaban - b/c they didn't just put the clothes on and off right. Wearing the clothes was a continuous activity!!

Tomaron - taking a photo is a *BAM* action - it happens in like 5 seconds and it's done. 

Celebraban - celebrating is a continuous activity. 

** The key here when is remembering that that preterite is a *BAM* action. It happens very quickly: Ie, emotions, taking a photo, jumping, etc.

Imperfect are for continuous activities: celebrating a holiday, when you were a child, loving your parents, taking ballet lessons, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 07:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this deserves a standing ovation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 22:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be honest, If i were him, I would be really upset is that was the explanation you gave me. To me, it still sounds like you are friends. Would it have been better to be more clear and said I like you, as in more than a friend, and that's not fair to your girlfriend. I don't want to break you guys up, but I need to do whats best for myself and get over you. That involves me deleting you from my life..

or something like that. Make it clear. If i was in his spot, it would seem like you're deleting him out of nowhere. That would hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 04:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is really rude. You don't ditch family when they are hurting and need someone to lean on. Especially if they've been good to you which it seems that OP's mom has been. 
Regardless of what OP decides to do (move out or not) You don't have a right to blame things on OP's mom for marrying someone she loved. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [pre-calc] Finding the range of a function </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 23:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> arsI haven't done math in 5 years. With that knowledge, can someone please Explain to me how you get the range of a function in this question? I'm really struggling here to grasp this concept.

1. f(x)=1x2on3x3

What is the range of f(x) on this interval

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't wear summer clothes in summer because my classroom is and icebox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 21:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'M SO COLD. hold me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
