<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3080</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thanks dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rory you gorgeous bastard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take some pics dude! I've wanted to get a smoker for ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rory is more consistent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monster drive DJ. Holy shit I love that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sergio is rattled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiger looking like a boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lads they need to make this tournament a four day event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gremlins mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in North Carolina so it's pretty cheap. Was like 8 bucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went and hit 100 balls at the range during the break. Decided to pick up 24 beers on the way home. Canceled my 7am tee time in favour of watching the rest of the Ryder Cup. It's too good this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually really like what both sides are wearing so far. Yesterday's clothes were class, as are today's clothes. I like the traditional look Europe went for and the more modern clothes the USA have a great too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just glad I didn't go this year. It's fucking appalling. You know things are bad when the American players keep having to tell the crowd to shut up and people have been marched out of there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the renowned "I BELIEVE THAT WE WILL WIN!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't be much of a megathread then would it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of folks on here seem ok with it too which is ridiculous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Missed it." Fuck you you cunt. Well in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should keep Fitzpatrick around. What a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total lack of class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. L1-B visa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they actually get kicked out? I missed that. Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people trying to play it down on here are a bit of an enigma. We all know it's only a few lads responsible on course. We aren't blaming the whole crowd. It is bad and there's fuck all wrong with highlighting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I BELIEVE THAT WE WILL WIN. I BELIEVE THAT WE WILL WIN" IS THE LAMEST FUCKING CHANT I'VE EVER HEARD. UP YOUR GAME, 'MURICANTS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of American fans at the Ryder Cup are shouting "I BELIEVE THAT WE WILL WIN. I BELIEVE THAT WE WILL WIN." ad nauseum. Probably the worst sports chant in the history of sports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 16:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fatrick Reed

For fucks sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 15:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got back from the course. How have folks been playing? Looks like McIlroy and Pieters are doing well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a job with a US company in Ireland and had them move me over. A lot easier that way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 04:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 04:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the races I was heading back into town and was getting a helicopter ride cause traffic was chronic. He was waiting for one for a while but I had prebooked one so they let me in and he had to continue waiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this par for the course, so to speak, in American golf?

There's just a few people responsible, but yes it is. We all wish it would stop, and that the people would be thrown out but it won't ever happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three putt for bogey? :D

Nicely done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that you Gerry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My swing coach does lessons all year round. If it's snowing he has an indoor area with simulation equipment. Not sure what their deal is man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Ryder Cup Saturday Pairings have been posted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should pick up the Come West Along the Road DVDs from RTE's online shop. Great trad music from the 50s/60s/70s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lad, it went to crap after Gay left it.  

I don't like Tubridy after an incident I had with him at the Galway races when I was given a helicopter before he was, and he lost the plot. So sometimes I feel a bit biased saying he's a shite presenter because I don't like him personally, but he really is a shite presenter which makes it all the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really will be fine. You might experience some racism, but you'll make such good friends with regular lads/ladies that it won't phase you and those mates will stick up for you as well. As with other places, it's usually the uneducated/poor/elderly which tend to be a bit on the racist side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 01:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is! I miss the Irish darkness, and the sky at night. I can see probably four stars at night because there's so much light pollution where I am in the states. When I'm home all I do is look up at the stars (when the clouds disappear, not often I know) and all my mates and family think I've turned into a lunatic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 01:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing. I won't get into a sports argument. There's other events that rival it for me - the rugby world cup, the All Ireland Hurling final... but that's subjective stuff on my part. 

It's one of my favourite times of year. Unfortunately I'm on call this weekend, 9am to 9pm but I'll be up at 6am to get some golf in and then settle into the Ryder Cup when I get home. It's such an exciting time. I wish it was four days instead of three! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 01:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went golfing on my lunch break today. It was not supposed to rain. I got soaked like a drowned rat. I only got to play three holes but it was still worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors that are dressing up for Halloween - what are you going as? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor Pepe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite dessert? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor Pepe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a piece of technology we don't have yet that you are excited about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How hard would it be to build a 'smart' golf ball? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about a ball that would record stats from every shot. Things like:

1. Air Pressure.  
2. Spin Rate.  
3. Velocity Info (speed, height, path, etc)  

It would also allow a person to find the ball if it went into the rough and so on. The device in side it would have to be charged wirelessly too.

I've found some patents on this so I'm not even sure if someone is allowed to make this sort of device now. Here's one of several patents: https://www.google.com/patents/US20150094168  

I'm a software developer, but I'm useless when it comes to hardware and I've no idea about the current state of GPS and RFID technology. I am a golfer so I have an interest in this. It would obviously be very important to have a good ball, so leaving a pocket inside the ball must not impact performance.  

It's also very important to note that ball manufacturers are not really interested in this because if people stop losing balls then their profits disappear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like someone is finally coming out with a smart golf ball. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pots and Pans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an Irish man living in the states on Ryder Cup week, this is how I might have to watch the closing stages on Sunday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The person who prays for God to change things thinks God has arranged matters wrong, and also thinks they can instruct God on how they should be put right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 04:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Davis Love III selects Ryan Moore as final Ryder Cup pick - Golfweek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 04:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1950s Arnold Palmer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RIP Arnold Palmer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you ordered anything from the TaylorMade custom shop before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their irons are D2 by default, wondering if they can make mine D4  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rory McIlroy wins the TOUR Championship in a playoff and is the 2015-2016 Fed-Ex Champion! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rory just knocked a 7 iron almost 230 yards in the TOUR Championship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DJ is free falling. Can Rory do it lads? He doesn't seem to be dialled in either. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have a stream for the final round of the TOUR championship? Non PGATourLive stream would be great. Sick of the featured hole coverage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tale of two halves. Took me a while to get into it today but my swing felt amazing on the back 9. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chapel Ridge today. Great weather. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hoping to get a few rounds in this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 20:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switched from SLDR to M2 today and played from the blue. New personal best. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 17:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This is America where hard work is rewarded. Stop thinking that you deserve special treatment. Move to Spain if you don't want to work hard." -- in a thread about the lack of labor laws (companies can make people work n number of hours with no break) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 05:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL North Carolina does not require mandatory rest breaks or meal breaks for employees 16 years of age or older. Companies can force employees to work 8 hour days with no breaks and it's not against the law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 20:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given the 14 club restriction, what clubs do you carry in your bag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I alternate between Driver, 3W, 5W, 7W, 4-PW, AW, SW, LW, Putter.

Obviously I can't carry all of them as it's 15 clubs, so sometimes I'll leave the 5W or 7W at home.

I don't bother with hybrids, I could never get used to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My office today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS want Trump to win... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother nature doing her best to ruin my round. Currently -1. I called the front desk and told the course I'm hanging out here until it passes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I played Lonnie Poole today. The course kicked my ass. I loved the GPS carts, and how they turn off of you drive them into an area they aren't supposed to be. The interactive maps were amazing too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good ways of avoiding small talk (with taxi drivers, hair dressers, etc)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feline hazard on the practice green. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor Caught With Cocaine in His Car (x-post from /r/PastorArrested) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor Caught With Cocaine in His Car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phoenix pastor arrested for impregnating 13-year-old, marrying 10-year-old (x-post from /r/PastorArrested) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phoenix pastor arrested for impregnating 13-year-old, marrying 10-year-old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stocked up on some golf balls. Got 240 AAAAA titleist velocity balls delivered today. Should last a month right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens was ruthless, and I love it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading through old essays and reviews from Hitchens in the Times Literary Supplement from the 1990s.

In 1998 he reviewed a book by Arthur Marwick - "The Sixties".  He really laid into Marwick, and as expected he didn't hold back. From the essay:

Paul Johnson, even at the time, would have had a legitimate quarrel with Marwicks account of a subculture which included the older left-wing journals (such as New Statesman, Tribune, and Left Review), the underground papers, experimental theatre, and the new radical Marxist journal founded by Tariq Ali, appearing on 15 May 1968, Black Dwarf. There are also several minor but suggestive factual errors in that extract, which Perry Anderson and Tariq Ali would spot like hawks. I mention this because, in considering a period where so many of the protagonists are still (to say the least) alive, it is derelict of Marwick to have made so little effort to find and question them. As against that, I grew weary of the American letters he repeatedly cited from some personal friends named Van Dyke, as if these were some trove from a lost antiquity.

In the end, this is in the truest sense an eccentric book: made up of the musings and fossickings of a graduate of the university of life. He is free to follow his nose, to pursue his interests, and to vent his (call me old-fashioned if you will) prejudices. It doesnt much matter if he doesnt know his Bukharin from his Bakunin, unless you care that the 1960s were the last decade of hot ideological disputation. (Cultural Revolution, in those days, was a fighting term and not one to be lightly deployed.)

Anyway, here is Marwick's response:


Sir,  Christopher Hitchenss unremitting rant (November 13) against my book, The Sixties: Cultural revolution in Britain, France, Italy and the United States, c.1958-c.1974, was so manifestly insane that a response is scarcely necessary. However, since he has blatantly abused the trust of your readers, I must record a few corrections.  
Flaunting his unfailing gift for tediously unoriginal quotation, Hitchens declares my book a pudding with no theme. It has several. The main one, evidently the root of the Hitchens hysteria, concerns what I term the Great Marxisant Fallacy which befuddled the protesters of the time as it has befuddled commentators since. There was never any possibility of revolution, though; as society was permeated (another central theme) by new ideas, the lives of ordinary people were transformed (my cultural revolution, another central theme). I identify sixteen characteristics of a unique era upon whose complex interrelationships the book is meticulously structured. Hitchens encloses certain words and phrases, for example strides  as in the pathetic cliche strides forward  and call me old fashioned if you like, implying that they are quotations from my book. In fact, they are as spurious as everything else in this review.  
The Sixties is based on ten years research in the archives of four countries.  
But, since Hitchens thinks he knows it all already, he wraps himself in the age-old reaction of the ideologue: Dont confuse me with the evidence. In a meretricious list of alleged errors, he accuses me of mistaking Bukharin for Bakunin. Actually, neither are mentioned by me; it would indeed be an eccentric book on the 1960s if I did.  
Lets face it: Christopher Hitchens is upset that I spurn the idols of his youth and challenge the familiar, comfy lefty myths. Regrettably, he does not have the integrity to say so straight-forwardly. Declaring that things we dont like dont exist is the ploy of a Stalinist moron; and if you cant ban a book, swamp it in mindless abuse.

And here is Hitchens response:

Sir,  In my review of The Sixties by Arthur Marwick (November 13), I believe I drew attention to Marwicks difficulty in making distinctions. To this point he adds emphasis by his letter (December 18). There is, first, the distinction between a wounded letter and a wounding one. To abuse me as manifestly insane and a Stalinist moron is to display ugly wounds on his side without inflicting any on mine. There is, next, the distinction between an instance and a metaphor. I did say that Marwick didnt know his Bakunin from his Bukharin. I didnt allege, as he expostulates, that he cited either name. But his indignance on this point is misdirected. The terms arse and elbow are likewise absent from his text. I merely meant to say that he would probably have let that distinction elude him also


As I said, ruthless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roald Dahl Failed On free Speech And Threw Salman Rushdie To The Mob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: The Royal Air Force claims the dubious credit for the first recorded use of aerial bombardment on civilians, when it bombed Kurdish villages in the 1920s. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 07:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strongbow is being advertised as a posh and expensive drink in the states. People here find it hard to believe that it's loved by homeless lads in the UK and Ireland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Times Literary Supplement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks,

I bought a yearly subscription to the Times Literary Supplement today. It's $185 which includes everything; hard copy to my house along with digital access to the archive going back to the early 90s. If you *just* want the digital access it's considerably cheaper: $115.  

Anyways - there's a lot of Hitchens content on there. He published lots of book reviews, polemics, etc. There's also some forward-and-back between him and people who responded to his essays.  

A lot of the content there is not in his published books: Arguably, And Yet, etc.  

I figured I'd let you lads know just in case you wanted more Hitchens content and didn't know where to look.  

Additional to the Hitchens content is everything else obviously. I think it's a steal for this price. If anyone has a subscription feel free to talk about his essays here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Featured hole coverage sucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a gripe against PGATour Live coverage. They only seem to do featured group coverage on the first couple of days and then move to featured hole coverage. It sucks. I want to see extended coverage of the field, which is how golf is covered in Europe. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor arrested for rubbing olive oil on church member's vagina, clitoris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reports: Hillary Clinton Leaves 9/11 Ceremony Early Due to Possible Medical Episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: The Lessons of 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: The Lessons of 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What books do you find yourself re-reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading a few books at the moment, but getting bored by them so I decided to pick up Lucky Jim by Kingsley Amis. I've read this book three times now since first reading it less than a year ago. I just can't get enough of it. It's just *so* funny.  

I am always reading Lord of the Rings as well. I'll pick it up, go through 300 pages, and not touch it again for a few months and continue on the story.  

I'm also always reading something by John Moriarty - currently working my way through his last book: Nostos continued.  

For me, Lucky Jim is one of my favourite books. I can't believe it took me 32 years to find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish boxer Paddy Barnes is one of us. Taken from a charity golf outing The Oscar Knox Cup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 00:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife is having surgery tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people offering prayers, which is fine as she's religious. 

I'm personally hoping her surgeon sleeps well tonight and is not distracted tomorrow. The surgeon studied at Duke, did their fellowship at the Mayo clinic, and has returned to Duke so I know she is in good hands.  

**EDIT** surgery was a success. Thanks lads   ladies. The treatment she received at Duke this morning was great. They kept me updated all along the way too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Thomas Jefferson's report after meeting with a Tripoli official in 1786 - before US foreign policy even existed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since reading Hitchens' works, and his influences, have any of you tried your hand a writing? Do any of you feel that urge to write, which he talked about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that typo is unfortunate. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Hitchens ever review or comment on Bukowski's writing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bukowski update - thank you so much /r/books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I ended up reading all of Bukowski's novels over the last couple of weeks, along with a few of his short story collections and his letters.   

I agree with what a lot of you said. Pulp was probably his best work. Post Office was his funniest. It was great writing. I just started Journey to the End of the Night by Celine. I'm really looking forward to this and all other works you lads recommended. Is there anything else I should be reading that's similar to Bukowski's work? Any other influences?  

Thanks again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can this be comfortable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 02:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 September Book Discussion: Arguably: Essays by Christopher Hitchens Part 2 - Eclectic Affinities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 03:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the delay folks. I"m currently on vacation, and have been since August 19th.  
Part Two of Arguably starts on page 139 and runs up to page 380. This is probably my favourite part of the collection, as it focuses solely on literature. Several of the essays in this section are some of his best writing. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> redditors who blame US foreign policy for ISIS: how do you explain the Islamist attacks on Thailand, India, Africa etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Henry Beresford, 3rd Marquess of Waterford got drunk with his cronies, wrecked a small town in Ireland, painted it red (literally), beat up a few cops and painted them red too. Thus the term painting the town red was created. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 06:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Henry Beresford, 3rd Marquess of Waterford got drunk with his cronies, wrecked a small town in Ireland, painted it red (literally), beat up a few cops and painted them red too. Thus the term painting the town red was created. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawson College faculty member Alexander Simonelis fails to grasp basic logic and throws ad hominem attacks at people on Twitter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six holes. That's how long it took Tiger to record his first eagle as a pro. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any golfers out there? Fancy having a meetup or playing a round some time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I post on /r/golf regularly but we're based all over. I don't see that many NC golfers so figured I'd post here as I live in Apex.  

Do any of you /r/triangle folks play golf? If so, do you fancy some sort of meetup (if there are a lot of us), or maybe just getting together and playing a round with me? I'm a member at The Preserve Golf Club at Jordan Lake, but I'm willing to play any course in the area really. We're spoiled for choice here and it looks like the weather is just about to cool down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else suffering from inconsistent form? Some days I just can't swing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote a little about this a few days ago, but it is something that is plaguing me and I'd like to open up the discussion. 

I've been suffering with playing consistently. There's some days I show up and I just can't swing properly. Here's a list of my scores since May 30th:  

Date|Score|CR/Slope|Diff|Course  
:--|:--|:--|:--|:--|  
8/31/16|74|72.1/138|1.6|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
8/30/16|87|70.0/128|15.0|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
8/29/16|72|70.0/128|1.8|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
8/24/16|75|73.2/141|1.4|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC / P  
8/20/16|76|70.0/128|5.3|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/24/16|89|70.0/128|16.8|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/23/16|77|72.1/138|4.0|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/18/16|71|70.0/128|0.9|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/17/16|74|70.0/128|3.5|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/16/16|75|70.0/128|4.4|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/3/16|77|70.0/128|6.2|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
7/2/16|82|71.6/135|8.7|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC / P  
6/25/16|77|70.0/128|6.2|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC
6/24/16|78|70.0/126|7.2|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC / P  
6/18/16|78|70.0/128|7.1|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
6/15/16|82|70.0/126|10.8|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC / P  
6/11/16|79|70.0/128|7.9|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  
6/4/16|82|70.2/128|10.4|Grande Dunes Resort Club  
6/3/16|89|70.8/131|15.7|TPC of Myrtle Beach  
5/30/16|96|70.0/128|23.0|Preserve at Jordan Lake GC  

As you can see the scores are trending in the right direction, but every so often I show up and just can't swing a club. I have no explanation for it. On the 29th I played from the whites and went around level par. My swing felt so smooth, the best it has ever been really. The next day I was absolutely brutal. The 87 could have easily been 117. I just couldn't swing properly. Today my swing felt amazing again and I played from the blue tees and was +2 at the end of the round.  

I just don't get it. The inconsistency is driving me crazy. I'm meeting with my swing coach on Friday to go over a few things and see if we can figure out what is going on. 

Up until now I've been writing it off as an off day, but it's something else. It seems to happen every so often. I have arthritis and I'm wondering if it has something to do with it. Maybe I'm not doing enough stretching.  

Anyone else suffering from inconsistent form? Were you able to figure out what's causing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curtis Strange's "You'll Learn" moment. This interview looks much different 20 years later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favourite time of the day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're fighting with your GF and she says she's pregnant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're fighting with your GF and she says she's pregnant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of reddit, what stereotype about Americans is actually true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 02:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allow a post title to be edited up to 30 seconds after a post. This will allow people to fix typos, which are almost always introduced by predictive text on phones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not back to work until September 6th. Looking for ideas on how to fill the days in North Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As described in the subject, I'm off work until September 6th. I've posted my scheduled tee times below which are all at my local course where I'm a member. Asides from playing early morning, is there anything else I should be doing to take advantage of being off? I plan on getting fit for my irons   woods on this coming Friday. I suppose I should schedule a few lessons as well. I was thinking of maybe heading to Pinehurst to stay there for one night and play No. 2 at some point. Are there any other clubs or courses I should be checking out?  

The Preserve
8/29/2016 7:40 AM  
The Preserve
8/30/2016 7:40 AM   
The Preserve
9/1/2016 7:30 AM  
The Preserve
9/2/2016 7:20 AM  
The Preserve
9/3/2016 7:00 AM  
The Preserve
9/4/2016 7:20 AM  
The Preserve
9/5/2016 7:20 AM   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Trump's fans Trumpets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 13:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warming up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you lads just head out to the first tee without warning up on the range beforehand?

The range was closed on my local course today for maintenance so I wasn't able to do my usual 40 minute warm up routine. 

It took me 14 holes to find my swing and start playing to my usual standard. I three putted, had horrible drives, left approach shots short. The works. All the way up to hole 14.

From hole 15 through 18 I was 1 under and my swing was so smooth and what I expect after I have gone through my warm up routine.  

Honestly though, I'm a bit pissed off it took so long to get going. I would have hoped, or thought it would only take a few holes to get going. Perhaps it was just an off day. 

Do you lads have a warm up routine? How bad are you if you can't do it before a round? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kavanagh's thoughts after last week's fight against Diaz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on the hijab and other religious garments which force women to cover themselves up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it's a human rights issue. Islam directly translated means submission. Submission to god and submission to ones husband. I think we have all seen the photos of Iranian society in the early to mid 1900s where women were not covered and resembled western society. 

Islam treats women as second class citizens, as does Christianity. The bible states that a woman cannot have a position of power over a man. Both religions subjugate women, and both are responsible for the appalling treatment of women for centuries. It's not too long ago since women in Ireland couldn't vote and weren't allowed in bars. When women were finally allowed in bars they were confined to a "snug"... Essentially a booth or tiny room... This is because of religion.

Forcing women to cover themselves up because the men get a bit rapey is a disastrous human rights problem. I think secular societies should ban the hijab, burka, et all. Islam needs reformation. It's not the only offender. Nuns, Orthodox Jews, and so on. 

What are your thoughts on this? How should a secular society handle this? When Iran banned the hijab in the 1930s lots of women killed themselves because their husbands wouldn't let them out of the house, so it's not as easy as just banning the garment. It's a complex issue but ultimately Islam needs reformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advanced reading copy of Hitch-22. Check out the Gore Vidal quote which was removed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planet Found in Habitable Zone Around Nearest Star - Pale Red Dot campaign reveals Earth-mass world in orbit around Proxima Centauri </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planet Found in Habitable Zone Around Nearest Star - Pale Red Dot campaign reveals Earth-mass world in orbit around Proxima Centauri </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planet Found in Habitable Zone Around Nearest Star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Played the tips at my local course today. My eagle attempt from 179 yards out clattered the flag and landed here. Ended up shooting 75. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who had a life changing experience, what's your story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My showerhead let's me know when it's too hot to get in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest addition to my bag - a mint condition 2014 Scotty Cameron Select Golo 5 for $157. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is the relationship with your family, given your atheism? Do they know? If so, what's the situation like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite first world comfort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we were made in "gods" image, how do Christians justify circumscission and genital mutilation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighting for your job on the PGA TOUR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 22:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was the first out today ahead of the club championship. I really should have played the tournament. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-youth pastor from Willis gets life for sexually abusing child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bukowski. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm late to the party. Bukowski was recommended to me a few years ago and I started reading **Ham on Rye** back then but stopped around a third of the way through because something came up. I'm not even sure what it was now that stopped me. I continued reading other books but I think I just needed history at the time and didn't want any more novels for a bit. You know how that goes I am sure.  

This week I read **The Post Office** in a day. A few hours actually, cover to cover without putting it down. I didn't even stop to piss. The style of writing is deceiving. He makes it look so easy, but it's not at all. Hilariously funny. I'm reading Ham on Rye again now and I'm half way through after a day. It's equally brilliant. I plan on finishing it this evening after work. Chinaski was a funny fucker as a child and his father is such a degenerate. **Women** is up next. 

I am going on a little vacation until September 6th and I just picked up the following as well:  
1. Pulp.  
2. Hollywood.  
3. Factotum.  
4. Notes of a Dirty Old Man.  
5. On Writing.  

The next few weeks are going to be wonderful I'm sure. There's been loads of threads on Bukowski here but I just had to get this out. Thanks for listening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is just the worst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 00:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have all of Christopher's books, even a signed copy of this particular one but this copy is exciting. An advance uncorrected proof not for sale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday Charles Bukowski. Born on this day in 1920. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob   Dave Kearney meet Paul  Gary ODonovan. Anyone have the full version of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the lads abroad - set up a free Amazon VPN to watch RTE, etc. I've been using this to watch the hurling for ages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the lads abroad - set up a free Amazon VPN to watch RTE, etc. I've been using this to watch the hurling for ages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Kurds of ISIS by Alexander Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shots fired. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 00:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 August Book Discussion: Arguably: Essays by Christopher Hitchens Part 1 - All American </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so ends our book club journey. I'm the first to admit and quite saddened to say the real life got in the way for some of this, which is evident by the late posting of this thread.

I want to run Arguably in sections because it's so large, so in August we will focus on the section titled **All American** which runs from the start of the book up to page 139.  

I think this breaks it up nicely.  

Happy reading folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'God doesn't exist but aliens probably do,' says minister. -- News story from Ireland making the minister seem crazy but what he says is pretty much in line with scientific thinking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a large scale slug attack a few weeks ago I thought my tomatoes were all ruined. I took some preventative measures and thankfully it worked. Today's harvest - half of one plant. So happy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 15:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suing is so prevalent in American culture that I'm surprised children don't sue their parents for being born. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 01:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do tomatoes from our gardens always taste better than from the store? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got this mail on LinkedIn a few moments ago. Recruiters are not even trying anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was on LinkedIn a few moments ago. Recruiters are not even trying anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I stopped reading digital books. Anyone else have a similar experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Editorial errors and typos are why I ditched digital books. I was sick of them. Some books were worse than others, obviously. I like reading the classics and they were the worst offenders, sometimes every couple of pages. I got tired of reporting issues. More often than not I never even received a response and the issues are still there. 

It's been so long since I used my kindle, it won't even turn on anymore.  

**EDIT** I don't pirate books so this is an issue with books pre-kindle, which have been either typed up or scanned badly.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryanair may ditch UK domestic routes as it focuses on growth in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I put some corn moonshine in a barrel at Christmas. Filtering it and bottling today. It looks and tastes outstanding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 03:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I put some corn moonshine in a barrel at Christmas. Filtering it and bottling today. It looks and tastes outstanding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 03:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany blast: Ansbach bar explosion 'leaves one dead' - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany blast: Ansbach bar explosion 'leaves one dead' - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do you play golf? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 05:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to go out every Saturday and Sunday at 6am. First one out on the course means I can be done around 9.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's currently 92F (33 celsius) and feels like 102F (38.8 celsius). I'd love to go golfing but I'm from Ireland and I will melt or end up with a migraine or worse. Are any of you able to handle golfing in this heat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

**EDIT**: you lads are fucking life savers! Thanks so much for the tips. I'm so glad I went golfing today because after the 75 and 74 I shot this Saturday and Sunday, I shot 71 today. First time breaking par and I owe it all to you lads!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Nicklaus tribute to Phil and Henrik after today's major. Very nicely put. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 03:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johnny Miller says Rory McIlroy cares too much about showing off his muscles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 01:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After yesterday's record 75 I decided to try my luck again. Shot a 74 today. I was even on the front 9. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Book Club Schedule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 05:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The following is the proposed schedule for the 2016 book club.

If you have any suggestions or comments please let me know.

I created /r/ChristopherHitchens_ for the book club, because the mod of /r/ChristopherHitchens is non responsive and will not sticky any threads for us. This leads to loss of discussion.


* **January**: And Yet...: Essays (2015)
* **February**: Imperial Spoils: The Curious Case of the Elgin Marbles. Chatto and Windus (UK)/Hill and Wang (US, 1988) / 1997 UK Verso edition as The Elgin Marbles: Should They Be Returned to Greece? (with essays by Robert Browning and Graham Binns). Reissued and updated 2008 as The Parthenon Marbles: The Case for Reunification, Verso. 
* **March** Prepared for the Worst: Selected Essays and Minority Reports. Hill and Wang (US)/Chatto and Windus (UK).
* **April**: Blood, Class, and Nostalgia: Anglo-American Ironies. Farrar, Straus   Giroux. Reissued 2004, with a new introduction, as Blood, Class and Empire: The Enduring Anglo-American Relationship, Nation Books, ISBN 1-56025-592-7
* **May**: For the Sake of Argument: Essays and Minority Reports. Verso, ISBN 0-86091-435-6
* **June**: Unacknowledged Legislation: Writers in the Public Sphere. Verso
* **July**: A Long Short War: The Postponed Liberation of Iraq. Plume Books. Originally released as Regime Change (Penguin).
* **August**: Arguably: Essays by Christopher Hitchens. Twelve. UK edition as Arguably: Selected Prose. Atlantic.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 July Book Discussion: A Long Short War: The Postponed Liberation of Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 05:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're nearing the end of this journey, with Arguably being the last book we'll be reading next month. Arguably is huge of course and probably should go on for longer than a month.  

This month we're focusing on a short pamphlet about Iraq, a great little volume that outlines why Hitchens was in favour of regime change in Iraq. 

It's easy to spot someone who is lazy and uninformed about Hitchens   the Iraq war, because they'll drop a one liner along the lines of the following "Well Hitchens was pro Iraq War and look how that turned out. He was wrong about Iraq".

Hitchens was not wrong about Iraq. All along the way he kept arguing that the US was not doing enough, they dropped the ball at every occasion and pulled out too soon. They did a terrible job.

Anyway, enjoy the short read folks. I haven't read it in a few years and I'm really looking forward to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After my worst round of the year on July 4th I didn't swing a club until today. Shot a new personal best this morning. Sometimes a break is all that is needed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How religion can drive someone to slaughter his fellow citizens and believe they deserve it -- by Alexander Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How religion can drive someone to slaughter his fellow citizens and believe they deserve it -- by Alexander Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Novella by Saddam Hussein gets English translation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far away is the smart golf ball? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 03:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you attended the week long Golf Academy at Pinehurst in North Carolina? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the following post from over a year ago and it really got me interested: https://www.reddit.com/r/golf/comments/2zdcl7/pinehurst_golfacademy/

Has anyone else attended this? If so, how was your experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mom died so give me karma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 03:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golfing in Germany? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. I've visited Germany close to 20 times in my life time. Most of the visits were to Berlin, Munich, Dsseldorf, and were usually to see my family there. One thing I never got to do in Germany was go golfing.  

Do any of you play golf? If so, can you recommend some good courses to play in Germany? 

I'll be going home to Ireland for a month next year and I'd love to stop by in Germany again for a few days.

Apologies for the lack of Deutsch in this post, I've unfortunately lost the language completely due to never using it. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tuesdays are no fun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 14:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former 'singing' priest found guilty of raping boy with a crucifix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relaxing after a tough day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went golfing with a pastor today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He spent a lot of the round trying to convert me, which would have normally ruined the day or me but I found the humour in it. I was able to shoot him down. He was just shooting the shit.  

He was a pure hacker and dug trenches through the whole course. He had one good hole where he got a par, and thanked THE LORD for helping him do it. Got on his knees and everything. I asked him where his Lord was for the previous holes  and it was as if the thought never crossed his mind.   

We had a lot of banter during the round, made a lot of fun out of each other, but I definitely got him thinking.   

I also showed him the sub I started, /r/pastorarrested and he was shocked. I talked about how the whole thing needs to be fucking regulated and how I was astonished that people are willing to leave their kids with these people.   

To be fair I cringed when he said he was a pastor but now I'm glad we met. It was a fun experience.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A child in London wearing the flag of a group assisting Assad in his massacre of Syrians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 22:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A child in London wearing the flag of a group assisting Assad in his massacre of Syrians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 22:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A child in London wearing the flag of a group assisting Assad in his massacre of Syrians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 22:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GMac's advice to me today when I asked if he had any advice for a 7 handicapper trying to make it to scratch: "Get better inside 100 yards". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 00:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing shocking or surprising about that really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 July Book Discussion: A Long Short War: The Postponed Liberation of Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 17:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're nearing the end of this journey, with Arguably being the last book we'll be reading next month. Arguably is huge of course and probably should go on for longer than a month.  

This month we're focusing on a short pamphlet about Iraq, a great little volume that outlines why Hitchens was in favour of regime change in Iraq. 

It's easy to spot someone who is lazy and uninformed about Hitchens   the Iraq war, because they'll drop a one liner along the lines of the following "Well Hitchens was pro Iraq War and look how that turned out. He was wrong about Iraq".

Hitchens was not wrong about Iraq. All along the way he kept arguing that the US was not doing enough, they dropped the ball at every occasion and pulled out too soon. They did a terrible job.

Anyway, enjoy the short read folks. I haven't read it in a few years and I'm really looking forward to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The little fella greeted me at 6am this morning. There's lots of deer on my local course and they're not shy around people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 15:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Class act lads. Congratulations! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 23:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite book by an Irish author? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must admit I haven't read a lot of our own literature. 

I've read **Dracula** and loved parts of it, the love letters drove me mad though I thought they kind of ruined the story. 

**The Picture of Dorian Gray** is the only work I've read from Oscar Wilde. I loved it, and made a mental note to read more from Wilde but it just hasn't happened at all.

I've read a lot of Irish History, books by Dan Breen, Ernie O'Malley,  Tom Barry, et al, so not really looking for suggestions there.  

John Moriarty was a great Irish poet and philosopher and I've read all of his works as well. 

**The Islandman** by Tomas O'Crohan was a fantastic read about life on the Blasket Islands before it was abandoned. He got his first pair of shoes the day he got married. Crazy to think how people lived a relatively short time ago.  

Are there any "must read" books I've missed out on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Considering moving away from SLDR Driver. Any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not actually had an issue with the driver, per se. I've hit the last 30 or so fairways with it and had two of the best rounds I've ever had but a lot of you have said it's unforgiving so I'm wondering if I would see improvements with a different driver.

Also, the crux of the issue is really that the driver I have is very lofted - 14.5 degrees which and I figure if I get a 10.5 degree or 9.5 degree driver I will gain some distance. 

I usually hit the current driver around 220 - 250.

Can anyone recommend a driver to try? Preferably one that came out from 2014 onwards. 

All of my clubs are TaylorMade but I'd have no issues getting a driver from someone else, be it Nike, Titleist, Callaway or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letters of Note: Charles Bukowski on Censorship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Players who tee off from the blue tees - when did you decide to start playing from here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 18:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm being cut to 6.8 tomorrow. I've been consistently scoring in the 70s for the past few weeks from the white tees. I figure it's time to start playing from the blue now.

Players who tee off from the blue tees - when did you decide to start playing from here?  
Was it a tough transition?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [x-post from /r/PastorArrested] Youth pastor's arrest raises safety questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 18:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being an atheist in the USA is a lot like being a sane person in a mental asylum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your goals / targets for this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was to break 80 which I've done three times now. I'm setting breaking 70 as a goal by the time I reach 35 (so 2 more years). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens political shift discussed in new Oppenheimer book: EXIT RIGHT: The People Who Left the Left and Reshaped the American Century </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens political shift discussed in new Oppenheimer book: EXIT RIGHT: The People Who Left the Left and Reshaped the American Century [link in comments] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 18:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/book-party/wp/2016/01/28/could-you-trade-in-your-political-beliefs-for-their-exact-opposite-these-six-people-did/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your worst experience with someone else's kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our first attempt at a garden. Not a bad effort for first timers. We have had several batches of lettuce so far. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 01:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last day playing golf until July 4th. New record 77 at my home course, and also 56 on a par 3 course. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 04:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Night time golf. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I took an extended lunch to play 9 holes today. +3 at the of it. It was very hard to go back to the office and not continue the round. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiding from a tornado between the 7th and 8th hole. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 00:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIELDS OF ATHENRY INTENSIFIES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often do you buy a new set of irons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 14:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piss off /r/Ireland in one sentence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any idea why the featured group coverage hasn't started for the US Open? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 14:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
