<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is a really cool shot from Matrix: Reloaded when their ship arrives at Zion and we see [a very futuristic, stark white control room](http://imgur.com/TpxRidn)

Edit: also the TV show Westworld has some cool futuristic bendable tablets and tons of interface screens and you might also find some movies in this [tumblr](http://sciencefictioninterfaces.tumblr.com/) that specializes in scifi displays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Places

The Judge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure all of these have rain:

Blade Runner

The Last Wave

Glengarry Glen Ross

The Matrix: Revolutions

Dark City

The Day After Tomorrow

Rashomon

Seven

Road to Perdition

Jurassic Park

Star Wars Episode II </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 09:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be that body image is the link? I was thinking that maybe people see all those fit looking pornstars and head on to self-improvement subreddits to get in shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 09:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so if two sections are next to each other, does that mean they are related? like porn and self-improvement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last one's focus was being posters for the movies themselves. In this one the Shire and Gondor posters could work as posters for the movies but the middle one with Balrog is not representative of Two Towers at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister bought his previous [LOTR triptych](http://i.imgur.com/BUtaICT.jpg) and it looks amazing. This one's cool as well, I like the focus on Gandalf, but I think the first one was a tad better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this should be the official presidential portrait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And it was "gettin stuff DONE" Kurt Russell, which is my favorite iteration of him.

I laughed hard at this. What other iterations of him are there, anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dinner parties gone wrong:

[Coherence](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2866360/) - a sci-fi twist

[You're Next](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1853739/) - a violent horror twist

[Clue](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0088930/) - a comedic and murderous twist

[Guess Who's Coming to Dinner](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0061735/) - a social/family drama twist

[Festen (The Celebration)](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0154420/) - a family drama twist

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone going to make a spotify/youtube playlist of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it has to be the first option, right? Because why would N decide to make an article about something so old? The exhibition isn't even there anymore. Except, I haven't seen the original imgur link anywhere before N made the article, so where exactly has it gone viral? This whole thing baffles me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed the article yesterday and I was quite amused by it. Especially when they quoted me as a surprised tourist (I am from Bratislava). But I don't understand why it's become such a big deal so long after I originally posted it (Sep. 2015). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before Midnight from the Before trilogy

Not a horror movie by any measure, but an excellent exploration of marriage and it can get depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think prisoners are given a diaper  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of surprised no one mentioned Ghostbusters.

Also, The Conjuring and Insidious have some moments where characters use technology to detect spirits, though it's not as scientific as Oculus. Both are still great horrors and worth a watch regardless. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  sci fi worlds that are beautiful and intriguing and have a fun/intelligent story to tell

Yep, it's called Star Trek. Consult imdb on which of the Trek movies are worth it, but I also strongly recommend watching the shows. TNG and DS9 in particular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> screwed it up with the cheese imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Descent - a group of women go spelunking and deep underground they encounter violent mole people (for lack of a better description). The tension and violence in this movie are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gatsby is literally a "Great American Novel" because it's, well, American - its author and setting are American. And it certainly put America on the literary map of the world, where it did not have much of a place before. This is what "Great American Novel" has come to mean.

Furthermore, the novel has a more sober view of the American dream. In the late 1800s and early 1900s the United States were a haven for immigrants who could start a new life. Poor Irish farmer with a starving family? Go to America, set up a business or get a big piece of land and become something more! It's what America was all about. But in Gatsby, the romantic American dream gets a more realistic and dark twist. Yes, America is the land of plenty and yes, you can go from rags to riches. But it does not buy you happiness or acceptance. You become a prisoner of it. And you still have to face the crowds of less fortunate people whose American dream did not come true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is 100% safe, for the most part.

Sooo... not 100% ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She did not bash football and MMA. She bashed a society that cares the most about watching violent sports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you take grams, convert them to ounces, then back to grams. Then you say you purchase ounces but the retailer measures in grams. How is all that not more confusing than just sticking to the metric system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot how to eagle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He neither wrote nor directed any of the two Cloverfield movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had very little to do with Lost after the pilot episode and he neither wrote nor directed 10 Cloverfield Lane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea this was going to be rated R. I cheered when he said motherfucker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That disgusting lump of orange shit is cheese? Are all the comments here sarcastic or are you genuinely excited by that thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? How do you not know about this movie if you go to /r/movies ? People here mention Prisoners absolutely whenever appropriate and often when not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you might as well include Nocturnal Animals in there, too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 11:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this whole youtube channel is great and iaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Solid seconds detonated

loving this typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like this video is reading too much into certain things while outright dismissing other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joj or Markiza? There is no way in hell that I'd watch Valerian on either of those stations. Or any movie, for that matter. between the endless commercial breaks and the terrible dubbing, I'd rather pay whatever sum of money for a movie ticket and see the film properly at the cinema </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The movie "Kon Tiki" had the best looking CG sharks I have ever seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wow](https://youtu.be/qjBRNqwDPrU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A visual effects breakdown video for Independence Day: Resurgence set to electronic music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if only the paint job was its only problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [the viral site](http://www.continentalquarterly.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The studio won't care about reviews until the movies remain profitable. The future of DCEU depends on the audiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie definitely puts the western genre on the pedestal of art </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they will be able to just sort of quietly leave her out of Ep. IX like they left out The Joker from TDKR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting that they thought it was easier to do this particular shot practically. No one would really notice or care if BB-8 was CG in this one shot where he quickly moves. And yet they went to the trouble of building the prop, paying a guy to operate it and erasing him and the gear from the final shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe they used RC, this blue guy and full CG in various scenes depending on what was needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, a good non-spoilery, ambiguous trailer does at least one of these things:

- little to no dialogue from the movie (Girl With a Dragon Tattoo, The Force Awakens, Interstellar)

- either just one extended scene that pulls you in (American Sniper) or many inter-cut images that engage your attention (Girl With a Dragon Tattoo, Gone Girl, The Handmaiden)

- memorable, standout music, which is either a song (Girl With a Dragon Tattoo, Gone Girl, ) or the actual score from the movie (The Force Awakens)

- images that set the mood but are not actually from the movie (Alien, Interstellar)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In retrospect that trailer shows a lot, including the final chase and some other things that might be considered spoilers, but the way it's all presented without dialogue and with fast editing is perfect. People who've already read the book will pick up on those moments they glimpse in the footage and go "fuck yeah, that was that scene!" or "wow was that the guy from that scene?" while people who don't know the story will be confused and uniformed, but still engaged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a good place to plug in your hair iron or electric razor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Honey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you probably should have tagged it with [suggestion] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like American Psycho: Nightcrawler

Like Basic Instinct: Body Heat

Like Wallstreet: The Big SHort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want campy but also good go with [The Blob](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0094761/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put on a fancy apron, play opera music and pretend I'm Hannibal Lecter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame they had to make those vibrant location shots look so drab and overcast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make it sound as if it was impossibly difficult and expensive to make good looking movies before computers were invented.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered about this. I see it all the time in movies and shows and it baffles me. In Europe people wouldn't dream of going to a bar by car. It's the exact opposite of what you do. When I go out for a drink I either check the buses, walk, or make sure I have enough cash for a taxi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's too much trouble to find a mansion and a pier on a lake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite thing about the English language is that "shit" and "the shit" mean opposite things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that the background is supposed to be the sun rising over the earth with a flare, but it kind of looks like an explosion, which isn't really tasteful in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marlon Brando got paid more for his appearance in Superman than Christopher Reeve. Everybody in Avengers got paid less than RDJ.

You get paid what you negotiate to get paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  who are you going to listen to?

Myself. I am capable of forming my own opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even thought it's Ridley Scott talking, a respected and popular film maker with many great movies under his belt, it's still just one man's opinion. It's not like Hollywood executives will read his quote and immediately cancel all super hero movies currently in development. It's also not like Scott is infallible. He made a couple of shitty movies himself. So maybe we should all calm down and not make such a big deal out of these click-bait stories where one film maker trashes a genre he never even tackled. It's just his opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they stick to that formula with Chapter 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that high rise is sticking up there like a sore thumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was reading my book when I noticed the name Una was printed with a large lowercase u instead of an uppercase U (elsewhere in the book it's printed correctly with a U) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question: are these sheep or goats? My whole family can't decide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 10:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this movie. It has my most favorite title sequence of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  La La Lasting impression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You took a risk mentioning David O Russel in this sub. Have my upvote as moral support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big pet peeve for me, too. English is my second language but I don't need subtitles to understand movies unless they throw in southern accents and mumbling. Hell or High Water was a big offender and I even had some trouble with The Magnificent Seven. However, I don't fault the actors or sound people* for this. If it's how these people talk, then it's how they talk. I know guys IRL whom I can't understand half the time either, so why not a pair of Texan bank robbers.

*I do blame the sound people if dialogue is obscured by noises and music too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 09:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is how ibuprofen is made </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How certain are we that Russia influenced the US presidential election and was is being done about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm with opposite situation: I am a very heavy sleeper; people have found it difficult to wake me up (to the point where they sometimes started to panic a bit). I don't snore, except once in a blue moon I do and with the faintest snore I wake myself up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  almost like an octopus

Now there's a disturbing image </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a side-ELI5, what exactly is mucus and what is it made of? Is mucus just a fancy word for slime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out The Affair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking news: in their personal lives celebrities look exactly like we know them from photoshoots except they make slightly different poses.

Maybe if the photographer at least took pictures of them in candid clothing and without makeup. These photos reveal absolutely nothing about these people.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I kind of gave up on network TV a couple of years ago. Am I missing out on anything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 09:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last network TV show I watched was Hannibal, which was excellent. All the other shows I used to watch were either drawn out too long or never really good to begin with. My girlfriend tried to convince me to watch How to Get Away With Murder, so I gave it a shot and turned it off during the third episode. There were just too many shitty characters, fake mysteries and tropes. I could just see them milking that shit with nonsensical revelations and twists for the next five seasons. It just seemed so network.

What do I watch? Game of Thrones, Westworld, The Affair, Sherlock, The Night Of, The Leftovers, Homeland, and Narcos.

Does ABC, CBS, CW, FOX, or NBC have anything really good to offer these days? Or should I just continue ignoring them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, this is Petrzalka, a large communist housing project in Bratislava, Slovakia. (I live here.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt the exact same thing when I first watched it and I still think the new characters are great and have potential. On repeat viewings, though, I just couldn't help watching Ridley's face. There is nothing subtle about her acting whatsoever. She constantly pulls one face after another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second half has two problems, I think. First, Starkiller base just randomly appears in the movie out of nowhere without any build up or a prior mention and just *suddenly* becomes a threat and a setpiece. The second problem is that everything that happens in Maz's palace feels kind of out of place and pointless. As I said before, the momentum of the movie simply stops when they get there. Then Rey's vision in the cellar happens in such an unexpected and jarring way that it feels like something from a different movie. Then Maz simply disapperas from the story because they cut her from later scenes in Leia's base and we don't get any resolution for those visions because they are a question for episode VIII. So Maz slows down the movie, vanishes without even a mention that she survived the attack on her palace and just leaves us with nothing but questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the Republic business appears in the novelization and it was confirmed the woman in that shot was an actual character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think the momentum of the strong first hour of the movie screeches to a halt when they get to Maz and it never recovers from there. The first hour is paced very well, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, the Republic should have been developed in the movie. They probably cut it because they were afraid people wouldn't be interested. After all, everyone loves to bitch about senate debates and trade agreements in the prequels. Let's just keep any sort of politics out of our little New Hope remake. But then why the hell should I care about it getting blown up by Starkiller Base? Why do they even mention the Republic at all if the audience has no clue what role this political entity plays in this world at this time? They show us the Empire regrouped in the form of the First Order, but they don't show or clarify in any way what happened to the rest of the galaxy. That one [reaction shot of a seemingly random woman](http://imgur.com/a/kUa88) they inserted into that sequence just screams deleted scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume OP is not a native speaker. This how/what looked like thing is one of the most common mistakes people make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch Jurassic Park first. It's a very well-made movie and great fun. Then watch Alien. It's also a very well-made movie but suspenseful af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With TFA I was just blown away by the movie more or less on the basis of "holy shit, I am watching a new Star Wars movie and it doesn't suck!" but as time went by, I began to recognize its flaws, such as the rehashed story, pacing issues, acting (I am not enthusiastic about Daisy Ridley) and a couple of missed opportunities (I think some of the deleted scene should have been left in the movie, [the final light saber fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TdEIzRUos4g) , etc).

With Rogue One I immediately recognize its flaws (first half of the movie is riddled with issues) but I still get a shitload of enjoyment from it. It was better than TFA but neither are anywhere near perfect. It makes me wonder: What the hell is so hard about making a good Star Wars movie? 

Also, as a side note, that whole reshoots situation bothers me. There are so many things in the trailers that indicate a very different movie. What happened to that version? Will we ever know all the things they changed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that bra thing is definitely holding them together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harrison Ford can be great if he wants to. Have you seen Raiders of the Lost Ark? He has so much natural charm in that movie. His best performance was Witness (which he got nominated for) and he has a couple good performances in other movies like Frantic and Fugitive. He can definitely act if he gives a shit, which, admittedly, nowadays he doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when I thought people got over Scarlett Johansson. She got a big break pretty early with Lost in Translation but not much after that. But now look at her. She is still number one on most people's fap lists, she's a pretty big part of the MCU, she gets cool action roles but also more interesting projects like voice work in animation and Her, not to mention indie scifi Under the Skin. So I wouldn't dismiss JLaw so soon. She is still popular and young and she will get ton of work. It's up to her if she picks the right projects and retains her charm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliens fits your description very well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Babadook

Oculus

It Follows

Don't Breathe

Lights Out

The Ring

The Descent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched this with my sister on the 24th. It's such a well-made movie that it's almost baffling. Like I know a lot of people who straight up dismiss it as a dumb kids movie, but even if you don't like adventure or mythology or you are incapable of having a wide grinning smile on your face, you could still watch this movie and *study* each shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Krampus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these have quite a few special effects and CG in them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some see Gone Girl as very amusing satire with elements that border on dark comedy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall Street and its sequel Money Never Sleeps (actual title, no joke) should be an obvious choice if you haven't seem them already. And Wolf of Wall Street, of course, although that's less about finance than about enjoying finance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blade Runner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I discovered *Eyes Wide Shut* as a kid roughly 12 years old. Needless to say its message and cinematic quality went way over my head at that time, but man was I blown away by its sexiness. Of course, there is that giant orgy scene, but that's not what I mean. I've already seen some porn at that time so while fun to watch, the orgy is not what I remember the most. It was this secret sexy adult world that really got to me. Doctors getting to touch brautiful breast as their job, parents getting high in their room after they tuck in the kid, parties with OD'd naked hookers, a costume shop owner prostituting his daughter, secret sex rings, dark day dreams about your wife's adultery... Man, this movie is when I first realized that everything in the adult world revolves around sex. There is this quote I've seen on the internet that describes it perfectly: *Everything in life is about sex, except sex. Sex is about power.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lone Survivor

It's more action than suspense but from what I can tell the combat is on point and it's a true story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember like it was yesterday. I went on a road trip camping vacation with no internet two days before the Fappening happened. By the time I got back, many of the pictures were already pulled down, thousands of comments were written, opinion editorials were published, empty bottles of lube were discarded. It was like waking up from a coma and discovering the zombie apocalypse already happened and was promptly suppressed. 

(Edited typos) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks a lot like Kim Dickens in this pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A true European treaure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose you've already seen *The Thing* but that is definitely the best answer as far as gritty scifi horror goes, even though it's not set in space. *The Abyss, Leviathan* and *Sphere* are all set in underwater stations, but it might as well be a space station setting and not much would change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both the Die Hard and Lethal Weapons series are staples of Christmas for my family. We also usually watch Kiss Kiss Bang Bang. All of these take place during the holidays but are not holiday-themed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't spoil the fact that the movie sucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't spoil the fact that the movie sucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are practical effects coming back in earnest or are they used as a gimmick to attract audiences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 11:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not going to be an argument about practical being better than CG. Both have their place in modern filmmaking and I enjoy both when they are done well. That is beside the point. What I would like to discuss is whether practical effects (big sets and props, large scale stunt work, prosthetic makeup, models, etc) are making a real comeback or if they are the new gimmick like 3D was after Avatar came out.


Naturally I welcome the apparent resurgence of practical effects, but I always wonder if it's not just another marketing ploy. As far as I can tell, the productions that most blatantly publicise using practical effects are all sequels to beloved properties from the pre-CG era. Both The Force Awakens and Rogue One marketing campaigns have been very outspoken about going practical. However, it doesn't sound to me like the comeback of a filmmaking craft. It sounds more like these productions have something to prove and something to overcome. 'Look, you hated the overdone CG of the prequels, but don't worry, we're not doing that, so please buy tickets.' Perhaphs I'm too cynical about it, but the way they presented the practical effects in those ComicCon videos was definitely just pandering to fans of the originals.


Another example is Mad Max: Fury Road. It was made very obvious and very widely known how practical the action is in the movie. So much so that it resembled a marketing campaign in itself. Thosebehind-the-scenesvideos that came out showing stunt tests and pre-color graded footage served as trailers for the spectacle you would get in the theater. Again I got the sense that these filmmakers are saying 'This won't be another CG action movie, so buy tickets for our practical fun!' So many 1980s properties have been revisited with sequels and reboots and so many of them were bad in part due to the modern sensibilities of their filmmaking. Was anyone back in the day pining for a scene where John McClane jumps onto the wing of a jet fighter while it destroys a highway overpass? Was there anyone impatiently waiting for the technology to catch up to this essential vision of what that character could do? No. John McClane is a regular guy and that shit is just not realistic. Just like the CG in that scene didn't look realistic at all. So is Fury Road a demonstration of how to make a better movie or is it simply a demonstration of how not to ruin your 80s franchise?


Jurassic World used some practical puppets and its sequel is set to utilize them even more. In fact, I know more about the intent to use animatronics in JW2 than I know about the story or cast of that movie. Why is that? Are we so sick of CG or so eager to see the jerky movements of puppets we grew up with in Spielberg's original? Is this reemergence of practical effects just a new way of pandering to our nostalgia or is it a real, honest to god return of a filmmaking technique?


Then we have movies like A Monster Calls, which I haven't seen yet but I already read five articles about its practical effects. It's like using anything else beside computers is an oddity that needs to be reported and scrutinized.Yesterday I watched Krampus and that movie is surprisingly loaded with practical effects. People in masks and costumes instead of CG critters. It was what The Thing should have done in 2011. (I honestly think the decision to scrap those wonderful practical effects completely ruined what could have been a very effective and scary prequel.) However, some of those Krampus masks are so obviously fake that again I have to wonder what it's trying to say. Is it an honest (if a little unconvincing) effort to do practical effects or is it just some on the nose retro call back that was purposefully done a little bit too fake so that we would notice it and recall some cheap 80s movies from our childhood? Are movies just movies these days or is everything about them winking at the audience?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 08:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be the first answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 08:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Strangers with Affleck

That is probably the remake of Hitchcock's Stranger on A Train, which he's been circling for a couple of years now. It would be amazing to see his style applied to Hitchcock, but on the other hand I do wish he'd focus more on original stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, James Cameron is not directing this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harrison Ford's appearance really takes me out of it. Why the plain grey t-shirt and terrible hair? It looks like Ryan Gosling stumbled into Harrison's house announced. It certainly doesn't look like Rick Deckard sneaking up on someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really have any specific names in mind, but, for example, Gleeson's character should be tall and thin, with a very introverted, quiet and stern demeanor. I wasn't really getting that sort vibe from him in the trailer. Daniel Bruhl's characters should also be older, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 12:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great book, I've read it this year. But I think the casting is completely off. They are all great actors but I don't think they fit the roles as described in the novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Whispers should be quiet, they are whispers. Explosions should be loud...they are explosions.

This is very true. However, you are not factoring music into this statement. There is nothing worse than a loud action scene that also has a loud score on top of it. Then it just becomes a battle of two loud noises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend Oculus as well. I learned about its existence in [this video about modern horrs](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zz6KOsePEHs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early morning view from a camp near Zell Am See in the Austrian Alps [OC] [1995x1122] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I haven't watched that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not forgetting that. I'm just assuming he hasn't done much over those 13 because he was convalescing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 11:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work on Episode VIII is well underway. In fact, I'm not sure if they haven't already finished principal photography. Of course, there are still reshoots, but I doubt any sort of feedback to Rogue One can significantly influence VIII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 11:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me wonder, though, if this is OK to do from a moral viewpoint. What is stopping them from using Cushing's face for whatever inappropriate stuff they come up with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 11:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Leader was CG too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 11:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> copying my review from /r/movies here if that is ok

The pros:

- They perfectly captured the look and feel of the original Star Wars world, which is both futuristic and ancient, sleek and gritty. And they expanded upon it perfectly with new locations, aliens, weapons, etc.

- The visuals are astounding. Beautiful cinematography and VFX. And all those wonderful designs! Darth Vader's hideout looked like something straight from Ralph McQuarie's sketchbook and all the aliens were neat.

- There was less fan service and nostalgia pandering compared to The Force Awakens (though it was definitely present)

- The ending was perfect. It did not shy away from character deaths and it tied things up wonderfully, leaving us where Ep. IV starts.

- We finally get to see Darth Vader kick some serious ass. You know which scene I mean. He was fucking terrifying. 

- We also see a lot more of the Empire

- Ben Mendelhson stole the show for me along with Donnie Yen. 

- The score felt very much like a Star Wars score.

The cons:

- The story is a bit all over the place and the pacing is off. The first half of the movie feels at odds with the beach planet finale. I think Rogue One could easily have been 20 minutes shorter and better paced without losing any important story beats.

- Neither the script nor the acting are perfect although neither gets anywhere near the high prequel levels of cringe.

In summary:

- Rogue One is a visual feast which captures the Star Wars feel perfectly. It serves as a great proof of concept for these standalone anthology films.

- It is not without issues of script and pacing, but these issues don't detract much from the overal very positive experience.

PS: Please excuse bad English and misspelled actor names.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 10:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's one of those situations where you simply can't please everyone. I'm happy this wasn't the Vader show. The filmmakers didn't blow their geek load and made something new with a new villain instead of fulfilling what I'm sure was their childhood dream when they played with Vader action figures. If this was the Vader show, people would complain they just rehashed stuff and didn't do anything new. Too much Vader would be bad and apparently too little Vader is bad too. But I really think they used him in just the right way. His first scene tied nicely with the prequels (the setting on Mustafar plus the fact that he was still in the healing process) and the second scene showed us what we always wanted to see. Why do more? Sure, it's always cool to see him, but on the other hand he's kind of sacred and what if they messed him up? 

As for the Tarkin thing...I don't know if that needed any major explaining. The Empire is a military operation and a relatively young new Sith Lord can't be expected to lead a whole big operation, especially since he seems to spend most of his time on Mustafar doing weird Vader shit. In Ep. IV Tarkin is there to keep him in check, I think, and supervise him for the Emperor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
