<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6420</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I don't know if this is just rumours and hearsay, but if someone breaks into your home with you in there, isn't the most you can do is tell them to leave and to call the police? You are not allowed to defend your home nor prevent them from leaving until the police arrives because they might sue you for assault/kidnapping/false imprisonment? I'm pretty sure if that's true then installing landmines to blow up whomever comes to steal the honey is going to be illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really pumped to see another season coming again. This is the only Masterchef series I'm actually following.

Best part about the video was how all those contestants were actually achieving their dreams, and not only the winners and the top 3 but others like Heather and Rose! For all the hate that Rose got from here, it's actually nice to see that at least she was successful in opening a cafe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the time? Tell them to go back to their own. Though this mostly only works in places like USA, Argentina, Australia, New Zealand, which have a majority of their population being immigrants. Unless they are aborigines (Native Americans, Maori, etc.) they don't have much more claim to a country than you do, they just moved there a few generations earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably explore. There are so many places on Earth that are both dangerous to be irl but really worth seeing up close, like volcanoes, mountains, jungles, Emma Watson's changing room, deep sea, or outer space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being unable to speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add to that thinking that they are smart when presenting really dumb counter arguments to your very valid points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, according to the article, it's going to take like over $4 trillion to fix infrastructure to an acceptable level. It's hard to even imagine that kind of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knew English, Spanish, and they tried to teach me French and Latin in Secondary School back in Argentina. Breezed through both German and Italian introductory classes at university despite never having much contact with either language before.
Also surprisingly, knowing Chinese (or Mandarin) actually helped me with some pronunciation in French, especially the umlaut.
I've also been able to mostly read a Portuguese text without actually having learnt Portuguese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, when my parents were teaching me Chinese the most confusing part was the difference in use of characters for time and direction. "Before" and "front" share the same character (), and "after" and "back" use the same character (). Like "day after tomorrow" if you translated it character by character it would mean "back day". It is honestly one of the things I used to struggle the most because it doesn't make sense for anyone that uses Latin-based languages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pros:

-As an Asian that is fluent with Spanish (not only that, Argentinian Spanish or Castellano) seeing Spanish-speaking people from countries like Chile, Peru, Spain, etc. hear me suddenly speak fluently with an unusual accent is hilarious, both for me and sometimes for them as well. 

-Specially with Latin-based languages, knowing one can be a huge help in learning others. Knew English and Spanish, with some French and Latin; breezed through German and Italian classes.

-When you get bored counting in one language, you can switch to another one to keep it different.

Cons: 

-Sometimes I forget to switch back to the correct language when I'm talking to more than one person.

-As I've lived in Argentina (which has a very heavy Italian influence), I actually use a lot of hand gestures when talking or use gestures like these https://youtu.be/Hxu50kiDVGc to communicate non-verbally. Most people have absolutely no idea what I'm doing with my hands.

-Not for me, but for my grandpa, he just uses random Spanish words around people whether those people speak Chinese or English. His English is very, very limited so this happens most of the time. He is probably used to it since most of my family speaks both Chinese and Spanish.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *-Sigh-* *-Head hits desk-* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the coworker wasn't teaching English, only OP was. And the coworker was probably a native of the country OP went to teach in so English was not his first language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caught a 1800 CP one in Taiwan a few months ago, I think it came out of a lure. Had to precisely angle the camera so that I could catch it among all the other Pokemon around.
Found a second one a couple of weeks ago, around 1100 CP, near my work and I've never even seen a Grimer around there. There's mostly water pokemon alongside the usual commons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they are insects, I can see they are moving, I can see their feet, but I still feel like you are just holding a bunch of scrunched up leaves that are moving from your hand flexing around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that going with friends is pretty helpful. Get a group together with similar free times and go together. That's how I started going to the gym and getting fit, I was kinda thinking about it and my friends convinced me to join them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this as torturing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it really is a dick move, but I can sometimes also see the appeal in it, especially when you are surrounded by level 10 gyms from any team for kilometers. Then I remember it's just a game and really don't have the free time to get another account just to kick out someone to get 10 gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started reading this thinking it was dessert. Probably still would have if not for the fried chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
