<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6123</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try getting it in your head that it's not the character you're playing but your account. Your character is just a (fun) 'tool' to get your account further.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://pathofexile.gamepedia.com/Essence_Drain

No offence but searching Essence Drain on Google takes a lot less time compared to typing your post ;-)

Welcome to PoE!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what about the part where he does the method in this clip? It worked.

And did you hear thelogic behind it? I listened to the whole explanation in the car this morning and the level of detail is insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause some of them have been nerfed and now you can get them pre-nerfed a.k.a. with insane stats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a new player right? For me your post doesn't make sense. It can only get better from here AND if you are a new player use this time to learn te game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny, a couple of days ago I read somewhere that someone found that the PoE reddit was soooo toxic and that this was one of the reasons he didn't play PoE.

We all know better ofcourse. 

How someone can be so wrong...

Good stuff OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be fine in SSF-mode, for those who would like this mind you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is! First perfectly with a couple of hours of fast map clearing. Gets my mouse-clicking-fingers all pumped up... Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the mood but mostly I switch between classical music and stuff like this

[NewRetroWave](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n4E4kjQIw6M)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with "cheap" he means low on chaos(/exalts). For a first timer you should try to aim at around max 40 chaos as a "cheap build", but that's my personal opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max level is 100 and you can respec a character but that'll cost A LOT of currency depending on how many nodes you want to respec (you respec per node) so the best thing to do is just start a new character honestly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max level for a character you mean? That's lvl 100. 

Finding a rare now seems like 'a thing' but at around 70-80 you'll find so much useless rares you don't even pick them up anymore, at least, when using Neversink's lootfilter, that helps a lot.

I really suggest :

Just play PoE and learn, watch a lot of Youtube clips that help you understand the game and idea behind builds, read a lot about what makes PoE PoE and not a 'choose a class and play that class' kind game. A class (like Shadow or Witch) doen'st mean a lot, it only really means where you start on the 'skill board' and  use a lot of 3rd party stuff likle PoE.trade, autohotkey, lootfilters, builds, PoE Ninja etc)

:-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure isn't 100% sure ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This helped me a lot as a first timer :

https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=668664722

Also it depends if you are using a build/guide or not? Of not - You are going to botch you first build, trust me. And that's perfectly fine, I know everybody else did :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presuming/hoping you are following a build (if not, it doens't really matter what you do with rares, you are going to botch your build anyway) try to follow the stats on the build-gear on the rares that you find. 

Other than that the rares you don't need for your build can be vendored till lvl 60-70 except for rare jewels, those are mostly worth using or selling on PoE trade. If you want to make sure what each item could be worth before selling them, download PoE trade auto hotkey checker ctrl+D while hovering over an item will tell you the current value based on a couple of things)

Also use Neversink's Lootfilter.

If you say you are low on storage space, do you mean the standard slots? Actually, it doen'st matter. If you are running low at a low level you are hoarding... :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah yeah yeah!!! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dafuq?! Holy shit! Congrats!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 'low level' drop that's remotely usefull for a longer period of time is Tabula Rasa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.pathofexile.com/forum/view-thread/1255624/page/1#p10631034 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's lying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said don't get hyped with the comming small announcement regarding trade. He didn't say don't get hyped with the general trading future announcements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because you give people two options -- You pay or you don't. Either way you can play the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah even better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to second this. And please throw in some D3... ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like you piss me off f*cking troll. People like you are always whining, pointing fingers at other people, people like you are always impatient, looking at faults in things and people instead of the good things. People like you have a miserable life.

Suck it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunday I tried the DEMO of Nier Automata and it rocked so hard! Can't wait for that game to come out in a month or so. 

And yeah, maybe some DS3 (played DS2 A LOT) or Bloodborne in between. I loved the slowness of Dark Souls though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's gonna be more hilarious for me cause I KNOW i'm gonna suck at this game ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afraid to try CKII now... ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
