<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject185</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do have the most expensive machine in the whole hospital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> H. P. Lovecraft was wrong - The Old Ones are under the Arctic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was going to post this - http://www.cascadianow.org/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *We've now had 77 straight months of economic expansion. 

 *We are currently enjoying the longest period of private sector job creation in American history. 

 *U.S. job growth has continued for a record 73 months in a row. 

 *Unemployment has dropped from 10.1% in October of 2009 to 4.7%. 

 *The number of job openings doubled, to a record 5.7 million. 

 *For The First Time In 30 Years, Unemployment Fell In EVERY State In 2014 

 *In 2015 3.5 Million Americans no longer lived in poverty. 

 *The stock market continues to set new records. 

 *Wages grew 2.5% in October from a year ago, the best increase since July 2009. 

 *after-tax incomes are up 14% since 2009. 

 *Middle class incomes had their fastest growth on record last year. 

 *Consumer confidence is at a seven-year high. 

 *The Federal budget deficit is shrinking. Its been reduced by two-thirds since 2009. 

 *Spending has increased only 3.3% annually, the lowest rate since Eisenhower was president. 

 *For 95% of American taxpayers, income taxes are lower now than just about any time in the previous 50 years. 

 *Our dependence on foreign oil has shrunk to a 20 year low due to record domestic oil production and improved fuel efficiency standards.

 *At least 10 million more Americans now have health insurance than before. 

 *Health care spending in the U.S. grew last year at the lowest rate ever recorded, and the Affordable Care Act requires insurance companies to spend at least 80% of collected premiums on healthcare. As a result, millions of Americans have received refunds from their health insurance companies. (over $9 Billion so far) 

 *The Affordable Care Act has added 13 years to the life of the Medicare trust fund. 

 *Since passage of the Affordable Care Act, we are seeing the slowest rate of increase in healthcare costs since 1960 and senior citizens have saved billions of dollars on prescription drugs. 

 *We currently have fewer soldiers, sailors and airmen in war zones than any time in over 12 years. 

 *Veteran Homelessness Has Dropped By Nearly 50% Since 2010. 

 *There have been zero successful attacks by al Qaeda on US soil since Obama became president and Osama Bin Laden is dead. 

 *There are fewer people crossing the southwest border than in the last 30 years. 

 *We now successfully catch and deport more illegal immigrants than ever before. 

 *The Obama administration increased the deportation of illegal immigrants convicted of crimes by 70 percent. 

 *Obama Has 273,000 Fewer Federal Employees Than Reagan. 

 *Inflation under Obama is the lowest in a half century. 

 *Manufacturing is coming back to the U.S. Growth this year averaged 15,000 jobs per month. 

 *Obama has cracked down on oil speculators.[National average, 1/1/16, $1.99 gal] 

 *Wind and solar energy generation has doubled. 

 *401K accounts and home equity have recovered from the Bush disaster. 

 *We've made historic progress on climate change and environmental protection. 

 *Domestic auto production is at a 12 year high, and GM is once again the largest auto manufacturer in the world. 

 *We now have new rules in place to protect consumers from unfair and deceptive credit card practices. 

 *We increased infrastructure spending after years of neglect. 

 *The United States is back in compliance with the Geneva Convention. 

 *The TARP program and auto bailouts are now closed, and yielded $15.35 billion in profit. 

 *The U.S. is Now the World's Leading oil and Natural Gas Producer. 

 *The US Dollar Is The Strongest In Almost 30 Years 

 *We created the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau that protects customers from financial industry abuses. 

 *To date, banks and corporations have been ordered to pay over $11.7 Billion in relief to consumers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cascadia earthquake finally arrives, levels NW coast

Living here in the PNW and gauging everyone's mood in my office, I think this would be welcomed warmly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add Open Borders and you've got a deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't have clicked that picture. I'm so startled! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's 1.5 million links for you to find out how this is done. Enjoy.
https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant ion=1 espv=2 ie=UTF-8#q=ediscovery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 23:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything at Arby's - one bite and you know that shit is unholy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, a parable about a man of noble birth who is about to travel so that he can be appointed king. As part of the parable, his citizens hate him and try to stop  the appointment. Meanwhile, he gives some slaves  a bit of money to invest on his behalf.

So, in this story, who does the king represent? A noble who has left his home to be among those who hate him but he will soon be anointed King? Could it be Jesus? If not, who? And if it is Jesus, he is indeed talking about himself when he says that those who would not have him rule over them killed in front of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for "pull a Frodo". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we've been producing over 8M barrels/day ourselves:
http://www.eia.gov/dnav/pet/pet_sum_sndw_a_epc0_fpf_mbblpd_w.htm

So, yeah, 30M isn't even 4 days of US production.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEAH, THEY SOUND AWESOME! HEYY, WANT ANOTHER BEER? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want to see Melania start a speech with, "What ever happened to Faye Wray?"

If all the Trumpets shouted back, "She went ape shit!", I could die happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like there's a Title Word thief on the loose in your area as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he said to kill those who won't follow him - Luke 19:27:

 But those enemies of mine who did not want me to be king over thembring them here and kill them in front of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abel didn't have sex with any one - he was dead.

Cain gets explained but that opens multiple plot holes. We all know about the banishment in Gen 4:
 Now you are under a curse and driven from the ground, which opened its mouth to receive your brothers blood from your hand.  When you work the ground, it will no longer yield its crops for you. You will be a restless wanderer on the earth.

But, hey, God's a cool dude so when Cain is worried that "whoever finds me will kill me", God cuts him some slack:
  But the Lord said to him, Not so; anyone who kills Cain will suffer vengeance seven times over. Then the Lord put a mark on Cain so that no one who found him would kill him.

So Cain sets off to wander the Earth until the day he dies, right? Well...
17 Cain made love to his wife, and she became pregnant and gave birth to Enoch. Cain was then building a city, and he named it after his son Enoch. 

1) The world population of the Earth should be 3 - Adam, Eve, and Cain. Why is Cain worried about "other people" finding him and killing him?

2) Wife? Where the hell did Cain find a wife. Must of been one of the "other people".

3) Cain built a city? But he's wandering the world with, now presumably, his wife. Why is he building cities? He's got a curse laid on him to wander. He ain't got time for building no damn cities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one asked you, Hermaninny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, uh, thanks for that mental image, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you are already more clueful than the last Orange Aproned One  I spoke with. My wife and I were looking for a new washer and dryer and asked the guy in appliances (yes, he was definitely an employee.) All he could do is run down the bullet points of features on each of the floor units and even then he missed a couple of key words on them so he was actually worse than no help at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might not be commenting to avoid that.

Or am I? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concentrate? I prefer fresh squeezed, danke schoen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a whole monologue by Leslie Knope on The Joy of Waffles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Robert Altman were still around to direct this, it would fit his style perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now THAT is scary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jesus.

No, Janine Lindemulder.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the wind turbine that looks like a tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civ6, sleep, eat, Civ6, sleep, Monday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so did he have a ruddy complexion or was he excessively intricate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revealing the location of the s'nuke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUDE! Spoiler tag that shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno - I think this "fad" thing is already played out. It's going to fade any generation now...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for "[do the needful](https://cdn.meme.am/instances/500x/67391367.jpg)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 08:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I think my bunny slippers just ran for cover." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dinosaur? LUCKY! I connected the dots and ended up with [this](http://www.supercoloring.com/sites/default/files/silhouettes/2015/05/baphomet-grey-silhouette.svg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'll just go to Siam and get over all of this

Slow down - have you *seen* dirigible fares these days?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Where is the swing?

[Still got it.](https://www.youtube.com/user/CaravanPalace) Gramps might not recognize it but I bet Benny and Cab and all them would be down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, except Chik-Fil-A makes a damn fine sandwich while Yuengling's is just pisswater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the root of all modern journalism

[Root](http://cdn6.bigcommerce.com/s-tu5jcd/product_images/uploaded_images/roots1.jpg?t=1459545482)

[Route](http://www.de-piramide.nl/Contact/PublishingImages/route.gif)

[the root of all modern journalism](http://previews.123rf.com/images/anatolymas/anatolymas1202/anatolymas120200007/12719262-Gold-dollar-sign-3d-image-Isolated-white-background--Stock-Photo.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to America - here's your bible and your assault rifle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least yours is a fun-filled. I got a regular old shit-filled. Feels bad man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B O Driftin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, instead of Lada Gaga doing celebrity guest spots, we'd get Celine Dion :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~Trumpbumming~~ Trumpegging

FTFY
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~Marco Rubio~~ Danny DeVito as Little Boy 2.

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And being a nasty woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 00:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, that's a great ide... waaaaait a minute.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 00:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tribal Village. ANd yeah, those huts look WAY too much like trees in a forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta stand on your toes, boy! I say, STAND ON YOUR TOES! They're goin' over your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm... now I want potatoes and molasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Father of Communism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't be - no breast plate and blonde wig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have to stop reading this at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Reddit is a haven for serial killers? TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How your mouth is linked to your migraines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this certainly is NOT a conversation I expected to be reading this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only works for one branch but I knew a woman years ago who referred to herself as a "recovering Cathoholic". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude just wanted his question mark back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sincerely hope /u/shitty_watercolour does **NOT** show up here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought #6 was Popeye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... get every weed smoker off the couch and to the polls on November 8.

Another thing WA state gets right - we [vote from our couches](https://www.sos.wa.gov/elections/faq_vote_by_mail.aspx).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> weather or knot its write, eye like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She should reply, "Just how certain words are spelt." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.businessinsider.com/donald-trump-tells-rally-crowd-to-vote-on-november-28-2016-10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sen. Sasse

More like Senator Sassy, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to read that twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Nov. 29 rolls around and Trump has a big press conference where everybody is expecting a concession speech but he rambles for 30 minutes and then suddenly unzips his face and Andy Kaufman steps out of the rubber suit he's been wearing all this time, I would be so happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lycos is where it's at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bless his heart" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Trump is [forked](https://www.wikiwand.com/en/Fork_\(chess\)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it has her head off to Houston to join the resistance. Gotta set up the sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had thought on 1st viewing the ship/alien blew up way too easily also. Then I watched it with someone else and brought that up and he proposed an explanation. Remember the big green clouds of gas that it spews out? That stuff is highly flammable. Inside the ship there's big tanks, bladders, or what have you. There's no open flames inside - aliens have better tech that doesn't require something as primitive as fire. So once that improvised molotov cocktail lands inside there - KAFOOM! So MEW didn't take out the thing because of any great skill or because whisky is super explosive. It was pure dumb luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  potatoe

Ah, I see you prefer the Dan Quayle spelling. Good on you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure hope so. The pivot promised it would play catch with me tomorrow, right before it went out for smokes. It's gonna be great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG! He went full "Who are you going to believe - me or your lying eyes?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey guys, I found Bigfoot! It was Bill Clinton the whoooole time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, be fair - his hands are so ^^tiny ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So at some point we can expect The Chewbacca Defense"? If so, I can't wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To quote Marcus Aurelius, jesus christ in a woodchipper ...


I have no way to prove that Marcus Aurelius never said that so I'm going to choose to believe it. TIL.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Who do the cops beat on?

There's always the homeless:
http://www.kiro7.com/news/local/police-responding-to-reports-of-officer-involved-shooting-near-the-jungle/456124427

KIRO sucks but that's what I found on the Interwebs. Local radio actually interviewed other Jungle residents who knew the guy and said he hated weapons of any sort so there's no way he had the knife the cops "found". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I was just [Half Baked](https://youtu.be/hkA9rz-1YoA?t=15). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you'll have to leave the county to drink it legally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But have you ever listened to jazz... *on weed*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloom an hour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does HRC wear Prada? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure [Gary Hart](https://www.wikiwand.com/en/Gary_Hart#/1988_presidential_campaign)'s head is going to explode any minute now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in 9 months, mini baby boom. For the next few days, people will have no power, roads closed, cell phone's loosing charge - but plenty of wine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estoy con ella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... 'Renewables' ... don't require hardworking Americans to work.

Pravda. Everyone knows solar panels can be gathered in the wild and that wind turbines can be grown from 0.375" hex nuts if you fertilize them with shredded tax dollars every quarter. Both just naturally connect themselves to the grid when they are mature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cue tape of /u/dalgeek:


 Milli/Vanilli sang every note of their songs. I've seen video of thousands of people rushing into the streets of NJ to cheer them singing. It was so beautiful. You wouldn't believe how beautiful all the singing and dancing was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 01:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to watch the keynote where they repeatedly have to say "Pen-S" out loud. Mmm...and then what people do with the logo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duterte's way ahead of you on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We're going to build a grow room and Mexico is going to pay for it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's been the M.O. of the anti-cannabis crowd since [at least the '30s](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harry_J._Anslinger#The_campaign_against_marijuana_1930.E2.80.931937). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why 1 cop in Seattle was responsible for [80% of the cannabis citations](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/07/30/seattle-cop-marijuana-tickets_n_5636307.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely saving that for the next "Reddit, what sounds like BS but is actually true?" thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 21:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby - the delicious treat that's as fun to make as it is to eat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of [this guy](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Bruce_Campbell_2014_Phoenix_Comicon_\(cropped\).jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Por que no los dos?] (http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/000/244/457/793.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's been pointed out that if Hillary were accused of raping a minor and that there were two witnesses, that's the only thing the news would talk about. This case though? Nothing at all outside the Internet. Maybe - maybe - when this goes to trial and the witnesses actually testify, this hits the major news outlets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, Reince Priebus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 23:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then [physically abuse 'em after you finish](http://www.snopes.com/2016/06/23/donald-trump-rape-lawsuit/).

 I personally witnessed the one occasion where Mr. Trump forced the Plaintiff and a 12-year-old female named Maria [to] perform oral sex on Mr. Trump and witnessed his physical abuse of both minors when they finished the act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's like the director has been spying on my dreams!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
