<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8579</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know about anyone else but I fell like HE is unbelievabley sexy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 02:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 02:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, May you take to fatherhood like a duck to water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 00:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a pain in the arse! Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 15:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you thank you thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I sell or get rid of additional houses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 14:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the option to buy one so our of curiosity I did think I would have he option to only move certain sims to that house and not the whole family at one time. 

I found out you can't do this as so now I want rid so I can move certain sims into it, can you help? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 12:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woo! Huffllepuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 21:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So here is a University Unisex dorm I redecorated :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 14:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 23:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I post this, forget about it, casually go on r/harrypotter 11 hours later and click on my post which is at the top, only to realise as I'm reading that it's my post 

Thanks :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 23:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok if you don't like it, don't upvote it, the more you upvote the more people are going to see it so stop moaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 23:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok if you don't like it, don't upvote it, the more you upvote the more people are going to see it so stop moaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 23:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I only just realised after I posted...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets go back to Harry Potter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 12:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets go back to Harry Potter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 12:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 22:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh me to, it was awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you who have won 'a year of..' Something, what did you win and how was it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 21:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 01:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My little brother used to do this all the time when he was little! He found, the fact he could actually do this so facinating! Oddly that year for Christmas he got several Spider-Man outfits and web thrower toy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the four 'capitions' for the houses of hogwarts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 13:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I alredy know that ravenclaw is 'wit beyond measure is mans greatest treasure', but what are the rest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 00:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have just finished our second year of college, going to separate universities in September, they don't offer them kind of services at our college but I guess I can go to a doctor and get some advice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 00:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? And that's what I am trying to do but she won't let me as far as she is concerned it is none of my business :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 00:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, it may make things worse between me and her, but I guess I can give it a shot! I just want to get her to at least acknowledge it herself!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 00:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I have been in work and only just got back to my laptop, she loves it, she laps it up because she has never had that sort of attention before, she only just recently had her first boyfriend and first kiss and stuff  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 15:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's finished would you consider putting it on Sims resource? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 01:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I check if my patch for the sims 3 is the latest patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 22:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read that some of you can do online dating and things on your games and I thought it must just come with an expansion pack that I don't have, but then I saw someone say they had it on the sims 3 university, the only expansion pack I have, and someone commented saying it was a patch update so can you guys help me? It would be much appreciated :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 12:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a gif from an epoisode of F.R.I.E.N.D.S when Rachel is left at home alone so she decideds to walk around her apartment naked just because she can :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 02:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really agree with this answer, I am not even 20 yet and even I realise this is a big mistake. You have practically given up very thing just to pay for this ring, I understands it's what she wants but that's all it is and it is really not worth it for the price, you can get cheaper brands as people have already mentioned so why pay this much. The chances are that she'll be so excited about you proposing and the idea of getting married to you and spending the rest of her life with you that she shouldn't care about what ring you got her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 01:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is what I would say to my 'friend' I I could

'Who the hell are you? Like literally I do not recognise you. 15 years of friendship and you think it is alright to talk down to me and treat me like shit everyday?! Yeah you may say it's a joke and at first I laughed along or took it on the chin or whatever but a joke only goes so far! 
I've been there for you nearly all your life, went through all of school together, been with you through everything but suddenly I'm not good enough for you? 
So what you think now that you are pratically anorexic and have evryone wanting you, that you're some kind of untouchable gold shit?! Just because you now have a 'friend' that can buy you all these things, which you flaunt in my face, that you can swag around with your fake posh accent pretending to be someone else?! Yeah I know the real you, you grew up on one of the roughest council estates in the area so loose the fucking accent! 
Do you have any idea how hard it feels to have your best friend of 15 years not take any ounce of interest in you for no apparent reason? To go off with this new friend who you seemed to have replaced me with all because she has money and then to never shut up about her all the bloody time! And I am not the only one annoyed by this I can assure tou of that! 
So Maybe I am a little jealous l, I will admit to that but can you blame me? Seriously. You make time for her but never for me, you don't invite me out anymore even to places with all our other friends, leaving me out. Oh you think you little miss popular dont you? 
Despite me feeling this way though, for now, I still care about you, I would still be there for you whenever you need me despite what I may feel against you!'

That felt good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I'm home alone... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 19:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 01:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just come to the realisation of where Johnny Vegas is from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 20:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because you designed this for your friend does that mean I can't get the same one? Even if I edited it a little bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey there Cowboy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 01:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 04:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me to and I could definatley see the weasleys being the head of any council estate ;) haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 01:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it me or does it half his hair disappears when he leans down?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The smiley face on the front of the barbeque contradicts the fire burning inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 17:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 01:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find myself a space under floorboards and live my life as a borrow would :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 00:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cardboard box! I could do anything with a cardboard box, a lot of doll/ play houses were made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this; http://i.imgur.com/0HjMY8y.jpg in response to googling the doll to find out how this doll would work... Wtf?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iwan Rheon anybody? you have got to love him! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 10:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 10:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is this? :o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So we'be seen a bit of Macklemore on this subeditor but how out some Mr Ryan Lewis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 01:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 01:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna high five this kid so bad! 

Got to have repect for him, he has a point! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually find it very attractive in a guy! It proves he is sweet not to mention it can point out exactly where you are with each other. Girls should note that they shouldn't be afraid to ask either :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i'm currently watching chamber of secrets so this video worked on me haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favourite from the Harry Potter meme centre :') </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 22:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 01:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 18:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I get this into my game?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How about a bit of Lee Pace? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 14:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 00:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A puddle of dark get/green bubbling goop, for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it a stupid question if I ask what OAG means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I find this kind of disturbing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 00:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 14:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know It usually is probably just a glitch in my game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
