<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 05:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! It's very, very hard to remember that my brain is conspiring against me and I needn't listen to it. And, honestly a lot of the time I realize it but don't have the energy to fight with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 05:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't get the period hiatus when I was breastfeeding!! Lucky gals!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually not very fond of sucking, but I love when he licks it with his whole tongue. Like you would an ice cream or popsicle.  :-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FA at butterfly nails (PC). Lines are not as sharp as I would like, but not too shabby considering.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 02:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FA at butterfly nails (PC). Lines not as sharp as I would like, but not too shabby considering.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 02:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I lost my job today... I feel like a failure in all areas of my life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 03:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a warning, this may seem to jump all over the place. I apologize in advance.

I had a breakdown in January 2011 and ended up being in the hospital 3 times that year. 2012 got a little better as I was finally able to figure out a medication combo that worked for me. I still wasn't feeling like I could work, but finally in September an opportunity arose that I couldn't pass up.

Well, that opportunity has now ended. The business was really slow so they had to let a few people go. Here it is, a new year, and 4 days from the two-year anniversary of my breakdown. I really don't want it to happen again, but I'm not so sure I can be strong.

I guess everything happens for a reason because since I've been working, I've been really bad about helping my son with his homework and turning it in on time. Now that I don't work, I will have more time to devote to that. I feel like a terrible mother because in spite of knowing that my son is at risk for retention of first grade, I haven't been able to get my act together and get on top of his homework. It's just such a battle getting him to do it and I just don't have the energy to argue with him.

My ex-husband also dropped on me today that he wants to claim our younger son on taxes this year. He owes me thousands of dollars, doesn't follow our divorce agreement of 50/50, and doesn't pay any child support. He thinks just because he has the younger one 3 days a week and both every other weekend, and buys them clothes that he deserves one for taxes. The best part: He isn't even LEGAL! I checked the law, and it is in my favor, but this causes a rift between us and the last thing I need is to be fighting with him about stupid shit. Don't ask me how he can file taxes because I have no clue. But, he does it. Who knows.

That's my rant/story. Thank you for reading.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 02:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so jealous! But very excited for you. I'm in search of a stand in. :-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 06:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it wasn't my job, but it was someone else's and I was on the receiving end of the "care". My dad had a small manufacturing shop with a secretary and about 6-7 guys working the machines. For reasons I won't go into, I was staying with him in a 5th wheel on the property because I was arguing with my mom. 

I had just had to terminate a pregnancy that morning and went into the office to use the phone (pre-cell phone era) to order a pizza. Well, on my way back out I fainted in the hallway. My dad's secretary had to help me to the toilet, change my pad for me, and then one of the guys had to carry me back to the trailer.

Not my finest moment. The bright side was that she had known me since I was a little girl so there was some familiarity there. I'm still angry at my mom for making me stay with my dad instead of being at home where I could have passed out on the bathroom floor.

TL;DR: Had an abortion, dad's secretary changed my bloody pad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 07:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> December 19th! 13 days and counting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-02 08:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Manuel Ferrara!! This video is sooo hot!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 01:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I learned about depression is you always have these thoughts in your mind that you don't deserve to feel the way you do because other people have it worse. But you know what? STOP COMPARING!! Your pain is just as real as anyone else's. Don't minimize it because it will just make you feel worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 22:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't use it as a replacement, just a "supplement". Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 22:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be wrong of me, a born and raised Californian, if I said I completely understand? I lived in Texas for 6-7 months, and my sister lives in Savannah, GA which I have visited a couple times. Those places made me realize that California has gone to shit. All of my friends and family are here, but if I could I would move out of state now. One day it will happen for sure.

I don't know what to tell you as you are in a very sticky situation. Good luck in whatever path you choose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 19:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so me. I've fantasized about having cancer. Or getting into a terrible accident. It's not ungrateful, or stupid or selfish. It's DEPRESSION. It's not you thinking these things, it's the depression making you think these things.

I know it's hard, but try not to make yourself feel guilty for the thoughts that you have. They are not you. They manifest from a debilitating illness that is a vicious cycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 19:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious. Do you find that mushrooms help with your depression? I'm on meds which have been working, but I have severe SAD so I'm spiraling downwards right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
