<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico compilation: lots of aquatic life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 02:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 02:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The acting is still atrocious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the universe is big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 14:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is why a lot of tentpole blockbuster movies fail, because they treat characters as secondary to story, plot and set pieces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 18:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. The story was over by season 4. The rest was just an abomination, kind of like what Showtime did to Weeds, stretching too much out of too little. Both shows were beacons that drew people to the network though, so in the end they did their "job", even if they were less than perfect from a thematic or story perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same with electric bikes. They're illegal unregistered vehicles and there are thousands of them on the streets making things unsafe. What we don't need are more unregistered people zooming around under mechanical power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 03:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about electric bicycles? Those should definitely be illegal/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 01:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very poorly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 14:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be an effective strategy if they were willing to stick with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 02:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a calming, relaxed instructor helps. Also, remember it's just breathing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 00:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something you've never done before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 18:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Multiple times ehhh. Ok guess my memory is flawed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 15:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mulder using a cell phone is out of character. Completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 15:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The infuriating thing about Obama is he'll do things like visit prisons while helping to preside over a system of incarceration that is inherently racist (War on Drugs).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 20:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish more studio execs would get the concept that less is quite often more when it comes to posters ... but most tend to fill each and every square millimeter of available space with whatever they think is going to help sell the film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or those who commit suicide by shooting themselves twice in the head?

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gary_Webb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 01:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I goofed was third dive. And good to know about black tips. I was swimming towards them behind the guy with the camera but I didn't feel threatened, they didn't seem to want anything to do with me or the rest of the divers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 01:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone else on the dive took the video but I was about even with him when we saw the sharks...SO AMAZING! My instructor was jealous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 01:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, video was made by another guy on the dive. I definitely could not have handled a camera on a certification dive -- breathing alone underwater was enough of a challenge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On my third open water PADI certification dive -- Black Tipped Reef Sharks ... needless to say I'm hooked! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 04:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 04:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great video! Nicely done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 04:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fought with a prof in grad school who insisted relatable was not a word. I argued back that it was citing the oed etc. and she argued back that it was a heinous word in academic circles. In the end it didn't matter much but prof bias should be culled from the system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could say what's the point of a bike lane if cars routinely park in them and pedestrians wander through them without looking and mothers with strollers stop in them to chat...it just goes on and on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 02:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 14:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only the media were taking Sanders seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 13:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 14:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Procedure is procedure. Don't like it, get it changed, but handcuffing suspects is procedure. So is using lethal force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 18:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People should learn from the story of RU -- don't fucking talk about dark net markets, how much you're making or how to do it. Publicity is not your friend, not in these days of the UPS (ultimate police state). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's new is maybe people are thinking about this in ways that aren't 100% constrained by ancient, racist prejudiced blinders. It's a shame we're limited to just expanding our collective horizons with "WEED" but there are plenty of other uses for the substances that we've demonized that could have medicinal applications. We're just still too small-minded, too provincial and hierarchical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're reading a 1000+ page book you probably should care what the author of that book thinks, especially about reading it. But hey, whatever man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking kidding me? Wallace isn't hard to read and you don't need a study guide, just the determination to get through it, to read and think like a human being. The last thing Wallace would want you to do it read a fucking study guide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what makes Wallace a great writer, his ability to make communities out of those people most trapped within the limiting walls of their own selves like addicts, those with mental illnesses, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never write anything in a professional email you wouldn't want published. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 03:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie is going to bomb. Hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stannis is a deluded by the Red God's Cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This from the transparency disinfectant President. Remember this in the coming election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no lines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an inspired casting decision by Netflix. BRAVO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koyaanisqatsi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't fucking eat at chain restaurants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 04:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US stopped being free after 9-11. Time to wake up, folks. Your freedom is a dead dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 14:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck with the bull, you get the horns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life without parole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 04:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody is going to do that and at bottom, that wouldn't help RU in any way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 03:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL only children on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 03:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should be top comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 22:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex wife is one who wasn't very devout until her mother died and then she it became more of a thing for her, thinking it was the only way she would ever get to see her mother again. It ended up becoming a wedge between us because I just cannot wrap my rational brain around some of their core beliefs or rather their core interpretations of the Bible. At any rate, good on her for getting out but it's not that easy for my ex without abandoning her mother -- or rather confronting her fears of abandoning her mother, and it's not that easy for her daughter, who has been taught its also the only way to see her nana again ... through adherence to this JW indoctrination spiel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 22:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The owls are not what they seem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 00:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. It's almost like you're not being punished for reproducing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 13:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the media has always led us to war. It's just that w/r/t Iraq the process was so transparent to anyone who cared. Turns out lots and lots of people don't care, or would rather not know, just like with the Snowden revelations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 13:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't look for meaning in holidays created by companies to foster consumption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 13:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who has been working a 40-hour work week? I've been doing between 45-60 for the last decade and that doesn't look to change. In fact, seems I'll just be doing more work. For less pay but the alternative isn't feasible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 13:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's what he said at the time, but it was also to add some detailed closure for those fans who needed more closure to the ending of the last book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 05:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was terrified of everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie is the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 01:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about JWs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out Alaskan Klee Kai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 13:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup. FDA approved drugs kill thousands a year and don't even get me started on the FDA approval process, which is a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 03:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well, because you say it, then surely it must be so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using Sir usually works for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 15:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck with the bull, you get the horns." And a picture of JFK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 15:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always well said, Mr. Lair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 14:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  South Gate also, according to Engle's report, anticipates future forfeiture revenue in the budgeting process... This should be criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. These asshats need to realize their outdated business models are outdated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 20:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some are. And from what I've heard, withdrawls are working, they're just delayed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone just needs to calm the fuck down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But nothing. Thanks for the post, anything to help counter the rising tide of FUD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 23:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's something. Not that I've been a doubting Thomas but ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is can anyone but that one guy withdraw?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
