<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9615</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 08:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a TWD whore. I don't care, show me Rick eating cereal for 50 minutes and I'll watch that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 03:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JDM is cool as Negan but I hope they add more depth to his character  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm late and I just got done watching the episode. One thing I noticed is that when Ken is on his laptop to masturbate the screen was casting a sort of pink/red light, and it automatically made me think that he was on redtube or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit your friends would go to Justice Park and film with their phones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with the artwork? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoever draws these is getting lazier and lazier. I remember in the earlier issues Tony Monroe made each character's drawing unique, but in the older ones some of them look exactly the same, although Charlie Adlard used to draw very good panels . I remember reading past issue 100 and I swear Aaron looks exactly like Rick in one panel. In one of the most recent ones there's a panel where Dwight is basically Rick's module with one half of his face burned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does Dwight look like Rick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrew Lincoln just keeps getting hotter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're already infected, so it doesn't matter either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say fuck The Broker too, but damn isn't that man likeable. It's like Negan in TWD, someone you love to hate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 04:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me say that I only included Fargo because of the criminal aspect- people getting in deep shit. 

But everything else is entirely different. Fargo has a dark comedy aspect to it that makes it unique despite touching on some heavy issues and moments of intense drama. But the atmosphere of Quarry is entirely different, but the drama is there. 

It's very grim, more like True Detective in that aspect. Or Training Day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the last episode is basically the length of a movie and it wraps everything well but it still leaves enough in case it gets a second season. 

But yeah it has an ending if that's what you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how they sparkled some posible future plotlines here and there but it was still written like it could be a series finale. That's how you do a finale the right way. I'll be so happy if it gets a second season though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quarry had one of the best finales I've seen this year and nobody is talking about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like crime shows like BB, Fargo, True Detective and or just crime drama in general you owe it to yourself to watch this show. It is set in 1972 and it follows a vietnam veteran who can't get a job and becomes a hitman. The premiere is very good and things get spicy towards the end, and the following 6 episodes are awesome although some people said it dragged a little. I didn't think it dragged, mostly because the show is much more character-driven than say, Banshee. But it still has riveting action scenes that are somewhat reminiscent of Tarantino.

But it was the last episode that really blew me away. It was 1 hour and twenty minutes, and the pace was fantastic throughout. The episode has a single shot sequence that, if this had been a Netflix or HBO show instead HBO's branch of Cinemax, it would be talked about a lot more. 

Please check it out. You won't regret it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love, love, love that entire sequence. It was so well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it worked out for this one. The last episode was the lenght of two episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Broker is an awesome character. The same man who had an asshole killed and saved a bunch of children was...this, a man who ordered the slaughter of innocents for some Heroin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quarry - 1x08 "nc chy  mn" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 05:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone comes to this subreddit without having seen the premiere they deserve to have the show spoiled for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you wouldn't be a sobbing mess if your family was being tormented in front of you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've seen 6 seasons of brutal deaths, why are these people outraged now? Didn't they see Noah get his face ripped off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love reading this in Negans voice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the bad episodes are those filler ones where they mainly concentrate on character development. I don't mind them, although some of them tend to be boring. 
 the show isn't  perfect  (the dumpster fiasco was stupid and the cliffhanger atrocious) but the show still delivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Walking Dead. Getting ready to watch Westworld now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stop being passionate about something you enjoy!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for letting us know that you do not care about this show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This episode was just something else. It brought up raw emotions, uneasiness, rage, sadness. What a roller-coaster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cliffhanger was dumb but I would be lying if I said this episode didn't bring strong emotions out of me. Damn. Can't wait for the rest of the season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shot at the end of them sitting at the table fucking killed me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? It ended up being intense and emotional as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 months ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kind sir! I'll give you a passing thought as I light my space shuttle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.. what to do what to do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Discard the coke then. I trust Xanax and Weed is enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody started doing drugs yet? I have an assortment of drugs that I will be doing to enhance the experience. Cocaine, yes? Weed is a most. Xanax is a given. A few cigarettes here and there (not too many though!) Alcohol? Nah, that makes me feel sick. 

So, cocaine to start with at like 7. A cigarette. 10 min before the show starts I pop a Xanax and smoke a blunt. Does anybody else have any suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 18:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The governor has an eye patch too and long hair. Dead giveaway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, no. East of Eden is amazing, but I don't think you realize just how many amazing books there are out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's my favorite rapper I hope he comes back to America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna inject alcohol into my anus, smoke crushed hamster bones and watch the episode when I come down from the high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Walking Dead: Surrounded 360 Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the last episode this Sunday before the premiere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. There's nothing left to her that I even care about. There never was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hay tiendas de libros en Puerto Rico? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desde que cerraron Borders en Plaza compro mis libros en Amazon. No hay una en la isla con libros americanos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like if the creators give in to these demands it may hamper the story a bit. Season 1 was almost perfect. They must adapt the same philosophy of not dealing with terrorists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone asks about your (shady) past, what's a good answer that will satisfy them yet prompt no more questions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 08:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MIND=BLOWN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you mean you haven't watched the previous 2 episodes? Da fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 09:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a social thing. It helps have a better time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do the creepypasta creators get paid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 08:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I just heard about this show and I loved the first ep. Very creepy. I've never read a creepypasta though, but they're like stories random people have wrote on the Internet right? This wasn't made by a book author? Sorry if  don't under the concept </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 08:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noice catch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 08:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. That would make his storyline meaningless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 08:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either that, or the new storyline was programmed that way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 08:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A picture of Bernard. Did you forget there's a huge thread where people are discussing this? Post there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 08:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I need more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
