<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2851</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually wrote that article before moving 1500km north,   I haven't found any new diving spots yet, but I love seeing what everyone else is finding (  eating my heart out *LOL*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly positive, one guy being all "r/poverty is that way"    a few who say that eating something they found in a dumpster is beyond what they're comfortable with

when I originally wrote this about 5 years ago, I posted it on the poor skills community on Livejournal   got SO MANY negative replies, I basically stopped trying to help at that point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ack!  Thanks for pointing that out, it's fixed now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumpster Diving - A How To </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Originally posted on /r/frugal, it seems there's enough interest for me to post here as well  :D

I wrote this years ago, but it's still as useful now as it was then   it's getting to be that time of year, where it's cold enough to help keep the smells down :D

This is an awesome resource for all sorts of things   can be a fun hobby

I live in a small-ish town, so I'm not lucky enough to have very many dumpsters to dig through, but the ones I've found are practical goldmines. At one point, I was spending $50 a month to feed 3 adults because of the food I was finding

My main problem in my town is that all the big grocery stores have compactors. But there's other places that sell groceries

Although a lot of what I find is food, it's because I don't have a good selection of stores. I've been doing it for a few years,   thought I'd share some of the tips I've learned


Bring a flashlight. Seriously, as well-lit as some dumpsters are, you'll want a flashlight to shine around inside the dumpster. Along with this one, go at night. I usually don't go out until after midnight,   I try for Sunday nights, or weekdays, so there's less people to see me. I'm not ashamed, I just don't want other people catching on to the awesome hauls :D

The very best time to dumpster dive for food is the night before a holiday. If stores will be closed on Monday, they'll throw out anything that would go bad on Sunday.

Wear clothes you don't care about. They'll probably get dirty/rusty. They may get torn.

You really shouldn't get in the dumpsters. I've been known to break this rule, but it was a special circumstance (the dumpster was emptied daily,   I could see the bottom of the dumpster, so I knew I wouldn't step on something   break an ankle or any other surprises. I also took along a small stepstool so I could get in   out without hurting myself,   a friend to help in case I got into something I couldn't get out of). There are a lot of reasons to not get into a dumpster though,   the one I'm most concerned about is the fact that a half full dumpster is half full of unknown things - you put your foot down   you don't know what's under it. As soon as you put some weight on it, you could sink straight down to the bottom, scraping your leg against broken glass, or landing wrong   spraining your ankle. Most of the time, it's not worth it.

Don't act like you're doing something wrong. If someone sees you, don't worry about it. Know the laws in your area. In my area, if it's in a dumpster, it's considered no one's property   is free game. Police or security guards can ask me to leave the property, as technically I'm trespassing because the dumpster is on private property, but they can't do anything more provided I comply. I've only been approached by the cops once, I was behind a building, they saw me drive in,   when I said I was looking for boxes, they told me to be careful   left me alone.

Keep a log. I make a note of what days I go to each dumpster, how full each one is,   if I get anything out of it. The days   fullness give me a decent idea of when the dumpsters are emptied out, so I can plan my route without wasting time. The loot log is more for my own interest, but if I've been going to a dumpster for a few months   it NEVER pays out, I won't go out of my way to go to it on any sort of regular basis, although I never fully cut a dumpster out because you never know when you'll get an awesome haul

If it's locked, leave it. Check every so often, as sometimes someone will leave it unlocked, or sometimes they just stop locking it all together. If it looks locked (chain   a locked lock), double check - a lot of dumpsters I've thought were locked actually weren't. If there's a sign nearby that says 'no tresspassing', then that's your warning that the person who owns the property doesn't want people on it. It's probably not worth it

If you're looking for food, cold nights   winter nights are the best times. I've gotten ice cream out of a dumpster,   it was still fully frozen (  not melted   refrozen). That is why I have no problems eating other perishable foods I find, as long as the temperature has been fridge-cold (at least) for the last little while (the dumpster I actually get in is the one I like getting food out of, as I know it hasn't been in there for more than 24 hours) Non-perishable food is good any time of the year, provided the packaging hasn't been damaged in a way that would harm the food inside. Expiry dates on canned goods   whatnot... this will probably bring up some debate. Personally, I'd eat them, as long as they weren't well past their date (I got a LOT of pop out of one dumpster recently,   I can taste the difference between the expired stuff   the non expired stuff, but there's really nothing wrong with it). Hell, when I was younger   poorer, I had canned goods that were probably older than the stuff I was pulling out of the dumpster. But with food, use your own discretion. I realize not everyone is going to be comfortable eating food that was in a dumpster,   that's okay. I don't have a problem with it though,   I just want to share what I know :)

Don't look at dumpster diving as something you HAVE to do because you don't have money. Have fun with it! To me, it's like a treasure hunt. When I was young, I always wanted to be an archaeologist,   now I'm digging through the rubble to find the awesome stuff underneath that no one knows about! it's also helping the planet, as this stuff isn't going to the dump (the pop bottles are now going to get recycled instead of just thrown in the dumpster). It may not be much, but every little bit helps


Other things I've found in dumpsters: Webcams, clothing, hair products, printers/scanners, pens, post it notes, cash register, plastic storage containers, plates, books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually make overnight oatmeal with bananas - mash up a banana, add a big tbs of peanut butter, some milk, flax seeds, chia seeds,   oats, then stir it all together (you want it to seem very wet, it'll thicken overnight)
shove it in the fridge   leave it for 8 hours.  It's really good,   you can get really creative with it  :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never asked permission, the laws where I live make it so i can help myself until asked to leave (provided there's no sign)
I would think that most businesses would frown on people digging around in their dumpsters,   probably lock them if they knew.  A lot of people aren't that courteous,   will leave a giant mess, plus there's the whole liability thing I imagine

I have anxiety, so I've never asked about unsellable goods, although I know some places that do that sort of thing, it's usually smaller stores (locally owned chain stores seem to be best)

Not as important as you'd think.  There were 3 good dumpsters within a 20 minute walk of my place,   I had a wheelie cart that I used for groceries,   I'd just drag it along with me on some nights.  Depends on where you live/what's near you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.snopes.com/vaping-causes-popcorn-lung/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I wrote this, I lived in a small town in Southern Ontario, Canada
my bf   I went together, it's more fun with a friend, plus it's a peace of mind thing as well (personally, I wouldn't go alone, but I'm a 5'3" female, so it's not like I could even see into most dumpsters *LOL*)
It depends on where the dumpster is, but usually I'd park in front of the business I'm diving at,   just cart the stuff over (or if it's a large haul/something heavy, I'd put it to the side of the dumpster   just pull up to put it in the car, then leave)

Most dumpsters I only spent about 10 minutes at, but there was one (for an office supply store) that I'd crawl up on the side of it   dig for anywhere up to an hour.  As long as no one seems to be giving me the stink eye, I'd stay there rooting around  :D
There was no other business or residence facing it, so I felt comfortable hanging out there while I poked around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been keeping mine in thick wax-lined bags in the freezer for years   have never had a problem.  Maybe it's the way it's stored more than where it's kept? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumpster Diving - A How To </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 23:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beans have a long shelf life, once it's been ground you'll want to keep it in the fridge or the freezer to keep it fresh longest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I followed a copycat recipe, but I think the problem was the matcha powder I used, because the flavour itself was off (still good, but not the same as Starbucks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
