<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3285</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously hope not, I don't know anything about parallel universes, and being in one would only be more confusing. I can look into it, but I don't even know what to look for. Thanks for your help though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look man, I don't need your insults right now. I got enough on my plate. In our time of technology I don't need to memorize my wife's phone number anymore. The call list is a good idea though. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wife and Kids Never Existed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Click Here To Read Part 2!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/641qml/my_wife_and_kids_never_existed_part_two/) 

I dont know where to start. Frankly, I dont want to start at all, but I have no one else to turn to besides an anonymous board on Reddit; filled to the brim with people looking to get their next fear fix. Well, this is perfect for you, because Im fucking terrified.

My wife, Christina, and I met around 9 years ago. We had the whole cliche of falling in love almost instantly and getting married only after 2 months of meeting. At least I thought we did, but thats for another time.

About a year into our marriage we decided to have kids. We had a girl, Myla, and then a boy, Attis, one year later. I loved them more than anything else in the world. I would spend every available second I could with them. Hell, sometimes Id even call off work and lie to them saying school was cancelled just to be with them.

At least thats what I remember doing. 

I got up and began my usual routine. I rolled over to find Christinas side of the bed empty, which was weird. She always slept in later than me. I got up and walked into the kitchen and started brewing a cup of coffee. I looked at the clock on the microwave and saw it was 7:55AM. 

"Crap!" I thought. Judging by the fact that the kids werent even up yet, I figured they were going to be late for school. I rushed over to their room to get them up and dressed. I put on my goofy-dad grin and began opening the door. Alright you lazy bums, ti- I stopped, completely shocked at what I discovered. The kids werent in their beds, but that wasnt the weird part. There were no beds. There was nothing in the room that belonged to the kids. 

I dropped my mug, and splattered black coffee all over the wooden floor. Thats right. The WOODEN floor, the kids always had carpet, theyve had it for years. Now all there was was wooden. A pool table sat in the center of the room, the corresponding pool cues in a rack resting on the wall. An old arcade machine (Galaga)  sat in the corner of the room. There were pictures of bands, a few paintings, and a calendar featuring some blonde woman with her legs spread across the roof of a Camaro scattered across the walls.

I was at a loss for words. I didnt know what to do. Then I remembered that I had some family photos (another cliche) hanging up in my living room. I shuffled my way over there and gazed just above the TV, where the pictures were hanging. I only found a huge plasma tv, an Xbox One, and a Star Wars poster occupying the space of printed family memories. 

I was freaking out at this point. Tears began to well up in my eyes. I had to call Christina. I opened my phone, pounded in my passcode and punched in her phone number. My heart sank, the phone number wasn't registered. I desperately clicked onto my contacts to find her. She wasnt there. She wasnt fucking there.

I scrolled through my pictures, videos, even Facebook. All I could find were pictures and videos my college buddies and I at bars and the occasional strip club, nothing of my wife and kids.

I dont know what to do guys. I dont want to tell anyone, theyll think Im crazy. I am freaking out. I KNOW that they exist, Im not a lunatic. I need all the help I can get, and would accept advice from anyone at this point. Please help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doge was the same age as me. Coincidence? I think not.

F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool man, you got this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Relapsed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I relapsed both today and yesterday after my first streak of about a week. I decided that it's best to not focus on how much progress I lost and to continue moving forward. I definitely need support, and it will indeed be a struggle, but I know I can eventually beat this addiction!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, I wish that was me  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's said stuff like this before (mostly when I watch horror movies) but never to this degree. The first few times were funny, but now it's just plain creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Think My Cockatoo is Possesed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I start I want to provide some insight to my situation:

A cockatoo is much like a parrot in that it can learn languages. The average cockatoo only learns about 20 to 30 words, however my pet cockatoo, Chance, can memorize what seems like an infinite amount. There will be times where Chance will memorize entire commercials and repeat them back to me. It used to kind of freak me out at first, I mean who wouldnt be a little disgruntled hearing your bird talk to you about animal abuse? But I eventually got used to it. Ill be cooking in the kitchen, or doing chores, and Chance will recite the weather, or some lines from Game of Thrones, and Ill think nothing of it. In fact, Chance has been what youd call a delightful pet. 

Things started to change last night.

When I got home from work, I heard Chance squawking and speaking gibberish as he normally 
does. Except this time, he said a phrase I hadnt heard before.

Mommy Help! Im drowning!

While I am a woman, and certainly like to think of Chance as my feather-baby sometimes, he has never actually called me mommy. I hadnt left the TV on since I got home, but I just chalked it up to Chance combining words, despite how creepy it was.
 
After ordering some Chinese takeout, I flipped on the news. It was the usual stuff. Someone was trying to pass a new bill, an unfortunate terrorist attack happened in the Middle East, but then the newscasters presented something else. Something that still sends shivers down my spine. A 9 year old boy had drowned in a public pool in Louisiana. Chance piped up and said

I told you so. I told you so.

He repeated I told you so probably 4 or 5 times before he finally stopped and began falling asleep. This was weird. This was very weird. 

After a few hours of other things not worth mentioning here, it was finally time for bed. Some people recommend locking your bird up at night, but it makes Chance upset so I leave him out. I dont mind having to clean up the occasional bird dropping, and plus it keeps him quiet. 

I felt my eyelids grow heavy, and was seconds away from falling asleep when I heard Chances wings flap over and his feet land on me. Before I had anytime to question his actions he muttered

Its your fault you know.

What? I groaned, not really in the mood to talk to Chance.

He drowned because of you.

This was beyond weird. I was about to say something else (I dont remember what) when he took off saying

Ill see you in hell! Ill see you in hell!

Thats all he says to me now. Whenever I go up to him and start petting him, Im met with Ill see you in hell instead of the usual happy chirps I receive. I left the TV on all day yesterday in hopes that hed pick up a different phrase, but have had no such luck.

I dont know what to do guys. If any of you have any recommendations, theyd be much appreciated. I will make an update as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, I know how hard it cam be to resist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, I'm 16 and just started my efforts to no longer masturbate. The best way to do it is to distract yourself from it. Whenever you get the urge or even thought, immediately move into doing something else. Whether it's video games, exercise, playing/listening to music, etc. You can do this man. I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I no longer watch pornography, and try to avoid anything that could be potentially mature. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm New </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 16 year old male and I have recently just started my efforts to no longer masturbate. I am currently on my 5th day of not doing so. I have a constant urge, and while I am very good at practicing self-control, it is becoming increasingly difficult. Long story short, I need help. What are some techniques or strategies I could employ to help get rid of or reduce the temptation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His head weighs 10 pounds and he's about to get his head chopped off by ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NORMIES BTFO REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
