<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3492</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coal mining? In Cleveland?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent! Nice catch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darwin Day Dinosaurs 7 pm tonight at the Euclid Tavern! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight at Euclid Tavern, celebrate Charles Darwin's birthday a few days early, and hear a paleontologist from the Cleveland Museum of Natural History talk about dinosaur tracks!

7 pm, Euclid Tavern near Case Western.
Presented by the Institute for the Science of Origins. 

https://www.facebook.com/events/1765351417050354/?ti=cl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the website:

DISCOVERY DAY

Enjoy free general admission on Martin Luther King Jr. Day!


WHERE
Cleveland Museum of Natural History, 1 Wade Oval Drive, Cleveland OH 44106


WHEN
1/16/2017 at 10:00 AM


PRICES
Members: Free
Non-members: Free


We're revving up for a great day of discovery! Visitors receive FREE general admission from 10am to 4pm on Monday, January 16. Curators will talk with guests outside of their labs and take out specimens that are not usually on display. Visitors can enjoy mini Shafran Planetarium shows for $1/person and participate in amazing demonstrations with scientists and students from Case Western Reserve University. Guests can meet Clevelands neighborhood wildlife in special live animal presentations, and make a craft to take home in Smead Discovery Center on the Museum's lower level.


The Rainey Chorus, featuring local children from 5 to 14 years of age, will give short performances at 11am and 12pm in Murch Auditorium. Their selections will honor Martin Luther King Jr., the Civil Rights Movement, and the season.


$10 flat rate parking in the Museum garage. University Circle, Inc. will provide free shuttle service to participating organizations. Parking will fill up fast! We recommend getting here early to beat the crowd.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *Free admission* at the Cleveland Museum of Natural History this coming Monday, January 16! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
