<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use paint stripper and 100 grit to get all of the rust and paint off. Then sand using 600-800 grit until the hood is smooth. Next, ensure that your paint area is tarped off. 

Use 2-3 coats of primer, wet sanding with 800-1000 grit in between. If you really want to use spraypaint, I used a $5 Bondo gun attachment for my bike project and it worked like a charm. Proper method is ensuring that the paint is applied in parallel directions in light coats, and that the gun never stops moving while spraying (spray in "strokes").

The most critical part is making sure that you are not impatient between coats, and if there is a run make sure to let it dry and sand that spot down to level. I'd recommend 1-2 hours in between coats with the primer, and a day per coat between paint, all the while sanding in between each coat.

Again, patience is key, and it is possible to make it look good if you keep that in mind. A good paint job should take around 3-4 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 15:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I've never really suffered from bad service there, and I go a couple of times a month...must've hit a bad patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 14:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...a majority of these aren't in Detroit...I mean some of those are over a half hour out. Might as well throw Blackstone in Flint on the list as well.

Underrated food establishments that are legitimately in Detroit:

Detroit Beer Company - Very good bar food to accompany great beer

Louie's Lounge - Just opened 2 weeks ago, phenomenal food hand delivered by the chef

Foran's Grand Trunk Pub - Best brunch in the city, bottomless Bloody Mary's are excellent

Traffic Light - Well-made food

Greenwich Tavern - Hole in the wall with decent food but prices that are straight out of the 1950's

Town Pump Tavern - One of the more underrated burgers in town

24grille - One of only two places that has ever made food that makes the hair on my neck stand up. A little pricey but worth it.

Anyone else with favorite legit Detroit spots?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well placed advertising, spokeo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 00:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 17:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannot unsee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 01:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. I have one and I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 01:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shinola Runwell, 47mm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 17:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I really enjoyed the process. I have a friend talking me into doing one for her at this point, so I just might have another one to post soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 16:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I wanted something unique and classic. I thought it was a nice detail in that regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wanted.....WAAAANTEEEED....dead or aliiiiiiive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. Hanson would probably settle for ".500 or bust" though...Always felt bad for the guy watching him make everything year after year for no particular reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 17:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one actually believes this is really Jason Hanson, do they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my search results have two pages, thus spelling "Google" correctly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 16:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 14:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice, I'll be sure to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 03:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATE: So the ex saw the post and texted me, trying to get me thinking about her again. All I could do is laugh. 

Thank you very much, bike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 02:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that...poor guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 22:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, no worries. Come say hi if you see me out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The places where you can have an entire block of houses to yourself would not be the places I would have fake guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 22:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the best bourbon I've ever had (so damn smooth), and the RP burned nicely. I'm glad you can appreciate the selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 21:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am genuinely flattered!. You literally put a smile on my face. Thank you; I'm glad you enjoyed the album! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'm glad you like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 20:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This bike had a lot of sentimental value to me. It has been in my family for nearly 30 years and I grew up riding it. Money can't put a price on it.

From what I understand as well, older Schwinn's were high quality bikes. I don't know what other beat up bike that was free and readily available could show more promise.

I appreciate the compliment looks-wise, and I can understand your opinion about the bike itself. Thanks for taking a look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 20:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I'm going to make my own parts diagram with my own names. Seems like some people would find that amusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 20:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, I'll have to take a look into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 20:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I have some slight residue on the metal rail, but nothing else otherwise, luckily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh. I would like to avoid having to involve using this as a trigger in the future, but thanks for the compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It worked out about as well as I could have expected. Gorilla Tape is the real deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sanded prior to removing the stripe. The base (red) was 1000, then covered. Primed, painted, and sanded the topcoat base color (steel) with 1000 as well. I wanted to sand it prior to removing the stripe to avoid sanding too deep and ruining the crisp lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 17:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I use tin foil for a lot of my painting projects. It's malleable and can fit into areas where a tape mask doesn't work (EX masking off tail lights on a car without needing to take them off, just slide the foil into the gap). I like the result of the bolts as well. Thanks for looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 17:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I'm sorry I caused you to yell at my abuse of the logo, but I'm glad you enjoyed the end product. Sounds like you have quite the collection! 

Can you potentially confirm my model? Endless Google searches have done me no good. I've heard Cruiser Supreme and Sidewinder, but there are variations of both that cause me to guess either way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 17:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good looking out, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 17:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. It would be foolish to not lubricate every component that is supposed to move. I was thorough in this process, I just didn't happen to capture images of the whole lubrication process. The closest I got to mentioning this is that I purchased chain lube during one of my shopping trips; should have carried that thought out, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 17:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had a space that wasn't my apartment and proper tools, I'd definitely consider it. 

I'm not sure, I haven't checked the market yet, but my dad told me the backstory on how he got this one, which I found amusing. Apparently he found it chained to a fence in a random front yard for sale. He bought it for 20 bucks sometime in the 80's.

This was the bike I grew up riding and abusing as a kid, so it has some sentimental value to me. That and the "hip" custom bike culture in Detroit is fascinating. I felt that fixing this one up was a win-win. 

I don't have the energy at this point to do another one, but I may as my biking experience evolves. Thanks for your kind comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 16:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a beautiful area up there, I'll be sure to do so. Same applies if you ever swing on by the Detroit area. A different type of trail, but great in their own respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 16:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting; I've never used a hook wrench before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 16:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 15:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've made too many mistakes during past projects when diving into the "unknown" of mechanical workings to try and mess with those parts without understanding the assembly process. Thanks for the compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 15:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just joined, I'll be checking it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 15:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted. Any feedback is appreciated, and thanks for the explanation. I hope you enjoyed the "restoration" aspect at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, I'm glad I could make you laugh with my ignorance. Thanks for looking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is excellent haha. I could imagine the guys at the shop's faces if I started calling the parts by these names. Thanks for the laugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words, friends. I have always tried to be descriptive and thorough in my writing, so I'm glad you enjoyed the (borderline over-) elaboration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't have minded that, but the different colors of the welded areas bothered me. I also enjoyed the painting process. Extending the time of the project was beneficial to me, personally. Thanks for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad someone else likes the logo haha, that has been the main suggestion for change. Thank you for the kind words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, if you have the help available, use it right? Thank you for looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much, it's been a joy to see such (mostly) kind words from everyone. If you end up doing a project, I'd love to see it here in the future! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I have about 100 more, but I needed to shave the album down for fear of disinterest and sticking to the main points. Thank you for your time in viewing my album, glad you enjoyed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good news is I was so engrossed by the project that I pretty much have forgotten all about it by the time I finished it. Thanks for the compliment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't considered it, but now I'm curious. Where does one go to get their painted projects baked? An auto shop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, any advice on where to start is appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My neighbors spend almost all day and night smoking weed, so I don't think they were worried about much of anything. Thanks for looking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had gloves, but the wrong kind apparently because that stuff burned right through (lessons learned). However, as irritating as it was, the pain vanished as soon as water touched it, so it wasn't that terrible in the end.

Thanks for looking and I appreciate the feedback! I am admittedly not a skilled enough painter to accent the logo or I'd consider it, but I'm satisfied with the monochrome look, so I'm not too worried about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Schwinn has lost it's clout (even as an outsider I understood that, all of the department store racks are covered in them), but it would feel disingenuous to me to use different brands regardless of their drop off since Schwinn's heyday. 

I still don't know much about bikes (especially nomenclature) but I've always known how to build things. Thanks for looking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bikes are simpler than they look, to be honest. The "clutch", or as many fellow redditors have pointed out to me, the derailleur was two bolts, one utilized by the rear wheel and the other attached to a spacer-type nut in the frame. 

The brake lines were one screw each line. The assembly of the brake lines is more difficult than the disassembly, but it's fun to calibrate them to your comfort level with the throw on the levers once you get the hang of it.

Thanks for looking, and it was definitely fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 14:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends where you are looking. Downtown, Midtown, Woodbridge, Indian Village, Corktown, New Center, and the Boston Edison district (soon) cost an arm and a leg. That's why I want a house when my lease is up. However, I do rather enjoy the rooftop pool at my building... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate you taking the time to try and teach me the proper terminology. I'll be looking to educate myself on the culture, and subsequently, the nomenclature next so this is very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No clear coat, but I wanted to keep the contest in the paints to a maximum. I figured I'd rather have to repaint if it starts to fail rather than being disappointed with a clear coat, so it's still on the table but not done.

I did polish the pieces I brushed for that exact reason. Thanks for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When there's a will, there's a way right? I'm enjoying the bike, and not in the least concerned with the breakup. 

Thanks for looking!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to agree with you regarding the bolts,considering it's a high traffic usage area. Thanks for the suggestion! Hope you enjoyed the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 12:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First joker on the thread. There's always one.

I was meticulous in ensuring the actual apartment was not damaged in the process.Abuses his apartment lease to overhaul a bicycle = check.

I was careful to ensure the apartment was not damaged during the process.

Primary residence in a inconvenient high rise = check.

"Inconvenient" is in the eye of the beholder. I can walk or ride to anything I need, what's inconvenient about it? 

Uses cigars and alcohol to try and be cool = check.

People celebrate in their own ways. My picture was selected by Cigar Aficionado magazine for use, if that is any consolation.

Crappy full tower attached to TV = check.

Haven't bought a tower that suits my tastes yet. Maybe I should build one.

Lots of couch space, no friends = check.

I didn't realize that couches had to always be occupied. Do you work on projects when your friends are over? Pretty rude, in my opinion.

Crappy rectangle shower = check.

It's an apartment, not the Westin Book Cadillac...didn't really have much of a choice.

Crappy shoes = check.

I get compliments on my Pumas all the time. Didn't know I was in /r/malefashionadvice.

Crappy pinstriping = check.

To each their own. What did you do during your bike project? 

what'd I miss?

I think we know why his ex left him, now.

Well, I'm just glad my ex wasn't my right hand. Hope you and Ms. Right are happy for a long time.

Thanks for looking.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 12:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detroit, actually. I've been asked about Toronto in previous posts, so I'm curious what building that is haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 12:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Lock research is next on the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 12:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 weeks (with 3 days didn't in Kentucky for work) and around 200 dollars. Can be done for less if you already have the proper tools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell the landlords, there may be grease stains in the carpet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bike I had couldn't be given away in the beginning. I'm thrilled you took a look with do many on your queue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. My issue has been using more coarse grit on automotive paint jobs. I used a finer grit to ensure the removal of imperfections, plus the peel technique worked well to ensure no mis-adhesion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything is better than nothing, bit I'd probably be devastated if this bike were ever taken, amateur paint job or not... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close to 200 dollars. Half of that in brakes, seat, cables, chain, and tubing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to get to that point; unfortunately, my first bike is probably not a good gauge haha. I'm going to try to get the terminology down for future conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated. If this bike was stolen, it'd be like tearing part of my heart out and running away with it. Any preventative measures are welcomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll attempt to do so until my diabetic scrawny legs give out, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just glad the terminology is the worst of it, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you understand that being new to bicycles has left me short of terminology but not short of mechanical awareness. Thanks for your understanding, it's much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I torqued until there was resistance on the bearings, then I let off and they've been free flowing since. Overtorque is a crime, no doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Glad you enjoyed the album!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It kept me away from my issue at hand, and for that it was the perfect project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope to see it when it's done sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in Detroit, nothing surprises me. Glad you enjoyed the bike though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't started looking yet, so I'm not quite sure in that regard. Hopefully I'll have one before the week is over though. Any good spots top look?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, the only proper way to use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Enjoying it is the only thing left to do!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paint has held up great so far, but that's with minimal usage. The sanding between coats and avoiding blotches is critical. Cutting the wind out and constantly wetting the tarps is necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 200 for the total restore. About 100 for parts and 100 for supporting materials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this a couple of times, but still can't pronounce it haha. Phonetic spelling anyone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are stupid enough for an average Joe to fix, on that note I agree 100 percent haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
