<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8234</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 23:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seinfeld is the only TV show I have ever watched that has been able to make me cry from laughing so hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 22:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was friends with this kid, lets call him Dave. 

Dave and I were fairly close in 4th grade, along with a few other guys. He had a rough home life, moved off for a few years. 

Fast forward to 8th grade- he's back, and doesn't care that I was his friend back in the day. He made it his personal mission to torment me by pushing me down, spitting in my face, and swearing at me nearly every day. He had changed completely, it was like he was another person. 

My dad, a homicide cop with the county, came in and intervened after a few weeks, against my will. Dave never messed with me again. 

Few months later, news report comes on about Dave and his tragic death- he had been  cleaning a gun when it fired, hitting him in the head and killing him instantly. Everyone thinks it was a cover up of a suicide. 

Always felt bad for Dave. He just had a shitty family and got dealt a bad hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 17:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never thought of that. Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 06:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Klipsch's X10 earbuds. I have a pair and they have great isolation. I use them while mowing and have no issues. Audio quality is also outstanding IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 06:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Klipsch makes great earbuds, the X10's. Owned a pair for a year or so and I couldn't ever go back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 06:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this smell like Chloroform to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 06:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a hobby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Gonna Be (500 Miles) by the Proclaimers. 

Also, American Pie by Don McLean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 06:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hummus. Healthy, cheap, and takes no time at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 01:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best TL;DR ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 07:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds vaguely like Walden Two by B. F. Skinner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 07:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike never has that problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 01:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, OP- you should check this guy out.

http://vimeo.com/21338911 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 07:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or pinche culero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about Suits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 08:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best country song in years, IMO, is Bourbon in Kentucky by Dierks Bentley. That is a song that I can honestly say stunned me the first time I heard it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer the term spite fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/imgoingtohellforthis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cumbox story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/relationships
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 08:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some believe we're judged by an omniscient, omnipotent deity. 

Some believe we're reincarnated into other lives. 

Some believe there's nothing after death. 

I'm not sure what to believe- I just hope that my actions in life lead me to a deathbed where I am content with my life and choices, and join those countless numbers of people before me who have passed from this life and into whatever comes next.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 07:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And then it hit us on how inappropriate this song really was." 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 23:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If I lay here.... If I just lay here.. Would you lie with me, and just forgot the world?" -Snow Patrol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 05:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/sex might be a better place for you to ask. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 07:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/headphones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 06:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://ametia.files.wordpress.com/2013/07/fox_zimmerman_laughs_130703c1.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 03:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/exposureporn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 00:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, OP, what did you use to stack those exposures? I'm trying to do the same thing but can't figure out how to get it exactly right.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 13:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always ended up having my partner drive because I sucked at driving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 21:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing this for years. I was mad at them so I said "Get me a fucking representative you cunthole" and was pleasantly surprised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 15:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, OP. I know what you're going through. I'm a guy. Had a girl lead me on for an upwards of two years. We were great friends, she was older, and didn't want anything. However, she dropped hints all the time that kept me around.. Right when I thought I'd be able to move on, she had me hooked again. 

All of my friends would tell me to leave her be, because there were better girls out there. I didn't want anyone else though. I did everything I could to win her- she had this kind of "come and get me attitude". I don't know why I stayed so long.. 

I would lay awake at night, wondering why she did this to me.. I don't even believe in God, and yet, I still prayed. I was more depressed than I had ever been. 

I realized one day that I wanted to be happy, but couldn't with her in my life. So I deleted her number, deleted her off of Facebook, completely had no contact with her for months. 

For the first time in a long time, I can say I'm happy. We talk from time to time, but I realized that it was all a game to her- I was her toy, and she had no intention of ever being with me. 

What I'm trying to say here, OP, is that you need to cut yourself off- it'll be the only thing that helps. It'll be tough, but you'll make it through just like I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 06:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue in Green By Miles Davis. 

Yellow by Coldplay. 

Chasing Cars by Snow Patrol. 

Nothing by the Script.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 06:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family used to live next door to Brittany Spears' family back in the day when her sister was a toddler. My grandma used to babysit her.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 06:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check online to make sure your version supports it. I tried with mine and ends up mine only supports 8GB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 20:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a close friend die of lymphoma a year ago. It's a really terrible disease. 

Glad to see you're kicking ass, OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 03:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/avocadosgonewild
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 01:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck your couch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 21:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a laptop bag from monoprice for 15$ and its lasted me two years.. Monoprice is amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 18:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my personal preference is to go to best buy to find and try out stuff i like in person so i can figure out if i like it enough to order it off of amazon.

example: headphones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 18:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> monoprice might be the greatest website ever created solely to give the middle finger to companies like best buy and radio shack

40 bucks for an 8ft HDMI? i dont think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 17:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the late reply. 

Close. Michigan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 03:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/unashamed
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 03:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think a sandbox world like Skyrim would be amazing for Pokemon. Ride a Rayquaza around, blow up shit with hyper beam, open a gym, design the gym, go roaming about the wilderness and find Pokemon in the deepest, darkest depths of the map.. It would be everything I've been dreaming of since I was a kid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 03:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally prefer bigger boobs, with smaller areolas. Honestly though, boobs are boobs, which automatically makes any boobs great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 22:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here with the TV Shows, except mine included stuff like Hercules, Harry Potter, or anything with any hint of magic or sorcery. In recent years I realized that my family's religion is a load of malarkey and stopped giving a fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be religious too. 

Then I stopped giving a fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 16:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should ask /u/PROSTITUTE_STRANGLER about his thoughts on that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 15:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, the thing is, is that if he had lived longer, think about how he could've changed our society even more than he already did. If he had more time, even five or ten years more, I've always wondered how much different our society would look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 07:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nikola Tesla.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 07:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Orleans at Mardis Gras. Booze and Boobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 07:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Babe.. Are you a beaver? Cause dam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 06:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American. I would rather lose a testicle than sit through that piece of trash again. 

The Men Who Stare at Goats was pretty bad too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 06:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, both of my grandfathers are Freemasons, and one of them is a master mason(the highest honor you can have). 

My family consists of conservative adventists who think that freemasonry is essentially devil worship, so that was a surprise. I used to believe that stuff when I was a kid, but I now realize how ridiculous it is.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 16:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two people did it- the model stood still while the photographer set the shutter open, flashed the subject from behind, turned the wire on, moved it, and then closed the shutter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 19:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still partial to /u/storytellerbob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 19:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's already got me.  I'm planning on buying some UE over the ears soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 04:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These tend to come out of your ears easier because they're listening headphones rather than actual sport earbuds- I have a job outside where I do a lot of walking and lifting and they occasionally come out but if you don't mind that, they're fine. You literally won't be able to hear anything outside if you have music playing so be careful if you're in an urban area. As far as the cord making sound, it does some, but it's not really noticeable if you're playing something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 02:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm friends with OP, this is our former high school 

What kills me is that these are Adventists, who bitch about EVERYTHING from Harry potter to eating out on Saturday to drums in church, and here they are anointing a goddamn rock.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 02:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. The sound isolation is fantastic- they make a seal with your ear, and, in my opinion, rival Bose on noise reduction. 

Fairly good on lows, great on mids and highs. 

The X10's rival any IEM or over the ear in sound quality- you'd have to go audiophile, and spend around 1000$ or more to get better. 

For the price, they're definitely the best you'll get without having to spend outrageous money. 

If you end up getting them, let me know what you think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 23:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an audio engineer, and my best friend who works with me sold them to me for 75. He got rid of them so he could get some monitor headphones for mixing. He got them for 90 on amazon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 20:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a pair of Klipsch X10 earbuds for 75$. Best headphones I've ever had. Blows everything else away. 

Also, Spotify Premium. Almost every song I want, when I want. Radio, playlists, and I can download for offline. I use Spotify 8-10 hours a day. It's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 20:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Your Pussy by Afroman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 18:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A buddy of mine was hanging out with this waitress we knew from one of our regular Friday-night hangouts at a Fourth of July party. She was tipsy, mentioned how hotel rooms were cheaper after midnight. 

He never got the hint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 17:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate when women deny flicking the bean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 16:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 years here 

It sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 15:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I stand up, my feet collapse in on themselves because I literally have no arch to support it. I deal with a LOT of pain with my feet, even if its just standing. 

I'm convinced that if they didn't hurt so much all the time, I would exercise more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 15:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I'll wake up with songs in my head that I haven't heard in years. I pull out Spotify and listen to it. Pretty awesome. 

Fun fact- when you have a song stuck in your head, the same parts of your brain are active as if you were actually listening to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 15:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I run over conversations I've had in the past, in great detail, and figure out if I said/did the right thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 15:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I walk around campus, I look around for all the vantage points a sniper would use and look for the quickest cover if he missed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This showed up on Facebook today.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 02:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 22:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "we", I was referring to the American people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 18:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There seems to be a mentality among Americans that people of other nations are people to be shunned and put down upon, when, in reality, people of other cultures and ethnicities enrich and diversify our own culture. America was founded by people of other countries so that others could enjoy the same freedom we do. In recent years, this had changed.. Sad to see, really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 16:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American here. 

How any issue here can be turned into a racial issue. We are living in 2013. We shouldn't have to deal with this kind of thing anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 21:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no. The dream of every guy is to have girls strip naked in front of them for absolutely no reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 21:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are living the dream of millions of guys. 

Don't ruin it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got lead on by a girl for years and then she ditched me like trash. I'm convinced that she did it to see me hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 19:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to do that. The most fun I've ever had on the water was at grand isle. Went crabbing and caught four dozen crabs. Those were some good eatin'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 15:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native Louisianaian here. I felt the same way. It's probably because of New Orleans + Mardi Gras + Boobs at Mardi Gras </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 04:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to live in Mossdeep- it's an island, great views, and if I need anything I can just RIDE A POKEMON back to the mainland.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could let google chrome remember for you since redditors are lazy

Source: I'm a lazy redditor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/unlimitedbreadsticks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 06:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering how long it'd take you to show up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 16:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If You Want Blood by AC/DC, Eruption by Van Halen, Hot Blooded by Foreigner. 

Can't Hold Us by Macklemore(Live)

I also really enjoy State of Massachusetts by the Dropkick Murphy's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 16:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially Big Balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 18:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean a freedom hawk egg, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 17:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you're reduced to selling Tupperware. What a shame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 17:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking idiots! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 17:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louisiana? 

God, I love my home state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 16:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I really appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
