<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7467</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not liberals they are corrupted incompetent assholes that deserve to meet Madame Guillotine.  Most French politics, regardless the side are corrupted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La jeunesse emmerde, le Front National!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyway total border control is impossible. Remember after the attacks when those terrorists just crossed the French - Belgium  border without any  difficulties? This was during a "high" security level... 

I cross the border several times a year and never got checked. If I see cops well they are 2 guys sitting in their car watching the clock moving toward the end if their shift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 11:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nop the South of France is preferred by Muslim immigrants. Probably the weather. If one comes from Africa and moves to Normandie he will regret it big time. 

Marseille is the city of problems right now, police is struggling to maintain order against guetto guys armed with AK 47 and uzi.. 

But yeah that is what you get if you use them for your own benefits. France used their grandpa against Axis forces in exchange for french nationality.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ve had a 2vs2 match against a warlord that would only run away and charge with heavy attack, rinse and repeat. The whole freaking match. This kind of behavior makes me rage quit since it is not fun nor interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha 'members me those battlegrounds on WoW. It was fun until Russia got fast Internet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything extra to download ?  Or just installing ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It starts in 25min chill man its all fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless we get a 3gb patch + some u play crashes. Only 2 days remaining then. Hurray  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No snow, at work.. 1h22 minutes till 3pm. I finish work at 4pm. Arg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree I like being able to play offline when I want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing in professional kitchens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](http://gadgets.ndtv.com/games/news/for-honor-street-date-broken-in-turkey-1657335) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 11:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So by your argument, we are already at the stage of cooking dieing out

Unfortunately it is not going on the right way in some countries, it's all about education, at school but most importantly at home, if the parents are cooking and teach their kid what is good/bad it will not die that fast. Thanks to all the Slow-food people in the world, trying to counter the attack of the industry. I know it's hard because we have to work a lot, life is getting very busy and time is lacking for many of us.

The problem is when I see my generation, like I was watching Twitch and those 4 American guys could not agree more on the fact that cooking sucks because you spend 1h in the kitchen for 10min of eating, so they just order and get food outside everyday... I was shocked. I hope they are not representatives of the American youth but I think they are, correct me if I'm wrong I am not from USA.

Picture this generation having kids, microwave food everyday... if no one teach the kids how to cook and show them why it is better for one's health and better taste wise, they will never know.

I have an example, my girlfriend in from Holland and she always hated pastry/sweet food. She met me, a French Pastry chef,  I couldn't believe she did not like it, I made stuff for her, she always loved it and she was surprised how different it is from what she had experienced before. She likes it now, when she gets the good stuff made with love.

Because sweet food in Holland sucks, they use so much processed food and ingredients. Even in a 5 stars hotel I worked, the "homemade" muffins for the breakfast were made with:

Water

Muffin powder

GMO soy oil


I quit this place after 2 months because this was just insulting for my diplomas. 

We could indeed teach them, I would love to have a robot to help me and teach him the good way, a very smart one like in IRobot. But then it's almost a Human being !

 Already we're pushing the boundaries of food science. Transglutaminase to bind together random protiens? Hot ice cream? Deep fried tequila?

This is like molecular restaurants, it's a new pretty innovative way of cooking but it stays very marginal, it had an impact on all the modern restaurants that picked up ideas to serve new things.
But to be honest, would people give up the classic nicely chimney roasted T-Bone for a foamy fancy shiny emulsion of a T-Bone, just because it looks cool, nah. At least not in Europe.

About the deep fried Tequila soaked dough things, I would expect the alcohol to evaporate white frying... maybe is it because the Tequila is water based and it get stuck in the dough surrounded by the oil.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then are we talking about a robot if the thing as an AI near the Human one ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, very fruity and fresh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol we dont have the same definition of being fast then ! Besides, who puts the ingredients ready for Mr Arms on the table ? This thing it so useless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a very evolved AI then, close to the Human one because it will need to learn how to cook, from a Human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15000 bucks for being slow, this little guy would get his ass kicked in a kitchen. But be would be great to peel stuff and clean the kitchen at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is too sides, the Dark side (industrial food, GMO, all junk food,all cheap food) is destroying our most precious good which is food. They destroy it by making people dependent on Take Away and other delivery food, "Dont cook, just eat" is the ad of a huge delivery food company in europe. If you don't make it yourself, you have no idea where it comes from, no idea how they made it.

Don't think, just open you mouth and eat is their goal so when they totally control the food system (Bayer-Monsanto...) money and huge power will come. 

Who controls food controls everything.


And there is the Light side, independent BIO food producers that respect their goods (especially cattle) , independent quality restaurants (I say quality because there is tons of shit ones working with the Dark side for profits), passionate chefs and of course everyone that at least try to eat less shit food so they don't sign up for it and encourage that crap to spread everywhere.


Microwave are a good help to melt/warm up things, but in real kitchens there is none because you don't need them, it is useful at home but not necessary. I have seen once a documentary in Paris where there was a kitchen with 8 microwaves, 2 Nigerians and hips and processed food already made, ready to warm up and serve to tourist and people who don't know what real food is. It made me so sad to see how some cunts have no shame to sell poor quality food (in the name of the French cuisine) to people. It is not respectful. 


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean most of the processed food currently is pure crap and unhealthy. So I don't see how a robot could know better what is tasting good, what is a ingredient of quality etc.. A human could teach a robot to do steps, but the robot is never going to go off lines nor discovering/improving anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you are right. But I am a Chef, and I can assure you that cooking relies on robot a lot currently, since we have to cook big quantities, so kitchen Aid and mixer, intelligent oven, gadgets that make our professional life easier and improve the Cuisine in several ways.

However, a good chef needs his 5 senses working full time and accurately, cooking isnt just add this and this and fucking bake it, there is love involved, skills, experience.  Sure a robot can do something one way and the same way for ever and ever but will never improve anything, you know why ?

Robots don't eat food.

The day robots are actually eating food and enjoying it, then yeah, I am screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies, I should have wrote: "Robots will never learn cooking PROPERLY". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in French ther re called Choux ! Lekker anyway ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chef. Robots will never learn cooking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
