<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I prefer to split everything into tupperwares right away. It makes it easier to make sure things are portioned correctly so my calorie counts are more or less accurate, and I also leave early in the morning to go to the gym, so it's much easier to just grab a bunch of tupperwares. I'm also gone for about 12 hours and have found it easy to manage.

I have a random collection of tupperware I've built up over time, so can't comment on the chinese take out ones. I have some that handle liquid better (twisting lids or locking lids) and others that were just cheap.

[Here's my fridge](http://i.imgur.com/TWSx8zZ.jpg) with 4 days of breakfast, lunch, and afternoon snack prepped and in tupperware, and I split my fridge with a roommate.

[Here's what I bring every day!](http://i.imgur.com/z6z7TtW.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 21:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I scrolled and didn't see it on there, but when I've looked at Zella online (lots of people seem to love their leggings) they seem to have some plus size options as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also recommend weighing the meat raw and looking up nutrition info for raw meat. It loses water and such while cooking so "1 oz" of cooked chicken won't necessarily be consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also worth noting that you probably didn't miscalculate, 5/3/1 starts light. It's not actually using 95% of your 1RM for Week 3, the program bases all of it's calculations off of a "training max" which is usually 90% of your actual 1RM. So it's then 95% of that. You're expected to get more than 1 rep on the first couple/few cycles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just get some fiber powder and drink it with your water instead. Probably safer than messing with the recipe, and the orange Metamucil tastes pretty good IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that you could bring beer into Centeroo, I was there 2 years ago and they were checking water bottles, etc, as well - no outside alcohol allowed in, but of course people concealed it there too.

I do think Firefly was more strict about it, though. At roo, they'd sniff water bottles and camelbaks. At Firefly depending on the guards they'd usually make you empty them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 14:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, corned beef, cabbage, and potato is a particularly New England tradition - apparently it became a thing for Irish immigrants here, mostly because it was affordable! And trust me, we're all busy getting drunk too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that's my favorite dessert right now. I add peanut butter but use water instead and it's still amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your video is private. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this exact thought every time I run a 5K.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also fuck you to the dude who doesn't even try to pretend he's not looking at my ass during squats.

I know this is anti-Whiny Wednesday but it reminded me how nice this dude was at the gym the other day. He was deadlifting behind a power rack - I asked if I could squat in the rack, and he nicely offered to move over a little so that he wouldn't be directly behind me in case that would "be weird." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of resources in the FAQ (linked in the sidebar)! For your goals you might take a look at a beginner lifting program + C25K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you recalculated your TDEE and deficit since you started? If you've lost weight your TDEE will go down!

Edit: and for beginner programs, there are some options linked in the FAQ in the sidebar that you can check out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank's Hot Buffalo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 14:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of weird but I actually drink a scoop of vanilla whey + some orange gatorade powder during my workout. Tastes like a creamsicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also prefer Pendlay rows over just straight up bent over rows - you start with the bar on the ground for each rep so it's less taxing on your grip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would guess that's probably due to the same issue - if you start with the bar too far out in front, your hips rise first and the lift becomes almost all lower back. Look at your body position after each rep - it's almost an SLDL at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're ending up with more than an inch. [This is how you end up after the first rep](http://i.imgur.com/oxI3xi4.jpg) - then it looks like you just bend your knees toward the bar, your feet/the bar don't really move.

I used to had the same problem with any rep after my first one, and it was because I wasn't shoving my hips back on the way down, so even if my first setup was great, the rest of my reps weren't. Focus on that, and in the meantime I recommend standing up between each rep and taking a look at where the bar is over your foot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have the bar way out in front of you and you're bending your knees to get to the bar - watch where the bar ends up at the end of each rep. It should be over your midfoot. Roll the bar to you instead, and when you're descending think about sticking your hips back first.

Edit: Also, is it... snowing in your gym? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's less exact, but I just weigh/measure things uncooked and calculate the total calories that way. Then I visually guesstimate when I'm splitting into tupperwares. 

E.g. If I'm cooking 8oz of meat to split into 4 meals, I might accidentally end up with 2.2oz in one and 1.8 in another but no biggie - it's still 8oz over the course of 4 days. Then I'd just count it as 2oz of meat when I'm tracking each meal.

I hope that makes some sort of sense... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah absolutely - like I said, I wouldn't sweat that.

/r/elcapitan_morgan seemed to have gone over all of her macros without going over her calories, which makes me think something is miscalculated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 17:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might be overthinking things (which is easy to do... there's a lot of crazy and sometimes conflicting fitness and nutrition info out there).

The girl you posted has an insanely low bodyfat. It takes years and lots of hard work to achieve that. It also sounds like you more or less understand what you need to do - you lost weight before but didn't have a lot of lean body mass, so you're working on it now. That's great! It'll take a lot longer than a few months, though.

To end up "shredded" you need to have a fair amount of muscle mass + low body fat. People get there in multiple different ways (different sports, different training programs, different diets) so there is no one right answer. Pick what works for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 15:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's odd... it might be because MFP calculates your macro breakdown with percentages and then rounds them, rather than letting you input an exact number. I just added up mine, though, and my macros total 1551 calories while my goal is 1550, so it's almost exactly correct, just a bit of rounding error.

Pfftwe is correct, macros are really just a specific breakdown of your calorie goal, and each gram of carbs/fat/protein is worth a certain number of calories (1g of carbs = 4 calories, 1g of protein = 4 calories, 1g of fat = 9 calories), so your macro goals should always add up to your calorie goal. 

If you just slightly don't make it (you go over calories a little, or you have a few too many carbs/too few grams of protein) I wouldn't sweat it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 15:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My nipples honestly show constantly at the gym, unless I'm wearing a sports bra with cups (and even then... nips like diamonds). They just automatically become rock hard when I'm working out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime you're eating at a deficit, it's probably gonna suck a little tbh. Things that help me:

Meal planning and food prepping is a big one. I plan out meals for the week (or at least the weekdays) that fit my calorie/macro goals and then usually pre-cook several days' worth. If my breakfast/lunch/snack is already prepared for me, it's a lot harder for me to find a reason to go get something else. This also means when I grocery shop I know exactly what I need and I don't keep anything around that I don't need. 

I also eat a bunch of smaller meals ~3 hours apart. This doesn't work for everyone, but personally if I start to get a bit hungry, it's really helpful to remember that I only have another hour or so until my next meal. Some other people prefer intermittent fasting.

Overall I try to eat filling foods that are tasty and keep a small-ish deficit so I'm not too hungry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been running it that long this time around (on cycle 2 and it starts out super light so the first cycle was easy)... had some big life changes this past fall and went from working out consistently to barely at all and then came back but just fucked around for a while. Oops! But I ran 531 for a while at some point before that and definitely gained strength, just don't remember the #s.

I'll get back to you in a few more months ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 21:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to but don't anymore. Always thought they kind of tasted like ass, and it was just one more thing to buy. Most of them are primarily caffeine, so now I just drink coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your calves are secondary muscles used in some of those. Lunges, for example, are using lots of different muscles in the leg, including your calves. You might also be tensing your legs, including calves for some of these exercises, e.g. pointing your toe while doing donkey kicks.

I wouldn't worry about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flair please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What glute exercises are you doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you eating 1750 net cals or total cals? Meaning, are you eating back calories you burned from exercise? It's normal for weight to fluctuate, but if the trend continues, this is a common issue we see... MFP and most other "estimators" tend to drastically overestimate calories burned by exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 14:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run it and really like it. As some others have said, I love that it's super simple but gives plenty of room to do your own accessory work, so if I want more volume, I'll just do some high volume front squats after my regular sets of squats, for example. I occasionally run on my off days, but I'm not a huge cardio lover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever gone to an allergist/doctor about that? My brother has a similar issue which we originally thought might be pesticide related, but it's actually related to some sort of pollen allergy:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oral_allergy_syndrome

Cooking the fruits/vegetables fixes the problem for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just leave my clothes in my gym bag in the car all day honestly. And then I wipe the gym bag down with a Clorox wipe every so often. 

Can't help with the frizzy hair unfortunately!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank's hot buffalo is seriously one of my favorite foods, I add it to chicken ALL THE TIME. But I've never done it with greek yogurt too, that sounds creamy and wonderful! Now I need to try it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope you can keep adding and it will keep weighing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 14:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a version with curry powder too! And another version with grapes instead of craisins (classic). And last night I was craving it after making this post, and the only nuts I had were wasabi almonds so I used those... still good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I burp constantly at the gym and I don't have anxiety. I figured it was just from gulping water and gulping air and not doing a good job at either one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken salad made with greek yogurt instead of mayo. Obviously we all sub greek yogurt for everything all over the place but mayo's really got its own thing going on, and I was incredibly skeptical that I could just replace it entirely.

It was so good that I made and ate it three times in one week.

[Here's the recipe](http://showmetheyummy.com/greek-yogurt-chicken-salad/) - sorry for the crazy long blog post, the actual recipe is near the bottom.

Edit/PS: although kinda "healthy" due to the mayo/yogurt substitution, watch it with the cashews and craisins because that shit adds up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the reverse discovery when I finally got a food scale... 2oz of chicken is like... nothing. This probably explains why I'm so pudgy. :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm meal planning also, so I just try and mix my shredded chicken breast with low cal things to make it taste like something different. The best is Frank's Hot Buffalo - instant low cal buffalo chicken. It's so good I don't even care that I'm eating chicken again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah one of my favorite meals right now is just spinach topped with tuna, sliced avocado, salt   pepper, and lemon juice. So good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 19:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's snowing again in Boston right now. YAY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, any kind of exercise helps relieve cramps. It sucks at first, but once I'm warmed up they tend to relax a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you with the 12-year-old boy thing. Anything with cups in it works for me (hides the diamond nips AND sort of makes it look like I have boobs).

I actually just got a hot pink sports bra from Target that I'm in love with - they had a great selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish March was actually going out like a lamb here in Boston... it snowed this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that makes sense, and really it's one reason why these calculators will never be 100% accurate. "Exercise" means a million different things at different intensities. I would input 4 days of exercise and eat at the recommended deficit for at least a couple of weeks and see how it goes. If you're not losing weight, adjust it a bit lower - you'll have to do that throughout weight loss anyway, since your TDEE will go down as your weight goes down.

I'm eating 120-130g protein, 50-60g fat, and the remainder in carbs, which is about what IIFYM recommends for my bodyweight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
