<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8542</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's another good point...my mother has iron-deficient anemia, and I previously never bothered to get formally tested for it because I always just sort of assumed that I had the symptoms of it, so I take a generic iron pill from the pharmacy. I finally got around to getting some bloodwork done recently, and I'll find out the results in about a week. Maybe it's worse than I thought and I need a prescribed dose?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I actually recently heard about the man who lost weight eating Twinkies. If you've ever listened to "Wait, Wait...Don't Tell Me!" on NPR, they talked about him on there. 

Anyways, thank you so much for the advice. I live by myself, and so I think part of my issues also stem from not having anyone around to hold me accountable for how much I eat during meals. But I definitely like the idea of making myself cook in larger quantities and then immediately portioning them for future meals, rather than allowing myself the temptation of taking seconds (or thirds, or fourths.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 16:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I have not! I've considered it, but have heard that getting into the sleep studies and related treatment options can be quite expensive in the US. If you don't mind my asking, was it financially difficult for him to reach that diagnosis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feel like my hypersomnia + chronic fatigue are making it impossible for me to stick with any kind of routine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 16:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, /r/loseit! I stumbled upon this subreddit after browsing Reddit for a place where I could gain advice about my particular problem, and this seemed like a great place. 

So, I'll cut right to the chase - I have been obese for nearly my entire life. I won't get into specifics, but I am currently nearly 80 pounds overweight. I am embarrassed and ashamed of how far I have allowed my weight gain to progress. I've tried quite a few different tactics, but I have a difficult time sticking to any fitness routine for more than a couple of weeks due to the fact that I have chronic fatigue and hypersomnia.

I recognize that the constant exhaustion has likely developed as a result of the weight gain itself, but it's so difficult for me to convince myself that I should take a brisk walk when I can hardly get through the day without sleeping for 12-14 hours at night. I've come to rely on (prescribed) stimulants and caffeine, but even those are only a band-aid on this constant feeling of lethargy and tiredness.

So, how do I develop a routine that I can actually stick to? Where do I start? There's something inside of me that yearns to wake up early every morning, enjoy the sunrise, exercise my body, and make it through the day without collapsing in exhaustion, but I feel so far away from that reality. I'm tired of using my fatigue as an excuse, but it often feels impossible to overcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can describe your life using a single clickbait phrase. What do you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 21:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Vyvanse 50mg was the first medication I ever tried. It remains my favorite. It allows for smooth focusing, a pleasant amount of energy, and has a pretty steady release throughout the day. I took it for six months and found that it remained effective throughout that time and I only built up a mild tolerance to it. Unfortunately, when I switched my insurance policy, it became too expensive.

2. Concerta was the next option. I was on 18mg per day. I do not like Concerta and would not personally recommend it, but ADHD manifests differently in everyone, and subsequently, so do its medications. I like to explain my experience with Concerta by saying that Vyvanse allowed me to pleasantly focus on one or two tasks at a given time, whereas Concerta made me feel like I needed to focus on a dozen tasks at a given time. Its release throughout the day had too harsh of a peak-and-trough effect. I have comorbid hypersomnia in addition to my ADHD, and so I also rely on stimulants to keep me awake. I was on it for two months and found that when it wasn't working, I was dead tired. When it was working, I felt nearly manic.

3. Adderall XR 20mg was the next attempt. It worked pretty well, but because of my aforementioned hypersomnia, I found that once I came down around 6-7 hours after taking it, I would abruptly burn out for the day. I was on this for only one month.

4. Aaaand finally, I'm currently on Adderall IR (immediate release) 20mg, twice a day. This seems to work pretty well for me. I take one when I wake up around 9 AM, and another around 2 PM. I still prefer Vyvanse, only because Adderall has a harsher comedown for me. I find that at the end of the day, I become very irritable. I describe it to my boyfriend as a kind of "sensory overload" feeling where I need very little stimulation, or else I'll become agitated. But it does help me to focus on a couple of major tasks at a time without feeling too overwhelmed, and it gives a nice boost of energy that I need to get out of bed in the morning and make it through class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 04:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WikiLeaks' Twitter account has done a pretty good job of highlighting the most significant findings. 

https://twitter.com/wikileaks

There's nearly 20,000 e-mails in total, so I wouldn't expect any kind of comprehensive guide to the entire leak for another day or two. That being said, it's awesome to see how many people are working together online to compile the key findings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ariana Grande was (unsuccessfully) vetted as a performer for some kind of Gala, lol

https://wikileaks.org/dnc-emails/emailid/14963 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://wikileaks.org/dnc-emails/emailid/14391

On discussing finding LGBT donors, one staffer states to another, "let's talk gays - when are you free?" 

Fucking *yikes.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleaning. I've found a few friends who share with me in this satisfaction of cleaning when anxiety hits.

Organizing my belongings, making my bed, folding my clothes, doing the dishes - there's something very soothing to me about creating a neater, more organized space. Sometimes, I'll dump all my clothes in a huge pile and re-fold them, just because it relaxes me in some weird way.

Except for mopping. I hate mopping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
