<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 07:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thank you! I'm so glad you've enjoyed my stories. If anything, this has increased the urge to write my gay horror. No amount of no homoing will stop me..

Here is the [cache'd version](https://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache%3Ah3Jml6RsjOcJ%3Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fnosleep%2Fcomments%2F50k8mw%2Ffather_knows_best%2F%2B cd=1 hl=en ct=clnk gl=us st=isjlbuew sh=1b43b6fa), with [the original for comparison](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4xxpv4/father_knows_best/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 06:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like...there was no paragraph breaks between the dialogue. I've never realized the importance of strategic paragraph breaks before I read it. It felt like one run on sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't highly upvoted. I just noticed it had the same name as mine and wanted to see what it was about, and there it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how else to describe it. Laurent is a clearly masculine name, the female replacement must have been on purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I don't think it was a bot account, either, just some random. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, it finally happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So someone wholesaled copy-pasted one of my stories, fucked up the formatting dramatically, and *no homo'ed it.* The main character's name (Laurent) got changed to a female one, missing the entire goddamn point. Honestly that and the horrific things they did to my formatting upset me more than the plagiarism.

The wonderful mods were on top of it instantly, but I'm still a little mad about it. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
