<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5460</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sakin rin! Puro marriage proposal at mga nagkaka-boyfriend. Ako na lang ang natitirang single sa barkada namin. Mga traydor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ang daming couple sa fb feed ko. Ayoko na! (*logs out immediately) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saan ka tumatakbo? Ang alam ko marami sa Ayala Triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Baka magkaroon ako nyan ng bagong PR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! Mga 2 years na rin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May mga kasabay ako dati, kaso nasa ibang company na sila. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sa makati. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 12:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minsan nakakalungkot tumakbo mag-isa :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uy salamat. Mga ganitong tema yung gustong-gusto ko panoorin.  
Try mo panuorin Ruby Sparks. My favorite movie about loneliness din.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 12:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lamon is over!  
Diet starts tomorrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy new year din sis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manalig tayo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Sana nga i-extend nila ng 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanggang kailan po showing ng MMFF movies? Sana makahabol pa ko. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 16:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Beauty/ American Psycho Album by Fall Out Boy.  
I cry when I laugh album ni Jess Glynne.  
I want it all - Karmin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irregular Menstruation then nakitaan ako ng polycystic features sa ovary nun nagpa-ultrasound ako. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gals of BeautyTalkPh, I need your help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 03:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Gals,  
  
Late bloomer here. I just started to become conscious about myself, specially the way I dress and move. I want to be more feminine which means I should wear more skirts and dresses. I am kinda boyish and manang so most of my clothes are either t-shirt or long sleeves. Please help me as I don't have a good fashion sense and TBH I don't know where to start.  
  
If you can recommend any instagram users for inspirations, that would be helpful.  
  
  
Edit: Thanks girls for taking the time to help me. I really appreciate all your comments and advice.  
I will consider all your suggestions.  
Maraming maraming salamat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed with nodular goiter in 2014 but I managed to reduce the size through running and a healthy lifestyle. Then last month, I was diagnosed with PCOS. My OB advised me to lose weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Perks of Being a Wallflower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking a nap at around 5 pm is not a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started running in 2014 right after I was diagnosed with nodular goiter (benign). For almost 3 years, I managed to reduced the size of the node and make my TSH get back to normal level and its all thanks to running and healthy lifestyle. Right now, Im preparing for my half marathon next month. My running shoes is almost 6 months old now.  
I would like to try Mizuno this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mobile9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inis ako sa mv nyan kasi wala man lang close up si Chungha my love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im planning to do my first ever full marathon next year. Still researching and looking for training plan that suits me but for now, Im preparing for my half marathon on January. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 03:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, saka pansin ko walang nagtatanong sakin kung bakit ako single. Obvious na ata sa kanila ang sagot LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 03:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cafe Mocha ng Pan de Manila saka [Great taste white](https://imgur.com/g7Q2sLw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What piece of advice would you like to give yourself right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From MRT North Ave.  
1. Take MRT North Ave. Station.  
2. Get off at Cubao Station. 
3. Go to LRT 2 via Gateway Mall. 
4. Take LRT 2 and get off at V Mapa station.  
  
Note: common point nila is V Mapa station. You can also visit Cinema 76 fb page. They provided directions and maps. I hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't found someone who has the same wavelength as me.  
And also, Im awkward irl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Monumento,  
1.Take LRT 1(Monumento Station) and get off at Doroteo Jose station  
2. Take LRT 2 (Recto Station)  
3. Get off at V. Mapa Station  
4. Depart on to Ramon Magsaysay  
5. From V. Mapa, ride a jeepney going to Pasig.  
6. Get off at Luna Mencias st. (left side) Landmark is Big Guys Pizza on the left and Dumlao Gym at the right.  
7. Walk up the street until you pass by the intersection of Luna Mencias and Araullo st.   
8. Cinema 76 is at the right side at the TBA Bldg  
Edit: line breaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yung Paymaya ko pang beep card narin. Kaya ayun, madalas ko syang nagagamit sa pagsakay ng LRT at MRT. Nagagamit ko rin sya pagloload ng cellphone saka nagamit ko rin sya dati noong nag-booked ako sa hotel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isipin mo na lang exercise narin. Approximately 150 calories din ang na-burn mo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seklusyon at Ang Babae sa Septik Tank 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put on some lipstick and you'll be fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May nagtatanong sa youtube kung bakit wala parin yung Milo Energy Gap sa itunes at spotify. Nakakaloka hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
