<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 14:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, this is totally cheating, but it works for me.  Use Google Translate, the "how to" is at the bottom of this page.  http://proxybay.info/alternate-methods.html

I have tried everything else and this is the only way I an access TPB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 14:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, different browsers, bypassing DNS, and even from different ISP's.....No TPB...also no mention of the outage on their FB page, which is unusual.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> found this little guy in my yard after homeowners association trimmed the trees. He was shivering and wet. Brought him inside and fed him and warmed him up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 04:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WACO explosion video 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 11:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 11:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different video of explosion here http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jAijUtQGH14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 11:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here it is from a different angle  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jAijUtQGH14

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 12:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but, who was camera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 00:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A better description of it...Chris Kyles words I think:  http://frontburner.dmagazine.com/2013/02/08/confirmed-american-sniper-chris-kyle-killed-two-men-at-a-gas-station-in-2009/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 00:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Chris Kyle were here he would tell you about the time two idiots attempted to rob him at gun point while he was refueling his truck.  They both had pistols pointed at him.  He shot them both.  Here is a post by Marcus Luttrell describing the events.

http://pistol-forum.com/showthread.php?4934-Chris-Kyle-Story-as-told-by-Marcus-Luttrell

On a bitterly cold morning in early January of 2009, the war, in a sense, found Chris again. What happened to him not far from his home outside Dallas never made the news, since the town involved didnt want the publicity, but the incident certainly would have made national headlines had a reporter ever gotten a tip about it.

Chris was minding his own business, fueling his pickup truck at a gas station, when he found himself at gunpoint. Two men holding pistols demanded his truck. Law enforcement will usually advise you to give in to the criminal in a situation like this. And thats good advice. But Chris took another route. Very calmly and coolly, he sized up which of the men was handling his pistol more comfortably. He put his hands up and told them he was going to reach into the truck to get his keys. Then his hand went under his coat. From a waistband holster, he pulled his Colt 1911. Swinging the pistol under his left armpit, he gave each robber two .45 caliber Hydra-Shock hollow-points to the chest. By the time the cops responded to the 911 call from the terrified lady who had locked herself in a car behind Chriss truck, the matter was settled. Elapsed time: about ten seconds. The service stations security cameras caught the whole thing.

I pray for anyone whose life gets so desperate that he or she chooses to resort to a life of crime, but its hard to resist a little cold laughter all the same: I mean, how unlucky a dumbass do you have to be to target a random guy for felony armed assault and find out hes killed more people than smallpox?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 13:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The back of his neck looks like a pack of hotdogs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love you imgur, but please... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 16:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..SHUT THE FUCK UP!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-03 13:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..but...who was camera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did I Miss Anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 18:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 17:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made my day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 17:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Get off my lawn!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 04:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sentence desperately needs to be reworded.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 11:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many PD's here in the states also carry stuffed animals for children, and not just for accidents, but for anytime we encounter a child who is hurt, afraid, skeptical of the police, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 19:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL...upvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 16:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are BEAUTIFUL.  Congratulations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 19:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure if joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 15:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, none of you will ever need any bedroom privacy.  I was hoping to see a stage with a stripper pole and then some sort of gloryhole setup in the back.  You motherfuckers are doing it wrong.  You're in fucking college...surrounded by hot, young women, and what the fuck do you do?  You move all the fucking beds into one big sausage party sleepover room and then setup a fucking gaming room next door?  WHAT THE FUCKING FUCK!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 21:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it be!

...see what I did there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont see how this is possible.  I think there is something missing, like an external monitor...I think it would work with an external monitor.  Plugging in this USB contraption does not change the fact that the laptop LCD is plugged directly into the "on-board video card" in the laptop mobo.  Maybe I'm wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 14:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> impossible.  This would not work with the laptop's LCD.  An external monitor, yes, but not like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Clawdette, a stray cat who adopted us when we moved into our townhouse last year.  Sadly, we couldnt take her with us when we moved out last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found some googly eyes while cleaning up my fiance's 9-year-old daughters room...expecting a visit from Chris Hansen anytime now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 20:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 14:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely fake.  Two things:  Look at the pic- that room is a corner room, so there is absolutely no way to NOT notice it.  Also, that isnt a painting.  Someone has thumb-tacked a paper printout to the wall (you can see the tacks) and then placed a frame around it.  I cant believe no one has mentioned this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 11:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you could hear the officers audio recording of the incident immediately after the kids walk off:
officer 1 - piss-ants...uhhhh no crime in the area with you guys around, lol
officer 2 - he'd shit his pants in a firefight
officer 1 - ..with a .22

"exercising their constitutional rights" is nothing more than walking around in public, looking like Rambo, attention-whoring, and possibly keeping a good officer from saving a life elsewhere.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 11:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I upvoted just for the title,  BEFORE looking at the image.  Hilarious. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 16:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reposted because it got absolutely nowhere the first time.   The ad is entertaining, funny, and the product is a fantastic bargain compared to what I am paying for razors now.  Maybe some jackass at Big Razor has legions of down-voters to keep this wonderful business from gaining popularity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BEST PITCH EVER! Saw this as a YouTube advertisement, loved it, and ended up buying the product.  Its a great service, Reddit, lets send this guy some business.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 05:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Man in the Cabinet" watches us masturbate in the kitchen.  Awesome image of a man in one of the kitchen cabinet doors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 04:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> electronic Knock Knock, Louis CK-style...with my girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 18:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 13:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> opened in a different tab, forgot about it, finally got to looking at it, thought it was Kim DotCom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 22:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see what I did there?  Next stop, hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Blind Man Carrying The Olympic Torch Through My City (FIXED)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 22:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 19:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh I would definitely hit that.  Even a tattoo to the face like that doesnt knock her out of the running for 'next big fucking mistake'... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-10 15:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and then their decapitated and tortured bodies were found in the streets because....well.....closed-minded, mislead, gullible, fuckshits doing "Gods work" couldnt stand to see something so beautiful.

Seriously, you're a beautiful couple.  I hope you live a long and safe life together.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 22:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> scumbag toad   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 18:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent work.  Stay clean.  Using always leads to a miserable dead end.  You obviously are gifted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 19:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have to voluntarily agree to be wallet-raped just for setting foot inside a theater, so fuck you guys.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 19:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 15:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my vote for comment of the year...lmao  

I totally just used this line at work.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 15:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont let it get you down.  I just turned 39...just divorced...LOST A HOUSE THAT I HAD OWNED SINCE 1992 in the fucking mess.  I went from 'walking on water' at work to barely putting out.  Its been a rough year, but I am finally over it I think.  I live in a nice apartment in the city now, no yard to mow, dating an amazing and beautiful woman.  I almost feel...and this is going to sound weird, but I feel liberated, like I can make my own choices now.  I am starting to love life now.  You look like you are going to be fine...the sense of humor...the lava lamp.  This is an opportunity!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 21:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But after hours of hard work and careful thought, she was left devastated when she was told that 26 pages were blank because her pen had run out of ink. "  Fucking hilarious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 19:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> starring Marcel Schlutt as Dennis.  Get it?..Schlutt...Slut..?  Huh?  COme on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 21:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep...actually hurts to look at it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you fucking kidding me with this? FIXED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-10 18:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-09 06:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 15:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honesty upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 13:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what? I cant hear you...your shirt is too loud... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like a Boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-30 22:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somehow I doubt this, Digg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 15:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-28 17:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your idea of 'completely destroyed' is makes self look like a moron.  Yeah man...he annihilated that Jesus freak.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-26 16:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> totally got me....I didnt look at the link and I was thinking 'what the fuck, this has to be theonion'   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-09 03:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Chris? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-09 03:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> come on...one other person....just one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-09 03:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAMN YOU ALL....I have been hitting that back button for two days... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its shit like this GMAIL...seriously, does anyone else do this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-09 03:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 18:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> armchair dipshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 18:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It really is a standard process."  No such thing.  No way would any knowledgeable law enforcement officer with any amount of common sense attempt such a foolish thing.  

"No such device could be attached to a person's neck." are you referring to some sort of receiver to detonate the explosives?  If so, you could not be more wrong.  Referring to am IED/bomb?  Still, you could not be more wrong.  Receivers are very easy to hide...and neck-bombs, well this aint the first.

If this entire conversation were about something not attached to a human, then I might agree with some of your statements....but that isnt what we are dealing with.  

Go back to your desk.

Now I AM being a dick.  I have worked around firearms and explosives for most of my life.  I was in the US Army and I was a sworn police officer for years.  You obviously have no idea what you're talking about.  Maybe you know something about physics...I dont know...but you have zero training dealing with explosives.  I doubt you've ever held a gun.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because you (not you specifically) do not know the outcome.  Its impossible to determine with 100% certainty what is going to happen.  This might be ok for certain other explosives, but not one attached to a human beings neck.  You cannot generalize homemade explosive devices.  Maybe the creator accounted for that somehow, maybe he will remotely detonate....too many 'what-ifs' involved to risk it.  

And please accept my apology.  I sounded like a dick.  I really thought you were trolling.  Sincerely.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why did I just upvote this comment.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude...that was totally the bomber....shifty-eyed...nervous speech... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize this has to be a troll attempt, but seriously?  SERIOUSLY?  Dude, throw out your TV.....and your internet.  

"standard defusing tactic for bombs"...all bombs are different...created by different people with different areas of expertise or interest.  The bomber didnt pick this thing up at Walmart and you dont detonate anything near a person, much less near their face or head.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-13 15:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> consequences will never be the same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-07 04:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....which will be passed right along to the consumer...fuck you MS...fuck you.  Fuck you.  Seriously.  Fuck.  You. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 19:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> update...that was it.....thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 18:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> already using it...maybe it isnt configured correctly....but been using it for ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I REFUSE to even glance at any ad that does this or F YOU GIANT AD THAT I CANT GET RID OF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 17:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-27 18:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhhhh...swinging door and a counter-top, the cripples natural enemy.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-10 18:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ass butt plug, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-01 17:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He means hamas  http://www.thefreedictionary.com/Hamas .  They've been in the news a lot lately...although I'm not sure what that has to do with Hurra Torpedo  covering Total Eclipse. Oh well.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-01 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually wrestled a crack whore...well, she looked like a crack whore.  Turned out it was PCP.  Bitch beat the daylights out of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 22:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> totally asked for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-15 15:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This IS great.  If my alcoholic father had handed me that, I would have cried and hugged him...something I have never done.  Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-13 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, he certainly went about it the hard way.  You get basically the same thing and all you have to do is wake-up in the morning and be your douchebag self.  Neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-13 15:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude..its a shirt with hundreds of tiny pics of YOU.  THAT is fucking awesome!  Only a baller could rock a shirt like that!  YOU ARE THE MAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-13 15:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear the hell out of those shirts....but I'm a total badass.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-05 19:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teacher was in the right.  Student was kicking a person on the ground.  The teachers actions may have saved a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 4-year-old nieces expression when I swore to her that the adult-sized bite in her sandwich just "mysteriously appeared there" while she was in the bathroom.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-11 17:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-03 14:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only are you physically beautiful, but you are beautiful on the inside....its obvious that you have a great attitude!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-22 15:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think your phone had anything to do with this.  An officer has a responsibility to calibrate his equipment (at least) everyday and to record the date and time of this.  He should also have recorded the date and time that his tuning forks were calibrated.  If you can show reasonable doubt that the officers equipment may not be working properly, then a judge cannot convict you.  That officer was half-ass at best.  He would have lost every case that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Local Newspaper is Run by Hugh Hefner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-09 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-01 01:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you not own a firearm?  If so, get it and prepare to protect yourself.  If not, just remain calm.  Dont get excited...wait, you are already excited.  So, stop it.  Seriously.  If you are  afraid, thats ok.  Accept it.  Fear is natural and normal.  Dont fight the fear.  Just try to remain calm.  You called emergency services which was the right thing to do.  Now just wait.  You dont necessarily have to act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-21 01:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least.  Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-21 01:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a former police officer, and just a guy with good sense, if those are the actual facts of what happened, then that police officer is a piece of shit.  A piece of shit.  One more time: that police officer is a piece of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 02:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the first memory that came to mind "i'll nail yer tits to the table"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-05 05:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that'll learn him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 17:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its true....I sit here all day jockeying this awesome dual 20" LCD setup, drinking coffee, and impressing my coworkers with my reddit karma points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, I dont actually bench-press them, but I could....as long as their combined weight isnt more than my bench max of 300lbs.  (totally bragging for the ladies here)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 14:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well said! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 13:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss Call For Help and Screensavers.....dont really miss Kevin Rose so much though...Sara Lane, Norton, even Leo.....but not Rose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 13:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one of my all time favorite shows.  They just dont make enough episodes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 13:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> our buildings/grounds guys set out some of these traps:  http://tomcatbrand.com/product/29-spin-trap-for-mice

So far I resisted the urge to disassemble and examine one of them, but only because I feel like all mouse traps, even unused traps, are dirty and diseased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 13:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bench-press the other IT guys in my department.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-02 23:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUNNY...I get that all the time...not sure if its a compliment or not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-02 19:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from a sign in posted in the kitchen at work....thats me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> do not feed the mouse....or the IT guy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-02 19:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-01 22:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> their top priority is whichever big company has the most money.  I could sell bags of shit and call it the fountain of youth if I crammed a few bucks in the right hand, which would, no doubt, already be fishing around in my pocket.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-01 22:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nutritional information label on the back does state the serving size is 3 pieces and that there are approx 6 servings inside.  Thats 18 pieces, which is correct, but who reads that?  I'm buying chocolate, I am not concerned with nutritional info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-01 22:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got it....and is that your real name?  Funny sending a mostly-empty box of Whitman Sampler candy to an unsuspecting gentleman.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-01 22:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, to be honest....I did eat ALL of that top row, so I dont know if its fair to say I was 100% dissatisfied....maybe 50%... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-01 22:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-01 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ahead and have a seat right over there.  I'm Chris Hanson with Dateline NBC.  We're doing a show on adults who....well, you know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
