<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4858</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. The UK is allowed to check passports but must allow entry to EU citizens and their families. http://ukandeu.ac.uk/the-uk-and-the-schengen-system/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 19:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the description as a cowardly, weed smoking, cat owner that lives in a basement, what do you think the odds are that Will uses reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 10:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine how outraged you would be if Scotland turned round and told most of the supporters of celtic and hibs to get out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 09:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh heh there isn't a single professional army in the world that wouldn't love to fight gun nuts it would be like extreme training or sport. Yeah you have extremely capable gun nuts on youtube nutnfancy or keanu but most gun nuts would be dead after 1 day of no sleep and a 10 mile walk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much water storage capacity. You only need 2 bottles and no camelback type thing. Ditch - 2 cycling jerseys, 1 bike shorts, 1 towel, 1 power pack and the bowl. You will probably pass several shops every day so don't carry too much food  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is trade between EU and USA/Japan/Australia/China etc and there is no free movement of labour needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So huff post nice clickbait title but how many people asked google and how old were they? When the daily mail runs the same shit with "mohammed now the most popular name in UK" it is the same shit. Nice way to twist data to confirm your narrative which is exactly what created this brexit issue in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at first they helped Erdogan destroy the deep state but that backfired fairly quickly on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO that would be St paddys day in USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 12:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you are spot on the Darian attempt to have Scotland's own colonies and empire bankrupted it and forced it to join with England but then all its massive wealth and success came because it embraced the British empire. Sometimes this is forgotten by Scots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 11:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm name the elite Scottish formations and don't say scots guards because they are not elite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 11:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then prospered by virtually running India and building all the stuff for the Empire plus growing tobacco with slaves across the atlantic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 11:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But only a small minority of exports go to the EU. 64% of Scottish exports is to the UK and less than half of the rest goes to the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 11:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sovereignty and control over your own future is the view of the Brexit camp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 11:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit posturing to try and shore up her vote amongst more "conservative" voters by saying she wants a stronger military. Some of  her voter base don't like her position on migrants/refugees and paying for southern europe via the European Central Bank and the Euro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 11:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be able to fit a rear rack if you get an adjustable one and perhaps mount it from the seat post using p clips. Your main problem will be heel clearance on rear panniers so perhaps use front panniers on the rear rack. They will still carry enough gear for you but be narrower giving better heel clearance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 10:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK his journalists lied, stole, harassed people and hacked phones. They bribed public employees for info. They destroyed evidence and lied under oath. Most people suspect that many of the higher up executives who were found innocent may not have been so innocent. Public outrage was so great he had to kill one of his sunday papers. Of course he says he had no idea and all the criminal activity was done at a low level by employees, no one close to him could possibly have known...May not be enough to convict him or his executives but more than enough for people to form opinions on his organisation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 09:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used schwalbe city jet for 1300 mile tour last year no problems and very cheap compared to tyres that will take you from cairo to capetown. They were 8 instead of 30 and weigh less. I did intend to get marathons but glad I didn't for the mostly road and limited gravel track on my tour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to say it...calm down please... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 12:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't really understand what this is about. It is an extremely local story about the little guy standing up to the 1% on a beach in a remote part of Scotland. I don't think the farmer is passing comment or trying to influence the USA election. And trump obviously does care about Scotland or he wouldn't be over there trying to hustle his golf course and wouldn't have spent lots of time and money on the courts trying to block renewable energy schemes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 12:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the example you choose to show modern journalism is a joke? The story is in a subsection of a subsection of UK news on the BBC website.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 11:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Juggalos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 11:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that your post says Florida is insane, ignorant and all on drugs then the comments only dispute your temperature claims. Guess Florida is crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 11:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a while ago and you murdered the guy who ordered it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 10:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one suggested that first world status would be taken from you. The ultra rich will just keep getting richer and the bottom segment will just keep getting larger. First world status encompasses the whole society. Nigeria looks pretty first world to the Nigerian ultra rich.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 10:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Covert hambone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angry Man Who Told Muslim Woman To 'Speak English' Gets Brilliantly Corrected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all these comments are some next level trolling and I watch the video and it is a massive spider/horror worm/alien fetus then well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment will be mentioned at your trial and the media will pretend not to see the ironic humour in username </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police reveal first words of Brit 'who tried to assassinate Donald Trump' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 11:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are if they know the "rules" but it isn't the west but seems that it is enough to give a false sense of security to westerners. But yes if you go with your family to have a holiday or on business then totally safe if you think you are in Thailand or Ibiza it can go wrong quickly (as of course it can there too). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 10:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrifically many of the foreign workers go on the promise of a hard but fair job  - maid /construction worker with long hours but agreed pay, time off, leave to go home etc but that is just to lure them there. When they arrive their passports are taken, their terms and conditions of employment change at the whim of the employment agents, it is made very clear to them that they have a large debt for being allowed to ship over to UAE for work they will have to pay that off or their families will be homeless and they will be jailed in UAE. They have no rights in the host countries. At best it is hard work but because they have no rights they die/get injured due to terrible working conditions or get raped and abused as domestic staff. Many go willingly as foreign workers but once there become forced labour with no option but to stay and work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Bali they have a huge carnival to scare the ghosts of to the mountains then the next night the whole place is in black out lock down so the spirits don't get attracted back by lights etc. After that it is back to normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as London.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UKIP has 1 MP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 09:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would hunt you for sport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farage isn't even an MP. His party has 1 MP. Even if the vote goes brexit Farage is still nothing. Comments here talk about it as if Farage would become PM if the vote is to leave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Student visas have always existed, in fact there are many non EU students already in Edinburgh proving there is no problem with student visas for those outside UK/EU.

But quite a high chance that Brexit would eventually trigger another Scottish Independence referendum which might see Scotland leave the EU as part of UK, then leave the UK and then try to rejoin EU. All of this would take so long you could be onto a second PhD by the time it is sorted! Enjoy Edinburgh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or perhaps if there was more honesty about the numbers and effects of immigration then people might feel more like go team europe! It was labour councils that finally got the Blair/brown govt to own up to the bullshit numbers it was touting for numbers of migrants back when this issue got mainstream. It took some brutal honesty from the local labour MP to turn the tide in the area the BNP won council seats. The BNP wouldn't have won any seats had people been more honest about immigration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2013 April: As part of Operation Pitsford 11 Muslim extremists are jailed for a plotting terror attack involving suicide Bombers.

2015 5 December: Three people are stabbed at Leytonstone tube station in east London, with one person suffering severe knife injuries; police subsequently announced that they were treating the stabbings as a 'terrorist incident'.

2015 12 Feb : Liverpool Ricin Plot: Mohammed Ammar Ali, an I.T. worker who rented a flat in Liverpool as a base of operations, attempted to buy 500 mg of Ricin, which could kill an possible 1,400 people, using the darkweb. He was instead delivered a white powder by the FBI. Evidence was also found of attempts to purchase rabbits or chinchillas to test the poison out on.

2015 7 July : Attempted anniversary London 7/7 bomb plot. Mohammed Rehman and Sana Ahmed Khan were found guilty of possession of 10 kg of Urea Nitrate. Rehman called himself the 'silent bomber' and asked his twitter followers to choose between the Westfield Shopping Centre or the London Underground for the planned suicide bomb.

Plus look at all the Muslim UK citizens who left the UK to rape and murder for ISIS and happily update their social media. The threat is real but it is as real for all British citizens as ISIS and the like kill far more Muslims than any other grouping. It is less of a threat than the 70s but most of that activity was in the province. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus there has been a lot of Nationalist terrorist activity including murders in Northern Ireland (which also increases the threat assessment). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA spreading freedom again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every non British person in the UK has not been fearing the referendum. Plenty of other nationalities in the world beyond the EU and even then if Brexit happens Eu citizens will have ages to adjust. If you have a job get a UK work visa they will still need all the workforce just they will give them work visas. On holiday? There are many bi lateral agreements that provide visa free travel and get you a 6 month stamp in your passport. In fact unless you are trying to claim benefits or get free health care I don't think much will change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 15:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he is being charged with murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are so fringe they are nowhere near electable. The BNP managed to get a few people elected to some a couple of councils but in the light of day they were seen to be incapable then the inevitable in fighting starts and the group collapsed, the same happen on the extreme left political groups. They form a group then dissolve. All very peoples front of judea, the splitters https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WboggjN_G-4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 12:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It drops in value by thousands of dollars the second it leaves the show room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 11:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irony being in the 70s women activists smuggled contraception into Southern Ireland from Uk Northern Ireland because sex toys, condoms, the pill etc were illegal in Southern Ireland due to the grip of the Roman Catholic Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 10:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really isn't a referendum on David Cameron, if anything it is showing how the general public has a growing mistrust of the establishment. By establishment I mean all political parties and all special interest groups that push an agenda like Oxfam etc charities/lobbyists are very established and deeply woven into the political establishment (which is a good thing). The average person in the street isn't very political and the most common reaction to statements from brexit or remain campaigns is, "Well they would say that wouldn't they." But the underlying thought is the UK political machine lied about immigration numbers and costs for 20 years so why believe anything they say now. Likewise the EU they have lied so often that why believe anything they say now. It is the distrust that people resent and why the Brexit camp is doing so well  when people thought it would disappear and the referendum was a done deal for remain. I think the public support for brexit has surprised the politicians/media. Also there is the fact that UKIP got more votes than the SNP but 53 less MPs so there is some silent public resentment in England at that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subjugating most of the planet? National pride might not go as you expect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 10:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Alhamdullilah [praise be to God] the people haven't caught you, or it's high building for you.'

You know like when ISIS videoed themselves throwing gays from high buildings. http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=f6d_1435932798 here is 1 of the many examples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 10:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you have never been to Scotland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 10:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fruit = sugar = carbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 10:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 19:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy the censorship is driving people to Donald just like real life then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not surprising but honestly I just don't care anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 08:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just reply to them on twitter or fb and let ISIS sort them out or drone strike them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he was a bit racist with all the white devil stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aldous Huxley's Brave New World (written 1932) addresses these very ideas. A perfect companion piece to Orwell's 1984 (written 1949) combined both books offer a perfect warning of ideological purity in practice. Both books never date and feel as relevant today as ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 20:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So all the guns are keeping Oklahoma free /s? But the article is stupid as this has nothing to do with common law ("English countries"?) but more to do with a corrupt system and apathetic population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia is not a threat to the west. Right now Turkey is more of a threat to western european lifestyles than Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 10:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect by now the Russians just hand him press releases to read out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 10:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really isn't and hasn't been since the 60s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 11:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True fact the vodka keeps your body relaxed when you crash making it safer just like how cats can survive high falls by being loose on landing. Insects also use vodka to survive high impacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 11:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> turkey fine turn on oven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 10:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not where I live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 15:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are so many wives and daughters who are also doctors and engineers playing a rape game in Europe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay $37....probably in Sweden
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Norway beefing up its border defences now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweden is so fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they exist within a structure that limits their free will to the point that the structure needs removed allowing people to make free choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is privileged about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High school and university are different, wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone is uk based or can access bbc iplayer you can listen to a 2 part dramatisation of Brave New World here - http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b07bt9qj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 11:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the antithesis of progressive development instead of reducing gender difference and removing sexualisation it reinforces it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 11:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am conflicted by your /s. Was the whole post /s? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 10:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are probably referring to WW2 (genocidal war) but the history and development of Europe is littered with small massacres and wars over religion and political dominance. People take the progressive society of western Europe for granted. More likely than the germans firing up the ovens for the muslims, is that states will begin to bring religion under control and restrict the interpretation of the koran and perhaps license muslim preachers/mosques. For example making it acceptable for people to renounce Islam. That is how Christianity was tamed by the state and it works. And for all the bleeding hearts crying "thats racist!" lets not pretend they have the same freedoms of religion in Iran or Saudi, try preaching against the establishment there and see what happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 10:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the feminists who join in with the Muslim calls for separate swimming not see the motives and long game? Do they not see it is at odds with everything they stand for? 

In the 1990s I knew a UK male student who went to an orienteering competition in Sweden where at the end they had large mixed gender open air showers in the forest. Everyone just got naked, fast shower then into warm dry clothes. That is progressive to break the slightly perverted view that the naked body can only be sexual rather than normal. Sweden is going backwards fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 10:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the entire opposite of what swedish culture used to be and what made it such a great country and ironically made it so appealing to muslim immigrants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 11:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I heard in this context was referring to the USA Tea Party movement years ago. What proclaimed to be a "grassroots" movement against the "elites", big govt and crony capitalism etc quickly became a Koch Bros funded political group aimed at giving them more control inside the Republican Party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 18:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this before or after they introduced the netflix continue watching screen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 12:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cartels and monopolies are all moderated and legislated against in capitalist economies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 10:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZiVe8qePd3Y 
Tessela - Hackney Parrot one of the best from the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 09:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blair ignored his military leaders, sent them to war underfunded and under equipped. On the initial invasion there was not enough ammunition for anyone but the very front troops. Logistics and engineers were crossing into Iraq with 20 bullets each. Whilst the military is to blame for the old crap vehicles, rubbish body armour, old radios, dodgy weapons etc Blair refused to allow the military to begin preparations for the war (ordering transport, organising the logistics, generally preparing xthousand troops for future deployment) which takes months until it was months overdue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 09:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The jobs he gets now are the pay off for the orders he followed when he was Prime Minister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 12:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 12:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left has a real problem addressing inherent issues in Islam. Islam seems to embrace so many left wing principles like charity, community and anti-capitalism plus the bonus points of being anti American/anti-Israel for the more radical and is an easy demonstration of non racism. But it does seem to get a pass in Europe from the political left that white European institutions do not. Separate schools, status of women, domestic violence, racism, acceptance of slavery, the fact it is a religion at all etc. Now some of these things can be leveled at extreme crony corporate capitalism but Islam is the only philosophy or method of organisation that gets a pass on criticism from the left. Left wing supporters and Islamists have joined together to fight oppression in the past but the Islamists usually end up crushing the left after achieving their aims. The Iranian revolution is a perfect example and perhaps to some extent the dismantling of the deep state in Turkey leading to emperor Erdogan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 12:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah because it would have been so much better under the benevolent Japanese Empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 09:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know already but just aren't dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 12:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The boys mother confronted the teacher and said it would remain secret if the teacher cut all contact with the boy and resigned from the school (PP offered). The teacher said she would but lied and kept having sex with the student. The mother then told school which lead to police and then 12 months jail and 10 years on a list (PP denied). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 12:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also she knew and had non sexual contact with the boy when he was 15 so it was taken that she "groomed" him underage and waited till he was 16 before abusing her position of trust further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
