<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 14:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saving these comments this is good shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 14:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word. If you are listening to a beat you just finished of course it's going to sound whack. You probably spent hours and hours listening to the same loop mixing it to sound perfect. If you leave and come back it'll sound alot better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 13:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parts unknown  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 13:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are all genres of music allowed to post?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every kid in Canada learns about this in school, it's a widely known thing in canada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even watch the video you're replying to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 00:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you find out you were psychotic if  you don't mind me asking?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 16:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn man thanks for such a good response. I'm definitely leaning toward the 2000. Thanks for the tip on the fx card though that's good to know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 00:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome brother thanks for the info! Il def message you if I got any questions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 21:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks alot to everyone who replied I gathered alot of information from this! Lots of good inside views from mpc owners exactly what I was looking for!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mpc 500 vs mpc 1000 vs mpc 2000xl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 15:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently a maschine user but have always wanted an mpc. I like the idea of not needing a laptop to create a whole track. Tried using the search bar multiple times but reddits search sucks. I'm looking for mpc owners to give me advice on which I should cop. Honestly I love the idea of a 2000xl it seems like the pinnacle of mpcs. I've ruled out the 2500 because I've done so research and alot of people say it doesn't have that mpc sound to it because they changed the hardware somehow. I also really like the idea of a 500 because it is so portable but it lacks the 16 pads and the screen is very small. That's why I think the 1000 is the best of both worlds. I'm looking for current owners that can give me advice on what to do and what they like about their mpc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 15:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lower the bit rate and make your own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 00:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the longest gif I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 23:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make money off royalties everytime it plays on the radio or in a club or on Spotify he gets paid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word that's the way it should be  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, just wierd if he was actually cripping I don't think he'd want anyone yelling suwoo on his tracks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Los awesome he does and I swear I've heard it in others can't find the exact tracks though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schoolboy q also yells suwoo in his songs I've always felt like he jumps from side to side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been going on waaay before that. Every producer should have a tag. Even of its simple like Erick arc Elliots laugh. It's so that people can recognize the producer even if his credits aren't in the title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go try and make a beat from a sample. Scratch that, go find a sample that hasn't been used before. Sampling is a are that takes talent and practise. It's alot easier to make a generic drill/trap beat then to make a sample based beat. Even Proclamation by the underachievers straight rips the rolling stones, it's still takes talent to re create that beat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great headphones but the cord is sooo damn long! Have to wrap it up so many times to stuff in my pocket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's true, I'm pretty sure you can automate the mix % setting I could just automate that to 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had and job and sold dope all through high school never really had to spend money on weed I'd always just sell enough to smoke for free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make music, go for a run, work out, video games, cook, clean your room, jerk off haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smoke alone probably 90% of the time. I've been doing it for 5 years now too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You buy it in grams you can usually get a half gram too. It'll be anywhere from 40 to 80 bucks gram depending on the quality. Look for clear Amber or yellow colors that you can see through. Less bubbles and it being clear are good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 00:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mpk mini is great for its price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 00:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just record in your closet with some blankets on the wall  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bypass effect for a pattern? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 23:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to bypass an effect only in a specific pattern? This would help me out alot if anyone knows the answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 22:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have rokit 5s but always busy out my ath's for bass  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/makinghiphop there's a how do I make this sound thread someone will know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Refugees of reddit, what is your story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 17:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either acapellas or hard eq and filters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 09:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 07:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well me personally I do that as a challenge occasionally and I'm sure others do as well, as this is a good way to improve sampling and experiment with different techniques. I couldn't see someone making all their beats like this but if you can/want to go for it, nobodies going to tell you you can't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 07:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked and yea it should be under audio and midi settings  midiand then select maschine mk2 and make sure it says on. Check this first because it's possible to be another problem but it's highly likely this is the problem you're having  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still the same answer...  Their are no rules to sampling. If you can chop that into a beat that sounds good then go with it, no one is making rules about what you can and can't sample  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 06:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Midi and audio settings go to routing and select maschine in to on I believe I'm drunk and can check if that's not right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 06:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in, imma work on this all day tomorrow and post it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmfao yes you can dumbass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 21:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very over asked question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I went to smoke signals the guy was really douchy and wouldn't stop talking about weed. Kept trying to make me buy expensive ass art pieces. They had a good selection but the staff was whack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bongia is a new one just opened! I've got a couple pieces from them they have good prices. Cannabis emporium is near it too that place has lots of stuff but a little bit higher prices. This n that is another one with good prices but it's smaller. Scotties are always good as well I believe their are a couple in ottawa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 19:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No have you mastered the ones in fl studio? Do you find that they don't work well enough or you can't get what you want out of them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha seen this exact paragraph so much lately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> subject9063 - Further </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be on my flair il link it in a sec
Edit: https://m.soundcloud.com/ustincox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of these and the amount of work you have to do everytime you start it up just to trigger samples isn't worth it. I use it for the keys only since I got my maschine. It can be done but why not just use your keyboard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word I'm a producer from Toronto let's work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 21:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just use the basic sine wav that comes with maschine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to the underachievers or flatbush zombies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always has this wierd ass message too haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a producer from Toronto but currently living in Ottawa for school, let's link up sometime next year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 18:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what you want out of your work flow. I personally do everything in maschine. Occasionally il export to ableton for more mixing but you can definitely do it all in maschine. It will take some time but just sitting down every day and fucking around with it will help you figure out how you want to go about it. You can find videos on YouTube of different work flows for maschine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 18:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorta confused about what your asking. Do you know how to sample with your maschine? You have the samples so what is your question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> subject9063 - Take You to Church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 00:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he meant he blew the smoke into the trashcan [6] oops haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such an awesome pipe! Wow it says this is almost his 3000th pipe he's made </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only got me to about a [5] but I'm gonna smoke a bowl soon it'll probably hit me good then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just curious if you had that as an exact amount or something haha. I've never thought of weed and alcohol like that :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh wasn't sure if it was hash or some  foreign fruit :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be the equivalent of a non drinker drinking 3 liters of vodka

Where did you get this from? 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/leaves and /r/petioles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you blow your bowl into a trashcan hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still don't know what I'm looking at </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't you just pack a bowl and put the joint in it? It's called a time bomb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I said surprisingly potent...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you didn't spend any money on weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I live 2500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I think this is sick, for a community of stoners this place isn't very friendly or supportive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put in about 4 or 5 grams of vaped weed and stems, extracted into coconut butter and made 5 cookies. I'm already at a [3] from eating the rest of the dough out of the bowl and just ate a cookie hoping to be around a [7] soon :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made some cookies from leftover vaped weed! Turned out surprisingly potent and tasty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Ottawa in a very old building I've never had a problem with noise and never got any complaints. My walls and floors are all concrete I don't think this statement is the same for all Canadian apartments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Original] subject9063 - Take You to Church Instrumental </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 16:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 03:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea bro forsure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 02:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only way to get it without the copy for your maschine is illegaly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit this is dope as fuck I followed you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods never do anything though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vinyl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The look of a content kitty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 20:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thank you for this I never knew that had a name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 15:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at that one google search and I have found 10 different daws....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 15:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what I'm doing today
edit: probably the weirdest track I've ever made https://soundcloud.com/ustincox/strange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 05:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude do whatever you want, as long as it's not making you alot of money no one cares. People remix current popular songs everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 05:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do landscaping it's decent money and a workout  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 04:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really that new, and that's the annoying part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 22:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't find your song but I found the lyrics 
Tell them haters stop all the noise that they makin' 
Make me lay 'em down, after that, it's no waking 
Don't make me pop off, you don't wanna pop off  
You don't wanna end up the one getting knocked off
Tell them haters stop all the noise that they making 
 Make me lay 'em down up, after that, it's no waking 
Don't make me P-O-P O-double-F  When them things ring, your boy never stress Beretta, 
yes, keep it with me

Maybe they had someone record it just for the show?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss old Sosa so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FL studio  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao I don't even have to click on it just look at the url </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No thanks, you have it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every song that features drake is regarded to as "drakes new song" even though it's not his song he's just a feature  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pitch it down and timestretch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gospel sample sythesised in something iris 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These don't even sound Christmas-y I don't understand the point of this post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't want to sound like I'm complaining but I think it would be nice to have the samples in wav format for the daws that don't accept mp3s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Original] subject9063 - Further, looking for feedback on a beat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never heard of anyone getting accepted to the police academy here in Canada without taking a 2 year college police foundations course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's what I've been doing in the meantime! Hopefully I can get it repaired soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was afraid of that, thanks for the vst though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know if you can make a stereo sample/sound mono in maschine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 16:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to get my bass right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 16:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nvm I found it under the effects folder not vst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 15:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *mitts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 14:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send me a message if you still need help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 14:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John mayer, Freddie Gibbs, pink Floyd, yung lean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 14:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I make this sound thread.... Those keys sound like nexus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 06:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get fake dicks for this too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 05:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I have a micro korg I've always wanted to try this but my midi port is broken :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The water flowing sound?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice there are names redacted... People are snitching  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GS9 Indictment Transcrips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 01:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Cause 3 has the best explosions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks alot this is exactly what I was looking for  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 22:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that is how I interpreted it as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just cause 2 was alot more difficult  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
