<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add on Mucinex, while it doesn't actually help  the sperm swim better, the fact that it makes your CM more liquid (when taken properly, with enough water etc.) can help them get closer to where they need to be. I definitely noticed a difference when I was taking it (don't produce much, if any CM on my own usually). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't shut up either (echoing u/WafflefriesAndaBaby and u/chaunceythebear ) so he knows pretty much all that is going on. He's an engineer so he likes to know what's going on and is getting more and more interested as the process goes on month after month. Of course I make sure not to treat him solely as a sperm factory but I will tell him when it's time to really go at it! He doesn't mind hahaha :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CD14. I find the first portion of my cycle to be so long, feels like forever ago that this cycle started. I'm going to start monitoring CM again and taking Mucinex and peeing on OPKs. I don't know how I feel about that: on one hand I want that info to help me know if/when I will ovulate, but on the other hand doing all that and trying to have sex every 2 days gets tiring after a month :/ We'll see how it goes, I have to try and not stress too much... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just chiming in to say happy anniversary and enjoy that drink! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, good luck! I also find the beginning of a cycle is quite uneventful! CD14 here and nothing happening either, but to be fair I've got freakishly long cycles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice!! Get at those hills :D

I'm still waiting for a positive OPK, never got one so far in 6 months (albeit only 2 completed cycles, but...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, that's great news! :)

ETA: Lol at the pic, I love it :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry you're going through this... I don't have any useful advice except be kind to yourself and allow yourself to feel whatever you'll feel... *internet hugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm really happy about it, feels good to have actual proof that we're in this together (I knew it but you know, the ring kinda symbolizes that in a more concrete manner).

No wedding plans yet, we're both low-key and honestly, for now being engaged is just fine for me. We're thinking about a late-summer country wedding, nothing too big or fancy, just close family and friends to celebrate our love. I'd rather keep my money for saving for a baby, taking a trip, etc. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever works best for you! I find that testing too frequently for me makes it worse, I question the BFNs and all, so I'd rather steel myself for the worst and not test too often, but I agree if I was you I probably would not wait 2 days! Fingers crossed :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, I'm just impressed you managed to keep the test in your pocket during your meeting without peeking!
I would test again in 2 days if I was you, especially since you could not look at the test at the 5-minute mark (or whatever time is suggested on that test). Good luck on that soldier! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish you get answers (and good ones at that). Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CD13 here and already feeling over this cycle. Ovulated at CD41 last time, so I don't feel like starting to pee on OPKs right away because this could be long. I am not feeling this cycle, I'm getting tired of all the waiting and hoping and the crushing disappointment at my body... I'm feeling quite silly as there is hope still, and I actually got engaged this weekend haha so I'm happy about that, but I feel like TTC is sucking the life out of me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, nice to see a good outcome to your story! Congrats :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats to you and I so so hope it sticks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I know the regular Astroglide doesn't work for TTC but will look into a TTC-friendly version! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Just giving you a shred of hope! I don't have PCOS (that I know of), but my cycles are super long and irregular and I've only ovulated once in 6 months... and that was on CD41! So I just popped in here to say that CD25 does not mean you won't ovulate this cycle.

I also think that trying to regulate your body with lifestyle and diet changes is a good thing. I mean it can't hurt to get a bit healthier right, even if it doesn't fix all your problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, congrats!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, yeah! I thought we'd be fine without, but I'll have to reevaluate! Apart from Preseed, are there any other good brands? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that definitely seems like it might have helped. Anyhow, I'll be asking for answers on that (I was at 3.7 in November). Thank you for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Thankful Thursdays are always pretty similar, but it's always a good thing to remind ourselves.
Thankful for DH who loves my like I am, even on my bad days, even when I'm being a nut.
Thankful for TFAB and the girls on here who answer questions, support, and commiserate (with a side of snark ahaha).
Thankful I now have a 4-day week, even if my day off is to work on my Master's- staying home in my PJs beats driving to the office 100%.
Today I am also thankful that my 4-year-old Great Dane is happy and healthy, currently sleeping on my couch. I found out this morning that one of her "younger brothers" (same 2 parents but younger litter) has died of cancer during the night... He wasn't even 3 years old and got diagnosed only 2 weeks ago :( I can't imagine the pain of losing my baby at such a young age...
Lastly, thankful to be (mostly) healthy and able to go for a run when I want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't agree more! I've only been on here for 2 months but already feel like a veteran. 
P.S. - So sorry for any annoying newbie posts or comments I may have done when I arrived on here. Even today I'm never sure my interventions are useful or relevant, but I figure I'll get told if I do make a mistake! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't know about the reason for the different thresholds. You got meds for a TSH at what level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for your 2 CPs, but also glad you got to see your doctor so fast. I hope things move along and your questions are answered. I find that it's always hard to get the *exact* time of day from doctors, you know? Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True that. Not putting your life on hold is hard when you're a planner. After 6 months and nothing worth shit to show for it except my sanity which is being tested more than usual, I'm trying not to think about possibly being pregnant or not for future events. Signed up for 3 races, including my 2nd half-marathon at the end of August, and will also plan a trip with DH (although we will try to go somewhere Zika-free, there's a difference between living and just plain taking unnecessary risks). I might also go for getting a new pair of pants, something I'd been holding off on since August (but what if they only fit me for a few months? -_- ). It's a daily struggle though, I keep thinking "well if I get pregnant this cycle I'll have a November baby"... Ugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Canada I was told they do not treat below 5, unless there are some other underlying issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost exactly in the same situation as you, my TSH level in November was 3.7, so in the "normal" range, but when I got to reading about Subclinical Hypothyroidism and how TSH higher than 2-2.5 could be bad for conceiving I was planning on bringing it up with my doctor, but also need more credible sources than, "some strangers on the interwebs told me so" ;) I think I read something to that effect on the Thyroid Foundation Canada [website.](http://www.thyroid.ca/pregnancy_fertility.php)

Also on [here!] (http://hypothyroidmom.com/infertility-miscarriage-and-subclinical-hypothyroidism/)

ETA: More details: my mom has Hashimoto's and my maternal Grandma had nodules removed from her thyroid, so I am wary of my thyroid from the start. Also, I'm always tired, often cold, feeling under the weather for close to a year now and have only had 2 very short periods in 6 months since stopping HBC (also pretty sure I only ovulated once in 6 months). I think all that gives me ammunition to ask my doctor to pursue the TSH investigation a bit further. Hope this can help you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woot! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CD9, nothing exciting going on. We had sex yesterday and ouch, it wasn't my finest hour at all... For some strange reason I was super dry just like when I was on HBC. Well that fuckin sucked haha, just needed to share. Looks like I really do need Mucinex to have some CM at all :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll use your words as courage to ask questions and advocate for myself :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll use your words as courage to ask questions and advocate for myself :) I'm always afraid of seeming too pushy.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! Life is definitely unfair sometimes! I wish they could understand, but then again, I couldn't deal with myself and my moods if I was him :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, it is frustrating, especially because I'd like answers, but I'm not sure exactly *what* to ask for, and of course I'm afraid to be overreacting. Also don't want to harrass my doctor haha, I've left 2 messages for her and am still waiting for her call :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy your results are positive! I understand the worry of being afraid that you won't be able to get pregnant, I've had that nagging worry in the back of my mind since I was a teen (never had regular periods). Good luck on your AI! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, will definitely look into it. My pregnant best friend is being followed by a midwife so I'll try to ask her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I haven't actually tried seeing a midwife. I think I'll reserach that a bit. My family doctor actually wasn't *that* dismissive when I went to see her after 3 months off HBC and no period. She ordered basic bloodwork and an ultrasound and told me to go back and see her 3 months later (February) if things were still not moving. I consider that 2 very short periods in 6 months is something to be looked at and will try to see her again quite soon, but I'm stressed because I don't know exactly what to ask her other than "Please tell me what the fuck is wrong with my body, NOW!" Lol, I feel a bit crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because other people may have bigger issues does not diminish yours, just wanted to remind you of that. I've been feeling extra-stressed about this TTC and extra-scared that I won't be able to get pregnant naturally since the beginning, as I never had regular periods at all (before HBC and since coming off of it). I felt silly for being such an emotional roller-coaster during my first cycle (which lasted 106 days!), and tried to be more mellow during cycle 2 (55 days).. But now I'm on cycle 3 in 6 months and that feeling is still there. DH wants a baby and of course is a bit impatient, but he is not the one temping and peeing on sticks and getting ultrasounds and analysis every shred of symptoms, so he can't 100% understand. At least we have TFAB and all the ladies and info on here ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yay, I knew it was coming up but I'm glad to see it's ON! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my God, that's really truly messed up. I'd be fuckin pissed if I was you :/ I hope she doesn't get pregnant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Always fun to actually be doing something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, exactly. :/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CD8 here. Nothing new on my end (as usual lol). I just feel like nothing is happening and time passes so slow, probably because we've only had 1 chance to conceive so far in close to 6 months TTC, but at the same time time just flies by, as we are already 6 months in with nothing to show for it. I'm getting a bit impatient and would like some answers or some sign of my body functioning normally... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job about the book! At least there is some good news in your world :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, welcome to the club. I've never been fortunate enough to have regular ovulatory cycles, but as all the ladies here like to say, "You're regular until you're not". It's like our bodies enjoy trolling us. Let's hope your stay here is still short and that the next cycle is back to your normal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .... and I'm back to waiting to ovulate. Took 41 days last time, so I have no idea how long this is going to take. Hopefully I'll have enough OPKs haha (bought a big box with 50 strips just about when I O'ed last cycle), not that it helped me last time, as I never managed to get a positive OPK at all.
Also still waiting for news from my doctor, but I don't even think we'll be doing anything for now because it's been *only* 6 months (which feels like fucking forever) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, that's strange! Anyhow, my 106-day chart wasn't that pretty anyway! Just wanted to share my similar experience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are extreme temp changes normal during the beginning of a cycle? Currently CD7 and man oh man my temps are all over the place.
I also only had my period for like 2.5 days, is that ok or is it too short?
[My chart.] (https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I only just noticed that! My 106-day chart was just so damn long that I never even noticed... Oops [My looooong chart] (https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I KNEW IT!! I'm so happy for you, congrats! Been waiting to see this post since last week'd BFP thread :D
I haven't been on TFAB that long but so many of the women that welcomed me here have graduated, it feels nice, but I do hope you ladies continue lurking in on us :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm back! Took an almost weekly break from TFAB due to a combination of many things- busy at work (for once), started CD1 last Wednesday, and trying to advance on my Master's during my days off so when I was working on my laptop I actually turned off my Wi-Fi to eliminate the temptation to procrastinate :)
So I'm currently on CD7, but with my super long and irregular cycles I haven't yet started thinking about when my fertile period will possibly arrive... Last cycle I ovulated at CD41 so... I got a huge box of Easy@Home OPKs and will start testing next week just to make sure I don't miss it, although I never got a positive OPK last cycle.
That's it for my pointless ramble of the day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, that moment like, "Okay, we're really going for it now!" was a nice moment... Nice to see the TTC excitement is still there for #2! Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. Like, she makes it out like it's SO obvious that your CM is this way for X days, then you immediately see a clear change. Like, NO WAY is my body behaving that nicely for me to easily read all its signs hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> | Also, you might find it reassuring that people get pregnant all the damn time without knowing any of this.

Lol, I need to remind myself of this quite often, I can't fathom how that can possibly happen when it's so hard for so many of us here on TFAB to get knocked up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a mix of both actually, wonder/anger simultaneously at how little we are taught about our own bodies, and about how doctors don't talk about the many effects HBC can have on your body for a long time even when you stop it... I went off HBC in August 2016 and so far have had only 2 cycles (106 days, 56 days) in almost 6 months... I'm mostly pissed. Haven't even finished TCOYF yet, it's so much information to process all at once and has got me freaking out about all the things that could be wrong with me to explain my fucked up cycles... I will definitely finish it and probably re-read it though (I also read "The Impatient Woman's Guide to Getting Pregnant" twice, which has some of the same info in less detail) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhh crap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm up in Canada and my heart breaks for all the people affected by Trump already... I can't wrap my head around the fact that all this is really happening, today in 2017... *sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( I'm sorry it stops like this for now... I hope everything works out for you and your husband, whatever happens... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha oops, sorry for being a killjoy, just adding a teaser to that preview of 'The temps of our lives' ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh, enjoy that happy hour drink, and I wish you a beautiful temp rise due to ovulation and not alcohol! ;)
I will likely indulge with a drink or two tonight as well, woohoo! Celebrating the start of my reduced-workload to 4 days/week in hopes of finally being able to finish my Master's! The perks of CD1.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yes, yes. Taking my BBT had allowed me to see that I actually did ovulate this cycle, at CD41! I would have never guessed that without temping, and that 1-minute task every morning is so worth all the data! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would wait for tomorrow, if you're able to handle it. You can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG that's amazing, I'm so jealous!! I NEED to go there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG yes, I always get super exhausted during my period, it's THE biggest symptom I have during that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hola cycle buddy! CD1 of cycle 3! I never get to hang on to my cycle buddies with my freakishly long cycles so far (106 days, 55 days). Here's to being on the same cycle-train for now :) Wine for us this weekend!

ETA: Holy crap good luck on your interview!! Sounds like a big deal :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sitting at my desk with horrible period cramps... :/ Honestly I feel like every cycle I have worse pain than before.. I never even used to feel my period, and now it's like I've been stabbed continuously since last night... On another note, stupid question: if my temp dropped yesterday (but was still above coverline) and my period started last night at 10 p.m., is CD1 yesterday even though I spent all day without AF, or should I start counting today as CD1 (my temp continued dropping today, is now just under coverline)? Not that it changes anything much, but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler alert: My nice triphasic chart amounted to... *nothing*, except  AF's arrival at 15DPO. So much drama! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks... It feels like more than cycle 3, with each cycle being freakishly long! I just wish us all BFPs quite soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww... :( I was told not to lose hope before AF shows, but after getting BFNs at 9, 11 and 13 DPO I just knew that this wasn't the one... I hope next cycle is your lucky 13! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, sounds like you have choices to make... Whatever you choose I wish you the best of luck! And ouch, I hope I don't need to do an HSG, it doesn't sound like too much fun :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15DPO, temp drop today... Waiting for AF, waiting for cycle 3 to finally begin (6 months in), waiting for my doctor to call me back so that I can harrass her and ask what we should do now... Waiting for my workday to end (oops!). Waiting for this weekend because there will be wine (only upside to AF). Bring it on cycle 3! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, hello! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, a year is so loooong :( But yes, a year is better than never I suppose.. I guess we'll see! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in awe of your discipline for working out at 5 a.m.! I signed up for a PiYo class and phew I hate planks too! But goddamnit when my abs are sore the next day it feels damn good! Now if only they'd try to make a teeny tiny appearance it would be nice hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, I hope this pays off with answers for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just pissed in general haha, but that's nothing new for me.
The only upside I can think of? Wine. Lots of it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, had very irregular cycles from 13-16, when I started HBC. Stopped HBC in August and have had 2 cycles in 5.5 months so far... I'm just hoping things regulate at least a bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. I always planned to have kids before I'm 30, and I'm lucky to be in a great relationship, to have stable job and a house at 27 so that I'm in a place where we're trying to have kids right now because we're ready. But you know what? Things don't always go as planned, and what if I find myself at 30 with no kids yet? Well, the answer is: *nothing*. It doesn't change anything, a mom is a mom and we should all support each other.
Thanks for this group and the support you all provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you feel out, but you're not out until AF shows. Symptoms can mean nothing at all and change from cycle to cycle... I know it's not fun to have your hopes crushed each cycle, but 8DPO to me is not an endgame yet. I wish you the best of luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *hugs* That sucks, I get how you feel, the last year has been rough on me too, and the added stress of TTC and wanting something so badly but you can't control it is really hard to deal with. I really hope you get answers soon though, don't be scared to advocate for yourself with your doctor if need be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
