<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7982</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Russell Wilson mic'd up is edited to not show Julio hitting Richard Sherman's head on the final play. They edited in footage from earlier in the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, Google Fiber is now switching away from totally in-ground fiber, and instead to wireless. The install will just involve the customer placing an antenna on their house pointed at the source.  Because of this, roll-outs may happen sooner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bulletproof contracts is how.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I heard that there's only one more episode of H H before the take a break. Is that true? That sucks really bad. My Friday morning drives were always better than the rest, and now they are going to suck.

/u/geoffrvb, can you make the next season longer? I don't know, maybe like a year long? With two episodes a week, preferably? Gah I just really like this show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 02:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just cant let real life get in the way. Its like how Cersei hates Bronn in real life... That just disappointing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to help! Like I said, nothing against you personally, it's just very hard to change opinions when everybody shares it in the city. Hell I would guess 90% of alumni have the same opinion as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's improved a lot, to be honest, mostly because of the new principal. In eight years, Roger's graduation rate has increased [more than 30%.](http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2014/dec/12/spokane-high-school-graduation-rates-hit-83/). Furthermore, last year their football team made playoffs for the [first time in 39 years](http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2015/oct/30/rogers-reaches-postseason-for-first-time-as-gsl-me/).

The overall improvement at Rogers has been astounding, and it's honestly one of the things I wish more of Spokane realized. The Spokesman Review had a great article a couple of years ago on what they have done. 

http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2014/feb/27/achievement-pride-soar-at-spokanes-rogers-high/

Among the highlights:

Math scores improved dramatically at Rogers, from 21 percent passing in 2010 to 74 percent in 2013; 

That's seriously an insane gain. Nothing against you personally, it just seems like a lot of Spokane has similar views on Rogers and it's one of the biggest obstacles they still need to get over. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, just imagine Andy and Steve.

Steve: We asked 100 people, name something that is a mystery to you.

Andy: Vagina!

Steve: * Looks directly at camera, blank look on face *

Steve: Now folks, folks, this is a family show. And this... This heathen, comes on our show, and uses this language..

\* Camera cuts to Andy's face - He's turning red *

Steve: Now, now, the producers are requiring me to do this. I don't want to, but they make me. Show me.... vagina!

\* Number one answer turns, revealing *Women* as the number one answer *

\* Steve throws cards in air, walks off stage * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy in the coconut

Sorry, but ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love posts like these. I think /r/roosterteeth doesn't have enough shitposts like other subs (/r/h3h3productions, etc). I like them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What animal would you least want to see appear in your kitchen when you wake up tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI...

https://my.spokanecity.org/projects/barnes-road-from-strong-road-to-phoebe-street/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man whatever you do message me when you get set up and I'll try it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want an idea of what trucks there already are, check here:

http://greaterspokanefoodtrucks.com/thetrucks/

I bet if you did just Hamburgers and ice cream you would make a killing. I went to a place in Oregon, [East Wind Drive-in](https://www.yelp.com/biz/east-wind-drive-in-cascade-locks), and they dipped their cones in flavoring somehow and it was incredible. You do something like that and I bet Spokane would eat it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Generally assassins try to keep their kills quiet. You are different, and want everybody in the world to know your targets were assassinated. However as hard as you try, your kills still look accidental </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will recommend again: Murder (Like the G-Mod one), in Minecraft. Set-up a map, and have Matt be the game-master. Each person starts in their own room, and in that room there is a chest. The chest can be accessed from the outside by Matt as well.

Before the game starts, Matt places an item in each chest. Assuming six people are playing, four get ~~placeholder items~~ nothing (thanks /u/Axlgrape), one gets an enchanted bow with a few arrows, plus a jack-o-lantern, and one gets an enchanted sword.

It will play just like murder, with hidden clues around the map they try to collect to get a new bow. If the person with the bow kills the wrong person, Matt throws a potion of slowness at them and they have to put on the jack-o-lantern head.

There are other rules they can put in place too, like the murderer must drop the bow if they pick it up. I'm not sure how well this would all work, but I would love to see it tested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory: Cow Chop will announce their move to California after the state votes to legalize pot this November </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 04:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't set it up as I'm on mobile, but I'm starting to think we should set up a restricted subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My request for a seasonally-appropriate antenna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So since they have decided not to show this in my city, does anybody know if this will be available to First Members at a later point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that stinks. You should go watch TV instead. There they only have 7 minutes of commercials in 30 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to see something really interesting related to this, check out [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-aQ2E0mlRQI). It's basically about how all these hundreds and hundreds of planes fly over across the Atlantic and don't get off course or crash into each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh sorry, I was just going based on their [old page](https://www.nasa.gov/centers/armstrong/news/FactSheets/FS-098-DFRC.html). Looks like since then they upped what they state it can do. That's crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it's been up for 12 hours, and can probably do another 12. That's crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not Southerners, trust me I know some of the idiots that fly it. It's high school kids that like Chew and shotgunning beers between classes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are rumors like this all around the country, yet almost every one is false. Do you have any evidence of this at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im aware of that.

Check this out:

https://theaviationist.com/2016/09/23/watch-two-f-117-stealth-jets-fly-over-nevada-together-8-years-after-retirement/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if this is why the USAF has been testing the F-117 in the Nevada desert lately. Making our own version maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a certain point, i think a cool stretch goal would be a community written short. It would be like /r/writingprompts, but the live action group would have to act it out and film it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I think I will! I liked your other foods too! Ive just been trying to recreate those and couldnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will second Whitworth.

/u/sillyribbit if you're looking here are the lessons they offer:

https://www.teamunify.com/SubTabGeneric.jsp?team=cmwac _stabid_=148218 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will definitely come in to your restaurant if you promise to still serve the Curry fries. I had those when your food truck came to my work and they were incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Gavin has a goal to contribute to an Easter Egg in all of his favorite games. Maybe not a purposeful goal, but this along with Tower of Pimps in Minecraft is pretty awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You get your chance. You are finally going to meet President Obama. He walks up to you, shakes your hand, and leans in to whisper in your ear: "We know your secret." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T_foQoCHQq8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A generation of children were born without imagination. The older generation attempts to find their only hope: Puff, The Magic Dragon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it! May have to go play it for nostalgia sake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anybody else remember that old Cartoon Network game, where it took place on an island with all the characters and you had to explore and do tasks and find stuff? I want Rooster Teeth to do that, but around the office. You could go and find characters, search for Joel's hidden gold stash, find Gus, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. 

RemindMe! 5 Days "Hopefully Lockett is doing well" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to help! It's still running if you're interested! 

http://roosterteeth.com/show/red-vs-blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming back from injury, Pete wanted to limit him (evidenced by Richardson being on Kick-offs). I think he's back to full-speed this week, and he expressed desire after this week to increase his game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh I hate to do this but Gold bet anybody? I can only bet one month but I'm predicting (hoping) for a breakout game. I'll say he gets at least 100 receiving yards and a TD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry man, it might be your style, but this sub has assholes that downvote more than any other sub I've seen. So basically Rooster Teeth is a production company from Austin, TX. They were first popularized with their Halo webseries Red Vs Blue. At this point they are big, and have a ton of different content to enjoy.

Let me know what you're into in other entertainment and I can potentially recommend something to watch. Comedy, drama, anime? Do you like watching people play games, DnD, Xbox, PC gaming, etc. Let me know and I'll help you out, and hopefully change opinions on this sub which can be shitty at times.

Edit: /u/sadlyf420 this goes for you too. I'll help you out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homer, but I think he puts up 100+ and TD against Jets this week, plus punt return TD. I mean, probably disregard this because I'm 0-3 in two of my three leagues, but I think Jets gameplan for Michael and Baldwin and ignore his deep threat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New drinking game. Drink every time you hear the word gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/blog/comments/54lwpx/join_team_reddit_for_extra_life_the_24hour_gaming/d82zcyo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Admin response to the RT vs Reddit Extra Life rivalry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I know that you made this comment four days ago but I just read it and had to respond. The reason they use billboards for their ads is that they have very few other options for advertisement. At one point they tried to advertise in local periodicals, like The Inlander. However the postal service refuses to deliver anything with pot ads in it, so billboards are the only thing left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they sell branded puke buckets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New sub maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 23:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is three. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my nephews ripped off a Barbie head. I put it on Batman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 22:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 18:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acestream dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 02:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh to be fair they have a point with the freeway. It's taken 15 years so far, and the estimated completion date is 2030 still. Only ten fucking miles! I just want it finished. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Rambo has grown old, and has grandchildren of his own. One day they invite him to a water balloon fight with the neighborhood bullies, and beg him to help them win. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Incredibly good so far. They're starting to change mindsets, at least to me. Going from "This is a good show for being from Rooster Teeth." to now "This is a good show!" I'm excited to see how it progresses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Although the fact that they hired more people is promising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's basically what Spotify, Google Play Music, etc do with their offline stations. Essentially you download the video to the device, but encrypt it. The app itself has the key to unlock the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man if I wasn't going out tonight I totally would. Thanks though! I'll keep an eye out for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awesome, I may have to check that out after work! Honestly the fact that you are working on improving it bodes very well. That means that you guys are invested into it, which is great! I'll log on tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. I kind of yearn for something like that, where communication and discussion is encouraged and everywhere. But I guess that's just growing pains, RT is so big now the community sense is lost in a way.

Maybe there is good community too, and it's just lost between the toxic people. I have to admit I haven't tried Discord much, is that active? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that you owned up to your mistake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, well I wish you the best of luck! Unfortunately subsection 2 of the law you posted is pretty clear about exemptions, and I don't believe the lists of exemptions is public anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, 100% in favor of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get pulled over? Was he following you, or just running radar on the side of the road?

To be honest, I don't think you stand a chance. They wrote the law vague enough that it actually states exemptions can be made. But who knows, maybe you'll luck out and get a sympathetic ear in the court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 15:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask an honest question? Is the RT website better than this sub? I come here everyday, but this sub just doesn't have the discussion, or even friendliness, that other subs do. Hell, even shitposts don't do well here. 

I know I'm complaining, but it just kind of sucks because I feel like this sub could be better, there's just something stopping it and I can't place my finger on it. I mean, looks at /r/cowchop. They have around one-tenth the subscribers, but any given front page post has probably a similar-ish number of comments. 

Knowing this sub, I'm pretty sure I'll get downvoted for this comment, and I really don't care, but I hope it spawns at least a bit of discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell me what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you go Mckinnon over Tate in a TD heavy league? Tate has sucked so far in my league (0 pts), but I'm not sure how much better Mckinnon would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 03:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mirror](https://streamable.com/8fgc) (if needed). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amy Schumer on South Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry! I know that, I meant that I don't want it to move to a model like T C where it's first only and you can't download it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP chairman demands interview with Clinton IT aides after Reddit posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 15:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not cancelled (As far as I know). It's really popular so I don't see that happening. There should be a new season maybe in a few weeks, if they follow the schedule they normally do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 15:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they don't make it first only. I'm a first member but I only listen to H H in the car, so that would really suck. There's no way to download it currently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has any progress been made with this? I get it as well. Have tried deleting X1 cache, but no luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 09:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people see constant demolishing as a viable strategy. Why shouldn't it be allowed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not RT, but I think Cow Chop is just a front for a grow operation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 16:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't watched this yet, but holy crap they are on fire with Let's Plays this week. A great GTA, 7 Days to Die, Gmod Murder, Dead by Daylight, and finishing it off with Minecraft Pixelmon. Nice job this week guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A spicy Bloody Mary, served with bent toothpicks through olives, etc to look like a scorpion tail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drugs are bad, mmkay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh agreed. I just want a way to download audio for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you find a way please let me know. I really want to listen to Twits and Crits in the car and can't without using a ton of data so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 20:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, here's the list of new places I made last month. Some actual restaurants:

Sweeto Burrito - Division and Nora

Sweeto Burrito - 9602 N Newport Highway

NUDO Ramen - 9602 N Newport Highway

Mod Pizza - 9405 N Newport Highway

Retro Donuts - Location Unknown

Slice - Pints and Pizza - 829 E Boone

Allie's Vegan Pizzeria   Caf - Working towards reopening after fire - 4803 N Nevada St

Kabob House - Ruby and Montgomery

Panera Bread - Looks to potentially be opening one near Lowe's on Division

Denny's - 3525 N Division St

Bruncheonette - 1011 W Broadway

King of Ramen - Division and Mission </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do. No joke we have relatives that come to visit and we struggle to figure out what to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, we're working on it. I'm personally supporting the new Honor Point Museum so I hope that get's off the ground. But at least my experience, when people come to visit there's nothing that "stands-out" about Spokane as a must-see thing. 

However if you know of some cool stuff, I would be happy to go and explore and see it. It just seems to me like every tourist attraction in Spokane can be seen in a different flavor in every other big city in the country. 

I will admit we score high marks on the outdoorsy aspect. That's probably Spokane's best feature.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. We don't have much nightlife, we don't have many attractions. If chain restaurants are all Spokane will get then we might as well turn lemons into lemonade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You comment a lot in RT subs. You're obviously a big fan so you need First! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me your email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the north side is really lucky with restaurants lately.

Sweeto Burrito

NUDO Ramen

Denny's

A new Panera bread

And quite a few more. It's really interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a First Membership you should try out the show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's Play is too far away for me to go. :( 6 hours is a bit too much of a drive. I hate that my city is decent sized but just has no RT fans. So I guess I'll be like all of the fans from other countries and try to live vicariously through posts on this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I live in a decent sized city, but the closest to me that I can find is 6 hours away. :( No bueno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you actually a Christmas Tree Farmer? Which one?! I've gone to quite a few different places in Spokane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Xbox One] Everytime I type in chat in-match my game crashes. Anybody know how to fix this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried an exorcism?

But honestly, I would try disabling and renabling extensions one by one, to see if any fix it while disabled. It's possible one is messing with the html/css on the webpage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lot's of stuff happening lately. If you haven't I would go on Spokane News on Facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 02:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, nobody cares (or has heard) about the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh, in this case I think it's useful. It's better than the ambiguous first name that even the head coach pronounces incorrectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Right after drafting Hausch-Money in the third. I'm a Seahawks guy. 


^^^/s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cover letters are a huge part in many industries, it's one of the main reasons I got my current job. But you're right that artistic jobs are probably way different too. So maybe it depends what job the OP is actually applying for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact! Taking money for palm reading/fortune telling in Spokane is illegal! I mean you'll be able to find somebody, and nobody cares about this law, I just saw this post and remembered this fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They're working on it](https://twitter.com/AchievementHunt/status/773236931530334208) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I'm hoping Rawls and Michael get in a big fight, then my fourth round pick of Prosise will pay off! Who's laughing now fuckers?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christine Michael listed as Seahawks starting RB in first official "unofficial" depth chart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be completely honest, I have a strong feeling they don't care about the cover letter. It would be your portfolio that gets you the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel bad, 90% of self-posts are downvoted in this sub! You're average!

Oh and for posterity's sake I do the same thing. It's fun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! I love it as well. Very happy I switched from US Bank to you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do the 'substitutes' (and Jeremy) feel they have to talk so much?

he's like a permanent stain on a t shirt I used to love.

This triggered me so much, but they aren't funny and just generally don't have entertaining personalities (in my opinion) , that's my problem with it, just look at the dislikes and comments on the video, they need to realize as an organization to put profits first

Too obvious, try harder next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please finish this sentence: Wake up in the morning feeling like _______. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely STCU. They are part of an ATM network, so almost any credit union ATM in the city (or country) will work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just perusing the sub and some people seem like really big dicks about Mica. Seriously even if you don't like her, why do you feel the need to shit on everything she does? I feel like there are some super toxic people in this sub. It's slowly becoming worse than Youtube comments.

Now, onto a second thought. If you are huge RT fan on this sub, but don't have a First subscription, do you feel like you are missing stuff? I kind of feel bad for the high school aged kids that can't watch all their favorite content because their parents won't let them use their debit card. I know I was there at some point (Not Roosterteeth but buying stuff overall). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burns is actually short for Burnstein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \:( 

Gus
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 22:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New episode comes out tomorrow or later tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like the time. It will be nice to have an RT show my girlfriend and I can sit down and watch "live", as we're usually both at work.

I think more variety overall in times for shows is a great idea, just so no matter where you are in the world you have at least one show a week you can watch live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I ever made it on Jeopardy, I think the hardest part would be figuring out something interesting about myself to share with Alex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo dawg, I heard you like posts, so we... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of hope one of my shot suggestions is on the first episode. I'm excited to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Always Open premieres tonight at 10:30PM CT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download a cookie tracker and delete the tracking cookies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know when you get done and I'll be happy to help you transfer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh Spokane Public schools stopped caring about it a long time ago. At some point in the week before or after the day kids get a day off for "learning improvement", but that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean I did both. Shit work and engineering work. And continue the latter at that company still to this day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that what interns are for?? I mean, I had to do stuff like that as an intern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Every person on Reddit is a bot, except for you. You finally start to notice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Twiiter and the RT Site are platforms to be seen during the podcast itself, while Reddit doesn't fulfill that need. [Burnie](/u/gussorolaverified) mentioned he went to Reddit *after the show ended*. If they came here regularly during the show there would be a lot more comments about relevant topics, not troubleshooting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that sounds like a win-win for you guys! I'm sure the collective minds of the moderators could automate the comments anyways.

"Did you see when Ryan said $YoutubeClosedCaptioning at $YoutubeTimestamp? That's so $ResponseEmotion!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So with these FAQ threads, is there a repository of questions and answers for people to browse? I was thinking about how many repeat questions are posted to the sub, and how the sub could deal with those. Auto-moderator could be setup to search post titles for common questions, and if it finds one remove it and send the user to the repository and the weekly FAQ thread. I think it might cut down the clutter a bit, and give people easier access to their answer questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh I like it. Or just go the other direction and go full Circlejerk.

DAE BARBARA HOT??

Or...

[Burnie Burns. If this post gets 1500 upvotes this picture will come up when people search Burnie Burns](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/SethRogen_7_2007.JPG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe just add a rule 10 - "Don't be stupid" so you cover all of your bases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... Uhh... You maybe should keep stuff like that to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want the NY tickets I believe they are sold out. You may have to search secondary sites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Finding Nemo, but Nemo's dad Marlin is played by Liam Neeson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 team. 4 pt bonus for 300 yards passing. 2 points every 50 yards for receiving and rushing. Touchdowns pts are dependent on length. 6 pts for the shortest (0-20 yards passing/receiving, 0-3 yards rushing) up to 10 pts (40+ yard pass TD or receiving TD) or 14 pts (40+ yard run td). I know these points are a bit strange but it's what I have to work with.

Start is 1 QB, 2RB, 2WR, 1 TE, 1 (WR/RB/TE), 1K, 1 def

Luck, Andrew IND QB

Foster, Arian MIA RB

Gore, Frank IND RB

Michael, Christine SEA RB

Miller, Lamar HOU RB

Murray, Latavius OAK RB

Austin, Tavon RAM WR

Gordon, Josh CLE WR (S)

Nelson, Jordy GBP WR 

Tate, Golden DET WR

Thomas, Julius JAC TE	

Aguayo, Roberto TBB PK

Texans, Houston HOU Def </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take Cam, Julio, and Brandon. Cam's going to be a monster again this year. And of the rest I just think Brandon will be your best point scorer week after week. But I suck at fantasy so you may want to do the exact opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 23:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a magician when I was 8. He brought me up on stage while his assistant rolled out a large red curtain on what looked to be a portable coat hanger. He said some magical words, I was pulled below stage by another assistant, and all of a sudden I didn't like magic anymore. It was ruined.

From that day on, I also hated audience participation. Try to bring me on stage to be hypnotized? Nah. An interactive Broadway show? Count me out. 

I tried to go up on stage once in middle school, but I had a nervous breakdown and ended up punching the drama teacher in the eye. At least I think that's what happened; I suppressed the whole thing. I think that's why the man with the eye-patch was so surprised when he demanded I get up from my chair. 

"Arrr! Stand up lest ye be executed!"

I held firm. 

"No thanks buddy. Not into that sort of thing."

My cruise had been incredible so far. The first day I had won $150 on the on-board casino. The second day I was able to lounge about at the adult-only pool, drinking Mai-Tai's to my heart's content. But the third day... The third day is where it fell apart. 

---

My wife woke me on the third day with her *lovely* wake up call.

"Honey! Honey! Look at this! It says there is a brand new show today, a pirate show!"

I groaned. But her look made it very clear we were going.

It wasn't all bad. It started out with the cruise director on stage, giving a brief introduction on the group. "Professional pirates" he called them. I was never really interested in pirates, so I was already bored. At least I was until one of the pirates ran out on stage. 

I would best describe him as short, stubby, and stupid. I mean I didn't know if he was stupid, but he looked like it. A bit cross-eyed, with a brown vest and puffy trousers. But out of the folds between his shirt and pants appeared a sword in his hands, shiny and well-kept by the looks of it. 

He bounded across the stage, and with one quick motion he sliced towards the directors throat. Blood began spurting out, a miniature red geyser. I have to admit I was a bit impressed at this point. The special effects were far beyond what I would expect from a cruise ship stage show.

To add to it, I heard faint screams coming from behind me. The surround sound seemed to be on point as well. But my fascination turned to horror, as I saw more and more pirates spill out from behind the stage curtains, and immediately run down the stairs into the crowd.

I pulled on my wife's blouse.

"Honey, let's go. I don't want any part of it."

She gave a loud laugh.

"Relax! None of this is real! Just enjoy it!"

I pulled her arm again.

"We need to go *now*. They're going to bring me up on stage, I just know it! And then all the special effects will be ruined and I won't be able to enjoy my cruise anymore!"

I was beginning to break down a bit, I could feel it. The priates were working their way through the crowd, forcing each male up towards the stage, and tying them up as they got there. 

Before my wife could chastise me for my immature rambling, I felt cold metal on the back of my neck. I turned, and was face-to-face with a pirate. An eye-patch on his left, part of his ear missing on the right, and a beard to make Grizzly Adams jealous. 

"Arrr! Stand up lest ye be executed!"

I held firm.

"No thanks buddy. Not into that sort of thing."

He turned his blade, pointing the sharp end at my jugular, making his intentions clear. But I wasn't into audience participation, and I intended to make *that* clear. 

I grabbed the blade, pinching it between my finger and thumb. 

"I am absolutely *not* going up on that stage, and you will not force me to do so!"

With my free hand I shoved the pirate against the wall and began to walk back up the path to the doors. But before I made it, I heard a loud scream. It was unmistakably my wife's voice. I turned, and the bastard of a pirate had his blade to my wife's neck.

"Get on the stage or ye lass' gets it!"


I saw red. 

---

I don't remember what happened next. At some point I realized these were less fake-pirates, and more fake-fake-pirates. I'm not sure how it happened, but the first coast guard member I talked to believed I set a record for most modern day kills with a sword. 

Beyond the talk-shows, presidential visits, and key to the city, our life went back to normal. I kept the sword, it's on the mantle above my fireplace. It serves as reminder, to both my wife and any visitors we get:

I really hate audience participation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a bit more context, one of the commenters is /u/captdope, who's real name is Colton Dunn. Besides acting, he was previously a writer for Key and Peele. What's really funny is that before last night he had only made two comments on Reddit in 6 years, one of which was the following on a Key and Peele AMA:

https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/121fka/we_are_keeganmichael_key_and_jordan_peele_of/c6rckcg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god this comment of yours from three years ago:

https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/121fka/we_are_keeganmichael_key_and_jordan_peele_of/c6rckcg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \**Clap clap clap*\* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
