<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject155</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The White House must take the lead on replacing healthcare, because Congress will not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Big Bend. Since it's a federal park maybe we could just station more border officers there to deal with incursions. So long as most of the border is walled and the gaps are manned it should work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was this Sanders when Hillary was robbing him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No doubt he will. There are so many things that need fixing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Found them](http://i.redd.it/bfqn35b2vogy.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the people's president. Connecting with the voters is kind of his thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trumps Perfume Is Selling Like Crazy on Amazon Despite a Boycott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like there should be a home vaccination kit. People might not have the time or money to get to a doctor in the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joan Rivers on The Ed Sullivan Show, 1967 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was all about communism. Russia was the enemy and it was a battle to either conquer the world with capitalism or conquer it with communism. Russia did quite well, taking a large part of Asia and parts of Central America. People who wanted to escape those places and come to the "freedom" of the United States were given sanctuary. Communism was mostly defeated by the 1990s but it continued in Cuba, which is why the refugee policy remained for a longer time with regard to Cubans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we can put a man on the moon, why can't we put a woman on the moon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can fine people tens of thousands of dollars for downloading a movie but there will always be others willing to risk it because it saves them a few dollars. The way to defeat it is to make it impossible to find the free version, and the way to defeat this problem is to make it impossible to find the cheap workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one thing there were so many sitcoms in the 90s, and many of them still endure. Friends, Seinfeld, Frasier, Cybil, Roseanne, Home Improvement, 3rd Rock, Everybody Loves Raymond... you get the idea, dozens of memorable comedy shows. There was a strong selection of sci-fi with multiple Star Trek shows, X-Files, and many others. Lots of kids shows and cartoons. It just seemed the decade for good television. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion no. I thought the 1990s were a golden era. It all went to hell when reality tv arrived. These days a lot of people are canceling cable contracts because there's not much worth watching on television and instead using streaming services to watch 90s shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who uses an expression like "Der Trumpenfuhrer" isn't looking at the situation with an open mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's only really three agencies. Not very convincing for the claim that a dozen or "17" as some people say are in agreement. That's the case for most of these stories. We're told of "reports" and "sources" without being told who those sources are. We're expected to blindly believe these extraordinary claims. Each week a new story, while the previous week's story quietly disappears after it has been disproved, and we're supposed to ignore the poor track record because this time surely it's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the names of those agencies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia as a scapegoat. Controlled mass media. It's right in front of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting how these panicked conservatives only appear in liberal publications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is exactly what the left is doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was always amusing when something damaging would come out about Clinton and suddenly the politics sub was normal for a day. All the rabid anti-Trump posters completely disappeared and people were able to have productive conversations again. We always said that CTR had put their posters on hold until a new narrative could be given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NASA likes Trump because he's committed to space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump hasn't committed any crimes, and Hillary has a copy of the FBI records so she has dirt on everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems reasonable to me. No doubt he is given statistics and takes them at face value. There isn't much time for researching data in a job like that. You've seen what's happening in Chicago and other cities. The murder rates are at very high levels in places. Maybe not 45 year highs but the highest they've been in decades.

Perhaps there are remarks which are slightly inaccurate at times but I don't believe there's any intent to be misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chaffetz seeks charge of ex-Clinton aide in email inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emily Ratajkowski: Slut-Shaming Melania Trump Isnt OK, Regardless Of Your Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fake news is mostly coming from the billion dollar media groups like CNN. There is a smaller independent press which is honest and accurate and needs our help to grow and displace those which are dishonest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spies. Of course, we have no way of knowing if the sources are real since they're never named. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reporting on classified material? That's deeply concerning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see how those people perform in their jobs before judging their abilities. The goal of this administration has been to take power out of the hands of the establishment where possible, which is why many of the appointments have been outsiders. The early actions have been ending TPP and making plans to negotiate on other trade matters, working with companies to bring manufacturing back into the country, ending healthcare penalties and working on healthcare plans, securing the border, and various small things that don't get their own headline. It's been a productive first month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Trump is wonderful. He's the first president of my lifetime who wants to serve the people and not the political class. Listen to Ron Paul, he knows this is the presidency we've all been waiting for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived through Bush. Liberals are throwing exactly the same theatrics now that they did then. They're even rehashing the same tired old jokes about a skeleton standing next to the president and telling him what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI reviewed the transcripts and found nothing wrong with what he said. He merely mentioned that the administration would probably be discussing the sanctions when they speak with Russia in an official capacity. It's nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We cannot wait for 200 nations to independently enact policies to reduce destruction of the Earth. Even if they would enact policies it would not go far enough. This is a problem which requires immediate and drastic action that bypasses governments entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most do not agree with personal attacks on twitter, however those are remarks against individual people, not broadly sexist or racist or xenophobic. The reason people support Trump is because during the ~ 18 month presidential campaign he visited communities all over the country and listened to the concerns of the people, and incorporated solutions to those problems into his platform. Now that he's president he's fulfilling the campaign promises he made. He's doing what he said he would do, and he said he would do those things because the people of the country told him those things were a problem. Not everyone is going to approve, and not everyone is going to be affected by the issues or see them as a problem, but a broad swath of the country does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Drops Two-State Solution as Keystone of Mideast Peace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidently he resigned because of the media's witch hunt and he felt like a liability to the administration, particularly if he mislead them about the contents of the calls. The FBI listened to the calls and found nothing wrong with the subject matter discussed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He talks about various things on a regular basis that mostly don't make it to articles, just clips end up on youtube.

 I think its politics more than anything else, says former House of Representatives Member Ron Raul (R-TX) regarding calls for an investigation of purported hacking by the Russian government influencing the United States presidential election. Interviewed Wednesday on Fox Business, Paul continues that, even if Russia did what is alleged, Paul does not think it made any difference.

 Paul  providing perspective on the matter  notes that the US government is interfering with elections around the world all the time. Paul also suggests reviewing the history of US government involvement in foreign countries, including how many countries we invaded, how many people we have killed in order to have our guy in. Looking to this history, Paul concludes, we dont have much room for condemning anybody else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is an outsider. People don't want the establishment to run things any longer. They don't want a Republican to run the country, or a Democrat to run the country. They want to run the country themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a tricky situation. Either someone is unsafe to be in society or they are safe to be in society, and if they are in society they have constitutional rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ron Paul agrees that the stories against the White House are fraudulent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the part of the swamp which most needs to be drained. The "shadow" government. The only governing body which should exist is the one elected to represent the people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to save lives and you're accused of bigotry and hatred SMH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pass a law requiring everyone to have ID. Then no one can complain that they're unable to vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no contradiction there. Just go to /r/writingprompts to see hundreds of fake stories based on a real premise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It turns out Flynn did nothing improper. The media owes him an apology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI reviewed Flynns calls with Russian ambassador but found nothing illicit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not so much the Democrats as the establishment in general, including Republicans. They do not want the swamp to be drained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter how well Pence is liked. He's a Republican through and through and would work hand in hand with the Republican Congress to advance every manner of bigotry and theology the party has adopted into its platform in recent years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence is one of the most anti-gay politicians in the country. He's one of the last people I would want for president. Given the chance he would pursue policies targeting gay people, and the 2018 midterms are expected to expand the majority of Republicans in Congress. Trump is the first pro-gay president the United States has ever elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he become famous by complaining about car jobs being lost to Mexico, and then criticized President Trump for bringing the car jobs back from Mexico? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No doubt they will respond that Nazis can only be white men with buzzcuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He performed better than Republicans normally perform. 13% of African-American men, 30% of the Hispanic vote, three times more Muslim voters than Romney. The Republican voter base was expanded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be no exchange of money between family and friends. If you have a skill, offer your help freely. If you have no time to help, offer a referral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valentine's Day recipe - Banana Split </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a very sensible attitude considering the Democrats were openly musing the possibility of starting a war with Russia. No one with any brains should want another cold war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freudian slip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonard Nimoy - The Ballad of Bilbo Baggins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this still a thing? The negative health implications of butter alternatives is well known by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you believe Trump or the media?

http://theweek.com/speedreads/678900/new-poll-finds-trump-administration-seen-more-truthful-than-media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US government is a government of the people. The further you are from a career politician, the closer you are to representing the people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Clinton's impeachment in the 1990s is also the reason Democrats bring up impeachment the moment something controversial happens. They're desperate to even the score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The voters did give him the power. Now he's the most powerful man in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps by tolerating people who have differing opinions? Besides, Mike Pence is not the president, despite what Reddit may believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems that starving it of ink would be a surer solution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there are 11 million illegals in the country, and close to 10% of those polled admit to voting, that's already a million fraudulent votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an article that belongs in the latter months of 2024, not three weeks into the presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would illegals vote for Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A significant percentage of the sub is gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a variation on the classic communism question. Why would anyone make an effort if they all end up with the same result? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would anyone try to better themselves if they know their money will be taken by the government if they become successful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elvis Presley - An American Trilogy [Gospel] (live in Hawaii 1973) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia doesn't need to do a thing. We're obviously using them for some purpose, most likely to ensure Israel's safety by swiftly taking care of Syria. After that we'll evaluate whether we still need a partnership with Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the millions of self employed illegals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can lead to suicidal thoughts, impair mental capacity and function, impair attention which leads to poor driving behavior, and many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afghanistan didn't have anything to do with it either. I always felt Afghanistan was the worst of the two wars, partly because it allowed the other one to be launched so easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would imagine it does give people an excuse to behave in such a way. If something isn't shocking to you it's much easier for you to do it. Something taboo is a more difficult barrier to break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always ask why someone would oppose fixing a problem if they don't believe it exists. See also: voter fraud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why the White House continues to indulge the press. They don't deserve briefings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The root of racism is treating people differently according to their race. The solution to racism is to treat everyone equally. Which side of the political spectrum identifies people first by their race, and treats people  differently according to their race? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other China is a communist dictatorship, which is exactly the type of country they're suggesting Putin is operating and why we shouldn't respect Putin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send it to Netflix. Maybe they'll realize it's better to just pull the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like an opportunity for bus companies. European kids often use a public bus to get to school, which may be subsidized if they are poor. Or perhaps parents can pay into a private bus service. Or the school may be compelled to provide a bus route to every student that is enrolled. There should be options beside driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The United States lags behind the rest of the developed world when it comes to education. School choice could be one of the factors. I found it unusual that American kids are expected to attend whichever school is closest to their house. A poor neighborhood might have a poor school due to lack of funding. Being able to send the kids to the well funded school in the rich neighborhood increases the value of their education and eliminates the complaints about minorities being set up for failure by being born into the wrong circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do Europeans think of Muslim immigration? Majority agree with Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is referring to people from the seven countries currently forbidden from traveling to the United States, one of the suggestions for improving the screening process so they can be allowed to travel here again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress can't pass laws which force a religion onto people or prohibit people from practicing a religion. In the past each state had its own official religion and didn't want the federal government imposing a national religion on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump != the Republican party. Republicans are useless. They don't have any intention of helping the American people or replacing Obamacare. This is entirely up to the president. It won't be easy since he'll need Congress to actually pass the legislation. The Democrats in Congress will have to do their job instead of being obstructionists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's take this moment to appreciate the grace of Trump in appointing and nominating people who are not yes men but independent thinkers who will speak up when they disagree with him on an issue. We would never have seen this from Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double standards were just as apparent under Obama. While his administration locked people up for using drugs and emphasized the law, they pretended not to notice when pictures emerged of his daughter using drugs. Where was her punishment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> POLL: Travel ban is one of Trump's most popular executive orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's already a common headline. Reddit just downvotes those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll probably be a more deserving recipient than his predecessor was. Let's see how the next eight years play out first though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the time and money for games but too much understanding of the programming involved to be able to fully enjoy them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Threatening the families of terrorists is the opposite of a potent recruiting tool. The primary reason they commit terror acts is to help their family, who receive money from the terror groups as a reward. If families are under threat it will be difficult to find recruits. Why blow yourself up if it leads to your wife and children being arrested and put in prison? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You people don't find it even slightly odd to have so many contrasting stories in this sub? First he's furious that Spicer is being mocked, now he hates Spicer and wishes he weren't in the administration. It all seems perfectly logical to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be a public option. Cover everyone by the government so they can get healthcare, even if it's not the best care. Those who want to ensure the best care can pay for additional private insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump cannot allow the Republican party to use this opportunity to benefit itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to know the minimum amount to bribe the police to ignore it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's doing exactly what he told the voters he would do as president, and those are the campaign promises which led to his election and winning states that no Republican had won in decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I visited one in Porter in 2015 which was planning to introduce the buffet. They had people from corporate looking around the dining room and discussing how it would work. Pizza Hut is not very good anymore though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you sit extremely close to the screen. I would think increasing the bit depth would be more noticeable for a television. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me see if I understand this. Democrats would rather have Mike Pence as president and give full control of the country to the bigoted, theocratic Republican party than have the country run by someone who enacts the policies requested by the American people and fights to reform the system to reduce opportunities for politicians to benefit themselves and screw over the people. Sounds logical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having spoken with people who worked in that field, it's just military aircraft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rappin' Ronnie Reagan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is always the problem. Whether Republicans or Democrats they want to rule and not serve. No doubt that is why the pendulum is always swinging back and forth, as people grow to loathe the party in power and forget how bad the alternative was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think moderation is the issue. They have to get work done, and show an interest in serving the people and not each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. It may be slow progress with the media entirely working against him but the results of the work will begin to show. In a decade or two people will look back fondly on President Trump as someone who was a genuine public servant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP has been handed the strongest majority it has had in decades. This is the voice of the American people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If his disapproval rating was 60% during the campaign, it's not surprising if it's over 50% today. It takes more than two weeks before people change their opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the media was so fond of pointing out, he went into the election with a 60% negative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the definition of fake news. Someone hears a rumor, or more likely a joke, so they publish it as fast as they can without even taking the time to think about whether it's something that could conceivably happen in reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be one bathroom for adults and one for minors. That way everyone gets what they wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's absolutely right of course. The difference here is that most polls are not intentionally misleading, they're just inaccurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this during the Bush years. Democrats put on such theatrics when a Republican is president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with the media's sudden demonizing of Putin? Are they trying to sabotage relations between the two countries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress could just vote to increase the size of the court and allow the new seats to be filled by the current president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money is ultimately worthless. It's more of an agreement than anything tangible. When these people die they will have nothing to take with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one thing I will criticize the government for. They refuse to provide healthcare, forcing many people into bankruptcy and homelessness, and then when others try to help the homeless they are confronted by the police and the food is confiscated and destroyed. You can't treat people like animals. Either help them from becoming homeless or help them when they do become homeless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A possible solution is to keep every citizen's fingerprint in a database. When they vote, take their fingerprint and flag the database so they cannot vote twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is pro-Trump though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now Democrats are behaving the same way because they are the ones out of power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't American protesters be doing this instead of beating people they disagree with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to imagine an anti-semite supporting Trump. He has a Jewish family, has been given the honorary title of first Jewish president, and is ultra supportive of Israel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clearly not the same as a ban on Muslims entering the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're pretty conservative in Texas. If she gets political it could get ugly, like Borat singing the national anthem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cracked has been ridiculous recently. They even put an anti-Uber video from 2015 on the home page because it was suitable for their political motive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most refreshing moments in Trump's campaign was hearing him lambast George W Bush for the pointless wars in Iraq and Afghanistan and the hundreds of thousands of civilians butchered by the United States. This is someone who will admit that America has wronged the world at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately that doesn't root out the sociopaths. They can be very charming but completely heartless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a belief among American evangelicals. I'm not sure I'd call them Christian, but since they worship Jesus I suppose they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's here in full force. Take a look at any negative story about President Trump. Within a day or two most are disproved. Either the journals are incompetent or intentionally misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the evangelical prediction of the end of the world. Russia attacks Israel and the United States stands by and does nothing to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
