<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 02:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for doing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 01:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dafuq? I live in a midsized city in the midwest and have six places--SIX, I counted--within a *mile* of me that sell at least 10 different kinds of cheese. There's a cheese shop on my way to work that sells three different kinds of "nice hard aged Cheddars" from Somerset alone, for crying out loud. Where the hell did you visit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 14:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic answer, thank you!

Followup, if I may, from someone very new to the subject: was there any pushback from the Saxons, Jutes, etc. at the suggestion that everything was being unified under the Angles? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 06:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 42069

So wait, the ISS is in western Kentucky now? No wonder people think they faked the moon landing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 01:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many acceptable spellings, but the one above doesn't come with an apostrophe.  I prefer p'tahk, myself.  

...aaand I'm debating the transliteration of Klingon words on the Internet.  Time to go outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 00:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue blood wine and, well, cities (which imply a transition from hunter-gatherer to agrarian food production) are a pretty good argument that Klingons are omnivorous.  Omnivores love sweet things.  

EDIT: Oh, also: [Klingons have fruit](http://memory-alpha.wikia.com/wiki/Zilm%27kach).  Yes, I'm nerdy enough to have researched that for eight minutes. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 00:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Memory Alpha says both Jake and Dax like theirs extra sweet, though, referencing "For the Cause" and "The Passenger" respectively. Also Tom Paris mentioned wanting one with whipped cream on Voyager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the exact meaning of the word Christian.  It's the point of the word--It means "Little Christ" in Greek.  The idea is that Christians spend their lives trying to be more like him, not that they are capable or should think themselves capable of becoming him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing in your comment does anything to address whether the statement on the sign is correct or holds theological water.  You're doing mental jumping jacks to keep a certain modern worldview attached to your Christianity that has very little to do with it.

Put simply, being homosexual is less of a barrier to being a good Christian than a lot of things the developed world takes for granted on a daily basis, but we don't like to look too closely at the inequality, the injustice, the poverty, or our own complicity in these things, do we? So we blame the "other."

Homosexuality has absolutely nothing to do with the core principles of Christianity.  It's a wedge issue, a fire stoked by politicians who wanted to make a fast point in the polls on the backs of people's hate and fear.  And you're letting them do it.

Christ wanted us to love one another above everything save our love for God.  He wanted us to take the plank out of our eye before addressing the sawdust in our brother's.  He wanted us to turn the other cheek when we are wronged.  He wanted us to give towards the goal of a restored world until it hurt, then keep giving.  That is the core of Christian principles.  You have to know that somewhere deep inside.

So cut it out.  You know that all have sinned and fallen short of the glory of God.  You are no exception.  This whole silly issue is the work of the devil, and he's doing a fine job of distracting you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible is pretty clear that you shouldn't *expect* to be able to do that.  It's saying not to look for loopholes, not that it can't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I write this long thing that maybe no one will read, I want you to know that I'm a lapsed Christian who grew up in a very religious household which put a lot of emphasis on good theological thought.  I'm not a pro at this, and I don't take all of it without at least a bit of skepticism.

I think the concept of sin is a really misunderstood one.  At least in the denomination I was raised in, sin is an outcropping of how broken we are.  When we talk about a cheesecake being sinful, it's getting closer to this concept, because what we are saying is that we know we are doing wrong by ourselves.

Think of sin as being anything that separates us from an ideal state of godliness, what's good for us according to God.  This ideal state, as repeated over and over in the bible, includes a happy, close marriage that produces well-adjusted children.  I'm not saying I endorse this viewpoint, but you can certainly see that being the case in the first century AD, no? The concept of homosexuality precludes the happy marriage above, at least in the mind of someone writing within a few hundred years of Jesus.

Anyway, sin encompasses all of the things that make us lesser than this ideal. Everything that brings us away from God is sin or the result of it.  It's an unfortunate result of a broken world which is best avoided, both for our sakes and our children's, not some cosmic balance sheet.

And that's where we get to another thing: it's important to also realize that not all lines of Christianity read the Bible with our intellectual hands tied.  Mine taught us to understand the historical viewpoints and biases that may have filtered to the paper through the hands that God chose to write his word.  

It creates a situation where learning to read the text with an educated eye is absolutely crucial, and therein lies the biggest problem in the study of the bible.  The upside of this is that if something gets repeated thematically over and over, turned over and ruminated on by multiple authors, then it's pretty safe to say that it was a major point that God was trying to get across.

So, what's perhaps the biggest one of these points in the new testament? Something repeated over and over again, quoted by Jesus in multiple sources, and discussed ad nauseam? You got it:  We are supposed to be good to each other, especially when it hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 01:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, now I'm gonna have that song stuck in my head for three hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  My theologian great-grandpa used to say it isn't sinful to appreciate a pretty woman on the street as you drive past, but it *is* sinful to drive around the block for another look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kidding.  FWIW I heard this first in the early nineties, completely detached from anything in the public consciousness related to the LGBTQ Movement.  That said, I was not implying endorsement of that belief, just felt that it was contextually appropriate to point out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some even say that the "Thorn in my side" Paul kept talking about was homosexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was overreaching a bit with "equals."  The bible is basically saying that wishing someone dead isn't necessarily better than killing them, not that the two are equal.  Christians and non-Christians alike (especially Catholics, the Protestants would say) have had quite a bit of trouble with the idea of sin as a demerit.  It's more an expression of how broken we are.  It's like a Heroin addiction.  Is the person really to blame? Perhaps not, but it isn't helping them live a healthy life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lapsed Calvinist here.  It's because being a Christian isn't about not sinning.  We're taught that we all sin, and it's only through God's grace we are redeemed, and because we *are* redeemed we're supposed to pay it back through loving and helping those around us.  

One of them is an example of how we fall short of God's standards, but that's okay as long as we try to better ourselves.  The other is an example of acting contrary to the very word Christian--which means "little Christ," i.e. someone who seeks to be like him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 14:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here I was expecting "The Claaaaw!" photo op in the queue for the character meet across from Toy Story Midway Mania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. I read that as market saturation. Didn't mean to mislead anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 21:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of note, deeper in the article is a prediction of slower times to come for downtown construction.  Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposed 12 Weston office tower project stalls; developer to explore other options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 21:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 450 feet under Lake Michigan, classic car cache rests in frigid silence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 21:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insurance law as we know it today is largely a British invention, and that model is widely accepted. It's not an "American" assumption, just a fairly safe one.

Not saying he should have jumped to correct OP though. What OP said is exactly correct in the States, too (well, in most of them).

BTW: do you not see the irony in looking down your nose at the guy above you by calling him an American, associating that with arrogance and jumping to conclusions, without yourself knowing his country of origin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liability by definition is the state of being legally responsible for something, and *all* insurance is liability insurance in some form.

 If your tree falls on the neighbors' house, your homeowners insurance covers it, because their job is to allay the risk of legal (monetary) responsibility from something like that happening.

This is the case even with medical insurance, which covers your debt to the doctor, thereby eliminating your legal responsibility.

Lawsuits are not supposed to punish by default. Their purpose is to allow the plaintiff to recover reimbursement for damages from the person who caused them. Insurance is doing what it's supposed to do if it gets involved in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DVR runs a custom version of Windows CE which AFAIK requires you to be in a protected maintenance mode to use the USB for anything but power. On top of this the recordings use an encryption-based DRM which makes the process far more complicated than a simple undelete.

I'm afraid there isn't actually a way to undelete on a Uverse DVR and I'd be very suspicious of any software that claimed otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. He gets squished under a rock. He was once a prince so it counts as a human death, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 14:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, this takes me back to the days of Goldeneye's DK mode and Turok's Purdy Colors mode.  Between this and the new Ratchet and Clank I hope this sort of thing is making a comeback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the new TV show set in the Prime universe before TNG? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knows? But somewhere in Activision's balance sheet it looks like a good idea to someone.  Companies only drop prices if they think it will spur more sales.  Activision doesn't appear to care about that.  It might be BECAUSE it's an annualized franchise that they do this, for the reason you mentioned above.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pricing isn't based on when it's "right" to lower the cost of a game.  A company bases the price of an older game on several factors, but overall it's a question of maximizing profit.  If the company believes they will continue to see acceptable sales rates at $30, why drop it to $10?  The real problem here is the number of people who still go out and buy the new one at $60, thereby emboldening them to believe they have a "premium" product.

Like many other people I've skipped over Nintendo this generation, so I don't have recent experience, but from Wii on back, first-party Nintendo games hardly ever dropped below $20.  This is because Ninty knows people will pay a premium price for Nintendo polish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 17:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't talking about Mongo in *Blazing Saddles*, are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell our patients about your acceptable short term loss while they're forced to wait for the Government to somehow figure out how to clone the services we already provide at a rate anywhere near our current level of efficiency, while trying to do the same for every other nonprofit, regardless of diversity of mission.

What you're advocating would utterly cripple our hospital system.  It would take a LOT of work to transition without catastrophic consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal income generated from a 501(c)3 is absolutely taxed just like any other business. Where on Earth did you hear otherwise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep scratching my head wondering where all of this extra tax money you keep mentioning is going to come from. You do realize that the very word "nonprofit" implies that all of an organization's surplus revenue goes right back into the cause, right? 

Sure, some people are overpaid (not nearly so in comparison to a similar job in the private sector, by the way), but I think you'll find the actual surplus across all organizations isn't nearly as much as you think. My executive director is a better example of someone at the helm of one of these groups than the head of the Red Cross is. Again, I'm afraid you're letting a few dramatic examples overshadow a chorus of more sensible ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Income percentages as a measure of a nonprofit's useful-to-evil ratio is one of Reddit's favorite chestnuts.

We're a doctor's office, so our administrative costs are incredibly high because of licensing, insurance, etc.  That doesn't mean we're less effective than a food pantry and our finances shouldn't be held to the same standard.

Moreover, the internal mechanisms of any organizations are far too complicated to reduce to a simple pie chart. It may surprise you to learn that, for instance, the majority of our funding for cancer testing and prevention comes from Susan G Komen's literally-hitler "awareness" effort.

Oh, and anyone who thinks we aren't already subject to lots of scrutiny from the government is out of their minds.  We're submitting to an external audit right now, in fact. It's something we do every year under Michigan law. No biggie, part of doing business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a low income clinic, we are strongly in favor of anything that helps us fulfill our mission. Obamacare isn't perfect but it's truly stunning how helpful it's been for our patients.  We don't support political or religious organizations, but you'd better believe the governor got an earful from us and others when he dragged his feet on keeping our state's Medicaid expansion.

That is technically lobbying. I think maybe you're hung up on the idea that it's always a bad thing, but it's not. As a group working day after day in direct contact with these people, we have a duty to speak up for them when we have the opportunity and we know they will be left behind without our help.

The thing is, no lobbyist is going to tell you different. They all feel like the government needs to hear their side of their pet topic. Black and white has nothing to do with this. It's nowhere near simple enough to reduce it to that.

Edit: also, "render unto Caesar" means you should submit to the authority of  Government and to God in their own respective deserved ways. The whole thing with the taxes was only the example Jesus used to get his point across (the coin is Caesar's, made in his image, so if he's owed it he should get it. Mankind has God's image, so...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we are accepting this, I also nominate the entire Spin Doctors catalog.

I feel old for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvin Gaye's "Got to Give it Up."  [Linky](http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/the-blurred-lines-legal-battle-explained-what-comes-next-20150320). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at a 501(c)(3).  We are a small (20 employees) private primary care clinic that seeks to provide high-quality medical care to those who can't afford it.  In doing so we serve the public good by keeping these people from entering the hospital, via ER, without a way to pay.  
We help people sign up for insurance if they don't have it. We teach them how to take care of themselves.  We work in the community to try to keep our neighbors from being ruined by their medical bills. 
We also seek to be a doctor's office...you know, like the one you have...instead of one of those dingy free clinics with the bullet proof window between you and the receptionist.  You'd be surprised how big of a deal that is.

Trust me, we do this for peanuts.  Our Executive Director drives a ten-year-old Sentra and makes less each year than my wife, even though both are RNs.

Would you really throw us out with the bathwater?

I can't speak to the Cato Institute.  Don't know the first thing about them.  But I suspect you are allowing the dramatic examples to overshadow the real good that quiet organizations like mine do every day.  Just because you don't see us doesn't mean we aren't all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would write down then hold long, bizarre conversations with myself. The Gollum to my Smeagol would be named Mr. Pickles.  Mr. Pickles wants to be a supervillain.

Edit: I feel the need to point out that I'm a thirtysomething white guy with a beard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly Perlmutter is the reason for no Black Widow film until now, too, right?

I didn't care that much for IM3 but I would've liked it a lot more with that twist intact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 03:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OF COURSE IT IS

It's a wonder we grow anything in this state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 02:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not realistic.  The police may take someone in if they are obviously intoxicated or suffering from a mental condition (psychotic break, for instance) and disturbing the peace or showing themselves to be a threat to themselves or others, but this is not necessarily an arrest and it usually would not involve handcuffs. There could ([likely wouldn't but could](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/False_arrest)) be serious liability ramifications if the above scene happened in real life.  Your mileage may vary based on local municipality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 02:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm...Posse Comitatus? Am I missing something?

EDIT: TIL the Posse Comitatus act only explicitly applies to the Army and Air Force.  That is very weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 02:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, it comes from an old (and I mean *old*) satirical poem.  [Here's the phrase's Wikipedia page](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bread_and_circuses). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have that too, but we call them high and low beam. Foglamps are that extra set of white lamps, usually mounted in the front bumper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cars in America also have E/parking brakes, *most people just don't use them* because putting an automatic transmission car in Park is usually enough.

OP was asking why he saw so many cars do it on American media.  I felt like this was a safe assumption for an answer. *shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was a church group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If complicated isn't your thing, it might not be for you. That said, my main barrier to entry was feeling like I needed to take it seriously. Once I figured out how the developers meant the game to be taken (Dark, but batshit), I had a blast. One thing I would not recommend for you would be to try 3 if those are your complaints for New Vegas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AC: I get that I'm supposed to convince you otherwise, but stop here unless you like pirates. It's all downhill from here otherwise.


Portal: have you tried 2? It kinda makes 1 feel like a tech demo (oh, I'm gonna catch hell for that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Souls (really it was Demon Souls I gave up on). I'm getting older. I play games to unwind, and I have less time for them than I used to. I roll my eyes when someone uses it to prop up their gamer cred ("I didn't gloat when I 100%ed THPS4, get off my damn lawn") or acts like difficulty should be the primary criterion for a game's quality, using it as an example.  I have adult responsibilities including parenting, so "no pausing" is a deal breaker.

Please disabuse me because I'm wondering if I'm missing something, especially with Bloodborne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I got distracted. It's 4800 lbs (2012 with SXT trim +160 lbs for gas + tow package + a bit of fudging because these things are never empty) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dodge Caravan is just under 2.5 tons US (~2200 kg) with the gas tank full. The current generation doesn't come in Manual, and I'm constantly having to remind myself that my transmission isn't going bad---it was *always* this bad. Remember that next time you see one parked on a hill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a custom job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American cars don't do that, *automatics* do.  Most cars in North America have automatic transmissions.  Cars in America also have E/parking brakes, most people just don't use them because putting an automatic transmission car in Park is usually enough. Sometimes there's a bit of give before the transmission grabs on an automatic, is all.


EDIT: please stop downvoting OP. The point of this sub is to clear up misconceptions about the States, is it not? The question was asked in good faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Veronica was the launch and support system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sony wasn't forthcoming about the contents of the fix but I seem to remember it actually had something to do with the disc drive getting a better firmware and the cooling fans being set to cool more aggressively when the drive was under heavy load. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 03:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hoooo that is NOT the right part of town to be making that joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier revisions had some trouble with later games that really pushed the system like Uncharted 3, but I think they fixed the issue with a patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 03:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, wasn't actually hoping you'd answer in a way that narrowed it down any :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a fricking Zip (the pedometer), wasn't it? I'm not missing one but I'm starting to suspect mine has more escape plans than Pinky and the Brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also clear across town from OP's stated area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a standard sticker the health department puts on the door of any vacant foodservice  business.  It absolutely does not mean the health department shut them down.  (Edit: had the wrong place so I deleted the second part of this comment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 16:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't where I had it (I swear it was near my MIL's childhood home near Potter Park), but try JJ Frozen Yogurt at 13070 Old U.S. 27 in Dewitt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 15:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you roughly in Michigan? I'm pretty sure I've had it in Lansing, too.  Also: I don't know if you saw this but I added a bunch on the East side of town since commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 14:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Richmond ice cream (name? It was at Richmond and Alpine) had it before they closed. This is where we got it after swim practice at Richmond pool. 

* That place in downtown Byron Center had it for awhile, but I don't think they do anymore.

* Woody's on 28th near Eastern used to when I was younger, ~~I would imagine they still do~~. EDIT: Their Facebook seems to confirm they still do.

* Too Tall's on Coit between 3 Mile and North Park had it a few years ago, but it's been awhile since I went there and they've changed ownership, so I'm not sure they still do.

* ~~I think that place on Remembrance just north of Leonard has it too.~~ EDIT: Confirmed, this place is [Double Dip Depot](http://doubledipdepot.com/).

* Rocky's in downtown Rockford definitely still has it.

* I've never been to Menchie's, but I hear they all have it.

EDIT: I poked around a bit.

* Kool Kone near the Northland Drive end of Plainfield, according to GRNow.

* Sundaes on Cascade Road just past the end of 28th street, before the bridge over the Thornapple, according to their Yelp page.

* I can't believe I forgot this one because I grew up a mile away.  Village Cone Shop on the north end of the Breton Village outlot (IIRC it shares a building with the D W gas station).

* The Whippy Dip in Silver Lake, according to vegangr on Instagram.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 12:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. I can think of at least two places here in Grand Rapids, Michigan that had them when I was a kid in the early nineties. I know this because I'm lactose intolerant, so my parents would take me out to get one after every swim meet in lieu of ice cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 04:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly it was Walt's favorite and he said he never wanted it removed, so they don't.  Dear goodness, that "modern" scene is like something out of an 80s sitcom, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 04:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please explain this Dole Whip mania to me? Is my hometown weird in that every third ice cream place has it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 02:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, you do know the whole purpose of this thread, right? You are taking this way too seriously.

I'm only going to address one point: I worked on a national level.  No, all hell breaking loose is not a common phenomenon in the southwest when it rains.  I repeat: only Los Angeles.  Not even San Diego.  It's a traffic pattern thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 01:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really, don't get me started.

I think a lot of the other posters explained this very well, but here goes.

My other comment in this same thread:
 Speaking as a former auto adjuster, Los Angeles is the only place in the entire country where people act like it's understandable that they got in a multi-car pileup because it started to *drizzle*.

 I once had the singular experience of driving from Indiana to O'Hare during rush hour, getting on a plane to LAX, then driving from LAX to Tujunga...during rush hour. Chicago drivers: I may not always like you, but I respect many of you. LA drivers: Fuck every last one of you.

 The food scene really is pathetic. I'd put Grand Rapids' food scene above LA's. I'm not saying this lightly; I really would. You know you're in for a great time when a freaking fast food place is at the top of that many travel "must eat" lists. And you know what? In-n-Out isn't actually that good. There, I said it.

Also: 

* How did they let traffic get that bad, and then worse? Don't they remember what mass transit looks like?  EDIT: Actually I have an answer to this, in the actual words of an actual Angelino: "Eeew... only, like, *poor* people take the bus!"
* How is it possible that the most cynical, stereotypical portrayals of Hollywood types I've seen in mass media somehow fell short of the mark?    
* EVEN THE FREAKING PALM TREES AREN'T GENUINE ^((they're imported from Florida)^)
* Hollywood itself is one of the most abrupt cases of expectation vs reality I've ever seen.  It's somehow both pretentious and slummy.
* Seriously, where's the good food?
* The air is third-world quality.  I've lived in Tegucigalpa and spent a good bit of time in Mexico City. I know third-world quality.
* Tell me where the urban planner touched you, LA.
* One of my least favorite places on earth is the never-ending, culture-free, soul-choking, concrete-worshiping sprawl around Detroit.  Take that, supersize it and add palm trees and self-absorbed people.  BAM, you've described most of the Basin.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 01:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Because Detroit has standards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 01:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the person on the Internet.  Admit it, you're in Russia or something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 00:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a former auto adjuster, Los Angeles is the only place in the entire country where people act like it's understandable that they got in a multi-car pileup because it started to *drizzle*.

I once had the singular experience of driving from Indiana to O'Hare during rush hour, getting on a plane to LAX, then driving from LAX to Tujunga...during rush hour. Chicago drivers: I may not always like you, but I respect many of you.  LA drivers: Fuck every last one of you.

The food scene really is pathetic.  I'd put Grand Rapids' food scene above LA's.  I'm not saying this lightly; I really would.  You know you're in for a great time when a freaking fast food place is at the top of that many travel "must eat" lists. And you know what? In-n-Out *isn't actually that good.* There, I said it.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually nonjudgmental Midwesterner here. I've spent over a week in each of the top six US cities by population.  TBH Philly was my least favorite one until I visited LA.  

Seriously, one week in LA and it took a backseat to a town that smells like dog piss four months of the year. I tried to like LA, I really did, but fuck everything about that place.

...Except the Queen Mary and Magic Mountain, but do those even count?

Sincerely, someone who lives within a day's drive of ***DETROIT***, and who has an UP-sized chip on his shoulder against the D Metro, but would still chose it over L.A.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 20:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 Rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 13:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/iamverysmart

Two can play that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough! Detroit belonging in both is why I thought you were just talking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 03:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AoS teased the energy shield a few weeks back.  Not saying I think they'll go that way (or that I want them to) but it was a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 01:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it's gonna be my pet cause around here to remind people that Detroit is not particularly representative of Michiganian cities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 01:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's spot on. Look at the top few comments--they all reject the question out of hand. It's not an unamerican question in the sense of us finding the question odious. It's because, to our ears, it's a bit like asking which drop of a lake is the lakiest. Our motto is *e pluribus unum*--out of many, one. The idea that one state would be more American than others goes against our very concept of what makes the States United in the first place: that they represent, at least ideally, a pluralistic unity of diverse interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 16:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For future reference, www.canistream.it will tell you if pretty much anything is available for streaming, and where. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for allowing me to proudly display Bloody Sabertooth Pac Man.  I was a little put off by Ann Arbor being represented on there and us being forgotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 08:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In many places our public transit system is a shadow of what it once was, or had the potential to become, because of concerted lobbying by the automakers to replace that infrastructure with their busses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 08:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally had zero opinion, good or bad, of Mormons until I spent two weeks in SLC with a family of them, and TBH it was hard to not let myself come away with a negative opinion.

The wife of the family was an old friend of my wife, and we were out there to visit them. I'd never met this family before, but they were our age and we spent some time in their social circles. We talked a lot about our respective religious backgrounds (I was brought up in a very conservative Calvinist community), and they felt welcome to do more than their share of proselytizing, both of their religion and of their Fox News-infused world views.

The way the family and others around them acted, while simultaneously being very nice to us and clearly good people overall, reminded me of the worst members of a community I'd turned my back on: nice, generous, but possessing a dangerous mix of being closed-minded, cloistered and way too self-assured. Exhibiting a passive aggressive boastfulness about their lives while acting as if different ways of life were obviously inferior, and anyone who dissented was simply, exasperatingly wrong. Completely unaware that certain tenets of their religion or culture, presented bluntly and as fact, could be taken as deeply offensive or even personally insulting by outsiders.  Way too eager to act as if any negative interaction they had with outsiders was more evidence of a concerted campaign of oppression against God's own chosen people--a people who, to a man, should be held completely blameless in any conflict, no matter what the cause.

Full disclaimer: the above applied pretty directly to me in high school. I know it's not exclusive to the LDS Church. That said, as a person who knows he hurt people back then, who has worked hard to grow away from it (here I feel like I'm patting myself on the back too much, if so I apologize), it was very frustrating to see those behaviors from grown people my age on that scale.  It's easy for me to see how someone could get a very negative image of LDS people if their interactions had been anything like mine.

TL;DR I don't begrudge people their anti-Mormon sentiment, even though I can see they are largely good people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 03:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 had a rep for ruining controllers.  It was verboten at our house for this reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your construction pluralized while specifying a quantity of one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
