<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rules of no sleep are that everything written is true. 

It spoiled it a little bit for me to read the ending as it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should let the guy go, this is cruel and really unfair. 
Just end this game now, I don't think hat your wife or daughter would like the idea of you doing this either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 02:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was good, but please refrain from breaking character :( it spoils it, and is against the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 02:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but it's better than the remake called quarantine. 
No rats though, I think it was a dog originally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 01:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't think that you're going to get paid bro.

I think possibly, it's more like a spirit of the sea or something. Those three men were the first in the lighthouse, and died as possibly an offering. No one has died since, but blood is required to keep the bad spirit happy? I don't know.

 Check lighthouse records for similar disappearances from original crews. 

Maybe you remember because you aren't actually a crew man? Or because the spirit knew that you were looking for him.

I doubt that the anti Christ lives on an island off the shore of Scotland. Especially as the anti Christ has to be born into this world first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who will find you? 

And I'm glad that you were saved last minute :) luckily you didn't end up the same was as your father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has always been possible, for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love someone to explain this to me. As soon as she finds the game board, the story just goes off the rails and stops making sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not a very good interrogator, and you don't seem to act like a well trained cop. The real world isn't saw... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It tells you who he is in part one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too long to read? This is actually fairly short compared to most stories.

Short and sweet. You're missing out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 16:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did the brother not say anything? How did they know the combination? So tragic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 16:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He set the trap, if you can prove that he constructed the trap, it's still murder haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 16:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy most likely killed your dog, and you didn't tell anyone? 
What if he had put your dog somewhere to starve or whatever, you could have saved him.

This guy attacked you, and is now stalking you. You're lack of action is exactly why you're in this situation now. Telling your parents at least would have meant not being Home alone.
Telling the police about the stalking, might have sent the cops over tonight. What if he's killing others still too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 22:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the point in living for ever, if you're just going to sit indoors?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I assume that you got away? What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 04:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't.. We dated while he was living here in the uk. Then he moved back home to Poland, a smallish place I think. Crazy coincidence! 

He loved ghost hunting as well and told me a story about a haunted graveyard. Crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 04:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, obviously. She is bad, mad, wrong and not all spruce in the caboose. But I still felt a twinge of pity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 03:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfection. Absolute perfect story telling ability.

I'm sorry for your situation op. I hope that you can sort something out. Maybe try to collect up the dolls. Possibly lie to people, and say that you're exhibiting them? Or trying to take pictures of them for some reason?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 03:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really weird, I had an ex boyfriend from Poland, with the same name and same love of all things conspiracy. When did this all happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 03:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fixation with 'cleaning' doesn't fit the way the murder plays out. Fixing the make up was a sarcastic example tbh.

But someone fixated on cleaning up and fixing people should really be more inclined to create perfection. Even complete lunatics know that organs = inside parts. I think he's trying to distract us from something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 03:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, killers do actually maintain some kind of logic, order and pattern. Usually they only begin to change things if they feel close to being caught. 
It doesn't make much sense for him to be careful for a week, just watching, to then be so sloppy committing the murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think you've thought this through. Where's the symbolism, the goal? 
How are you making them clean, when you're making more mess? 

At least fix their makeup, or repair their flaws. You're literally just cutting them up.
That hardly fits in with all of the planning that you do up to that point. Slow and careful in the hunt, but rash and sloppy in the execution?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murder can also be caused by negligence, undue care etc etc. It probably varies a lot all over the world, but if this was the uk he could be tried for murder (if he was older) because shooting at someone can reasonably be expected to result in the outcome of death, as well as injury depending on the outcome.

In this case, it was a pellet gun and he was ten. So I think, the devil used his knowledge to trick a good soul into ending up in hell. Because he ended up committing suicide, rather than dieting naturally and going to heaven. I wrote 2 comments and can't remember what I actually put lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 00:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I still feel bad Vanessa. She went too far yeah, but still. My heart goes out to all the girls and guys in the 'friend zone'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mary wasn't just the beginning though, you've 'helped' others... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying that something swung into the wind doesn't mean that the wind changed the course of the pellet. He was taking a pot shot at someone who was a good target, and one of the shots got 'lucky'.

I don't think that God would send someone to hell for that, not at the age of ten. Especially as he seemed super good as an adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It 'swung into the wind', it didn't swing in or with the wind. Plus the devil says that the uncle at aged ten, targeted the hobo. Probably for fun, but I guess he did shoot at him on purpose.

The uncle probably didn't even know that the hobo died though.

Strangely though, Catholics preach that confession saves you from hell. So the fact that he killed himself, seems like he cared more about his reputation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 20:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What skin products did you order, out of curiosity? Where from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comments on this story have been my favourite ever.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep acting normal, don't let "her" know what's up. 
Then, jump up out of the blue... Vault out the window.

Or run out the door like your backside is on fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that you keep following up with them 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 11:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of nutcase finds an angel, or a humanoid that looks like an angel, and thinks gee I'll just cut his wings off... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 10:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this literally a nosleep story about a fart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 10:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, you said that you were taking your dog Ava... But then never mention her again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 10:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is assume that you didn't die then, what happened after you fell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 10:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there nothing more you can do, only talking?
Can't you try to arrange a respite week, or weekend away? Encourage them to vacation with friends or family a while? 

Anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 14:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure whether I understood this, honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 11:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where the belief of the whole celebration comes from.

Either way, you should try the police again. Just tell them it's a missing persons report to investigate, don't tell them all the unusual stuff.. See what they find out.

I think the best bet would be to ride that bus, with a bag full of supplies and maps. Might take a while before it turns back up though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 02:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 18:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please call the police, that girl needs to go home.
Your parents are lying, someone loves that little girl and wants her home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it? Anyone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like she accidentally got a ride into the Mexican afterlife. 
There are two levels, where the good go if they are remembered by their living families and the place where the forgotten spirits go. If she went someone that was full of cheer and bright colours, then she is in the happy place. There are ways out, if I recall correctly. But I don't know that much in detail.

She can look for the ruler, a female goddess I believe. Who will help her, but unless you get on that bus too... There's nothing that you can really do from this side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the rules dude. Nosleep is real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I didn't actually even look at the link until the end. At the very start, I thought it might be a type of spirit board.. Until it mentioned the sister riding it to work lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 13:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing it has a cat pattern, like the one in the link. 
I had no idea what a penny board was at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 13:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the shadiest adoption process, definitely speak to father. It sounds like back in Egypt they knew what was going on and wanted to ship the problem away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 11:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so hear me out.
This could be a demonic voice, demons talk to people as a way of slowly taking them over and breaking down their mental resistance. Others who hear the voice will have bad things happen to them, because unlike you, they aren't being protected from the negative effects of the voice. 
You should cleanse your home, and also see if there are any unusual symbols around the place. Commonly found hidden under beds, or where you sleep. The symbol will be what is 'protecting' you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the agency just hacked the scp foundation. I hope that you don't end up as a category D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 01:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be miles away by now, it's free and might just bugger off to live in other shadows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The endless tunnel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silence. The unmistakeable, tangible and smothering absence of sound. True silence, not a single sound to be heard. There is a dark and stormy sky, the clouds are full and heavy. Rain is lashing down, being blown almost horizontal, by a strong wind. The kind of wind that should be howling through the skies, almost like an angry animal. But everything is silent. The huge clouds above are being whipped into a frenzy but the gale force wing, moving across the sky at a dizzying speed.
Lightening flashes in the sky, briefly illuminating my surroundings. This is when I realise where I am, and what I can see around me. I am seemingly floating, slightly above an endless plain. A dark green blanket of grass covers the ground for miles and miles in every direction, all laying perfectly flat and stretching further than I could ever see. It's like a green ocean, immeasurable in size. The grass below is waving and rippling with the force of the wind, and I can see patterns twisting in the grass as it is illuminated by the brief flashes of light in the heavens. 

The only break in the monotony of this view, comes in the form of a gigantic mountain. It is standing, directly in front of me. I am dwarfed by it size, a single spike of rock, jutting from the broken earth like a jagged tooth. It stretches high into the sky, a snow capped peak disappearing into the darkness above. It is night time, or perhaps this nightmarish land has no sun at all. I have no way of knowing, and even less desire to find out.

I can feel the silence now, pressing in on me, even though I have no form to speak of. My consciousness is here, whilst my body is sleeping elsewhere. Perhaps I am merely a visitor, here to observe this world and nothing more. There should be noise, cracks of thunder, bellowing wind... But there is nothing. This dream is silent, completely silent.

I'm floating here, invisible and nothing happens for an age. I know that I am dreaming, I am aware of that fact, but I have no control over what is happening before me. I am simply stranded watching a silent storm blowing through the grass below me. How long has it been? Dreams are short, but feel like hours. My mind feels like it's beginning to slip away, becoming confused as to where I am. This is a dream, I repeat this mantra hundreds of times. The words begin to sound foreign and strange to me. I have been stuck in this loops for so long.

After what feels like days, I see movement. I turn my head down towards the base of the mountain, i blink. In an instant I am lower, did I move? Or is this just a trick of my mind? This is a dream. I am positioned approximately 8 feet from the ground and I am level with something that I had not seen here before. Was it always here? Maybe not, this is a dream. It is a gaping tunnel, no, a pipe. The mouth of a pipe is sticking from the side of the mountain. It is dark and wet, like an endless hungry mouth. It smells of copper and Earth, water is flowing slowly from it. It looks like some kind of run off pipe, the kind that I've seen on tv, but not in real life. I really do not want to go into the tunnel, or any closer to it at all. It's wide mouth has filled me with fear, the darkness is looming in front of me. I can feel it there, waiting. This is a dream, I want to wake up. My mantra has changed, because I am terrified.

I divert my attention back to the movement that caused my to move here, anything to look away from that pipe. I can see an elderly couple walking slowly towards the mouth of the pipe. There is no easy path up the mountain, they seem to be struggling. They are holding hands, and have their heads bowed down in the rain. Their long khaki raincoats are billowing in the wind, and they look so tired. Their backs are bent in the force of the wind, I wish I could help them. I try to call out, but they cannot hear my voice. They cannot see me either, it becomes immediately clear that I am merely a spectator here. The man and the woman are heading to the tunnel, they seem determined. Why?

I am terrified, I am over come with fear and dread. I am cold. This is dream. Why would they enter the tunnel? Why? 

The first and only sound that I hear in this nightmare is a voice, it comes from the mountain. It does not echo from the tunnel; or whisper into my ear like a lovers secret, it just comes from the mountain. As if the mountain were a man, standing tall in front of me. The voice is male, deep and strong, the words are clear but not loud. 

"Watch them enter, watch them die."

That is all I hear, but I know that the voice is talking still. I know that it is telling the couple to enter the pipe, walk in. Walk right in. I am screaming to them, begging and pleading with them. "Don't go in, you'll die. You're going to die!" They can't hear me, nothing gets through. 
I know that it tells them to go deeper and deeper into the dark, turning them left and right inside of a pitch black labyrinth. Don't worry it says, I know the way. I'm still screaming, my throat feels like it's tearing apart, I'm crying out of pure desperation. I feel like I'm smashing my hands into a wall of glass, trying to break through into this nightmarish world. The voice tells me that I cannot save them. 

The tunnel mouth is gone now, but I know that the couple are trapped in the mountain. Walking in the dark forever, just waiting to die inside that awful coppery tunnel. I can feel their determination to reach the end of the tunnel. I can feel their love for each other. I can feel their fear, their pain and their uncertainty. Before I wake up, the last thing I feel is their cold acceptance. They know that they are going to die, lost, cold and alone. They will collapse, exhausted, onto the wet floor and slowly fall asleep. Hand in hand, and I feel it as they go cold.

"You will never save them. You don't remember." I try so hard to remember.

Every day when I awake, I am tired and sad. I feel lost.
A few days ago I sent my description of this dream off to some famous dream expert, I saw an advert on Stephen Kings Facebook page. Apparently he is about to release a new book about bad dreams, and his literal 'dream team' were taking requests for dream analysis. I thought it might be worth a try, maybe they will ease my worries. Maybe if I understand the dream, it won't be a scary.

The version I sent off was a lot more condensed, but it was still longer than the reply I received. I got a Facebook message that simply said "remember us". I freaked out a little over that, because I didn't think it was funny. I didn't hear anything else from the page.

Ever since, I've been finding those two words scribbled on my university notes, highlighted in newspapers, traced onto steamy bathroom mirrors... Never anything else, just "remember us".  What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok fine, but how do you have time to cook a stew in the morning? Tell me your secrets! 

Also, just feed him other girls and not yourself... Otherwise eventually Randall will be left alone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that your parents knew? Which is why they usually go out every time you go to the cabin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 01:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume that English is not your first language? As the flow of this was a little unusual.

Did anything odd happen when you first heard that song? The entity seems to have followed you to America, where it seemed more powerful. 

What was the significance of you 'talking to yourself'? Do you think that you were speaking to the entity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 15:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, nosleep has finally served its purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 14:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why are you on death row ten or so years later? Did they reinvestigate?
Or were you an adult when this all happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 14:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If at 5 years old she doesn't understand that self injury is bad or stupid, I think that she needs help. I would take her to a therapist or something stat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 10:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, didn't even notice that! Curse you auto correct! _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 03:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of something, but I can't remember what.
Scary stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 03:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it for whoever is on your next shift lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 18:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you did t even go to hell, as you weren't really dead per say. The demon, devil or whatever that had you might have known that it was only temporary and just wanted some fun.
I don't know if a 14 year old has lived enough for God to justify an eternity in hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still fucking play neopets haha. I'm 24, ten years this year. It wasn't me though, promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 21:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should take a closer look at your home, if you own the house.. You can renovate or move stuff right? 
It seems odd that you've never checked out the loft (attic), I'd have inspected and personalised every inch of my new space.

Maybe check out some baited traps for rodents? Or even try to track down the unrelated teenager to see what was so weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 18:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For gods sake Anna, are you cleaning in there or just messing around?! I don't want to have to ask again!"

My mum has just started chewing me out about not cleaning the bath. It's become a frequent argument in this house, almost every single day there comes a shout from down the hall. 'Clean the bath' or 'why don't you wipe down after yourself?'; it's become part of the morning ritual.
The thing is, I always wipe down after a shower. I stand in the bathroom bundled in a towel; turn off the the shower and grab a new towel from the rack, to start the aggravating process of wiping away all of the water droplets from the ceramic tiles. It takes even longer these days as we had a new bath and shower fitted. Instead of a plastic shower curtain, we now have a big glass door hanging from the wall. I wipe it clean, and dry, every day so that there are no water marks or gross smears left behind.
Then, the damp towel gets hung up to dry. Simple enough. After this morning, after what I've seen, I'll never clean that room again. Hell, I'll never use this bath for as long as I live.

I suppose I should take a step back, and start from the beginning. A handful of months ago, our landlord paid us a visit to check out the place. He is a fairly absent guy, but he makes a habit of stopping over once a year to make sure his property is still standing. He lets us know when he is coming over and all in all he is a pretty decent landlord. We pay our rent, he sorts out any issues we have and that's pretty much it. We've lived here eight years now, and it's a pretty nice setup for me and my mum. Our house has been standing for 60 years, but it's in good shape.
Before all my problems started; we had noticed that our bath had been looking pretty dull, the enamel was worn and chipped. Our shower sputtered and the plastic coating was faded. Some of the white tiles on the wall were loose or cracked. I guess the bathroom tiles were pretty old at the time anyway, I mean, the cracks had been there since we moved in. Generally, you looked at the bathroom and just thought that it needed a nice coat of paint and some TLC. 
So when the landlord announced his annual visit, my mum made a plan to ask about getting a new shower and a can of paint. She didn't want to push her luck, so she was going to offer to do the painting herself. That's the kind of person that my mum is. We were both totally shocked when the landlord announced his plans to get a whole new bathroom refurbishment for us, a new bath, new tiles, new shower... Hell, he even said we could choose the colour scheme. 

Fast forward two months later, the workman are all gone and we have this awesome, shiny new bathroom. My mum picked out this beautiful Aqua colour scheme, white tiles and a crisp white sink unit. The first time I used the shower, I felt like I was in a 5 star hotel. The water came out with no false starts, no ridiculous temperature issues and best of all, there was a working extractor fan! I was pleased to finally not have to deal with damp towels. It was nice to have a new bath too, it was shiny and new. With big clawed feet, like I'd seen in posh magazines. I thought at the time that it was an odd choice, as I thought that would have been an expensive option. But what did I know about baths? 
For a few days, everything was perfect. Until my mum started yelling at me, "you're leaving hair in the bath!". At first, I simply thought that I was being forgetful. I'd walk back along the hall, pick up a towel and wipe down the bath. I'd polish the silver taps, clean the smears from the glass and pick out the odd strands of hair laying the the base of the bath.

I assumed that the hair was mine, as it was long and black. Just like my hair was, and my mums. So I mean, it could have been her not bothering to clean up after herself. After a few more days, that's what I began to think. I was certain that I'd already cleaned up. I was 100% certain of it. I'd wiped this surface, I'd cleaned that wall. Where was this water coming from? Why was there so much damn hair I'm this bath all the time?

After a couple more days, things took a turn for the worse. The long black hairs started to multiply, once there was a hair or two at a time. Then 3, then 4 and sooner than I realised, I'd be finding small knots of hair. Wet, slimy hair. It honestly looked more like it was from a dirty lake, than from my clean bath. I didn't know what to do! My mum never seemed to see it, and it couldn't be from anywhere else. So I ended up just doggedly cleaning it up, time after time. Before long I'd be trying to pick up clumps of hair, stringy back webs of hair.

Black, brown, blonde and grey. Wait, blonde hair? Grey hair? I lost it at at that point. The hair was turning up in all kinds of colours and shades. My mum and I definitely both had black hair, so I was at my wits end. Cleaning up hair was a frustrating task as it was, have you ever tried to pick wet hair out of a bath? It's a nightmare sometimes, especially when you're trying to hold up a towel with one hand already. I was convinced that there was an issue in the pipes, the builders must have fucked up the pipes. I was sure it was something like that, what else could it have been? 

This morning was the final straw, I was standing in the shower. I'd just finished washing my hair, and I found myself looking down at my feet. I was watching the shampoo remnants wash away down the plug hole, between my toes. When I saw a hair, waving in the current of the water. I thought nothing of it, other than annoyance at its presence. Showering had become nothing short of a chore, ever since the hair had started appearing. I hated it. 
I was about the resume my shower when something made me look back down. Something was wrong, but I didn't know what. A stray fleck of soap dripped down from my skin and swirled away into the blackness of the plug hole. That's when I realised, the single strand of awful hair I was looking at wasn't washing away. It was writhing in the water, coming out of the plug hole. It was fighting the current, not moving with it. 

I was perplexed, but still, I finished my shower as usual. Turned off the current and stepped out of the bath. I shrouded myself in a towel, and bent closer down for a look. The hair was no longer moving, and I told myself that it had just been a trick of the light. Or something like that. I reached into the base of the bath to pluck the hair from its watery resting place, but it slipped from my fingers. It slither further into the plug hole, hanging across the silver divider between the bath and the dark pipes below. I grabbed the hair with two fingers and I began to pull, the hair was longer than any I'd ever seen. It kept coming, more and more, being pulled out into the light of my bathroom. The hair was now pulling more hairs out too, strand after strand. I was pulling up clumps of dirty, matted hair, all wrapped in sludge from the depths of the pipes underneath my bath. There was a stench building, growing in strength as the piles of hair in my bath grew. It reeked, like rubbish and decay. I gagged, but I was determined. I was almost in a frenzy to get the hair out of my bath, out of the plug and free from my pipes. I was like an animal, in my mind I thought that this must be the cause of my problem. Some age of clump of hair, stuck in the labyrinth of pipes buried in the ground. 
I pulled and pulled, suddenly the hair went tight. The hair was stuck, I felt like I was so close now, this must be the final clump. I climbed into the bath and kneeled down, slipping over the disgusting piles of hair. My knees slick with water and ooze. My left hand was clutching the hair, my right was holding onto the bath rim in a bid to stable myself. I tried to pull on the strands, to free the clump. I still had to be careful not to snap the hairs or drop them. I couldn't risk losing them forever back down the pipe. 
The hair wouldn't loosen, no amount of pulling or tugging was inching this mess of hair closer to freedom. I decided to try and get a look inside the plug, the light was on already so I leaned forward. I was trying to lean forward, I couldn't get a good angle to see down there and I was getting more and more annoyed with each passing moment. 

My hair fell past my eyes, but before I could brush it back from my face, it was snagged by the plug. No, it was grabbed by something in the plug hole. I panicked, I could feel my hair being pulled down into the inky black below, I tried to stand up in a panic. But I couldn't. My towel slipped from around me, and I was stuck, naked in a half crouch. Before my mind could clear enough to think about my next move, my hair was yanked incredibly hard. I was pulled forward so hard, that I slipped and smashed face first into the faucet. I let out a cry of pain, my cheek was in agony. My hair was pulled again, and my face was once again rammed into the taps. I felt a crunch, and my face exploded into white hot pain. I tried desperately to pull away, my hands slick with water. I felt my hair lose tension, as whatever was pulling on me relaxed its grip. I hastily crawled backwards on my hands and knees, my eyes blurred with tears. I gripped my hair in both hands, trying to free myself from this nightmare. But suddenly I was pulled again, there was an inhuman strength in the pull and I flew back towards the taps. I saw a final glint of silver, before the faucet hit. My mouth struck the taps, my lip split as my teeth were smashed from their roots. I screamed through a mouthful of blood and loose teeth.  They plunked down onto the ceramic underneath my swollen face, sounding like pennies dropping into a well.
My hair finally ripped free from my scalp, with an agonising tear. I saw skin, and blood fly past my field of vision and plop down near the plug. I watched in muted amazement as the strands slithered off down into the darkness. What the fuck just happened? I knelt in disbelief, crying in pain and dripping blood from my ruined face.

I could hear my mum walking up the stairs, shouting something. I couldn't focus, I could barely see. I blinked hard, trying to clear my vision. Blood was swirling near the plug, when I saw something that sent me reeling. I stumbled, trying to stand up and grab a towel. I panicked, screaming in fear and pain. I could hear my mum at that point, outside the door, shouting about cleaning up. 

I haven't moved yet, I'm still sitting with my back pressed up against the door. I'm watching the plug; where a single, thin and pale finger has emerged to reach my spilt blood.

Now I know that the hair wasn't mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But still.. The police would be a good bet, regardless of who the killer actually is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 17:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it literally says that the mum fell asleep with a cigarette. She did it, nothing to do with the dad.
Pls she was fucking some other guy, I don't think the dad was wrong at all. She seemed like a stone cold bitch tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 17:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the hell don't you just go to the police.

Charlotte is dead, you found a shack with evidence of Brady's clothes.

You now have a bloody shirt.. Are you going to let more people die? 
How can getting in trouble for walking in the woods seriously be that much of a problem, compared to a little boy's life?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 17:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to read up on memetic contagions, you can find a list of all currently known memetic hazards on the scp foundation site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
