<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6310</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright name 5 things that aren't Jackie Chan
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Suggestion) Being able to ALT look around while downed. Also being able to pick yourself back up with the right medical tools. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So here is my expansion on the idea. 

1. So the timer for being down should be 20 seconds.  
2. You should be able to alt while down.  
3. If you have the right medical tool, maybe something different than the syringe to be able to dress your wound. Maybe Adrenaline shot? made with water and a new medicine component plus the usual syringe ingredients.   

Now here are the stipulations/balancing things. 
  
1. No more RNG getting up  
2. ALTing is a lower sensitivity and more restricted while on the ground (maybe fuzzy vision/blurry)  
3. the self dressing/healing takes 15 seconds to complete.  
4. Using the syringe (new medical tool) does not restart your 20 second timer while down, so there is a potential that you don't get it off in time if you're ALT looking for too long while you're down.  

Let me know what you guys think or if you have any improvements on this suggestion. 

My thinking is this will vary combat a little bit more with PVP, It will also make it so there is a lot more actual killing happening so you can see who killed you instead of them just letting you writhe on the ground and die. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only comment to this should be

"thanks team for adding this feature that we've asked for!"

 The complainers and the "ZOMG finally I've been waiting 8 years for this about damn time" need to calm down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ethan! man i find you in the strangest places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thar she blows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A co-worker and I have been on a diet. He saw this on my desk and left the appropriate verbiage on a post it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know a game trailer that can give me chills like this one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chopper Times/Tips (Request) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know exact timings for the chopper spawning into the island? 

I've been tracking it for the last couple of days and it seems to alternate between 2 hours and 3 hours. Somewhere in the day that changes and sometimes it comes an hour early or an hour late. 

Also what are you best tips for taking on the chopper? weapons/strats/base builds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks McJay! you're the man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright no one is going to see this but a good way to help your grip strength is doing Pullups/farmer carries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stubbs please stay alive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
