<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9926</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are doing a good part of the french section next year. 

So stoked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have to pay deposit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a weird quirk both my sister and I got our SS# the same day. I am 7.5 years younger then her but the guy handling it processed my paperwork first. Thus mine ends in 206, and hers ends in 207. 

I tease her from time to time about having a younger number then me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rather just buy a phone for $700 instead of having all the extra "free" crap thrown in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Guinness book people haven't contacted you yet expect their call. 220k is certainly a world record for one of these POS to still be on the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised Toyota , and subaru haven't started surreptitiously pasting kia badges on these since neither company wants to take the blame for how awful these turned out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like  smurfette, a koi fish, and a transformer had a unspeakable late night  rendezvous down in Cabo, and 9 months later this was their unholy dumpster baby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm. Encouraging news. 

Hopefully this is the case when I order tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I am seriously considering going to VZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not alone 90% of my entire twitter history is interacting with t farce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need any of the preorder bonuses. I never use my other gear VR, have beats studio wireless cans, and will do fine with my 128 GB sd card. I guess I could recouped a bit of money from the great VR, but I don't know if it is compatible with any other phones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is kinda BS that Samsung raised the price. How much will the note be? Over $1000? Maybe this is the year I just get a one + </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule #1 post your **own** vehicle.  Come up with your own snaps to tease your buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but this is the base model and doesn't cost anymore then the note 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be excited to get a reliable 10mbps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually really cool. Imagine a family with one dock, connected to keyboard, mouse, and monitor. Whoever wants to work on something can just drop their phone in dock, and boom they are on. Next person comes up, and boom all their files, and settings are right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I cringed so hard I thought I was slipping into a epileptic seizure. I couldn't believe that he got good reviews for that speech. Politicizing that woman's pain, that he caused was just classless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate having to look away for speedo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The (burger clogged) heartbeat of (white trash) America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing the s8 I would still much prefer my note 7. I like physical buttons, and the camera is no better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but all the debt ceiling drama from a few years ago was very irresponsible. That tactic is not something that should be used going forward IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends. May want to call and ask.You most likely will be able to jump after paying off 50% of your phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BOGO on att is looking pretty nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only $130 for a phone I may not like, and decide to jump to another phone, thus losing the $130? This is definately against the spirit of JOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I hate the wall, I am not for the Dems shutting down the government. This should not be the new normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are still a pinko for the yamaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://blackflag.jalopnik.com/further-proof-stadium-super-trucks-are-the-pinnacle-of-1704504634

I love this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh that is disappointing. I don't mind paying whatever the fraction of the phone is but I refuse to plunk down $130.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone confirm this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was a millionaire over night, buying a trophy truck is much higher on my list then a Lamborghini. It looks like so much fun to just be able to tear ass anywhere on any terrain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A GTI out of warranty LOL. 


Enjoy your retirement living in a box under a overpass, eating cat food, and wishing you haven't ruined your finances with this POS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  . But I understand how some people need at least 3500mah especially with an OLED display.

OLED display is more power efficient then LCD right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the point of Jump on Demand if you have to pay $130 just to get a new phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't abuse JOD. I only used it once last year to jump to Note 7. After everything went down, I was forced to get a iphone for a few months, until the S8 came out.

**REALLY** disappointed that I am going to have to now (for the first time) have to pay $130 for the most basic S8+ available for me to purchase. 

One of the core reasons I am staying with tmobile, despite sketchy coverage, and in light of the VZ Unlimited deal, is JOD.

I really hope they reconsider this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know whats fucked is that someone is in here downvoting all the JOD comments. Yours was hidden due to being -6 on the score. WTF is some shill over here trying to stop people from complaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im interested as well. Can we rally the troops to complain, and make them reconsider? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has this been confirmed? If so this may tip the balance for me going to VZ. The only thing keeping me on Tmobile is JOD, and if that now requires $130 per phone, I am out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I regretted going coral blue. It wasn't dark enough for my tastes. Too Easter egg IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was so used to getting them early, that I was disappointed lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why no gold? We gotta floss over here too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Americans butcher the pronunciation of Seat. They always say it  See-t like "please have a seat", which is totally wrong. 

The correct phonetic way to say it is Sh-it like "your car is a piece of shit". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the plus side, it must be much more comfortable riding 4 wheelers with a baby cock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry gas will be cheap forever. The CEO of Exxon is now the Secretary, of State. I'm sure he will work in the interest of keeping prices low, so you aren't forced to sell your body, just to drive down the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Aoki was spinning records back in the mid 90s. I went to a few raves he spun at. Pretty good longevity for EDM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People were rightly worried when BMW stated producing minis. However it all turned out to be unfounded. There is something quintessentially British about how these shit the bed mechanically, and the electronics work for shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait it is 2017. How did you buy a 20 year old 2014 civic?

If you have the power of time travel you should have bet your 401k on the pats in the super bowl, and then gone back 70 more years and cock blocked Trumps dad's game. 

Oh and hook me up with a iPhone 27 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did your mom hand this down, or your other nom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those years of blowing him finally starting to pay off!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It boggles the mind. Ignoring the problem won't make it go away. You can have your own interpretation of the data, but to just delete it is unconscionable. 

What have people done electing this guy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty pretentious. I only watch it to give my 4k TV a workout, with HD food porn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the new mods can get rid of the [draconian] posting rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it is driven by a guy who leaves a new woman, and child, Every time he goes to get a pack of cigarettes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baltimore has plenty of people to kill, stay down there ya bridge and tunnel terrorist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the proper protocol for bailing on a 40 foot ramp? I assume you want to avoid hitting the top edge, but land in on the top is only a 10 foot fall vs this where he barely had any of the curvature to break his fall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No tip? Ya cheap ass lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn that danger noodle came out of the gates ready to fucking rumble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came to post the same thing. Commas people!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No pita no care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does talking about the venerable 4.0 engine, subconsciously make you feel bad about your poor academic performance?

Perhaps a VW with a 2.5 would be more your speed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silken tofu in car form.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so apathetic to a silver e46 sedan, that I can't be bothered to roast it. 

Pure distilled middle of the mall, mediocrity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This vehicle bears a uncanny resemblance to my poop, after a three day green juice cleanse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the word Sline mean off the side of your car? Is that German for poseur?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about how many tampons you can fit in that thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turbocharged women's studies textbook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3/5 Scale model of a 1990s ford explorer, carved entirely out of dog shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is annoying how drip drop the media center portion of ps4 is. I was doing all kinds of dlna streaming, from my home server years ago on ps3. I ended up buying a nvidia shield, but it is still annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  count

cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty buzzed right now, and I don't think I have ever lusted for anything as much as I lust for those onion rings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone ever questions your assertion that America is the greatest country in the world, show them this gif as irrefutable proof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesbian in the front, awkward office sheet cake birthday party in the back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90% of all meetings are that way. We have a average of 3 meetings a week, that span between 45 minutes, and 2 hours. 

The majority of time it is someone giving a presentation that is not at all pertinent to anyone in the room, or just having a one way conversation with us, and not asking for input at all. It could easily all be avoided by just sending out a email. 

But then what would all the middle managers do? It seems that there only function is to stop all work, so that they can verbalize a email topic. Meanwhile the phones are on fire, the world is collapsing into itself, and we are stuck in this meeting trying to hide the animosity in our eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck your mother. 

Those wine glasses are a national treasure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First smoke on my master built. Chicken, pork tenderloin, and smoked Mac   cheese. Early grave here I come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an odd phenomenon when people mod their cars to look like everyone else's. 


You would think that taking a perfectly serviceable car, poured over for months by a team of engineers and designers, then making drastic changes to it's aesthetic, and function would be a act of individuality. 


However taking a clapped out e46, slamming it on its nuts, and buying the same 7 series wheels as a infinite number of other guys, is actually a sign of conformity. It is a signal to all the other douche bros in the stance community that you belong. 

You could probably save yourself some money, and just get really into vaping. You will be able to mingle with the same subset of society, and still be able to go over a speed bump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They vary from region to region, and shop to shop. My best ever kebab was in Tours France, and it was just like the one in the OP with some big steak fries, and this amazing smoking, spicy sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like someone commissioned H.R. Giger to design a door stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's odd that it sells as a premium cut in some places, and at a scrap price in others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best Kebab/Gyros come with the fries inside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not clairvoyant, but I 'll bet When the Marshals come to seize your assets, (after the judge rules in the plaintiff's favor in the wrongful death suit, for strapping a giant metal bar at exactly head height and driving it around on the street) they will leave your trailer with nothing but a half a carton of Marlboro Mediums, and 10-12 bankers boxes worth of Homosexual pornography.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not often that you can have 2 of something, and be considered the world's foremost collector. 

Assuming they both moved to that spot on their own power, 2 running dodge Omni's certainly makes you a connoisseur, with exceedingly rare tastes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no Hondas in this picture.  That is a Isuzu with a H badge stapled on the front  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right. I'm getting down voted, but honestly I don't even know why he shared that information.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any recommendations for healthier smoker recipes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got a smoker, and I am looking at all the amazing recipes. However I am about to start a diet so I wanted to find some chicken breast, veggies, lean pork recipes etc that are good, but not necessarily full of butter. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe the world has gone to such shit that I admire fucking Lindsey Graham do being a man of principle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got one today. My first dish was a digorno pizza right at the tail end of seasoning it for about 15 minutes. Best frozen pizza ever lol. The peperoni came out so tasty, and even the cheese infused. 

Stoked to do some chicken tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember walking past some of the lady boy bars in Phuket Thailand. Directly next door was a like late night tattoo shop. They had a wall of their previous tattoos  up. Lots of standard issue chav shit. 

Then there was one German guy. He was baby fat overweight, and looked late teens. Looked to be from somewhere in the agrarian part of Germany. I have been through there enough to spot a guy from there if I see one. 

Anyway he had his entire chest done up with Tupac standing there cross armed. Then tupacs skinny torso ran down his body, they shared the same belly button, and tupacs six pack was tattooed on his blubber. In true meta fashion he also had tupacs giant THUG LIFE tattoo across his stomach. 

It wasn't  the most I'll advised tattoo of all time, but this dude was not pulling it off in the slightest bit in the picture. The expression on his face was half smile, and half I just had sex with a guy who looked like a girl, did a bunch of drugs, and then had a life sized Tupac tattooed on my large body, this isnt going to end well in small town Germany. 

I was just passing by the photos on the wall but it always stick with me as the most absurd shit I have ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks way worse, and offset looks shit compared to the stock silver wheels. 

Good job  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it will look good up on jack stands in your driveway, as you pass by it riding your Walmart Huffy BMX bike, starting your 20 mile commute through the hood, to start your day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have $40,000 to spend on a souped up economy car, but God forbid I do one thing right, and drop $300 on powdercoating my wheels starter pack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you do us a favor and plasti dip your head, just to cover up your face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with used penis trucks is that you end up pretty low on the food chain. Sure you have the truck, and not a prius, but it's not the new shiny one. If you are going for alpha male, then this leaves you pretty low in the pecking order getting the sloppy seconds from the guy in the newer truck. 

You think you are beating your chest with this truck, displaying your virility to the world with a show of overexuberance. But at the end of the day you are just a cuckold with a old used up truck, with a old used up broad, in a old used up faded affliction T shirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust funders. 

One of the many things that bugged the shit out of me when I lived in NYC. I was husltling my ass off to make ends meet, and still have beer/cab/date money. I had a bunch of friends who were just idle, graduated school and were just chilling. Not even looking for work, just on a never ending cycle of hanging out and attending events with other spoiled cunts at 2pm, on a Wednesday.  

The worse part is that they would slum it with the Broke cool kids, and then shoot out to Switzerland for a weekend of heli skiing, and be back on Tuesday dressing poor and acting like nothing happened. 

I will never live there again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow this gif is a scathing critique on my 2017 so far.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes me want to puke actually. I love cheese but there is no circumstance where I want to eat 2 pounds of it in one sitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't be doing that bad, because I'm on the front page, and you're not

-ObLaDi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it odd that you are reaping all this karma off of your failed relationship SO dog. He is a cutie, and you got my up vote, but something doesn't sit right for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props to Paul he has skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I have read many accounts of it, however I never remember seeing this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the first bad decisions, on the long road to Porsche finally selling out, enough to produce a mini van.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking Jamaican rave drum and bass announcer at his day job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big props to whomever does her videos. The production values are top notch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I usually say people are entitled to their opinions, but this is unequivocal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do but I reserve my indigestion for dinner, and late lunches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When these were new the exuded so much machismo, that there was a Harley Davidson edition. Now the best you could do is get a Androgen testosterone replacement therapy collaboration  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aggressive front end styling write checks, that the hamster wheel in the engine bay, and steel wheels shod in slippery wooden tires, cannot cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you find yourself in that situation again, do not confront the guy, just run away and call the police. If he had gotten that far, where he was willing to sexually assault you, there is no reason to believe he wouldn't try to get you in his car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you snitching? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the 1000mph tail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mostly raw onions have no place in my breakfast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Calling this debacle a goat rodeo would be an insult to the noble men and women of the goat rodeo industry who work hard to organize novelty livestock shows for your entertainment.

Is the funniest thing I've read all week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least she isn't blowing the priest, and the ring bearer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a similar situation up until recently.  Worked at least 50-60 hours every week for years. 

It was a double edged sword. On one hand I had fuck you money,  helped me advance my standard of living, and purchase a home. 

On the other hand I gained a massive amount of weight, a drinking problem, and a unhealthy relationship with my SO. 

Lately a few things have changed, and my responsibility is shared with a whole other department so suddenly we don't even have volunteer OT. It's almost hard to adjust to the 40 hour week. I almost don't know what to do with myself, all my hobbies withered over the years. It's like I am getting out of jail. 

Luckily I set my life up to run on 40 hour per week, a lot of my coworkers will have a day of reckoning since they have BMW payments, and expensive mortgages to pay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proletarian here, don't worry, no offense taken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm half black, and have never seen that painting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phill is a good boy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you gingerly dipped the bottom  into a tub of baby shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rear end of these cars look like the perfect blend of a 997.1 Porsche 911, and a roll off dumpster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
