<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4555</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what is your definition of successful? If you think it is a slim chance do you have other options that you would like to follow? It sounds like you have a passion for flying, if the Air force doesn't work out, you should consider the navy. They have lots of pilots and I'm not 100% positive, but it's probably a lot less competitive than the Air force. Things take time. Don't be discouraged if they didn't work out the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love how easily I can learn new things. Hate how I can't comment because any opinion going against hive-mind gets downvoted to shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me I know how you feel. You can PM me if you want to talk. I think you first need to understand your values in life. Where do you want to go? What is important to you? It sounds like you don't give a lot of credit to yourself, so if your self-depreciating around people they might not enjoy spending time around you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 07:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LSD. Still want to try it, but I know I'll have a bad trip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 07:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who experiences hallucinations regularly, I can honestly say a lot doesn't scare me anymore. I guess even still the scariest are when I see a lot at once and just want it to go away but it won't. Sometimes they can be threatening, other times it just seems like I'm walking through hell. My brain doesn't like me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 07:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
