<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royals trade with A's for something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 22:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nobody really knows who he is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Trout hit a grand slam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 00:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Trout and Albert Pujols currently have 60 homers combined. The entire Atlanta Braves have 58. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 00:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone please nerf these men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone actually had a grief report prove fruitful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 21:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game froze for me and I lost the game. Is filing a grief report telling them the game froze gonna be enough for me to get the win, or at least void the loss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrissy Teigen to John Legend on Twitter: "for the love of god u better tweet out meek's album if you're ever on it" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 09:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Likely 83/84's to become Gold tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 06:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are just predictions by me based off the stats of players

Lorenzo Cain

Kris Bryant

Joc Pederson

Zach Britton

Alcides Escobar

Matt Holliday

Carlos Martinez

Josh Reddick

Huston Street

Stephen Vogt

Scott Kazmir

Brandon Crawford

Tim Hudson

Drew Storen

Jake Odorizzi

Alex Gordon

George Springer

AJ Burnett

Corey Dickerson

Carson Smith

Joe Panik

Obviously there is no way all of these go gold, but these are the ones to go gold, if any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whataburger with the meme satire again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 00:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it so hard to find a setlist to the J. Cole/Big Sean/Jeremih/YG etc show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adrian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 21:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beltrayyylmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The greatest "that's right MF'er" feeling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 18:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wilt shoots over Bill Russell [early 1960's] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for something entertaining to do during the offseason? Help my archive of old basketball photos/footage! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browse /r/classicbasketball, we're slowly gaining subscribers and are eager to add more. We'd love it if fellow /r/NBA subscribers could come and submit photos, videos, or GIFs of plays that are 10+ years old. Googling your favorite teams/players/jerseys and jumping down the rabbit hole of the NBA is a fun experience, and if you find anything awesome, uploading it to imgur and submitting it on the subreddit would be appreciated. 

Also, to demonstrate what that subreddit could become, our much older subreddit, /r/ClassicBaseball has over 1000 subs and has daily posters always contributing. 

Hope you check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carmelo playing Summer League [2003] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, if I own an All-Star, it's in my best interest to sell them ASAP, correct? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 06:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doc Rivers said Deandre shouldn't have called Cuban regarding yesterday, and that they stayed around because they "just wanted to be there for him to sign the deal" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 22:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doc Rivers is officially on my NBA shit list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Deandre Jordan a bitch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 04:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Paul is EN ROUTE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kern's Music Shop in Seattle [4272x2848] [Canon XSi] [OC - My Pic] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 00:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun online browser-based game to play with friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 07:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was dominating a guy and he offered to friendly quit. I accepted. Was that the kind where I get the win still? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 05:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're up 1 and you overthrow the first baseman late in the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 05:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wesley Matthews and Deandre Jordan followed each other yesterday prior to the announcement of both of their contracts. Is Twitter follow-sleuthing officially a good indicator of players' futures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This probably doesn't mean anything, but Wesley Matthews followed Deandre Jordan and @HouseP0rn. Is he looking for a new house with Deandre? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This market is... Ridiculous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 02:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody is trying to flip. It's nuts. All prices are coming down across the board.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rangers activate Josh Hamilton, send Joey Galloway to Triple-A [News] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 21:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Show has to nerf Eddie Gamboa... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 22:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fucking ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What catcher do you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 01:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having a hard time finding one that works for me. What do hall use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curious to who has committed the most to flipping cards. How many pages of completed orders do you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 17, not a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSFW Lelbron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 04:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do I have to do on this goddamn game to not have 2-3 errors every game??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 10:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, a deep fly ball, let me drop it. Oh, a simple third to first throw, let me bounce the ball out of my glove. What is the deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to get custom DD player to 99 stats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guy is at 97 OVR but his hitting stats are all about 70. What's a cheap way to get this up? Is there a cheap player with good stats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worth picking up: Josh Hamilton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 03:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked him up for 1k last week when he was 74, roster bumped him to 81 OVR today. He's currently at 939 stubs so he is definitely worth the buy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we have a weekly thread dedicated on what players to pick up for DD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can really work these cards like a market, and I think a weekly thread on cards worth picking up would be neat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radio interview of reporter who attended the infamous 10 Cent Beer Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 07:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm going to a local Hearthstone tournament next week, and it's based on Basic Decks. Which is the most OP to use, and best way to play it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 23:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty noobish to this game as far as strategy goes, and I've only really played mechmage so some strategy to go along with a deck recommendation would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE AL WEST STANDINGS CURRENTLY SAY HATASS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 04:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT IS ALL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a nice little gift for signing in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 08:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a snitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] April Edition of photos from /r/ClassicBaseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 22:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1000 subscribers to /r/ClassicBaseball! Thank you to all who contribute to this great subreddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's to more fun times here in /r/ClassicBaseball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PHOTO] Alex Gordon in the stands after his catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fan photo of Alex Gordon, professional baseball player, after an amazing catch that took him into the stands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Heyman] Angels and Rangrs have agreed on trade for Josh Hamilton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 01:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Josh Smith behaves like Microsoft Word and provides the back-up save! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 05:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reds Manager writes first post-game article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 02:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moves Like Jerebko </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 22:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Emoji Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 20:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Jefferson dunks on Brandan Wright </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 05:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome, former home of the Minnesota Twins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife texted me this picture while I was at work yesterday afternoon. Apparently he kept saying "fuuuud" for food. I've never been more proud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 23:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dirk Nowitzki jokes about Livingston's grab on his junk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vines aren't allowed so here's a text post

https://vine.co/v/eB792ImLKzX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Sonny Gray gives up his first hit of the night in the 8th inning, receives standing ovation from crowd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] Adrian Beltre forgot about the new step-out rule, tries to correct himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure how I got this one to work, but a free run is fine by me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I love the ESPN K-Zone" - Miguel Cabrera, minutes after he invaded Poland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOOKY WARNING] This photo was taken this morning before Wrigley Field's Opening Day Festivities. Notice any ghosts? 2kris4me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bear cub at the Cubs' Opening Day. [1916] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 18:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> haha guess what I like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 18:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha it's baseball haha if you liked my meme, please hit the upvote button.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Gutierrez] Dirk on Livingston's grab on his private area: "I really enjoyed his tight grip." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The challenge system is now in place on The Show! Pretty cool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 03:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Uniform Design for the Texas Tittytwisters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 02:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> haha i have funny meme about zlatan in the text post. it is a knock nock joke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 10:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> knock nock

whose there?

zlatan

zlatan who?

god

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

haha. if u like my meme pls upvote. thank u redd it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> upvote if u like zlatan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 09:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like zlatan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPTROUT/UPYOST/UPKRIS IF U WOULD THROW THIS GRENADE AT HITLER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 00:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While I'm here looking at these utopias on the subreddit, I'm trying to figure why my shitty urban area all has ebola </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 06:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moses Malone with his NBA Finals trophy after his first year in Philly [1983] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> haha what is your favorite meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 07:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like kris bryant haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upvote for visibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 00:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kris Bryant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lebron casually hits a 40 footer like it's a free throw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] March Edition of photos from /r/ClassicBaseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For every game Steve Nash played as a Laker, he made $430,769.23, and for every minute Steve Nash played in a Laker uniform, Nash was paid $14,444.16 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 23:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ain't nothin' more important than the* ***mula***

EDIT: other stats

For every basket made, Nash made $108,108.11

For every assist made, Nash made $71,428.57

On the Suns, Nash made $2,967.14 for every minute he played

On the Mavericks, Nash made $2,205.63 for every minute he played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Greg Hardy Complex: At what point do teams allow anyone semi-related to the gauntlet that is associated with domestic violence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done a lot of reading, listening, and debating on what to think about Greg Hardy. Currently, I don't know. And I might be seen as an imbecile for even still pondering this, but it's too easy to give a pass on Hardy given the current stance the NFL has on domestic violence (No More).

Most /r/nfl-er's have the consensus that Hardy is likely innocent, citing the calamity that is the NC bench trial (how it's basically the equivalent of an indictment) and the [911 tapes](http://www.cbssports.com/nfl/eye-on-football/24562942/greg-hardy-911-calls-show-conflicting-information) (where Hardy sounds like he is the one being berated by the female). 

Hardy was up against a judge with a 90% conviction(?) rate on domestic violence. There was no jury, and only a judge. The argument is that the judge gave Hardy a guilty verdict to push the domestic violence agenda (which was not as stressed in American society at the time, as this was before Ray Rice). It does sound fishy however that the woman allegedly abused by Hardy did not show up to court. It implies Hardy paid her off due to the fact he was already seen as an abuser and had low chance of winning the case, but could also imply the case was steadily unraveling, and this was physical proof. But how can a woman that was supposedly crazy abandon a trial at the last possible moment? Sounds suspicious, and needed to be further examined. Unfortunately we don't have that privilege to investigate further, as only Hardy and those in the house are the only ones who know what happened that night.

With all things considered, there is shaky concrete evidence of Hardy abusing the woman. The woman had broken bones and lacerations, and it's hard to imagine somebody inflicting that kind of damage on themselves, regardless of drugs in her system (to be fair, cocaine would likely cause her to have a higher pain tolerance). The 911 calls suggest Hardy was being attacked by her. So here's my questions:

* Should the NFL allow someone who even has the possibility of being a proponent of domestic violence to play and make money on a team?

* When are players who commit serious crimes allowed to be back on a team? 

* Do fans even care if a player has a aura of suspicion?

* Does it make sense that the [Cowboys were supposedly wary of giving money to Dez Bryant considering his past](http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000000424785/article/cowboys-concerned-about-dez-bryant-off-the-field), yet signed Greg Hardy less than 2 days after meeting him?

* Is Greg Hardy forgivable at this moment in time? Is he forgivable down the road?

EDIT: changed wording </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rondo with the backwards circus assist to Monta Ellis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dirk nails a 3 and his shooting coach, Holger Geschwindner, celebrates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 02:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in 1943, the LAPD allowed white servicemen on break from war to beat, strip, and urinate on Latino boys aged from as young as 11 in order to let out their frustrations at the "hoodlum" culture cultivating in LA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYU v.s. UNC at Madison Square Garden [1948] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 22:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swing First </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 22:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some cheap gold players (in the range of 5k coins) that could be instant upgrades to a pretty average team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a 4 star french leaning team, looking to get it better. Which players can get help get my team to be better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> here's a gif of will ferrell give me karma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] Will Ferrell fields the ball from CF, hits the cutoff man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kyrie Irving crosses Tyson Chandler, avoids Dirk, and connects with J.R. Smith for the three </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeKalb officer shoots, kills unarmed naked man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 03:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving down the road when... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yu Darvish at his first press conference in English when asked if he quit on the Rangers last year: "That is bullshit." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elton John performance at Dodger Stadium [x-post /r/OldSchoolCool] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 22:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We did it Reddit! Google is finally accurate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 00:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video of a flagrant foul in 2K15, if you've never seen it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the cheapest way to get tickets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm entertaining my options for my trip to Seattle, going to a Sounders game being one of them. Is there a good way to get to the game for cheap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know why this is so satisfying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 19:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Two Brothers Challenge is a great way to waste an hour of your life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 18:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just letting yall know we like Kendrick Perkins now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And fuck Charles Barkley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW I find out DONKEY is bishreksual </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 03:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1995-99 Hawks "Futuristic Jerseys", with Dikembe Mutombo sporting it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 03:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> did u guise know le baseball starts soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 03:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so le awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] February Edition of photos from /r/ClassicBaseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following the deaths of 3 Muslims in the Chapel Hill Shooting in NC, young Muslim woman posts a viral story of being followed by a gun-totin' Texan. Turns out she made it all up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 18:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have 6 gold safeties... Do I complete the set or just sell off the safeties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 21:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE not like Charles Barkley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 07:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New basketball subreddit: /r/ClassicBasketball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 05:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello users of /r/nba! My mod team and I have created /r/ClassicBaseball, a subreddit for old baseball photos and videos, and decided to broaden it to basketball as well. So, we have created

**/r/ClassicBasketball**.

You can add any photos from any moment you deem "classic" in NBA history. From Wilt having a regular 50 point game, to Jordan flying high at the dunk contest, you can post it for sure on /r/ClassicBasketball. We formed great success and an awesome community on our baseball subreddit, and we're hoping for the same on this new subreddit.

Now, we're just getting started, so once we've got a manageable amount of photos, we can get a sleek CSS look and some flair as well. But we need some great posts first! Finding some old photos is the first fun part, the discussion in the comments of your post is the second. It's a surprisingly relaxing hobby.

So subscribe, post a photo or two, and join the community at /r/ClassicBasketball, and enjoy the NBA in its heyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New basketball subreddit: /r/ClassicBasketball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 03:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Russell with Red Auerbach [1966] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 03:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 COIN GIVEAWAY. Guess how many glue sticks are currently on my desk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] [THROWBACK THURSDAY] Jamie Moyer charges mound back in 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Addition of "Uniforms" flair! Special thanks to /u/JOE619 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 05:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've added a "uniforms" flair thanks to the genius idea from /u/JOE619. Now you can get that nostalgic feel from those uniforms from back in the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> do u guise liek baseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mis it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the easiest card to snipe and sell back at a higher price? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 01:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I pulled a Jon Ryan out of the Game Changers. Should I sell or keep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My team is at 89 OVR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 120 years ago on Feb. 6, 1895, Babe Ruth was born, and 57 years ago on Feb. 6, 1958, Ted Williams became the highest paid player in the MLB at $135,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 22:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 05:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Hershey's Chocolate is owned by the CEO of Comcast, Adolf Hitler. EDIT: Thanks for the gold kind sir! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hank Greenberg hits a homer at Comiskey Park on Opening Day [1938] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 09:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> well damn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW space aliens steal my Mars rover so I put out a new rover by the name of "Attention" on Venus and that one is also stolen by space aliens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11-time NBA Champion Bill Russell taking in the sights at Fenway [1962] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Doerr, Ted Williams, Dom Dimaggio show off their verticals [~1940] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1912 World Series @ Fenway. You think people liked hats back then? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1914 World Series @ Fenway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Sox players walk off the field at Fenway. Shows how similar today's Fenway is [1937] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Ferrell and baseball clown Al Shacht pose with giant glove [1930's] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 01:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guide to easy sets for big rewards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 04:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've literally never done sets outside of bronze players to silver players, and silver players to gold players. Is there a set worth finishing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pre-game interview before the 1987 World Series at the Old Busch Stadium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 02:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] Top 25 Photos from /r/ClassicBaseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 01:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babe Ruth at Lou Gehrig's Funeral. Sad. [1941] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 03:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Addition of "Colorized" flair to sidebar flair search! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 08:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you can filter by recolored photos. Hurray! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COLORIZED] Polo Grounds during a Giants game [1955] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 08:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COLORIZED] Harvard outfielders, Richard Hoffman, Richard Fisher, and Matthew Botsford [1955] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 08:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COLORIZED] New York Giants on Opening Day at the Polo Grounds [1917] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 08:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Post-Game Thread] Mavericks defeat Timberwolves 98-75 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 04:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://scores.espn.go.com/nba/boxscore?gameId=400578923 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Scott, leader of the Civil Rights Movement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy MLK Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [spoilers] Anybody get an anti-war vibe from American Sniper? I feel as if I'm the only one on here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 22:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me everyone feels as if this movie glorifies war and the death of "infidels". I disagree. There were multiple parts of the movie that combat this idea.

* The man in the initial opening where it is implied he forces the woman and child to throw the grenade at the troops. 

* The "shut the fuck up" comment made after he shoots the woman and the kid, and his partner tells him good job. It shows he obviously felt awful about it despite the fact he had to do it. 

* The family that attempts to help the troops after the troops come in and almost ransack his house. I felt like this was a really impactful scene. The fact that these troops go in and treat everyone like terrorists when there's people just caught in the middle of it that just want it to stop. 

* The murder of the father and the drilling of the child. This showed that Kyle was desperately trying to save them and couldn't, as he was pinned down by sniper fire.

* The terrorist that ate with the soldiers. Showed that they have personal lives. 

* The rival terrorist spending time with his family before the call to go and snipe.

* Kyle's constant lack of chemistry with his wife. He couldn't seem to feel well with her until the war was completely over for him.

* The man praising Kyle at the car shop. Kyle obviously felt very awkward about being praised for killing people but just kept saying "Oh yeah thanks, yeah I'll come down there sometime" in an obvious attempt to have the situation end ASAP. 

* The PTSD moments Kyle had. The lawnmower, the car shop, the staring at the blank TV while thinking about gunfire, the attempted sucker punch of a dog, it all showed that the war had really affected him internally and he put up a front to make it look like nothing was really happening inside.

* The high blood pressure test he had at the maternity office coupled with telling the therapist(?) that he had no regrets essentially about his work as a soldier. You could tell he was lying through his teeth.

* The constant death of people he knew around him. The suicide letter complex, the blood diamond thing where the man was almost killed but had his life changed forever. He got a different ring because that ring would've reminded him of the war and he couldn't have dealt with it. 

There were some flaws in character development, but then again the movie was 135 minutes. You can only go so long before you lose ticket sales because people don't wanna sit for so long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SUGGESTION] Addition of a yamaka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 07:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be all for it, for username reasons rather than religious reasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bart Starr wasn't that great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 18:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turns out the article was not a negative piece about the Oculus Rift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 04:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BART STARR WAS NOT THAT GREAT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 04:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 years ago, Mark Cuban purchased the Mavericks for $285 million. Here's an article about his time as owner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 21:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Post Game Thread] Dallas Mavericks (25-10) defeat the LeBron-less Cavs (19-15) 109-90 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 21:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nowitzki with  15 pts/5 rebs/3 asts

Parsons with 14 pts/4 rebs/3 asts

Chandler with 14 pts/ 8 rebs/ 3 asts

Rondo with 4 pts/4 rebs/8 asts

Ellis with 20 pts/1 reb/2 asts

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Love with 30 pts/10 rebs/3 asts

Miller with 3 pts/2 rebs/3 asts

Thompson with 8 pts/11 rebs/2 asts

Dellavedova with 10 pts/3 rebs/7 asts

Irving with 6 pts/2 rebs/3 asts

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

**INFO NUGGETS**

* Mavericks finish the game with 6 players with double digit points (Nowitzki 15, Parsons 14, Chandler 14, Ellis 20, Barea 14, Jefferson 11)

* Shawn Marion with a nice statline of 13 pts/4 rebs/1 ast in 20 min off the bench

* Dion Waiters shot 4-14 for 8 pts/2 rebs/4 asts

* Mavericks shot 56.4% from the field today, the Cavaliers shot 40.7%.

* Greg Smith played 9 minutes, finished with 0 pts/0 rebs/0 asts

* Raymond Felton had an assist today so that's cool I guess

* No starting Mavericks played for 30+ minutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discounted PS+ and/or controllers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 00:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know where I can find either of the two? I've been patiently waiting and can't seem to find either. Help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Unique" Steam games worth playing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 07:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just started really getting into gaming w/ Steam, and some of my favorite purchases were things like Goat Simulator, Surgeon Simulator, and The Stanley Parable. I've tried using the tag system the games have on them, but to no avail. Does anyone know of any novelty type games worth playing like the ones I've listed? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone fill me in on this "Holiday Trading Card" thing on Steam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 22:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fail to understand what happens if I get all 10 cards. A badge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This game is quite the experience. [The Stanley Parable] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 07:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't help but feel like this game is SO GODDAMN SCRIPTED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 02:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How in Jordan's name can I go up 3-0 in the playoffs on MyPlayer then not even get a fucking chance in the last 4 games of the series. It makes no fucking sense. The game is not based on skill level of the player, if it has a desired result, it puts out that desired result. It's fucking ridiculous and really frustrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Smith pretends he's not Greg Smith and slams it home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 05:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's my [F]irst thyme posting here ;) i'm a grill btw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 23:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WE BACK UP BITCHES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 07:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find high res photos from NBA games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 08:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to make a background with Rondo, but I can't seem to find any without a watermark. Anybody know where to go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chandler Parsons last 5 gms: 24.6 PPG, 59% FG, 59% 3pt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh hell yea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this... vehicle? at a Taco Bueno in Texas today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newest addition to Christmas Ragonk Music... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 01:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the most attractive baseball player, and why is it m'Trout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 19:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know where I can find a regional viewing map for the Browns/Bengals game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mavericks Christmas Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 18:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derek Jeter sentenced to 10 days in jail for being 105 years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 04:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad that fucker's in jail. I HATED HOW MUCH APPRECIATION HE GOT FUCK JETER LONG LIVE KONERKO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else finishing domination games, only to have it not register on the servers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 23:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just played my second straight game with enough points for three stars, and then there's nothing on the domination ladder. What shit is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite small market team? Fuck A-Rod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake Michael Irvin + /r/agonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 01:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ragonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 01:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historical baseball pics, all sorted to your liking, over at /r/ClassicBaseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 23:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the offseason, so you're most likely in need of a dose of good baseball. Over at /r/ClassicBaseball, we've got 300+ entries of photos, videos, and articles all dedicated to the good ol' days. Come check it out if you're interested, and even help contribute to our collection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to push search function out of the page (concerning link flair filters)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 09:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sub working on is /r/ClassicBaseball. 

I've made filters for certain subjects, and need to get rid of the search function at the top when you click on the filters in the sidebar. I had it successfully done by using href and the coordinating two-letter code associated with each link flair, but since that causes the user to be stuck on (i.e. pn.reddit.com) that two-letter code, it screws up the rest of the subreddit, and some users may not realize they need to delete the pn out of the URL. 

I tried to explain that well, but I don't have the best knowledge of CSS. Any ideas?

I saw /r/Halloween has it done, and I don't know how.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to /r/ClassicBaseball: Introducing Filters! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 09:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After extensive flairing of all posts submitted to this subreddit, we now have filters! Now you can search through photos of a certain type by clicking any of the colored buttons in the sidebar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My neighborhood ice cream man has been lying about his scoops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 02:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got two scoops when I paid for three that cheeky cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 20 years ago, during a high school football playoff game in Texas, a team completed 3 onside kicks in a row, making a 24 point comeback in less than three minutes, only to have the opposing team run the ball back for a touchdown to win the game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wondering if I can include a picture in the link flair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 11:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm currently setting up link flairs on /r/ClassicBaseball. Next to flairs like "World Series" I think it would be neat to have the world series logo next to it. Is that possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roberto Clemente warms up at Forbes Field [1970] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah, Pablo Sandoval signed with the Red Sox. But I think we're forgetting the fact that A-Rod is a chode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck A-Rod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ragonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 19:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help changing every submitter's name to the same thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 05:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to make everyone's name "Ragonk" in /r/agonk.

Also, if you can, I want to be able to make the sidebar and top of the subreddit say "Ragonk" instead of "agonk". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ragonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ragonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/agonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ragonk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 04:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW my lord Trout and savior finally received retribution from the grasps of Miguel Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 07:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> scot's plays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> stev r u ok </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> listen to me kendrick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I get the best deal selling my old gen GTAV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 22:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rockets are "that guy" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 00:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently Nets.com is up for sale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 18:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.nets.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mods here at /r/baseballcirclejerk dug deep and found tweets from MLB players before Twitter became huge. 100% sort of real. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 20:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the new NBA2KTV episode have a locker code? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 06:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Congrats to the 2014 World Series champions, the San Francisco Giants! Couldn't have happened to a better team." - Adolf "Cabrera" Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 05:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I dug deep and found tweets from NBA players before Twitter became huge. 100% real. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 23:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old NBA Player tweets (more in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 23:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My reaction when I realized I just watched an entire 2KTV episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 00:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody know what's up with nets.com? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 02:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW a woman I'm trying to impress tells me receding hairlines are her fetish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 00:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I am a proud supporter of getting rid of net neutrality. I also like the Giants." - Manny Machado </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 00:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the kids I need VC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 03:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Sure hope the Giants win tonight" - Osama Bin Laden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 02:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I really enjoyed the Giants' win last night" - Joseph Stalin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the Musers going to London, here's Jub on TalkSport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 01:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
