<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Just because a large CROWD chants, 'I hate pancakes!', doesn't make a ONE person who yells, 'I hate **eggs and bacon**!' any less of a hater.

FTFY

But on a serious note, I couldn't have said it any better. Just because someone hates on you doesn't make it okay to hate on them. We can discuss our opinions in a civil manner, right? 

Plus, I personally don't get how you could hate either Chloe or Warren. They're both pretty fucking awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of now, our tiny time traveler is beating Doctor-motherfucking-Who. Wowser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *"Oh come on, Che***,** " Max **said** as she pouted. The Bluenette leaned against her truck, pulling a stick out and **lighting** it cooly, **and gave her** another refreshing smirk **.** *"Che is Overrated, Mad Max."* And just like that, Max knew deep inside her whirlwind of a head that Chloe **had taken** her heart. She smiled back without a single worry in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't scare me, but I do think I understand better now that you have to just accept your actions with complete conviction and keep on moving forward. But for me personally, Life is Strange was an external introspective experience (if that makes sense; it was an outside look in) that taught me a lot about love, friendship, how important the people around me are, and my own morality. After Life is Strange, I'm more grateful for the friends I have and I appreciate them more. I was always a very up front type of dude, but now I'm just a little more emotionally open and honest with people. In a weird way I feel exposed, but also less scared than ever. Of anything. 

I don't want to end up dragging on too long, so I'll leave it at this: Life is Strange taught me a lot on so many different levels, and I feel like I've actually matured as a result.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing that's been keeping me from burying myself in fanart and fanfic is the absolute *assload* of studying I have to do right now. As soon as winter break rolls around, I'm just going to submerge myself in Pricefield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to drift off while I'm awake, wondering about what hijinks and adorable escapades they could be getting up to together, and sometimes that's how I ease myself to sleep at night, but I usually don't night dream about anything along these lines. 

My night dreams are either a) complete and utter neural diarrhea, b) absolutely nothing, or c) a result of stress and anger and loss of beans that manifests in mah subconscious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. It's really sad, but it's also oddly comforting. Even if Chloe is gone, she'll always be with Max. Max is never alone. I can see Max walking on those train tracks by herself, lightly smiling with the knowledge that Chloe is still there with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will come a day when the feels are too great...

***BUT TODAY IS NOT THAT DAY*** 

Repeat after me: BAE OVER BAY. BAE OVER BAY.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels like so long ago...but also like just yesterday. The feels are back. 

(*who am I kidding, they never left*.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot diggity damn, I can practically feel the storm around me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one can shake their bony white ass like Maximus Caulfield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 09:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I likes. Very clean sketch. Looking forward to seeing it Pricefield-ified!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 08:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannah fucking rocks! I'd love to see her pop up in some more games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 02:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was what Chloe wanted. She wanted to do something good for a change. She wanted her last action to be one of selflessness, or heroism, and of love. She believed that the people of Arcadia Bay deserved to live more than her. 

But sometimes people are wrong. And as Max, I decided that Chloe was wrong. It wasn't her choice to make, though maybe it should have been: it was mine. 

And I'm not the hero that Chloe is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 02:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the movie Interstellar, Anne Hathaway's character mentions how love is something that transcends time and space in a kind of inexplicable way (well, it probably can be explained, I'm just dumb *and* paraphrasing). It draws McConaughey's character across the galaxy back to his kids, and [MINOR INTERSTELLAR SPOILER](#s "Hathaway's character to her boyfriend, who was on another planet"). I think Life is Strange gives us something similar. Max and Chloe's lives are forever intertwined; across all the different timelines and realities, they're pulled together by love, or maybe "destiny". Whatever you interpret their love as, it's something very powerful. The best evidence of this is probably when Max gets her powers in the bathroom. Max gets her powers when she sees Chloe get killed by Nathan, but at the time she didn't even consciously realize who she was. Maybe her subconscious recognized it was Chloe, or maybe she "felt" that it was her through whatever bond they have, but either way that was enough for her to summon the ability to rewind time. That's enough evidence for me to suggest that their bond can't be broken. *Especially* following the week they just went through. I can't see them splitting up again. Whatever the hell they do moving forward, wherever the hell they go, they'll always be together. 

And in terms of the Bay ending, I like to think that there's some kind of dimension or reality beyond our reach where Chloe is watching over Max from. Once again, Interstellar style. A reality where Chloe has all the memories of their last week together in Arcadia Bay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very neat! Missing a few hellas, some beans, and a dash of shaka brah, but still hella dope!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be the teddy bear. He be creepin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not. Joyce has got, as Frank might say, some serious lady balls. If she knew David hit Chloe, she'd go Rambo on his ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched a let's play of Episode 1 by Goldglove on a whim, and I ended up getting really sucked into the story and atmosphere. I binged all of Episodes 1 and 2 that morning (Episode 2 had just been released). I do regret watching that much, but I'm just glad that I actually found such an amazing game. And later an amazing community! It's been hella dope here with you Shaka Brahs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was eating those beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Our choices mattered, because the choices we made are what formed our feelings that influenced we individually picked, hence; making us all polarized in the end.

...so, that's what the name means.

Thanks for posting this. Well written and very interesting. I agree completely with your points. It was beautiful seeing Max and Chloe have such a tender moment with the storm in the background; it was a very pensive moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, there's two en- ohhhhh, right, right, there's only one ending. Sorry, I misunderstood. 

Welcome to denial, the story of the last few weeks of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 09:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually she will. You just can't hold those kinds of things in; they start all starts to build up and become volatile. You need some kind of release or outlet. Like talking to a friend or a therapist (Jesse mentioned that below). No one can deal with everything on their own. 

Edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 09:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously both outcomes suck for Max. But at least in one she doesn't have to deal with it alone. And before you say it, I know she has Warren and Kate and all after the Bay ending, but she can't tell them about anything that happened. Everything just gets bottled up inside Max's head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 08:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to hella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 23:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better late than never. Go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 23:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably the best LiS cosplay I've seen. I love the background and lighting as well; substance and style! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 22:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am thankful for your truth bombs. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 22:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today, Franksgiving. Tomorrow, Black Beans Friday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 22:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, Max getting kidnapped, drugged, and violated by Jefferturd had completely slipped my mind. I thought the Bay ending was fucked up enough already; this really does change everything for me. She needs someone to be able to talk to and confide in. Having to bottle that up alongside everything else... 

Fuck me, I hadn't even considered that trauma. You just blew my mind, Jesse. Like, there's a hole in the side of my skull and all mah brains are dripping out of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 20:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chloe doesn't just die. Max has to let Chloe, the person she cares about more than anyone, die alone in the bathroom. That's not the same as Chloe just being killed by Nathan; that's on Max. And she can't tell anyone. That would fucking break you man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 18:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal philosophy is that you always start with yourself. You and yours come first; if you aren't okay, how can you help anyone? You can't expect to be able to help a hundred, a thousand, 7 billion people without helping you and yours first. If Arcadia Bay goes, Max and Chloe will make it out as stronger individuals. If Chloe dies, Max is broken. What happens to her next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe there's meant to be an explanation for it within the context of the game's story. It's why I don't, and never did, believe the theories that suggest that Rachel and Nathan and Jefferson could've been time travelers. I think her powers (and the storm) are metaphors more than anything else. The game is about Max's evolution, isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [EP5 SPOILERS MAYBE](#s "The most punchable face in all of the world. Thank you David.")  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bear should respect their privacy and GTFO. Perv.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually ridiculously cute. The face-poke is so very Chloe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How awesome is this? We did it cinnamon rolls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, but my personal opinion is "nah". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay Maxaroni (insert smiley face, because NO EMOJI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's arranged alphabetically, but I thought it was pretty funny that directly under Life is Strange was Mad Max.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chloe seems like the obvious option (Nathan too), but I think doing a paper on Max would be hella fun and fascinating. That nightmare sequence was an amazing look into her subconscious, so it would be *criminal* to pass up the opportunity to analyze her. We've already got a pretty decent grasp of Chloe and Nathan's mental states, but Max is a lot more enigmatic. I say go for it OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who woulda thunk a shy little hipster from Arcadia Bay could kick Arnold's ass? 

Also, someone needs to make an edit of Max as the Terminator saying "I'll be back".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a door closes, a window opens.

Or something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowser. That's some nice wall art! I would buy if it was made into a poster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 20:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max? Maxine? Maximus? Maxi-pad? Maxter? Maxaroni?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 19:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We need...acid."

"Hella yes!"

"Hydrofluoric acid." 

"...oh." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*I can't see your wings, but girl you're an angel*](https://youtu.be/SN4DGGzVXEw?t=30s)

[*Oh, my, my angel*](https://youtu.be/SN4DGGzVXEw?t=30s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 15:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journey. That game has a sort of warmth and serenity about it similar to the first few episodes of LiS. The sense of wonder that I felt playing Journey was actually pretty similar to what I felt exploring Arcadia Bay. The game is also a personal journey that you go on with a friend (albeit with no dialogue).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 15:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: Loki is Jefferson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 15:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not judging a book by it's cover is probably one of the biggest overall themes of LiS. Everyone starts out as a walking stereotype, from Max herself to the elusive Nathan Prescott. In the first episode you think you have everyone figured out; bitchy girl, douchey drill-sergeant stepdad, evil rich kid, etc. But then you start to see other sides to these characters. We start to be able to understand their positions. They stop being good or bad, and they just become...people. Real people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 08:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  to watch 6 hours of horrible movies? GO APE!!!

Horrible movies? Have you seen the original Planet of the Apes? It's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says that the player is human. It says that the player is flawed. We all have slight insecurities buried deep in our subconscious that, unknowingly to us, directly influence every action we take and every decision we make. The nightmare sequence is so intriguing because it's when we really get to see what makes Max tick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it does fit the Bay ending. It's a sort of melancholy tune that alludes to moving into an uncertain future together, which is exactly what the the Bae ending is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to write a fanfic. The thing is that I'm more of a visual person; I'd rather direct a short film version of my epilogue (yeah, not happening) than write a text version. But who knows, I might. I just might. ;)

Also, I think I'd also pick "Captain Chloe" over "I love you". It'd just be too cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 18:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) I agree, its pretty weird how Warren just instantly believes Max. If my best friend came up to me and told me he could rewind time, I wouldn't believe him immediately. That's hella crazy. But keep in mind, Warren *is weird*. And not necessarily in a bad way. He's obsessed with Max (once again, not calling him a creeper, put down the pitchforks for now), and he *always* has her back. Warren's the kind of guy who would take a bullet for Max, even if she wouldn't do the same for him. In that respect, I think it actually makes sense for his character that he *does* believe her. That's the kind of person that he is. The conversation is too brief though. 

2) I loved the hallway sequence. I understand how it can get tedious, but I remember being completely immersed in the sequence. I was scared, worried, angry, regretful, reflective, and I was just walking through an empty freaking hallway. I thought that sequence was great. The stealth was a little odd looking back, but I didn't have a problem with it at all. It felt like a dream alright. 

3) I love the Bae ending. I love everything about it. Initially I was a little disappointed by the brevity, and later I thought about the nature of "Obstacles" being re-used, but I still really liked it. Now I like it even more, having thought long and hard about it. I think they showed us just enough, even though I can practically see the budget constraints jumping out at me. "Obstacles" is still a perfect song for that scene, the dialogue and hug under the lighthouse is GODDAMN PERFECT (I know it isn't our Pricefield kiss, I was initially disappointed at that too but then I realized it would have been out of place), and the ending shot(s) is beautiful. I love the overall feel of the scene, and also the prospect of a fresh start and implications of Max and Chloe's future together. *That said*, I woulda really liked one last dialogue tree. Let me break it down for you: 

*In the truck, preparing to leave what remains of Arcadia Bay. Chloe turns to Max, a somber yet hopeful look on her face. You have four prompts.* ***1) Are you ready?*** ***2) Where to, Captain Chloe?*** ***3) I'm sorry Chloe.*** ***4) I love you.*** *This results in a brief one or two lines of dialogue from Chloe (and possibly another from Max (***"When a door closes, a window opens"***)). Chloe smiles warmly at Max, a gesture which is returned by the brunette. The partners in time turn their gaze to the road ahead of them, as they begin to drive off into tomorrow.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say I really know how this feels. I feel little connection to the places I've lived. I don't have any real allegiance to either country, and I don't have nostalgic memories about the *places*. I remember the people more than anything. My friends/family/IdontgotfriendsIgotfamily make the places worth living in. I'll go with them. You're going back to that town for your family. Fuck the location. It's the people around you that matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max doesn't rat out Jefferson in this timeline. Nathan does. He gets arrested for murdering Chloe Price and ends up spilling the beans on his mentor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Combine *"When a door closes, a window opens (or something like that)"* with a blue butterfly motif. That'd be hella dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be honest, Chloe is the definition of cool.

...among other things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate your punography.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Frank Bowers. 

Yeah it was Warren. First episode, first time meeting him. When he gets his black eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 23:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Window Opens

True Measure

Behind Closed Doors

Distortion

By Time and Fate

(the last one is a literary reference)






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 23:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode 1: Aperture

Episode 2: Exposure

Episode 3: Focus

Episode 4: Chiaroscuro

Episode 5: Perspective
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 22:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *I know right why is there no "cuddle" option...*

Because no number of pixels can contain that much cuteness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 22:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit, it makes me a little sad that some regular posters from before have gone. But this sub is still hella dope. It was hella dope when I found you guys in June, and it's hella dope now. I love you peoples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 22:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alice. Her name is Alice. 


*And she is the definition of adorable.*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...music is math, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season...3? Slow down there dude. We still haven't even got over the trauma of the first season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask how Professor Price is doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That probably won't bode well for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry for everything you've had to go through. I can't even really fathom what it's like to lose so much. Keep your chin up. If you say that you and Chloe really are like the same person, then you're probably hella dope :) You're always welcome here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

He took a few shots too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 08:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 08:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think you're right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 23:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like a cop out saying this, but I think Max's powers are nothing more (and nothing less) than a narrative tool. *Life's about choices; what if you had the power to change those choices?* It's about who Max is, and who you are, as a person. Time travel presents us with the ability to mold ourselves into the people we choose to be. 

Part of my logic behind this is that, if you wanted to turn Life is Strange into a novel or a movie or any linear form of media, you would have to omit her rewinding abilities. Yeah, that would completely *kill* it, but how would you write in that rewind power while retaining the core themes? The story isn't about time travel. The inclusion of rewinding strikes me as DontnoD taking advantage of games as a medium for the story they wanted to tell. But once again, that's just my thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 23:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it really works like that. Autopilot Max (which is what "zombie Max" is usually called) is still the exact same Max Caulfield. Taking that into account, either a) Autopilot Max and Chloe get the Bae ending, or b) this creates a mindfuck time paradox where Autopilot Max will always try to rewind through the photo and...freeze time? It hurts my brain thinking about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 23:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the very start I found Chloe's character to be really attractive (not like that, at least not in this context). I completely understood everyone saying that she was selfish and kinda bitchy, but I still couldn't keep myself from being drawn her. Later I started to recognize elements of myself in her and also began to understand her better, but still from the get go I knew I was Team Blue all the way. There was just something about the character of Chloe Price; I still haven't quite put my finger on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 23:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thanks Shaka Brah! 

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. OH. Oh. Oh. Oh. Ew. Ew. Ew. Ew. Ugh. Oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 13:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this episode Max doesn't really care about getting to the bottom of everything. Her objectives are a) escape the Dark Room, b) stop Jefferson, c) find and save Chloe. We don't get any info on where Sean Prescott fits into all of this or where Max got her powers from, but I can't really imagine either of those things were on Max's mind at the time. I kind of like the story where questions are left unanswered; it would be strange if every single loose end (and god there are a lot of them) got tied off. Besides, mystery keeps Arcadia Bay interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 13:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the concept. Good luck making the game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 13:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though Max is the one who coins the phrase, there is a moment in Episode 5 where Chloe calls her "shaka brah".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 13:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm okay with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 00:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad things happen no matter what. I'm just saying you have to choose which problem to solve: save Chloe or save everyone else. 

Also, people are drawn to unsolvable problems. Because we're adventurous. We want to solve the unsolvable. Not that relevant, but it was bugging me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 23:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also feel like I can connect with Chloe (a lot of us do; thank you Dontnod!). But I haven't gone through with the loss and grief that she has. I relate with her in a different way. Chloe Price is a person who always has her armor on. She's cocky, confident, snarky, stubborn, passionate, independent, and often difficult. She gives the impression of being a strong and badass woman; she is a strong and badass woman. But underneath her armor is a more sensitive, wounded person. She wants to be loved, and she doesn't want to be alone. Chloe feels like the world is working against her, trying to take everything from her. I feel like I can relate to that. I'm brash, I'm cocky, I'm confident, I'm independent, but it's a direct result of being burned before; the armor goes up to protect myself. It's not pretend, just like Chloe's persona isn't pretend (and just like Jay Gatsby's persona isn't pretend; amazing character, but I digress), but it is concealing something. We get to see firsthand how sweet and cuddly Chloe whenever Max is around; she's like an excited little puppy. Not to mention how she pines after Max (her texts in the Alt. Timeline for example). I don't usually let it through, but I'm exactly the fucking same. I'm a romantic (hopeless romantic), sappy little puppy who pines after his best friend who he hasn't seen in years too. But there's only really one person who brings that out of me too. Otherwise I always have my armor up, just like Chloe. It doesn't mean I can't be myself, but it means I can't let anyone in. By spending time with Chloe, I got to understand myself in a way I never did before. My persona, while 100% real and 100% me, is entirely armor. 

That got a lot more long winded than I wanted it to be, and also kind of sadder than I wanted it to be. I wasn't coming here looking for sympathy, so I apologize if it came off that way (plz furgiv mee). But yeah, Chloe Price is my spirit animal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're killing me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is very much solvable. You just need to specify what exactly the problem is. Or rather, who the problem concerns. Each player answers that for himself/herself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've gone through my own chrysalis after this journey. I don't know if I can, or *want*, to go back to what I was before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have been the only one, but I never really wanted to know how Max got her powers. I understood it as being more of a narrative device than anything. The story was, to me anyways, always a personal journey. That doesn't mean the journey is all that matters though; the destination is hella important. And with that in mind, I don't really see why people are so upset with the two outcomes. In terms of the personal journey that Max goes on, both destinations are excellent (narrative sense, not how it makes you feel). And the path to them is also excellent. Sure, some of the time travel logic gets *really* inconsistent towards the end, but is that really what we should be focusing on? (not that I'm trying to tell you what you should focus on, this is just my opinion)

At the end of the day, I don't think Life is Strange is about time travel. Time travel is just the tool DontnoD chose to use to show us something greater, and it's a tool that was specifically chosen *for the interactive medium*. 

Just my two cents. :) I do understand why some people felt cheated by the conclusion. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like Brooke saying she hopes Max isn't jealous all over again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *This* is why I love Arcadia Bay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I didn't even consider the other option. I'd never do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked how mundane, and frequently *unceremonious*, things often turned out to be. My favorite example is the death of Nathan Prescott. Some people seemed really disappointed at his death off-screen, but I thought it was brilliant. He was so *unceremoniously* removed from the equation. No fanfare, no buildup, no last hurrah. He was just gone. It was brutal. Real life often works like that. That's a message that I felt LiS drove home a lot. With the death of Rachel too. We have all these wild theories and insane plots in our heads, but at the end of the day life is usually not so dramatic. We don't always get the storybook ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel ya. If you get the eyes wrong, you get the entire likeness wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *insert groan here* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop thinking about it either. I don't want to do anything other than just sit and remember and daydream about Arcadia Bay. 

The finale had a weird effect on me. Like everyone else, I was feeling kinda empty after ending the story. I was reduced to my roots, which are Life is Strange, calisthenics, the Gameovergreggy show, and my best friends. At first I thought I just didn't want to do anything that didn't have to do with Life is Strange. I didn't want to play any video games, I didn't want to listen to any music (sans the OST), and I didn't want to watch any TV or YouTube or anything. Then I realized that I just didn't want to listen to or watch or play anything that I had *before* playing the finale. I want to leave all my old stuff behind and not look back. I only want to listen to *new* artists and watch *new* shows and play *new* games. I chose the [EP5 SPOILER](#s "bae") ending, which is very similarly about taking what's most important to you and leaving the past behind you. I dunno, it's...weird. I don't know if I will ever go back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I couldn't listen to the soundtrack without tearing up, I be crying constantly. It just makes me feel a little sad, a little empty, and a little reflective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *To all of you* 

*American girls,* 

*it's sad to*

*imagine a world* 

*without you* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of how shitty you think the draft is (I love it btw), your ideas are awesome. Substance over style, innovation over execution. Don't be too hard on yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because you got to know that one person more intimately than anyone else in Arcadia Bay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could say the same about Jose and his fans. No one knows for certain what's going to happen in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. I'm picturing a lot of that front leg side kick to the thigh from McGregor. I think he's going to try and give Jose a taste of his own medicine with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 01:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say either stick with Max and Chloe, or leave Arcadia Bay and give us a new cast, new setting, and new powers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
