<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7496</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 13:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no IAP. Maybe I'll add later something like 'unlock all pets' for inpatient ppl, but at all I don't want it to be coins-grinding game. 

Auto-jump: not everyone is good in jumping, I saw that majority of casual gamers found it easier to jump on click, so it is a bit problematic case ;) but I think that there are few games that are more challenging (panda has easy games, wolf has harder).

Thanks for the review and feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 11:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Thanks for 2 downloads ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 10:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both look like Tamagotchi but are kinda different. For example Hatchi   Tama always starts from egg, here you have 12 real pets 'beggings'. + more minor differences. It's just matter of taste. Somtehing for everybody ;) Thanks you for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 10:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, lot of ppl saw that but only you noticed. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 10:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More codes included + you got your special one ;) have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 08:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. Thanks for downloading ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 08:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With progressing in game you unlock games   pets. Multi for pet is available when it reach adult stage. There are so many pets so 2 days of ideal care is enough for 1 pet to reach adult stage. Thank you for downloading ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 04:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's game that I've made with my girlfriend. It took us few months.
Game is free for download.

More info and promo codes for iOS version (you may play with them via wifi) in x-post :
http://www.reddit.com/r/IndieGaming/comments/1vhlq0/weve_made_ios_android_retro_tamagotchilike_game/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
