<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4368</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend heard me talking about the new Zelda game so she got me this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel this dude's pain. I do alot of buying, selling and swapping online. One forum I can't stand using are local Facebook selling forums. They're great if you want to unload something for a quick buck, but it always seems a hundred people want to ask you a hundred redundant questions about things they most likely don't intend to buy. I'm currently selling my old RPTV and 5.1 home theater for like $80 (just the home theater system alone is worth $180 easy.) And I swear the stupid questions I get are ridiculously dumb:

"How big is it?" "It's fucking huge as you can clearly see in the picture. Who cares - it's $80"

"Does it have HDMI input?" "No retard it's a rear projected television."

"Is it loud?" "It's a home theater so..."

"How much?" ""

And after answering all these questions, I assume they decide not to buy when I never hear from them again. It's not like it's a major life investment. I'm selling it for next to nothing... Do you want it or not I mean come on.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also fail to realize that the wages illegal immigrants get paid is substantially less than livable and that if an employer was to hire legal, taxed workers, they'd have to pay them atleast minimum wage, which most are not equipped (or even willing) to do. It's not that Americans aren't willing to do the work - they're just not willing to do it for pennies on the dollar like illegal immigrants are. It's not that hard to get by on a less than standard wage if it's not taxed, your living expenses are covered and you basically live under the radar. 

Employers absolutely love hiring illegal immigrants not because they "do the jobs Americans won't do" but instead they'll "do any job and undercut the cost ". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do not get me wrong - I understand skill ceilings and game mechanics. Being from a long legacy of FPSs I can honestly say with pride I've been there since the beginning. Shit, my pops was one of the first people to download Wolfenstein 3d on Apogees old DOS based BBS modem server. I'm not a noob to Battlefield either, seeing as this is my 4th go into the franchise. Battlefield 4, with all its flaws, is a personal favorite.

My problem with BF1 is this game seems to just flat out not work correctly. It has very little if anything, I feel, with skill at all. Just to put this into perspective, I've spent the last 37 minutes just trying to get into a quick play... I shit you not. I know... Without a doubt... Now that I literally JUST got into match, it's going to be nothing but a giant buggy mess. My problems with the gameplay I was having earlier came after two months of just trying to get it to APPEAR on my screen :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's sounds bad.... But I wish I had their bravery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This I will certainly try! As soon I'm done having my stroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was one issue I had initially that I felt weighed down like my character rightfully shit his drawers just before heading into battle. I did adjust the sensitivity and was able to better control movement afterwards but the issue of aim control is still much to be desired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only game I've ever played where I feel like aim assist is either not working or working against me (IE lag... Perhaps I'm simply shooting dead air) I've done PC gaming in the past (grew up with Doom/Dukematch, Quake 4/ Arena, Unreal Tournament, etc) but being a console gamer at heart, never felt held back using thumbs to aim. Except this one particular game haha.

I'm only level 5 mind you, but I've been having such difficulty with this game already that I've already turned to Reddit for answers. The sniper I've been using SMLE MKIII Marksman with Chevron optic and 2.50 zoom. Not that those details mattered, but it took me roughly 6 minutes to bring up this damn solider screen so I thought I'd let you know. My most successful arm seems to be CeiRigotti Factory with Optics with only a measly 14 kills. I seem to jump back and forth between them but haven't found a groove with anything.

I'm beginning to suspect that for some reason I'm having a particularly hard time getting my console to communicate with the server's properly, which may be the root of my problems, but then again, I came to Reddit to get to the bottom of it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On for sure. I actually kept going into options to check it because it doesn't seem to be working. I kept restoring factory defaults and turning on and off in feeble attempt to... I dunno... Let the game know it doesn't seem to be working? Lol. I even made a several adjustments to everything to maybe compensate but it didn't seem to do anything. So right now it's back to factory default. But no, aim assist for sure doesn't actually seem to be working. I meant to mention that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a short film on YouTube I found awhile back that uses alot of the same effects and atheistic that this movie uses. It's a pretty fun watch: https://youtu.be/uHywX3DbLRQ I especially like how the VCR effect is used to show changes in time. Very cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one am totally behind this deportation stuff. I live in a small suburban town in Central California that is surrounded by vast farmlands in which droves of illegal immigrants work on. Along with this came about a meth epidemic since alot of these guys came over here with addictions and will only work if they can get ahold of the stuff (they're out there from like 5 am to about 8 pm). Unfortunately, this has torn our community apart since meth is seen as a big business opportunity from larger neighboring cities and has made my small town a hot bed for meth labs and dealers :/ it's sad really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in South Korea for a year when I was in the Air Force. During orientation, we were told all the missle tests, nuke tests and saber rattling were in reality "cries for help". What's really happening is North Korea knows exactly what they're doing: they puff out their chests and dump all they're funds into military R D when state wide famine hits all time highs. Then they negotiate "disarmament" in lieu of foriegn aid. The neutral countries all meet with the  PRNK, SK and the US at the DMZ to discuss disarmament and funding, PRNK normally agrees to the tune of several million dollars to do away with their testing, they then take 75% of the aid, dump it back into their military, then give the remaining 25% towards other things (like feeding their citizens, fixing their infrastructure, etc.) And when the money is all gone, they turn around and break the disarmament agreement until more aid is discussed. They keep getting away with it because they keep China super close and.assume that if anything happens to them, China will get involved, which due to SK being a peninsula, they'd pretty much be screwed at that point. PRNK likes to pretend they have everything figured out and they're self sufficient but all they really do is extort money from first world countries to keep them from stupidly creating half assed nuclear warheads and basically killing everyone on the peninsula. Why China let's then get away with it.... I'll never understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to buy my own boot and simply boot the tow truck and charge them to take it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at a loss at the amount of downvotes I've gotten. I'm just trying to be real with people and say that this was cheap cash grab by Nintendo to cash in on nostalgia. Truth is you could have bought an SD ROM cart for you classic NES and it would have done the exact same thing and it's been out for a decade atleast. The amount of bias towards this product is appauling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
