<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1610</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actors' Final Film Appearances </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 22:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 00:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly [this Mini-Golf Let's Play](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mlnTuHE9kNs), which is why Gavin and Jack don't have a big presence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aka The Most Disturbing Thing I've Ever Made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Achievement Hunter Makes a Porno (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But where are the spaceships in those movies? 

I imagine there's a difference between a 164-page dialogue-driven drama, and a 180-page effects-driven sci-fi. Higher page count means higher cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any of these work? https://imgur.com/a/zVMHS/all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 06:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Six words that shook the world: "Elaborate on this cum box, please." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should see someone about his drinking problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 08:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/movies' philosophy is to eat everything as fast as they can and then act surprised when they're full. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was editing a larger project and I stumbled upon the beautiful thing I've ever seen: Nicolas Cage Driving [0:19] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 12:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 01:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling I know what the comments on *BvS* will be. Nobody is going to know which parts Goyer wrote and which parts Terrio wrote. So, anything good about the writing will be attributed to Terrio; anything bad about the writing will be attributed to Goyer. 

I think the same thing is going to happen with *Ant-Man*. Anything good about the movie will be attributed to Edgar Wright, before he left the project. Anything bad about the movie will be attributed to Peyton Reed, who stepped in after Wright left. 

You see it already in this sub, when people talk about "producers" or "studio" as an evil entity. If a movie is bad, everybody blames the producers. If a movie is good, nobody credits the producers. Because the popular narrative says that producers are "bad". And everything has to fit the narrative.

Once you have "good" or "bad" assigned to you, then everything that falls into your category is automatically dumped on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find myself quoting *The Rock* a lot: http://i.imgur.com/lh91dOb.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 05:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the subject of movie trailer announcers messing up: [the trailer for Comedian](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fVDzuT0fXro). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Slow-Mo Guys, set to Pink Floyd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the CIA ever tried to prosecute a whistleblower, but dropped the charges because a trial would expose too much information? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear I read about a case like this. Someone made an enemy of the CIA (I think), and the CIA brought them to court -- but quickly dropped the charges because the ensuing trial would have revealed too much of the CIA's dirty laundry. 

Does this ring any bells?

[And if this isn't the right subreddit for such a question, any suggestions for a better place to ask it?] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 09:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you like sex, Mr. Lebowski? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Scientific Study on the Bouncyness and Blowy-Uppyness of Assorted Vehicles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 21:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Special Executive for Counter-intelligence, Terrorism, Revenge and Extortion

Only slightly less subtle than Every Villain Is Lemons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 19:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/movies watches the trailer for *Taken*:

"Wait, they show the daughter getting abducted? What the hell, that spoiled the whole movie."

I don't know what you guys want from a trailer. You're getting mad at a trailer showing the **inciting incident**? What did you want instead? Not every trailer can be [this](http://i.imgur.com/7yuMc6V.gifv). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but Marvel has consistency. Marvel isn't releasing a horror movie one month, and an animated comedy the next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So?

I've never thought of reddit as an *All for one and one for all* kind of site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  From the studio that brought you *X-Men: Days of Future Past*

I've always thought that's such a weird thing to note. Same producers, same directors, same writers, I can understand. But studios?

Assuming "The studio that brought you *X-Men: Days of Future Past*" is 20th Century Fox, it also happens to be the studio that brought you *Ice Age* and *Fight Club*. 

It's like saying "From the planet that brought you *Hitler* and *Gandhi* comes *Da Vinci*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 20:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying the 10-second tag at the end undoes the 30 minutes of content beforehand?

If someone likes the video and wants to subscribe, will 10 seconds of "Like and subscribe" really turn them away?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 20:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way Christopher Walken says "No" at the beginning is the most Christopher Walken way of saying "No" you could ever imagine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you apply? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 08:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/himZD0M.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 23:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made this http://imgur.com/a/yaNP1 a while ago, might help your GTA sightseeing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 22:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Los Angeles, so welcome to my life. 

It makes navigating the game a lot easier though. 

*I'll take "La Cienega" to "Sunset", left on "Highland", then loop around onto "Franklin" and head up to "Griffith Park".* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. There's no such thing as an objectively great script.

You can't put all the blame on the readers if your script gets a 4 -- just like you can't give all the praise to the readers if your script gets a 9.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Gerry had a line saying how much he loves Pepsi, I have a feeling this controversy would be twice as bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually never bothered by that one. 

I mean, Gerry's in the middle of a zombie apocalypse, society is crumbling, people are dying -- Anyone would be looking for *one*, just *one* remnant of the way things used to be, or the normal life that's never coming back and then he passes a soda machine. And boom. One fleeting moment of normalcy, amid the chaos. 

[Not to mention: Gerry's practically just solved the zombie threat at that point. Wouldn't you celebrate? Somehow? Any way you could? And it even has a plot point attached to it: Gerry releases the cans onto the floor, and the loud clattering noise draws the zombies away from the doors.]  

It just works, in my opinion. If you were facing the zombie apocalypse, and you came across a remnant of a better time, wouldn't you take it? A can of pop? Fuck it, sure. It's the same reason why Will Smith plays golf and drives a Mustang in *I Am Legend*, or why Tallahassee likes Twinkies in *Zombieland*: because it's comfortable, in an uncomfortable time. 

They do the same scene in *The Road*, too. It's the post-apocalypse, and the Man and the Boy stop at a Coke machine for this one reminder of how things once were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 05:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that, but the problem is, it matches Lou's state of mind -- but it doesn't match *our* state of mind, as an audience. 

If you show us something horrific and you put uplifting music on top of it, there's gonna be a tonal disconnect -- no matter what you say about the anti-hero's state of mind. The music may mirror his attitude perfectly but it doesn't mirror *our* attitude. There's an unspoken assumption that a movie's soundtrack is "on our side", so to speak. But in *Nightcrawler*, it's not. And that's why it doesn't fit, in my opinion. 

Other than that, fantastic movie. But every time the music swells, I'm just left with this feeling of "really?" 

If Gilroy is trying to create unease I gotta say, we're already uneasy, given what we're seeing. The tonal disconnect is the wrong kind of unease: it's like a technical unease, not a diegetic unease. All the other components (the themes, the exposition, the camerawork, the delivery) are "on our side", aiding our experience, helping us feel the moment -- but the music is working against us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 00:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I do my shitty Chris Walken imitation, that's my go-to quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 21:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a train wreck from start to finish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 27:30 - Ryan's "I cut off my own arm with my pocket knife. They're making a movie about it." is a reference to *127 Hours*. 

30:29 - Geoff's "Hit it with the Sword of Crota!" is a reference to [Destiny](http://destiny.wikia.com/wiki/Sword_of_Crota). 

37:26 - Jack's Tron/beacon [reference](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jQQCo9FqUOc), also seen on the [poster](http://cdn.collider.com/wp-content/uploads/tron_legacy_final_poster_hi-res_01.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 21:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean [this hand](http://www.digital-polyphony.com/polthand.jpg)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there *is* a big clue outside Verbal's story: [spoilers](#s "the Hungarian man who survives the boat slaughter and ends up in the hospital, says he saw Keyser Soze, and provides a sketch of him -- and that sketch is Verbal.") The sketch is [here](http://api.ning.com/files/DbrwTSp7ycMPWkT-ZedYDOt0E093EEuR878V*0uu90X4UTfZWhAT9VGeQQcXb-8wJu0VF5gBzdlbW6Xv*E1eQWaBnE0EYCjF/keysersozedrawing.jpg).

That scene exists *outside* the flashbacks, and directly confirms Soze's identity. That's the smoking gun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 20:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I recall correctly, that waiter was a member of the other IMF team shadowing Ethan and his crew. 

So I guess you could say he killed one of his own. Which is less bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 01:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 41:47 - Gavin's *Bourne Identity* "Through the window!" leap is [actually from](http://youtu.be/uLt7lXDCHQ0?t=1m8s) *The Bourne Ultimatum*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are better hills to plant your flag in. 

I mean, this movie means nothing. It doesn't hurt you, it doesn't rewrite your childhood, it does nothing to you -- and if it really "offends" you, then that's more a statement on you. 

It's a *Ghostbusters* movie, not a crime against humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 06:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And *Catch Me If You Can*, so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 06:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flattered, but could you possibly omit my email address? My username is fine. I just wouldn't want my contact info floating out there all freely and whatnot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
