<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to learn a skill that would help me freelancing. For example learning Adobe softwares, a programming language, a DAW but I don't know where to look for online resources. Can you recommend websites that'd help me learn these skills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're probably wasting time. Funny thing is I  actually  did well in high  school but I have become a  depressed fuck now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree with others and your karma goes down the drain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What do you consider a huge waste of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I got downvoted I see. Maybe my comment was...misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant competition is so much you won't believe it so don't think we're lazy. It's just  very hard these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said they don't treat me with respect LMAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my best friend told me he slept with your mom.  I highly doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned that sleeping with OP's mom would require tough work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booty and the boobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I  took OP's mom to Europe and she told me she is married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I slept with OP's mom for the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindsey Lohan, Kim Kardashian, Alia Bhatt, Kylie Jenner, Drake, Lady GaGa, Zayn Malik, Rihanna, Taylor Swift, Justin Bieber, Britney Spears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you're  writing lol like a stupid teen. Go hide in your cave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking a  fight with a stranger on the internet. Wow. So tough. I admire your bravery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Competition is unreal so don't tell us we're lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook is shit though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet you're wasting your time. I am the MREXPERIMENTER who experiments day in and day out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is how you engage a stranger in a meaningless conversation. Congratulations! I  was experimenting to see  if I can waste your time and I have succeeded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baseball is for fatsos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than baseball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Only losers like you would say that. Go hide in your cave now mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. You're being mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom. Ayeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why cricket is a great sport? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope he responded  with an  emoji. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am serious. All they need to do is treat people with respect. That's a  huge turn on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't quit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, who's to say that few losers aren't downvoting me? Maybe the people who downvotes for no reason are themselves in some kind of a denial and take the frustration out by downvoting me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make money as a college student online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make some money online. I can't work outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider it a lot thank you very much kind stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIGHT! FIGHT! FIGHT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of comment karma but not post karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if I don't want to live anymore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think I would like to live anymore. It all seems like an illusion and I just don't see any point. Meow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not worth it. Take your time and explore stuff. You wouldn't live forever so know what career you want and then go into it. Don't major in something stupid like gender studies and all those bullcrap fake degrees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it offends you I can understand but just because you disagree you shouldn't take my karma away. As I said I take my Karma seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why dropping out is a good idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example Kim Kartrashian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you people voted for Trump. Well, then again, you were fucked either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get girls without even trying. People love you and would compliment you even when you do something badly because of your charm. You will be ahead at your workplace. They'll consider you smart based on your looks. Believe it or not being attractive puts you ahead and not so good looking usually remains in the shadow of them.  
P.S I am not incredibly attractive but somewhat good looking because even in my depressive phase few girls would come to me knowing I don't have much to offer. I have seen very attractive people and life is somewhat easier for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends are pathetic and they are not there when I need them yet expect me to  come for them all the time. I can't get a girl that I like. I have a pressure to find a job because my parents refuse to work. Life's just hell and I am annoyed. I can't believe how much my life has sucked. If I had a choice I wouldn't choose to be me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it when they treat me and others with respect. Today many bitches are entitled and act like they're a queen. It's so good to see when they act nice and gives respect to others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like formatting. It's very confusing for a beginner. Also, I hate it when people downvotes a comment or post just because they disagree with them. I take my karma seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My keyboard needs replacing sheesh!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But breaking in like a motherfucking boss is cooler than unlocking with keys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can say that but she had a broken heart at that time so..I'd say..so close yet so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is SO fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they don't want to :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking your friend's sister must be a very satisfying feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jogging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can never buy gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because my keyboard needs replacing. Not my fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I really want the world to be peaceful. You know how crazy that sounds? Because rational people would look for their profit and consume as much as they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Jackson. Probably eccentric but who knows? Certainly  interesting and all the psychopaths are interesting as well...dangerous maybe but ...interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Must be at least 1 year old  
But I am 19 years old!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sound advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The way you feel right now is the way you'll always feel. The people you know that are happy and healthy and full of life will mostly retain that glow. The people you know that are sour and unpleasant will mostly remain that way.  

Quite scary for me because I consider myself quite negative ...so this means I'll be like this for the rest of my life? I mean I have always been quite negative as a kid as well and it hasn't changed much. I feel it is my fundamental self but ...it is not fun to be me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well,  I don't know. I have suppressed loads of things but one thing stands out is my friend who I considered my best friend didn't tell me about a lot of things for a long time and I was friends with him since 9th grade. It devastated me because I thought we were best friends. Then I kept wondering if I actually even knew this person or not for all these years. I was really into at least 3 girls and they all rejected me. My self esteem went down and I was feel as if people just don't like me now. I am too afraid to go out there and express myself. There are plenty other bad things that have happened and I am not sure if I can write them out right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well being born in a family is not your choice so I'd put at least that on my destiny. Not my fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right but what I was implying is that it's the kid's destiny that he is living a childhood like that but once he grows up he has his destiny in his own hands. As a kid he doesn't have a choice to choose his family but as a grown up he can change his fate if he is willing to work for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you cope up with the fact that your every friend makes more money than you and gets more girls as well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A life full of regrets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you do if at 19 years old you have nothing but TONS of regrets and no one to support you? No friends that care. No parents who support emotionally. No luck with girls. Just no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason it was quite heart warming especially this
 My gorgeous wife. Yes, I know that at 12, I wasn't sure whether I wanted to get married, enter the priesthood, or what. But it's true, I'm married. I think you'll like her.
My three kids. They all look a little bit like me/you, and certain aspects of their personalities are similar, but the middle one is way more outgoing than I am, the older one is a little more intraverted, And the little one is a girl. Can you believe I have a daughter?
The book I wrote. Yes, it's actually in bookstores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you do meth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My keyboard needs replacing mate. Don't blame me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider a 10 year old kid living with an abusive father. Do you think kid has the choice or the kid is just destined to live like that? Where else the kid will go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can be compared  but it's just unfair considering they have their unique value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your 12 year old self is standing in front of you; what do you tell them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. They're the people who have  not faced a REAL trouble yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticks and  stones may break  your bones but words  might   kill your soul. WHOOWHOO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But even as a  kid you still have choices like whether to  go to school or bunk the class. You  just have to face  the consequences.  Isn't it the same when you're an adult? You have a choice. Either work and  pay the  bills or live  with the consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outright lies. Can't  believe people say  these  things and deliberately fucks with  young minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would work  in  an   ideal world  where  most of the people  are like this. However,  reality  consists of people who are worse  than monsters so hiding  your  true  self is understandable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it's   best to  let  the  dreams be  dreams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be  fair they  have their own taste and value so  comparison is  unfair. They both  have their unique characteristics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or if your video  of dancing  naked in the middle of  the  street has  gone viral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destiny is a real  thing. If you really  don't have  any control over what is being happening around  you then that's your destiny. If you  can  control things then you can make  your own  destiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't  talk to your  dad like that son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of a person would you consider a loser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you're an adult you can  do whatever  you want..... only catch is that if you don't  abide by rules you might  end up starving or  in jail  that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually doors won't open and you'll have to  fucking  break  in and  get  what you want like a motherfucking boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say money  can't  buy happiness but it can help you to ask out   your  crush  and take her on a  date. If you're broke nobody  will  talk  to you  because you're  not "fun". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, tbh  the  friend I  spoke  about  in last comment has also grown apart and  I sometimes feel we're just dragging it now. Change is scary but seems like it is the reality now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I  was in for  a  shock when  high  school  ended and thought I was  an adult and  everyone is mature now. I go  to college and  it's just like I am with kids again. After   1 year of  college I understood nothing is going to change. I still feel like a  kid and  will probably feel  this way  forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have  a  friend who lives in his fantasy land. I try to  give him  a reality  check but he says it stresses him  out and he doesn't want to listen. Well, I tried telling him it is not always about him but he doesn't want to listen. He'll  understand when life burst his bubble. He'll understand everything with experience. I guess it's one of those things that you learn with experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't take internet too seriously. Your life lies outside of virtual world. Nobody on the  internet knows you so they can't make decisions for you. Your facebook or instagram likes means nothing. They don't land you anywhere. Do things that will make you a better person and don't spend too much time in front of a screen. Also, you never know who's behind the screen you're talking to. It could be an interesting person or it  could  be a loser in his  30s or  40s who has no job and sucks at life giving you advice on philosophical or academic queries. Lastly, just live your life. Go  out with  friends, party like crazy, ask out girls/boys, make mistakes and learn from it, take your  studies seriously and hit the gym.  
Ironically, I am a stranger on internet and you shouldn't take my advice too seriously either but that's the whole point. You is you and nobody can take  place of  you.  So, go out there, live, make mistakes, learn and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the traits which pushes other people away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they were just playing with you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I  have  advice  for you. It happens to me as well and recently my  friend got tired  of my shit and I also got tired of him constantly talking  about him and his relatives. So, I stopped talking to him for a  while like 6-7 days and after that he was more enthusiastic to  see me and the conversation went smoothly. I guess it's about giving space to people and if that doesn't work then  straight up tell  them to discuss something else.  
Not sure if a break will help you guys but it is  a suggestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you  Joe Gatto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair you should  avoid politics and  religious talks if  you can. It can get  nasty pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll  call  you Lucy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die  peacefully without  pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> calm  down satan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the  gold  kind stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear is getting hated by everyone. Most heart breaking is people just usually don't  give a  fuck....not even friends...sometimes not  even family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What to do if you don't have a single friend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depression and anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that I agree. That's a big question and the girl should know if you're taking it seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once  straight up called  a girl I  had a  crush on and  she   thought I  was   a creep. Then  she blocked me on Facebook and made sure  I could never contact  her ever  again. lel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, thanks  for that BUT I most probably won't get her but hope to  continue being  a friend  and  occasionally text. lel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it so wrong? You  might  actually inspire  others to do  good  work  as  well. Might look as attention seeking but social  media is just about that.  It's about displaying bits and  pieces of glamour of an  otherwise  shitty life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's limited because men don't have to dress to impress. Money talks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say it also just depends on the person  and/or situation, possibly culture as well? I think, say asking out someone via text  would be good if the culture frowns upon on a girl and a guy hanging out. In some  cultures, they don't give enough freedom to some  boys and  most girls  to hangout together neither as  a  friend nor a couple. Do you think in  a  situation like that  texting is a  smart idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. You're unfairly judging. I have read lots of threads where asking out a girl via a text message is considered a "pussy-move" by many. I am  just curious why is it a "pussy-move". Not over-analyzing just curious to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then I  see people saying women are not some "magical" creatures. They're just people so treat them like one. Well, I  text people all  the time and then it isn't considered that I have  lack of confidence. Why  do girls have  to over analyze when texting is clearly the safest option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it wrong to ask a girl out via text? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How should an idiot spend his life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone does it though   at least  to some extent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I ramble too much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say I ramble a lot.  I have no friends. I feel  as if everyone makes fun of me. Nobody likes me. I don't like me. My life is hell and  it  might never get better. Help.
P.S I rambled again. I am  such a sucker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't it weird we can lose everything we have in just one moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it so easy to lose everything you have in one moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I   gave you the 999th point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you happy in life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
