<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9850</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wales National Park Time-Lapse Film   Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reasons and Examples Why 24mm Possibly the Best Focal Length for Landscape Photography </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for Better Smartphone Photos - Simplicity is Key, Underexpose the Sky, Use the Same Tools as for Your Real Camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rumor is that Sigma Will Unveil New 14mm f/1.8 ART and 135mm f/1.8 ART Lenses in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Productivity Experiment I Failed Miserably: Eating only soylent for a week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Bailey Interview With David Allen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian occupants in Abkhazia expand training range at the expense of old XIX century Polish cemetery and church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Schengen: 4th Military Base put on alert in Georgia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian occupants in Abkhazia expand training range at the expense of cemetery and church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian occupants in Abkhazia expand training range at the expense of cemetery and church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia to publish anti-Ukrainian Ukrainian newspaper in occupied Crimea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia uses collaborators at UN to deny its repression of Crimean Tatars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poisoned Putin critic Vladimir Kara-Murza: "What can I do if someone wants to kill me?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poisoned Putin critic Vladimir Kara-Murza: "What can I do if someone wants to kill me?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six Outrageous Lies Russian Disinformation Peddled about Europe in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support in Russia for bloody dictator Joseph Stalin at record high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support in Russia for bloody dictator Joseph Stalin at record high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has more than torture to hide in FSBs Ukrainian Crimea Saboteur Plot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has more than torture to hide in FSBs Ukrainian Crimea Saboteur Plot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has more than torture to hide in FSBs Ukrainian Crimea Saboteur Plot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trains go to Lugandon through Russia, bypass blockade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Embassy to Ukraine expresses concern about occupied Donbas blockade, advises establishing transparent movement of legitimate goods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Embassy to Ukraine expresses concern about occupied Donbas blockade, advises establishing transparent movement of legitimate goods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Embassy to Ukraine expresses concern about occupied Donbas blockade, advises establishing transparent movement of legitimate goods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spy agency confirms murder of North Korea leader's half brother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flynn in FBI interview denied discussing sanctions with Russian ambassador </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says I inherited a mess, blasts media and detractors at combative news conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says I inherited a mess, blasts media and detractors at combative news conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flynn scandal hits the foundation of our democracy. We must investigate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flynn scandal hits the foundation of our democracy. We must investigate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The presence of the SSV-175 Viktor Leonov off the coast of Connecticut is a sign of Russian weakness, not strength. The spy ship's limited and outdated electronic eavesdropping gear can only listen to radio communications: "I hope they are having fun listening in on Classic 101" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The presence of the SSV-175 Viktor Leonov off the coast of Connecticut is a sign of Russian weakness, not strength. The spy ship's limited and outdated electronic eavesdropping gear can only listen to radio communications: "I hope they are having fun listening in on Classic 101" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says hell issue a new executive order on immigration by next week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ignore that spy ship off the coast. The Russians aren't coming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony a99 II - how does it stack up to its a99 predecessor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photography Tips How To Improve Your Wildlife Photography </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PhotographyTalk Wildlife Tips Part 1](http://www.pta.lk/akhemdq)

* A Quick Equipment Tip (DSLR, 70-300mm lens)
* Pay More Attention to Focus
* Shoot Eye to Eye

[PhotographyTalk Wildlife Tips Part 2](http://www.pta.lk/8pmtbqf)

* Be Aware of the Background
* Show the Ecosystem
* Working According to the Sunlights Schedule
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 Macro Photos of Insect Eyes and Hairs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 Portraits of Insects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixing Digital Noise by Blending Together Images Taken at Different ISO Levels - Step-By-Step Guide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Fix Digital Noise in Photoshop by Blending Together Images Taken at Different ISO Levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surface Book vs MacBook as a photographers tool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump promises Israel that Iran will never get bomb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to host Netanyahu in meeting focused on Iran, Middle East talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin Tells Media to Cut Back on Fawning Trump Coverage, Sources Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin Tells Media to Cut Back on Fawning Trump Coverage, Sources Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Insights from "High Output Management" by Andrew S. Grove </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Atlassian Does Performance Reviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Why Amazon is Seeking Daily Feedback from its Employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Amazon is Suddenly Seeking Daily Feedback from its Employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine, Turkey citizens to use internal passports while travelling within these countries - Ukrainian Foreign Minister says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Poland will not accept carving up Europe into spheres of influence. Never again Munich or Yalta," - Polish Foreign Minister on Russia threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican presents its new "Letter to health workers" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican presents its new "Letter to health workers" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Image of Russian Ambassador in Turkey murderer wins World Press Photo contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unique collection of OUNs official records found in Ternopil region </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Image of Russian Ambassador in Turkey murderer wins World Press Photo contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Image of Tuckish Assassin Wins World Press Photo Award </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian instructors certify another 15 Ukrainian EOD experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump expects Russia to return Crimea to Ukraine: White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cardinal Marx: Always loyal to the Pope - The Council of cardinals issue a statement showing their support for the Pope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator McCain calls on Trump to provide lethal aid for Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian Prosecutor General slams fake cases against foreign investors in Ukraine - law enforcers go to various businesses, especially in Kyiv, bully them and charge money for leaving them alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lutsenko slams fake cases against foreign investors in Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Official: Russia Violated Missile Treaty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator McCain calls on Trump to provide lethal aid for Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator McCain calls on Trump to provide lethal aid for Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is "more business-oriented insights". I decided not to copy all the article (summary) text in the submission to make the submission shorter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Employee Engagement for Everyone by Kevin Kruse - Book Summary   Insights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Kruse boldly appeals to everyone in his title, what both intrigued and impressed me is his rejection of the one-size-fits all approach to employee engagement. Instead, he recognizes that each business leader must identify a solution that fits the unique needs of his or her company.

**Employee Engagement Affects More than Profits**

The correlation between employee engagement and profits is alarming enough on its own  companies with engagement levels under 25% suffer negative total shareholders return, or TSR; (this and other eye-opening statistics linking profits to employee engagement collected by Kruse can be found here). Beyond profits, when you neglect employee engagement, youll also suffer in the areas of quality, safety, retention, service, and more.

**Use the Four Pillars to Improve Employee Engagement**

There are four essential aspects of employee engagement. They are trust, communication, growth, and recognition. How you balance the four pillars will depend on your organizational needs. Kruse provides detailed, actionable steps about how you can improve each aspect, but heres my overview:

* Growth. You must challenge all of your employees regularly and make advancement opportunities available.
* Communication. Check in frequently (once-per-year reviews no longer work, weekly check-ins do) and establish a two-way feedback loop with each of direct reports.
* Trust. Show everyone how they fit into company goals.
* Recognition. Lastly, giving praise and showing appreciation can go a long way in making employees feel their efforts are validated.

**Give Everyone a Role in Employee Engagement**

Interestingly, Kruse provides strategies that can be adopted by both executives AND their employees. Not only does he show us what we can do as leaders to drive engagement, but he presents simple solutions for employees to help show managers the ways in which they can be engaged most effectively at work. For employees, this puts some of the power in their own hands, and for leaders, it emphasizes the point that engagement is a unique endeavor that must fit well with company culture and can be further tailored to meet the needs of the individual.

**Address Actively Disengaged Employees**

Kruse refers to actively disengaged employees as Debbie Downers, and says that not only do we need to find unique solutions for handling them, but we must also avoid becoming one. This is of monumental importance, as active disengagement can easily become contagious if not handled appropriately. Find the solution that fits best with your company culture by asking your employees questions about morale in your weekly progress reports.

**Dont Treat Engagement as a Top-Down Issue**

As previously mentioned, EVERYONE can play a part in driving employee engagement. That means that CEOs alone shouldnt carry the burden of improving engagement; rather, it needs to be a team-wide initiative. Managers are best suited for overseeing the employee engagement of their direct reports, so collaborate with them to develop solutions for improving engagement. They may have better ideas about how you can use team-targeted engagement solutions to drive focus, performance, and commitment, and ultimately, achieve aggressive goals to secure big wins.

**[Source: Book Insights: Employee Engagement for Everyone by Kevin Kruse](https://www.atiim.com/blog/employee-engagement-for-everyone-by-kevin-kruse/)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summary   Insights: The Power of Full Engagement - instead of focusing so much on time management, we should instead approach it as energy management </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Full Engagement by Jim Loehr and Tony Schwartz - Summary   Insights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was also some previous discussion here about the book: /r/books/comments/35be7f/i_just_finished_ashlee_vances_elon_musk_biography/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Insights from Elon Musk by Ashlee Vance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Use your Past to Fuel Future Motivation**

In this biography, we learn that Elon Musk was born in Pretoria, South Africa. He had a less-than-ideal upbringing, and his family life was tumultuous. Vance reveals that Musk never felt as if he fit in with the culture  which idealized athletes and jocks  in Pretoria, and as his family quibbles escalated over the years, he envisioned a way in which he could escape. Despite an imperfect start, however, Musk remained extremely ambitious into his later years.

**Network with People who Identify with Your Passions**

During his time at the University of Pennsylvania, Musk began to associate with physics majors, who were aligned with his interests and passions. After spending some time with his like-minded cohorts, it became apparent that Musk, too, was of similar intellect: he received a 98 on a paper on solar energy during his senior year. His enthusiasm extended beyond receiving good grades: When I was in college, I wanted to be involved with things that would change the world, Musk said. What we can all learn from Musk is that working with like-minded people often yields impressive results, because shared passions are a powerful tool in any entrepreneurial endeavor.

**Be Willing to Put in Long Days and Late Nights (at least in the beginning)**

Musks original startup, Zip2, didnt take off right away. In fact, it required many late nights, during which Musk would actually sleep under his desk. Hed ask other employees to wake him in the morning so that he could start working again. This kind of relentless drive and dedication is what Musk used to build not only startups, but startups that were sustainable.

**Know when to Practice Restraint**

In 2000, Musks fellow executives cast him aside as CEO of the company that would eventually become PayPal. Despite being forced into a lower position, Musk refused to react bitterly towards the other execs. Instead, Musk remained supportive of the company. He was PayPals largest shareholder, and by 2003, his shares amounted to $250 million. Having restraint when facing challenges at work  especially those that may seem personal  can help you to succeed in the long run.

**Communicate Openly**

For a period of time, Musk evaded the public eye. While some speculate that he might be a shy individual, Musk learned quickly that CEOs and entrepreneurs must be comfortable with an open exchange of regular communication to be respected  and to garner positive attention for their companies. Musk is active on Twitter, and he believes that CEOs and other execs must assume a role of responsibility in communicating with their target audiences about their products or services.

**[Source: Book Insights from Elon Musk by Ashlee Vance](https://www.atiim.com/blog/book-insights-from-elon-musk-by-ashlee-vance/)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Top 10 Books for CEOs (Horowitz, Conley, Chouinard, Lencioni, Welch, Collins, Gladwell, The Arbinger Institute, Drucker, Buffet) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Photograph the Moon - Article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is DxO ONE Worth the Price Tag? - Article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Largest Lenses for Photo Cameras Ever Created </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Get the Most Out of Your Time Using Steven Coveys Prioritization Matrix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Zorian Rotenberg, Atiim CEO, breaks down his startup CEO role today into 6 categories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * **Strategy   Execution**  The CEO must set the vision, must know how to get his company there, and must execute and manage operational execution towards that vision (which at an early stage is a ton of arduous work without resources). 
* **Recruit A-Players**  Build out a great team (thats 80% of the battle).
* **Sales**  The CEO must be the first sales rep of the company and needs to build a predictable and repeatable process that scales sales with newly hired sales reps.
* **Marketing**  The CEO must do the marketing to get those leads into the sales funnel he must evangelize the company and then do something innovative to be able to build a cost-effective customer acquisition funnel.
* **Cash**  Its all about growing sales while keeping a laser focus on managing money effectively.
* **Resourcefulness**  this is the least talked about role of a startup CEO but this one is probably the most critical success factor of a startup CEO and is far more critical than for someone who is a CEO of a billion dollar company.

[**Full Article: Achieving Unique Goals with Zorian Rotenberg, Founder   CEO of Atiim**](https://venturefizz.com/blog/achieving-unique-goals-zorian-rotenberg-founder-ceo-atiim) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Allen: Why things dont get done? - There needs to be at least one person who has accountability by assignation or default for bringing something to the finish line. Being nice and not deciding who it is, is not really nice at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Trump Weighs Thaw With Putin, EU Set to Renew Its Blacklist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Trump Weighs Thaw With Putin, EU Set to Renew Its Blacklist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Trump Weighs Thaw With Putin, EU Set to Renew Its Blacklist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We must vote as Presidential Administration tells us,"  independent MP Rabinovych on Opposition Blocs stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United States and Ukraine sign agreement to share tax information (FATCA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Understanding Photo Camera Aperture in 5 Easy Steps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Coming: Nikon D820 or D900 Rumours and Surmises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How HDR, Time-Lapse Video, Burst Mode   Add-On Lenses Benefit Your Phone Camera Images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collection of nine spectacular sunset shots and a few tips and tricks along with them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 Smartphone Camera Settings You Should Try Out - HDR, Time-Lapse Video, Burst Mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puppy   Infinity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Space And Reflection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No case for relaxation of Russia sanctions, Boris Johnson to tell EU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No case for relaxation of Russia sanctions, Boris Johnson to tell EU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blockade in Donbas: Bandits (titushky) arrive in Bakhmut under police protection, - MP Parasiuk. VIDEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dramatic Impact of Illegal Amber Mining in Ukraines Wild West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dramatic Impact of Illegal Amber Mining in Ukraines Wild West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The United States has stripped Oleh Liashko, leader of the Radical Party fraction in the Ukrainian Parlament, of his American visa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Goodbye, America!": US annuls Liashko's 10-year visa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian parlament calls on foreign parliaments to condemn Russia's deliberate destruction of Avdiivka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian parlament calls on foreign parliaments to condemn Russia's deliberate destruction of Avdiivka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Ambassador to Ukraine Ernst Reichel cancels press conference amid scandal over remarks on Donbas elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Ambassador to Ukraine Ernst Reichel cancels press conference amid scandal over remarks on Donbas elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trump Will Soon Put Putin on Notice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trump Will Soon Put Putin on Notice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain rails against drawing equivalence between Putin, US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. McConnell: Putin's a thug, US is exceptional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Russian Slot Machine Hack Is Costing Casinos Big Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKRs   Achieving Unique Goals. Zorian Rotenberg Describes His Job as Startup CEO   Founder of Atiim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Google sets goals: OKRs - Objectives are ambitious - Key Results are measurable - The sweet spot for an OKR grade is 60-70%, low grades shouldnt be punished </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superpowers at work: OKRs are a critical component of how Googles leaders managed Googles growth from day one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Handle the Million Task Boss with OKRs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Insights from Work Rules!: Insights from inside Google by Laszlo Bock. Most pertain to Googles People Operations, modern equivalent of HR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Improve Performance with OKR Goals**

One way to drive performance is by emphasizing personal growth. One of the reasons Google uses OKR Goals  and why **theyre so powerful  is because they simultaneously drive personal growth by encouraging employees to meet their own individual objectives while contributing to company goals,** since all priorities are aligned.

OKRs consist of Objectives and Key Results. Some Objectives should be aspirational, while others can be operational. Key Results are used to determine what needs to be done to accomplish the Objectives, and should be measurable.

Google still uses OKRs to this day. Not only are they effective for accomplishing goals, but research demonstrates that you can improve employee performance when you invite individuals to be committed to their goals. Likewise, youll improve employee engagement when you collaborate with your people to set ambitious, specific goals. Treat Your People like theyre Irreplaceable

Bock said that prior to his experience at Google, he was frustrated with the fact that **leaders always spoke of putting people first, and then treated them like replaceable gears.** Google, however, has an incredibly stringent hiring process. Google recruiters use sample work tests to see their candidates in action, and they tend to hire individuals with ambition and curiosity over experience.

If you take the time to hire the right people, they really will become irreplaceable. And thats a benefit for both you and your hires: when you find the right fit, Bock says, people require less training, and on top of that, employees will be put in a position where they can really use and build upon their strengths.

**Learn to Give Feedback Separately from Consequences**

Your aim in providing ongoing employee feedback should be to drive performance. When someone is performing below your expectations, the feedback you provide shouldnt be about repercussions, it should be focused on giving that employee everything he needs to succeed (resources, information, and clear expectations, etc.). Compensation and promotions are separate entities, and are therefore are not main components of your ongoing, continuous loop of feedback.

**Use Actions to Support Your Mission**

Every company should have a mission, but more importantly, Bock believes that **each companys mission should be specific and driven by actions and activities.** If your mission is too vague, or if you never drive your mission through tangible actions, its likely that it wont resonate with your employees.

**Dont Weigh Your Company Down with Rules**

Bock recommends trusting your employees to do the right thing without setting forth too many strict guidelines. He believes that **when too many rules are enforced, creativity and motivation are diminished,** thereby thwarting productivity.

**Never Start Out with Negative Assumptions**

**Managers and execs who start out with the belief that their people are inherently good will fare better than others,** according to Bock. If you start out with the assumption that your employees are out to rip you off, you risk developing a rule-driven, negative environment in which employees do only whats required of them from the get go. Bock believes that this sort of optimism is what sets great organizations apart from others, because its there that people can truly excel, thrive, and do their best work.

**Excel by using Small Experiments**

Google takes an interesting approach in trying out new systems and tools: they try them out, as would a scientific researcher, on different groups of people before implementing them fully. Always fond of data, Google execs will study the performance quality and morale of the test groups to see how well the new tool or system is working. You, too, can **collect insights from your employees after you try new things** by retrieving data through your weekly progress reports.

**Build Trust and Commitment through Transparency**

Bock advocates always keeping your employees in the loop about whats going on inside the company. This, he says, fosters commitment, because it encourages employees to think that theyre all in it together. The emphasis in your company should be on unity, not on division. As such, you need to remain open and transparent on all levels. Without that transparency, you wont be able to build trust, and your people will be less likely to commit fully to your company.

**Take Advantage of Mistakes**

Google encourages its employees to take sensible risks, and as such, they acknowledge that failure is sometimes inevitable. But as Bock notes, failures can breed intelligence  people tend to learn more after mistakes than they do when things go smoothly. Failures can actually be successes, because they ultimately foster growth and development. Yet, in order to achieve that growth and development, you must let your people know that its okay to make mistakes.

**[Source: Book Insights from Work Rules by Laszlo Bock, SVP at Google](https://www.atiim.com/blog/book-insights-from-work-rules-by-laszlo-bock-svp-at-google/)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How OKRs Complement Scrum - Define Goals, Clarify Success Criteria, Develop Autonomy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bird Photography Mistakes to Avoid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landscape Photography Primer: Getting Sharp Images With Depth of Field and Hyperfocal Distance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Take Better Photos of the Milky Way - Guide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone Has Stolen Your Photo. Now What? - Article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Little Egret - In Space And Reflection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACAB's memorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia through Google Street View </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Friends Are Reading The Book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zone of Absolute Discomfort : A Photo Essay on People living in Northern Arctic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glass Beach: Natures Way of Recycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
