<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6654</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dawn of the Tail of the Dragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3000?  Subaru says 6k... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 22:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my favorite either but it doesn't affect me, yolo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just outside of Atlantic City NJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just outside of Atlantic City NJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yessir, see here: https://www.reddit.com/r/ft86/comments/4m289m/i_too_keep_adorable_shit_here/?st=itq1fwz2 sh=010d7541 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the comments about magnets below, that's what I did.  I live in NJ too (smh), but now I can take the plate off and on again with ease.  I've been driving without the front plate on because the ticket only costs like $40 lmao

https://www.reddit.com/r/ft86/comments/4c2uvw/magnets/?st=itq1vly7 sh=7ea83336 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty in the rain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 03:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure one of the earlier BRZ TV ads was a girl trying to stuff a giant teddy bear like that into the car, and ~~failing~~ succeeding.  

Props, that's impressive

edit:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VBYZ-sm1myA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Def not factory..  I have a series blue and it's the same as stock.  Pretty sure hyper blue is stock as well.  Plus, I doubt a 2016 hyper blue would have 63k on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> P D U O L W L N </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Math work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How well did that do on the beach?  I drove on the sand last off season and got stuck well...  within 10 feet of the road I turned off... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful.  Covergirl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short circuit happens when electricity travels along an unintended path. What happens in a long circuit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh out of University CS major, critique my Resume please! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get "Out There"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recent college grad here. Just got a job and am now living on my own, never had too much luck with the ladies.  I'm single, 22 and a virgin.  

I've been on dating sites and apps (Tinder, Bumble, OkCupid to name a few), but honestly, the area I live in (South Jersey) is really sparse when it comes to women on social dating sites.

Honestly, the main problem here is just finding people. Due to finances, I'll be moving back at home soon for a bit.  Hopefully it'll be easier because it's a much more populated area, but this just gets me more depressed every day.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in IT and have to orient new users with their computer.  This one woman was so computer illiterate, so I had to show her how to do things step by step.  She put in a complaint because apparently I "made her feel stupid". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he "baked" cheese on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh out of University IT Professional, please critique! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 03:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a tie! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/og37y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same!  See my recent post in /r/CompTIA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but, your flare says asphalt FRS... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Passed SY0-401 with an 806! Here's what I did to study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just took the exam and passed with an 806/900, and wanted to share my experience!  About this time last year, I took a Cyber Security class in college which taught right  out of the CompTIA textbook for Security+.  I wanted to take the exam in February 2016 but couldn't because of unforeseen circumstances.

I studied for this from the beginning of July to yesterday (09/21).  I watched Professor Messer's videos, while taking notes on everything.  My textbook came with a voucher to "Certblaster", so I had some practice questions to work with.  I also purchased GCGA's 30-day access with mock exam questions.  Also took use of examcompass.com.  Lastly, when I purchased the exam from CompTIA, I took the 2-exam bundle with CompTIA's CertMaster access.  I had quite a bit of resources for this exam.

My exam had 72 questions and 4-5 simulation questions.  It was hard to say the least.

I was halfway through the exam and I was pretty confident I failed it already, as many of the questions I had to answer with educated guesses.  After submitting the exam and taking CompTIA's post-exam survey, I was so shocked that I passed with such a score.  

That's my experience guys, thanks for all the help and good luck to you all!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those tires stock?  I was going to do TOTG this summer but I didn't have enough confidence in the Prius tires and didn't have the cash for better summer ones :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 13:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using examcompass.com, CertBlaster, CertMaster (compTIA), and Get Certified Get Ahead.  All but the last one were free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking Security+ on Thursday! Any last minute advice... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are some topics you guys wish you studied "that much more" before the exam?

I'm pretty confident I'll pass, as I've been getting 90's and above on the mock tests I've been doing.  But, what would you have studied more of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was at Bally's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly, I dunno, AC has people coming from all over the country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cause you left your passenger vanity mirror light on :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, who drove up to Atlantic City from Florida? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PUNCTUATION MAKES ALL THE DIFFERENCE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as learning manual goes, let the clutch out slower

why not wave back when someone waves to me? that makes me the a-hole..

Also, don't be an a-hole and wave when a fellow BRZ/FRS owner waves lol

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL hamsters are hatched from eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 14:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 15:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I would tap that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here ya go: http://imgur.com/gallery/6PlRXhI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuinely lol'd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> t...  tell me of your ways.  Does it connect to the speaker system just fine?  I'm assuming you took the head unit out.  What are the connections like behind the plate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 00:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bubble bubble bubble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 00:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha no, I would not like to check.  If I found any of that, it'd just piss me off.  Ignorance is ~~key~~ bliss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 00:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my first thought too, but I don't have window tints and I'm most likely not going to tint them (cause NJ sucks).  Wonder how smoked everything will look on clear glass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait..  is that a sex joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to keep her clean! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah.  I used the brush, after this pic was taken.  But, whenever I go to the wash bay, I pressure-wash the brush with the hose to clean any grit left on the brush.  Then, I brush from top-down to avoid any road contaminants getting into the brush.  I haven't noticed any micromarrs, but that's good to keep in mind.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 21:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and why not?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New tails and sidemarkers... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sup, possibly looking into swapping out the stock tails and side markers soon.  I have a WRB BRZ, and can't tell if I like the smoked color scheme or clear, as I haven't seen either on a WRB to compare.  Anyone have some input, possibly pics of your WRB setup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly.  That's strange...  never happened before iOS 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10 message effects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all- I wanted to test out the new effects in messages,  such as Slam, Loud, Gentle, and Invisible Ink.  I sent messages to my self to see how they would come in.  When I choose (any) effect and send it, the message is delivered 3 times.  Does anyone else have this issue?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> bubbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has this gone too far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 19:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has this gone too far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 19:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deaf people of Reddit, how would you describe a fart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 21:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T/C off, I like your style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered the power of the 86?  It's not the fastest car out there, it's pretty laughable.  These things you call "features" are more-so factors put together to make a car that handles as well as this one does.  

Have you looked at a used g35/g37 perhaps?  maybe an e36 m3 or a mustang? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like many others have said on this post, although you say it must be sporty, perhaps it's really *not* what you're looking for.  

For it's price range, the 86 is one of the best handling vehicles on the market.  There are better cars to sit in traffic in.  This one is loud and things rattle inside the cabin.

I saw your post in r/cars, you didn't even know this car was RWD.  RWD isn't necessary for racing per se, but it's essential to a great-handling car.  

Have you looked at some sedans on the market?  There's plenty of sporty ones out there.  

I honestly think you should do a bit more research on what you want to be your next car.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/DesirePath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 09:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Certified Get Ahead.  http://getcertifiedgetahead.com/index.php/security/security-study-resources/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 123,456 next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That oversteer though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat, looks like the light was refracted through the headlights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked certmaster, but I feel that GCGA's 30-day access is better.  420 practice questions, also performance-based questions.  I'm taking the exam in a week or so, I felt that it is very helpful (for now) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any more like this?  This is the first American ad I've ever seen for a BRZ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into the STi wheels...  or take a look at a Series.Blue BRZ, it's the same body kit with the wheels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 01:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks so sad to not be on Mars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 15:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the title and thought, "Wait, Galileo wasn't still alive in 1999..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 20:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are those the mysterious amazon tails?  how do you like them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the Apollo astronauts get into the LM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I recall correctly, there was a tunnel for them to crawl through.  But when I look up images of the LM, it just looks like a port for docking.  Did the astronauts have to space walk to get into the LM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 16:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanna touch it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't consider myself to be a "terrible" driver.  I'm more defensive if anything, I've never hit anything from driving for 5 years other than a chipmunk (RIP lil guy).

Other drivers..  yeah they suck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also, to be safe just make sure he didn't chew on any wiring in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol'd @ nuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call a PDR (paintless dent repair) dude.  I had a baseball-sized door ding in my passenger side door, $75 and 10 minutes later shit was GONE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a jersey driver, yeah we suck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 19:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7IYR_rELyE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 19:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would but I don't have anyone to help me with the job lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General cost to wrap roof? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to possibly wrap my roof in a gloss black vinyl.  I'm not sure the price range for something like this, so I called a car customization shop by me, and quoted a roof wrap to be $500.  This sounds overly expensive, but I have no idea what wraps go for.  Does $500 sound about right for a job like this?  If I could do the job myself I would, I just don't have anyone to help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juno's first glimpse at Jupiter's North Pole! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is winning the Human Race? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 16:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's starting to come back again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little bit of a back story. I'm a recent college graduate who is turning 22 on Sunday. It took me until now to come to senses with how I've been feeling lately.

Because my college internship hired me full-time, I accepted the job because it was employment right out of school. When we all graduated (my roommates and best friends), we moved out of our college house and parted ways. I stayed in the area for my job, and found an apartment to rent. My summer was great, because one of my other friends from school roomed with me for before he had to go back to school. As of last Wednesday, I've been living on my own for the first time in my life.

I don't know many people in the area, and my phone sure isn't buzzing like it used to. Besides the fact that I don't have a significant other (or never have for that matter), I'm not the most social person. I'm living in a pretty rural area and finding people (not only someone to date, but friends also) is hard to come by- even dating/meetup apps have been not helpful for me.

It's taken me until now to realize, that I really don't have anything in my life besides work. Work is starting to become a bother, because I'm incredibly underpaid for my field and my take net take home is about $200-$300 at the end of the month (after all expenses). If my parents weren't able to help me out with my groceries, I would be going into my savings to work at a job I'm not happy with anymore. I plan to have a new job before the start of next year. A lot of the time I question why I didn't just find a job back at home and live with Mom   Dad for a year or so.

I've dealt with depression in the past, and have been prescribed SSRI's which I did not like. I felt that they didn't work for me and I felt mad at the fact that I had to take a drug to make me feel "normal".

Tears are beading down my face as I'm writing this post, as it looks like I'll be spending my 22nd birthday alone- the first birthday I've ever spent not in the presences of friends or family.
I really don't know what I'm expecting from this post. Maybe some advice, or a feeling of comfort. Mainly just to vent out because I haven't had anyone in my personal life to talk to about things like this for a while now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many ounces are in a 40? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting malt liquor with some friends but I want to know how much I'm drinking exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how I feel.  No part of me wants to end my life.  I just need to move passed this rut in my life and every morning when I wake up I feel like I just hit a brick wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proper lighting can make WRB look incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep mine raised (almost) all the way.  I'm kinda short (5'8) and the extra height is better for my visibility.  Additionally, if I have to throw someone in the back seat for whatever reason, their feet have the ability to move around now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  You'll probably see an FR-S at a lower value sooner than a GT86 or BRZ.  Essentially the exact reason why I bought a BRZ instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the power with the truck.  But to be honest the truck is probably faster... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 14:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high school physics teacher tried telling us that gravity was caused by the earth's rotation, and wouldn't take no for an answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Students of Reddit- what's the most pretentious thing you've heard a Teacher or Professor say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 14:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of things going into this.  I don't necessarily like the job anymore, and am looking to move on.  There are much better locations for a similar job paying much more than I am getting now.  
I don't want a raise, as I'm not looking to stay with the company much longer than when my lease ends.  The $1-2/hour raise won't help much in the grand scheme of things.  
I am looking into new places of work.  I just don't know when/how to let my supervisor know about how things aren't really working out.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking for a raise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Put your friends birthdays in your phone as reminders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 03:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this from Juno? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 03:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this from Juno? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use my iPhone and google maps.  Have never touched the map function on the head unit, the radio is bad enough... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *86 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny thing is, I came from an Altima haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah, fuckin' right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I know I won't make it without scraping, yeah I'll avoid it.  Speed bumps I take with extreme caution.  I've learned to just never go into a bump/ramp/hill straight on, always going in on an angle will help avoid scrapes.  I park on the streets if I can't make it up the driveway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a BRZ Series.Blue.  It came with the STi body kit (side skirts, lip, rear bumper fins).  I'm afraid to lower it at all because of how low the lip already makes it...  Scrapes are inevitable and I can't make it up some driveways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plasti-dipped Altima... close enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $11k to sell...  it'll cost more to buy it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic dogs we know today are descendants of wolves. Are domestic cats descendants of larger cats, such as lions and tigers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I ever die... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be very disappointed with the progress of human medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i.e., broken glass and bare feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What two things make the worst possible combination? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1, don't use a potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 23:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to caption...  oops.
Door ding the size of a baseball, had to call in a PDR guy to fix it.  those are his tools in the door lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I get my favorite bathroom stall at work... it's the little things in life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you never not have a dishwasher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you don't have a dishwasher, you are the dishwasher. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tequila Mockingbird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 01:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *just in Tein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SY0-401 Practice exams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the title says...  Looking for some practice exams for Security+.  I have already used ExamCompass, Comptia's CertMaster, and CertBlaster.  Are there any other resources for this, preferably free of charge?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for a car without an accident.  That's pretty much all I can say, as you're guaranteed to not have to worry about things exactly like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Song] It doesn't have to be like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard this song at my friends house while I was mid-waking up, so I didn't think to Shazam it.  All I remember is that its chorus went something like "It doesn't have to be like this".  Searching Google did no help for me.  It sounded like a modern rock kind of song (I think).  Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If carbon monoxide kills you, does carbon dioxide kill you twice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this something off the McDonald's menu?  McHammer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly mistake.  You're thinking of HAIR conditioner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it act as a fog light?  I know the white lights on the sides of the triangle are the reverse lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man those drill holes :(

1) You could go the expensive route and replace the front bumper if it's that much of a bother.  
OR you could check out Bumper Plugs.  https://www.bumperplugs.com/index.php?route=product/category path=1_11

2) No clue.

3) Good luck finding 0% ethanol on the east coast

$) Never changed my tires/wheels yet.  Probably gonna next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that triangle light (in the US at least) doesn't do anything?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She doesn't drink? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all- this should be quick.

Started talking to this girl that I'm pretty into now, we're not official yet but have gone out a few times.  She tells me she doesn't drink because of family history with alcohol and all.  I don't have a problem with this as I'm not a heavy drinker, but personally, I'd like to get drunk with my girlfriend every once in a while.

Would this deter you from a relationship with someone you liked?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely wrecked my STi passenger-side side skirt because I was impatient, drove around someone who was stopped in the middle of the street for whatever stupid reason.  Didn't even see how close to the curb I was until it was too late and the skirt was destroyed.  Scared the shit out of me.  Those things are a bitch to replace, but I'm glad I didn't fuck up the wheels.

Just goes to show how low to the ground these cars are, and now I'm much more careful with mine.  Lesson learned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like 44,176 photos... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello from Atlantic City, New Jersey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, however and in the many times family members have tried to purchase out a lease, it was always more for whatever reason.  But that's just our situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but typically that price will be higher than if you just financed it in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll still have to pay for a chunk of the car and in the end you won't own it.  That being said, if you were to ever modify the car, you'd have to convert it back to 100% stock when you return it.  Typically, this isn't the kind of car that you would lease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought that curb stop was a lip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 06:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why you're posting that to this specific car sub... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 03:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> different font too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 03:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was probably set for like 75-80 or so while I accelerated past the cruise setting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed that mpg...  must've been accelerating, lolz (photo taken by passenger) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 86mph in an 86 on 8/6. Happy 86 day y'all! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the Limited's do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 02:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably a pretty decent deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So *THAT'S* what that smell is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly how I feel about the WRX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was about 28k OTD after tax and warranties and what not.  But was also a Series.Blue so it'll be a bit more than a regular BRZ Limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I did.  Actually bought it a few months before graduation.  

One tip- Make sure you can really afford it.  Yeah, you're out of college and might have a full-time job but if you don't put enough down in the beginning, those payments will haunt you for years to come.  Unless you just buy it with cash in full.  If you have a car that works and is paid off, run it till it won't run no more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but your flair says WRB BRZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That feeling when you leave the office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 15:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hope that my Future Lawyer would already know english...  heh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um.  Did you get a hold of the 2017 wheels a little early or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What club? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the button by the steering wheel won't pop the trunk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh maybe not you then...  Saw a Hyper.Blue on I-95 north on Sunday afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you on I-95?  Definitely think I saw you but we were far behind in my roommate's e30.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security+ Hands on section? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there- I'm chugging along at studying for my Sec+.  I'm doing well on the examcompass practice exams, and other studies as well.  But, what kind of questions can I expect to see in the hands-on portion of the exam?  i.e., questions that aren't multiple choice.  

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So uhh...  How'd the prius tires handle the Dragon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a hairdryer next time (if you didn't already). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
