<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8379</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hilarious genius has built a Twitter bot that tricks idiots into arguing with it for hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I wonder if that could be used nicely for the skeptical community.... Thanks for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazil will release billions of lab-grown mosquitoes to combat infectious disease. Will it work? | Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Utility-Scale Energy Storage Facility in Massachusetts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He Calls Hillary Clinton a Demon. Who Is Alex Jones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 15:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI:
The Monsanto Tribunal will be livestreamed online, so that people everywhere in the world can watch and listen to the Judges, the lawyers and the witnesses. Click on the video screen to follow the hearings from Saturday Oct 15, 8:30 am GMT+2. For the People's Assembly, see the information below.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Tale of Two Rivers: The Charles and the Mystic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 15:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For The Record: Mock trial distracts from real dialogue on the worlds food and agriculture needs and the full realization of human rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Maine-based Bigfoot expert found himself at the center of the national clown frenzy - The Boston Globe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's media on this here: http://www.politico.com/tipsheets/morning-agriculture/2016/10/hirshberg-pushed-clinton-on-gmo-labeling-216798 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the solar coach for my community. We are getting a bunch of sign ups, but there are some people who have barriers.

1. Many people in this urban setting are in multi-family/condo units. There are legal barriers, or family disagreements, in some. Also, local laws not that great for multi-unit situations.

2. People have been turned off by aggressive vendors in the past. I hear this a lot.

3. People heard about PPA/leasing scenarios affecting later sales. Confuses them, because some could own and not have this issue. But they don't understand the distinctions. 

4. People have approached other companies in the past who won't touch slate roofs, flat roofs, or multifamilies. They assume they can't participate (they can in our program).

Some are waiting for better tech, some heard the Nevada story and assume they'll get screwed. We also have a lot of renters here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you have to fake a trial, or fake the science, you are absolutely bereft of credibility. 

http://www.nationalreview.com/article/440934/anti-gmo-activists-stage-fake-monsanto-tribunal-hague </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm torn on this. I agree it's 100% bunk and counter to the laws of physics and chemistry. 

But this kind of study would give payers ammunition to discredit the treatments--places like Canada where there is government coverage, or even in the US where it's federal payer systems for some people. So there may be some value in it, ultimately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is scientific bunk worthy of study? Among respected scientists, a debate ensues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why It's So Hard to Get Solar in Florida (That'd Be the Sunshine State) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been to a BASEA forum before, but I would like someone to walk through this. So I may attend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University makes six-figure lawsuit settlement with creationist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MA DOER's 'Next Generation Solar Incentive Straw Proposal' | Forum Oct 13 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 00:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am intrigued about this being in Uganda, and I hope it works there. I would love to see how it works in the US, with different sources of nonsense and different media routes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are awash in bullshit health claims. These scientists want to train kids to spot them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a number of them in Cambridge. But the legendary ones are in Brookline. Total turkey street gang assholes. http://www.bostonmagazine.com/news/blog/2015/04/03/urban-turkeys-apocalypse-boston/

So far there are no reports of a Somerville gang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter Hill Turkey tries to open bank account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I support bike paths, bike lanes, and would like to see many more safe cycling options. I'd give you some of the streets if it was up to me.

But I think this argument is unnecessarily divisive. Pedestrians who also use the path for their commutes or to avoid auto exhaust fumes are not your enemy or the real threat to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Chemist and a Designer Team Up to Weave Solar Panels Into Fabric | Innovation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 15:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 03:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it's cold, so I forgot about Tipping Cow: http://www.tippingcowicecream.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't base any of my opinions on this film. I'm a survivor of illness caused by GMO's. I'm speaking first hand from experience.

He or she should take those claims that they've been harmed by GMOs to a lawyer. That'd be the first case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the WHO celebration on measles could backfire on public health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moved to Sunday because of weather: https://www.facebook.com/SomervilleArts/posts/10154151547074585 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/09/27/1607187113.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bababrinkman.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be better to argue less with a homeopath? Maybe give that little shoulder-shimmy to succuss yourself, and be done with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winter Hill Brewing: https://twitter.com/WinterHillBrew

Somerville Bread Co: https://twitter.com/SomervilleBread

Lyndell's (since 1887): http://lyndells.com/

Those are my favorites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somerville's first AgriCultural Festival to celebrate food, farms, arts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-vaxxer Jenny McCarthy's autism summit peddles dangerous treatments, features discredited doctors | Debunked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newborns deadly heart arrhythmia caused by mosaic of mutant cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they cause Zika. Of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it shows they are a smaller but shoutier group. This is a point we keep making on most anti-science and nonsense peddlers. There are not as many of them as they think there are and they are disproprtionately represented in the false balance sort of reporting.

And they are like crackheads. They have to keep going back, reinforcing their biases. It is probably really hard to break that circuit. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm certainly concerned that even if we avoid the shitgibbon in this election, the underlying problems that are pushing him along are not resolved. They will only fester for 4 years, while we are treated to a constipated Congress that's trying to interfere with the first woman president the same way they obstructed the first black president.

It's going to erupt eventually. I don't know whether it will be another terror attack, or something internal like the ranchers. But it's going to blow. I feel it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Conspiracy Theorists Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 14:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UVLrx Therapy Lights Up Charlatans Dealing In Medical Devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah, it's sad. Most of the scientist I know have stopped relying on Consumer Reports for anything.

If they can't be trusted on this, who can say their other ratings are valid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London man 'training to cure autism' filmed abusing client - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a dozen articles on the bogusness of organic gatorade. 

This is the only piece I saw on bogus food tests that are actually harmful. 

I hate the media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you went over there and told the author that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 18:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really should revoke her MD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 14:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop educating based on science. Yah.

At least we know what we are really dealing with: zealots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 14:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 03:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PepsiCo claims it now contains organic sugarcane where the non-organic stuff used to be  which, lets admit, does have significant environmental advantages

Yeah, can I see the evidence for this claim, please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 23:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "steamed clams"

I laughed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dangers of Snake-Oil Treatments for Autism |Autism's Fringe Therapies: Stem Cells, Weed, Psychics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaking with: Bad Pharma author Ben Goldacre about how bad research hurts us all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see there are consequences to harassment of scientists. That's rare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly right, it's not like absentee. It's real voting, just before the official day.

It is a great idea. Business trips, challenging work hours, even traffic can screw with voting on only 1 day. I have always hated this mid-week single day thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the primary article: The Role of PIEZO2 in Human Mechanosensation

http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1602812 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover gene behind sixth sense in humans | 2 humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might do it just because we can. And I want to encourage this for the future as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Voting at City Hall Oct. 24-Nov. 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vaxxed pulled from festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zikas Making Some People Sick. Its Making Other People Crazy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. But seems a bit high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the parts where the stupid was just too much, and Myles could only shrug.

The stupid burns that badly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a good podcast on This American Life a while back on that. http://www.thisamericanlife.org/radio-archives/episode/543/wake-up-now

I am not sure about the study you mention. I'd like to know about that too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solarize Somerville: Where We Stand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 14:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you haven't seen the literature about there being sufficient fat in the diets? Yeah, you seem to have some gaps in your education. 
http://dotearth.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/08/27/from-mark-lynas-to-michael-pollan-agreement-that-golden-rice-trials-should-proceed/?_r=0
His first concern is that there may be too little fat in the diet of potential beneficiaries. It is true that a certain amount of fat is needed for the bioavailability of vitamin A. However, according to the literature only 5 g/d are sufficient, whereas even in the poorest quintile of households in India average fat intake per adult equivalent is 35 g/d, and e.g. on the Maldives the fat intake of children aged 1-3 years is 22 (11) g/d, i.e. for Golden Rice to work no additional fat is needed in the diet of the target groups. (Otherwise suggestions that people should simply eat carrots, papayas or mangoes would run into the same problem.)

I know this researcher, by the way. I'm sure you'll dismiss him as a shill because it runs counter to your claims, but he's not.

Edit: Looks like we have some downvotes from the anti-science brigade on here.

Oh, teh irony. You are the anti-science brigade here, you see that now, right?

But one thing always surprises me: how much anti-GMOers don't give a shit about farmers. Benefits to farmers are a big deal for me (and for farmers and their families). [Reducing pesticides is a major benefit--especially to poor farmers](http://theness.com/neurologicablog/index.php/bt-brinjal-destroying-the-anti-gmo-narrative/). I happen to think that's good for everyone as well. But I guess if it's not affecting you personally at your keyboard it doesn't matter. Maybe I shouldn't be surprised all the time at the self-centeredness of people who can't be arsed to understand the larger picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 14:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this posted about upcoming openings: http://davis-square.livejournal.com/3720536.html

Saturday, October 1, 2-4 pm

Thursday, October 13, 5:30-6:30 pm

Saturday, October 15, 2-4 pm

Thursday, November 3, 4:30-6:30 pm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 05:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I stand on scientific consensus on this. I have deep knowledge of the field, and I see the opportunities and benefits. 

For you, if you can only imagine people have to be paid to do this, you don't understand the issue at all. It's much more like vaccinations, stem cells, and climate change than McDonalds. That's why it's in the skeptic repetoire. Educate yourself and you'll see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in my tweet on this I wrote: "Now?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man v rat: could the long war soon be over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'March Against Monsanto' Is Now an Anti-Vaccine, Conspiracy Movement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. Secret knowledge is a big lure of these things. All of them, not just vaccines or 9/11. 

I'm kind of impressed she admitted this out loud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was an anti-vax crackpot  until this happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 15:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer con Belle Gibson's $75,000 payday for 60 Minutes interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Misinformation Age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 23:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I didn't expect cocktail party advice. Well done, I'll pass that along too. 

Thanks for your work on this. I thought it was important and well done and I appreciate that you folks worked so hard and carefully on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early farmers selected for compounds that were deterrents. http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9431670

Because pests were (and still are) a huge problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a new site that has some helpful information at Purdue: https://ag.purdue.edu/GMOs/pages/scienceofgmos.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed watching the creationists attempting to evolve their arguments, in a spectacularly failing manner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related question: did any of the participating authors get new FOIAs after this came out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Via Davis Square Live Journal: http://davis-square.livejournal.com/3720099.html
Postponed to tomorrow evening because of forecasted thunderstorms tonight.

Edit to add:
Also, the time tomorrow is 5:30 pm rather than 6 pm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1pm ET Sept 19: Science AMA Series: authors of a recent report on genetically engineered crops for the National Academies of Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The official reports from all sorts of government groups and scientific societies are important, and I rely on such assessments and consensus sorts of documents on many scientific fronts. Especially those that our outside of my field.

But many of the people who seem to be the most misinformed dismiss these anyway, claiming payoffs and other conspiracies.

What do you think is the best outcome for these kinds of documents? Are you reaching for policy makers? General public? Do you think this accomplished what you'd hoped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 03:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the burrito maker still struggles to recover from an E. coli outbreak last year

Hypocrites are at the top of my shit list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen any, but I'll post if I see some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved finding out answers. Things that I didn't know, I would research, and find facts that were very satisfying to me. It even began with things like ghost stories and Nostradamus, and unearthing the reality behind those. Finding out they were bunk, and why, made me feel good.

I grew up with tepid Catholics, more of the cultural sort than the religious sort, and the pieces of creation stories and the lives of the saints and their magic tricks were open to question. So I did.

Training in science brought this all to a formal structure. And I do feel that science is our best bet for answering questions. It isn't perfect, but it's better than the other options.

But now, I keep going because the harm to vulnerable people by vaccine cranks, cancer cranks, GMO cranks, and various stripes of science deniers is having real consequences in our world. And that makes me want to wrest the steering wheel from the clown car that they have managed to put us all in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soon You'll Be Able to Climb Somerville's Prospect Hill Tower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 01:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very few of these types of articles offer anything constructive. But I thought the piece about the training at the end was particularly hopeful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Difference Between Rationality and Intelligence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 22:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Challenges of Science Communication: An Interview with Kevin Folta - CSICon Las Vegas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 16:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's too bad. They've actually done some pretty sane (ironically enough) stuff on science, cranks, and conspiracies in the past.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moms Across America Are Selling You All Natural Chemicals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 19:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, god. Who will ever go into public health ever again? So thankless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's off patent now--you can do it. Go ahead. https://www.technologyreview.com/s/539746/as-patents-expire-farmers-plant-generic-gmos/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The next green movement: Plant biology for the environment and sustainability </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, every zombie claim in the swamp is now coming back up with the Bayer stuff. Sigh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This does highlight the real problem. The "worried well" cranks are not the ones at most risk from their BS peddling. Either vaccines, fluoride, GMOs, whatever. 

It's harming the most vulnerable in our society. And that just aggravates me to no end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 16:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A method that Rachel Carson--patron saint of many of the so-called "environmentalists" who do most of the shouting--preferred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plant Sale | Somerville Garden Club | Sat. Sept 17 Davis Sq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somerville hits $10M jackpot in national high school innovation competition - The Boston Globe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We also have to worry if it gets too small--it will be more powerful then, right? 

Er.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SomerStreets: Strike Up The Band | Highland Ave, Sunday Sept 18 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this very good assessment of it as well: http://nutrevolve.blogspot.com/2016/09/jama-internal-medicine-sugar-industry.html?m=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not a molecule of sense | A push to disabuse Germans of a homegrown form of quackery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, she did. She specifically called them out at the end. It was a partial reference here, but it was subject of her piece just a few days back as well:  http://www.vox.com/2016/9/6/12815250/amazon-health-products-bogus

The reason this bugs me is because it's aiming at the wrong target. People find this crap because someone like Gwyneth or FoodBabe or Mercola lies to people and they seek this out. Amazon is the far end of the pipeline. The misinformers are the real problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it say Trump on it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree on all counts. Vox is good at this.

But I don't understand their ire with Amazon. I think the far worse offenders are the actual shit-peddlers like Mike Adams and Joe Mercola and Gwyneth (although they do call her out too). 

Amazon is no worse than Whole Foods (or many other pharmacies and groceries). I accidentally walked into some kind of Whole Foods satellite that was nothing but bullshit wellness crap. I was just looking for a bottled water. I fled. 

But Amazon doesn't write up conspiracy theory and anti-science BS to peddle their crap. Whole Foods, Mercola, etc--they all use their narratives to hit the vulnerable up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the way his brain works. He's so effective with such sparse (typically) graphics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The saddest thing about this apple she's commenting on: it's going to reduce additives and preservatives. Sigh. 

I am allergic to a lot of preservatives and additives..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, many of them actually prefer "natural immunity" and peddle a lot of BS about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "my friends and family are to sue the poo-poo out of YOU my dear FDA and Dept. of agriculture and congress and senate" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a common misconception that anti-vaxxers use: why is my unvaxxed kid a threat to yours? In this case it's because the cancer treatment wipes out the ability to combat infections.

But there are other cases too. Even just protecting nana from the flu because senior's immune systems aren't that great either. Or older cancer patients as well. People who got transplanted organs. Some are medically fragile in other ways that are less visible too. 

Anti-vaxxers are actively putting at risk the most vulnerable in our society, because of misinformation. That's the saddest thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my nephew had leukemia, I would have decked a measles-spreader if they had been in our area. Luckily, we live in a place where science and evidence continues to mostly work, and he didn't pick up any of those awful diseases that anti-vaxxers want to restore.

Good news: he got through chemo safely and is in remission. He's several years past it now--his mom posted that he had been vaccinated and was up to date a few months post-treatment.

Wishing you and your circle the best outcome. And thank you for trying to protect this vulnerable kid at this very hard time for the family. I know what it looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 01:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had flown out of Boston/Logan to California on Sept. 10. It was for a biz trip that had been re-set a couple of times. It could easily have been the next day. I think about this sometimes and it still makes me queasy.

I was up early the next moring (because east coast wake-up time), and I was ironing my work clothes with CNN on and watched it all happen. It was so baffling. I went into the business meetings that day, but mostly we were all just checking for news and we didn't get much done. 

I got stuck in California because of all the flights being cancelled after that. I couldn't get home. And I didn't have enough room on my credit card for the hotel from this business trip. 

Eventually I got home, of course, safely. But it was so hard to watch from the west coast when things were so uncertain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Centuries of Boston Light | A look back at the shining history of Americas first lighthouse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 15:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...and then you can have a healthy brain, like I have." [21:30]

That is the furthest thing from a healthy brain I have seen in a long, long time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice: registration and program is now available. You're gonna want a copy of this too.

http://en.monsantotribunal.org/program </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaaaa????
I'm here to tell you today as a scientist--as a lab director--that the official narrative on Zika, microcephaly, and DEET--is a horrible hoax.

Oh, Mikey, Mikey, Mikey. You dangerous fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumed the Movie - An Unofficial Recap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be some crafts people at the Riverfest this Saturday that could help you out. I've talked to a number of jewelry vendors there in the past.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing about a measles outbreak in France years back, and I found out it wasn't the Wakefield stuff but some other kind of crank source. But the numbers of infected people were astonishing.

I had to travel through Paris on some flights, and I got booster shots at the travel clinic because of that. Airports? Measles? No thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is It Possible to Measure Supernatural or Paranormal Phenomena? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think Americans fear vaccines? Check out the French. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my precinct I asked the cop if it had been a busy day--he laughed. 

I'm watching results here, but they aren't getting updated very quickly. http://www.masslive.com/politics/index.ssf/2016/09/2016_massachusetts_state_prima.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 03:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are raising 500,000 just for the stunt. Imagine also the plane fare, accomodations, food, etc. Nevermind the time spent on this nonsense.

Can these people really not think of something that poor farmers might be able to do with that kind of money instead?

I loathe these drama queens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 03:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. But does it matter that much to the individual sitting on the porch in the bayou which one of those it is? Isn't it more fun to imagine it's the latter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, thank you. Keep this up. Into October.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa--just came across this piece today, which kind of crystallizes that view in a cohesive way. Look for the section on the "deep story". 

http://www.vox.com/2016/9/6/12803636/arlie-hochschild-strangers-land-louisiana-trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somerville Dog Festival  A Unique Event for You and Your Dog | Sunday Sept 11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I was really worried about how the World Ferret Union was going to come down on this.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does say that there is a Tribunal TV thing, and a stream. But I don't actually expect these techno-boobs to do it right. It will also be Euro daytime, I assume. I'm not getting up to watch cranks in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was explained to me once, by a wise older woman: people who are into all these conspiracies are folks who aren't doing all that well in the current framework. And there are real reasons for this--they have been screwed by corporations, and jobs that used to support a lot of blue-collar workers have disappeared. Things they used to understand, they just don't anymore--technology, culture, etc.

They find it exciting to think about some alternatives--any alternatives--and they imagine that in some new structure their bunkers and weapons and whatever their survival skills are, will make them king of the new heaps. Somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Riverfest at Assembly Row, Sat. Sept 10. Music, vendors, fireworks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 15:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's on the signers list. Yes, it's a huge case of crank magnetism over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing reviews about it. Even people who are inclined to hate Monsanto and buy organic seemed dubious about it. 

http://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/movies/ct-gmo-thriller-filmed-in-illinios-starring-taylor-kinney-column.html

http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/consumed-laff-review-803641 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming Monsanto Tribunal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in October there will be this Potemkin "Tribunal" held at The Hague.

Yes, team weenie will be renting a room in the city with the famous name and holding a fake court. 

We think that fake tribunals need some fake news and coverage. I expect to be fake live-texting updates--stuff like: "Woman testifies that #GMO corn once slapped her in the ass." Or perhaps: "Testimony: #GMO canola transferred genes, now my ears flower." That sort of thing.

So over the next month if you have some choice suggestions, I'd love to fake-live-tweet them when we find out what their hashtag is. 

GMO effects, rulings from judges, any other ideas would be great.  

http://www.monsanto-tribunal.org/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I kind of agree. Why Amazon, and not your local CVS pharmacy selling homeopathy? Or the actual huge quackeroos like Mercola or Mike Adams in the US?

I also showed Julia the Brain Coat. I mean--hey, if we are taking people's money for BS.... https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00K0PX1KG/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_x_BdZZxbH1AW932 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy hell. That was the most excruciating thing I've read in a long, long time.

Every paragraph was like watching another car accident happen right before your eyes. 

Unfuckingreal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomorrow: Beekeepers in Poland? 

Next day: Monsanto Patents GMO pot?

Day after: Danish pig farmer paid by Syngenta?

Lather.

Rinse.

Repeat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha ha....

But sadly, this is the problem when you traffic in conspiracy theories. The line between facts and fiction are impossible to grasp for these folks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds rumors hurting Zika efforts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 14:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he's even quackier than the article conveys? Swell.

Edit to add: it's true, Henshaw has history http://www.quackometer.net/blog/2013/03/the-bbc-will-make-you-sick.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 14:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hairdryers? Hairdryers? As someone said to me on twitter, "This article is a train wreck." I think that's pretty much it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 02:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, fuck, the nonsense....sigh.
Air pollution, obesity and a rise in electrical and magnetic fields is blamed for the surge in childhood cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I saw another great take on fucking up zika: https://ecomodernistmom.org/2016/08/30/gmo-mosquito-conspiracy-nuts-whats-your-vector-victor/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk aims to refit 5m homes with solar roofs | Guardian Sustainable Business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 15:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 14:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this headline go past, and I was all excited, But it didn't seem to cover much of the small-scale stuff if I read that right. 

Facing stricter climate goals, California passes 4 bills to boost energy storage
http://www.utilitydive.com/news/facing-stricter-climate-goals-california-passes-4-bills-to-boost-energy-st/425671/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dread every moment before I can get the shingles vaccine. Shingles is very bad in my family, and it's been the beginning of the decline for a number of them. 

Glad to hear sanity is winning. But I still feel for the kids whose parents prefer that they suffer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's one of 'em: http://www.bostonmagazine.com/news/blog/2016/09/01/mbta-excuse-generator/

I recommend the Keytar Bear inclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I just got this one. I've been a postdoc, but didn't think of this:
#MBTA: #BlueLine: Minor delays due to a debt-laden postdoc with a guitar and a dream at Airport. We recommend you #GrabaSnickers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one of the uses mentioned, but not the only one. Nor is herbicide tolerance unique to GMOs. There are plently of non-GMO associated herbicides. Corn is "naturally" atrazine tolerant. Sunflowers are herbicide tolerant due to a handy mutation.  If you don't like herbicides, fine, but I hope you like hand weeding. Farmers are going to need your help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm all for more biology solutions. But demonizing GMOs will make it harder to get there, and conflating the issues also doesn't help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Eastern US could get a third of its power from renewables within 10 years. Theoretically. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if you don't farm it's probably not important to you. But I think it's also important to think about the tools farmers need to use. And if it wasn't glyphosate it could be worse herbicides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey--reporter wants to talk to you: https://twitter.com/ndungca/status/771389972981116929 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, since neither corn nor soy is bee pollinated, the majority of use on GMOs is probably not bothering them. 

That said, there's plenty of non-GMO use, and if that was a legitmate issue in the field (not just in lab experiments), aiming at GMOs would be a mistake. I keep trying to explain this to people who keep conflating GMOs and herbicides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genetically engineered crops and pesticide use in U.S. maize and soybeans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's wicked pissah, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fundraising appeals for the desperately ill are moving, but evidence is crucial | Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are free to talk to other vendors and get quotes. But if they want to get the Somerville program pricing they have to go with our partner. We vetted their proposal, had them work with our city inspector, and we are monitoring their efforts. 

I'm the solar coach, btw. If you have any questions about how the program works, I'm happy to answer them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creationism: You know that there's a whole organization doing this, right? Monitoring legislation all the time, testifying in public hearings, etc? Alerting us to activity in our local area? https://ncse.com/

And I think the FoodBabe takedowns have diminshed her influence a great deal. But that's just the most recent one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DW: Area 51 alien craft and other detritus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nye Just Blew Up Your Favorite Conspiracy Theory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genius. I was roaring earlier when I saw it.

It may already have it, but I feel it needs some Matt Damon sightings, maybe also apples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm hearing that a lot. I'm afraid it's made people very wary. I will say, though, that at our booths and events when we tell people this is a city- and state-based project, they warm up to the idea again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a company at Greentown labs that's doing something close. http://www.sistinesolar.com/

I took a tour over there, and they showed us samples. Looked very cool. 

But I can't even see my roof, I don't care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other headlines were great. This was my favorite:
9/11 and the Zionist Question: Is Noam Chomsky a Disinfo Agent for Israel?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. I might be up for this, but it would have to be after my current gig with the volunteer effort I'm doing. 

One good source might be Will Brownsberger (state Senator). He gave a talk I attended a few months back. Supporter of solar, has array on his house. Seemed strategic about legislation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bright Ideas: Solarize Somerville Helps Property Owners Make the Solar Switch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to me there are 2 ways to approach skepticism. 1) You can be a theoretical skeptic, arguing about the philosophical tenets and historical foundations.

2) You can be an applied skeptic, on-the-ground countering bad claims, raising awareness of harmful practices and practitioners, bringing current news and issues over.

Some people do both. I think Steve Novella is a good example of that. 

But I prefer applied skepticism. And that seems to be where many of the folks who post here like to be as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Power Is Booming In Vermont -- But The Energy Source Has Limitations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it makes your team look really bad, I know. But here's how reddit works: if the community likes content, they vote for it. Scores go up.

If they dislike it, scores go down. Now, next to your comment I see the phrase "comment score below threshold". 

Now, use your logical skeptic brain to tell us all what that means. 

In case you aren't as familiar with skeptics as you claim to be (which we'll assess from your mathematical conclusions), we post things that homeopaths, anti-vaxxers, chemtrailerz, and alt-med folks are doing all the time. You might want to learn more about how these groups act, because it may help you to understand what anti-science behavior looks like. It's a transferrable skill across many types of science, including plant science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 22:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww...c'mon, English isn't their first language. And this went out quickly, probably not reviewed. 

Don't throw anything in your rage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No chemtrail classes in Minneapolis adult education offerings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, there's a statement from the conference organizers about this [PDF]: http://eucarpia2016.org/images/docs/Statement.pdf

Its around 11 oclock when a group of activists enters the conference room of the ETH Zrich, throwing urine on the audience while painting Shit on technology on the wall. When they were gone they left considerable damage, a mess of rotten eggs and poo and an audience full of incomprehension behind. 

and
Two of the escaping activists were arrested by the police thanks to the courageous reaction of two local congress participants who followed them.

So they got a couple of them. At least plant breeders are fit enough for the chase! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. I used it as an opportunity to reach out to local religious organizations about our city solarize program.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated this article, but I was withholding comment to see what the chatter would offer.

Luckily, Steven Novella covers my position perfectly here: http://theness.com/neurologicablog/index.php/in-defense-of-pseudoscience/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously--who hates plant breeders?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-GMO Group Throws Feces and Rotten Eggs At Plant-Breeding Conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was one of the witnesses that WCVB talked to in the report I saw. I'll look for the video later. 

EDIT to add video link: http://www.wcvb.com/news/bicyclist-struck-killed-by-mbta-commuter-rail-train-in-somerville/41408774 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As More Parents Refuse Vaccines, More Doctors Dismiss Them -- With AAP's Blessing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First DNA Sequencing in Space a Game Changer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop Using the Word Pseudoscience | American Scientist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this article was excellent. I hope he gets the mites. 

Then, of course, the campaign to save the mites from Monsanto will erupt....sigh.

But it's such a good illustration that people are aiming at the wrong target. It's not the GMOs, and even if you banned GMOs today you would have solved exactly nothing to help the bees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Govt launches no vaccine, no Haj campaign this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 02:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw this on the news, and it sounds so strange. People yelled at him to stop, but he didn't. Crossing lights were working. So tragic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing to me. And it really is everything haters claim to want: 
*seed saving/sharing
*reduced pesticides
*aimed at poor farmers
*increased profits for farmers at markets
*nothing to do with herbicides

And what the scientist was saying in the podcast about how much money Greenpeace has spent to oppose this? I really can't fathom that they would stand in the way of something like this. They are like Plant PETA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/feb/05/welsh-home-installs-uks-first-tesla-powerwall-storage-battery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will a merged Tesla-SolarCity put a solar-powered battery in every home? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 15:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 14:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, water is totally a bogus synthetic solution, amirite? And if you add stuff to--you know, [like all the inputs permitted in organic ag](http://www.ecfr.gov/cgi-bin/text-idx?c=ecfr SID=9874504b6f1025eb0e6b67cadf9d3b40 rgn=div6 view=text node=7:3.1.1.9.32.7 idno=7)--now it's a different category?

Organic is the most hilarious and anti-science collection of allowed/prohibited stuff. But in addition to the laughter, I stay for the abject hypocrisy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 04:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's huge tension in the "organic" industry because soil-less growing can be called organic. Fundamentalists hate this. http://www.keepthesoilinorganic.org/#!cornucopia-institute/cf3o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
