<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5149</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemme outta this jail, hyooman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cat likes to climb stuff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Explanation of "AYAT-AL KURSI" | Nouman Ali Khan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 10:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lions strolling in the park; Baby throwing up in the car;

No? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 09:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone in the world has read more books than anyone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/oK13E03.jpg

This is a lichtenberg figure on the human body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frozen Lightning inside an insulator is called Lichtenberg Figures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One hour of Sunlight is enough to power up Earth for one year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes a lot of sense now, Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it was an easter egg because the Doctor Strange movie was ~~wasn't~~ probably decided at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if Project Insight is as sophisticated as the machine from Person of Interest TV Show, even then he wouldn't be termed as a threat to Hydra until the accident and until the therapist gives him the files of Pangborn. And I doubt the events of Winter Soldier took place in between the accident and the doctors journey to Kathmandu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Dr Stephen Strange already an enemy of Hydra in Marvel Cinematic Universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Light slows down in water. The radiation is faster than the phase velocity of light in water, which is less than the speed of light in vacuum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cherenkov Radiation looks like a movie scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 12:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very apt post. I don't buy phones that often. Here are my phones in chronological order.
HP iPAQ
Nokia C6
iPhone 5
Galaxy Note 4

The first two were complete disasters. iPhone 5 was a great phone. 
Note 4 was great at first.

As a user who uses the phone for a long long time, I can say this for sure, when the devices are new, the performance is even on both the devices. But after an year of usage, Android really starts deteriorating. 

A couple of days back my Note 4 was damaged so while it was getting fixed I used a spare iPhone 4s ( in 2016 ). Believe me when I say, the performance of 4s was at par with the Note 4. Snapchat performed better. And sleeping with 100% charge, I found it to be in the 90s itself. There have been days that I slept with 60% on the Note 4 and woke up to it being switched off. 

I like the Note 4 in some aspects like the ease of transferring music, pictures and of course, Truecaller. It's a pain to use truecaller on the iPhone. I still use the EarPods on my Note 4 so that's a plus for iPhone. 

Overall verdict - I can't wait to get back into the Apple ecosystem. The next iPhone ( 7s or 8 ) would be my next phone unless the Google Pixel is really kicking the ball out of the park.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as I saw that the link wasn't working I deleted the post.. Any how. Until next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many examples of tag clouds without the different font-sizes, with/without number of posts badge etc. 

Also, in the post page if a reader drifts off mid way through the article, there are no links for him to stay on the site. Most websites who worry too much about the bounce rate have a sidebar to aid the distracted readers. And direct links to the blogpost may also increase the bounce rates. According to http://www.alexa.com/siteinfo/technobyte.org/ , your bounce rate is 25% which is not too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from what _ffffff said, there is no way for me to see all the tags. Each article looks like its classified in a separate tag. Maybe one generic and one specific tag plus a tag cloud would reduce the bounce rate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes Nick Fury with both his eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gifted (2017) - Trailer # 1 - This is what happens when your dad is injected with the super-soldier-serum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you try Internet Movie Database? It will show you all movies' synopsis. Parental guidance for nsfw stuff. Cast. And pretty much everything available. Do check it out - www.iMDb.com  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> xXx: Return of Xander Cage Trailer 1 - Vin Diesel, Deepika Padukone, Nick Fury and Neymar jr(??) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and me are on the same boat bro. I discovered reddit and stopped using Quora. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one ever looks at an argument on the internet and change their beliefs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it. A vegetarian will always remain a vegetarian. If he sees an argument between a meat eater and a vegetarian, then even if the meat eater won the argument, this guys beliefs won't change. The only way they would change is if he himself is open to the idea of him changing his beliefs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And then they said, 'Real Madrid only buys talent'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HIMYM ending was a complete disaster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Joey and Rachel love story timeline in season 9-10 of Friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In India you have to pay for each plastic bag too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to delete this post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Next Generation Powerpack: Tesla Just Made Its Biggest Battery Twice as Powerful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
