<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5873</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dildo-monster. The worst kind of monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't she have just found one of moms dildos instead? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your style. Do you take house calls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be on to something, ghost-friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trouble Sleeping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter just turned one and she is finally starting to sleep in her own room. It has been an awful struggle to get her to sleep through the night and pure exhaustion forced us into letting her sleep in our room for quite some time. I am sure many of you parents reading this can relate. About three weeks ago she started to get less clingy at night and would let us put her down in her crib. We would probably get five or six hours of solid sleep before she would wake up and need us to walk her around for a while before settling back in for the rest of the night.

It was fantastic! I couldnt remember the last time my wife and I just laid in bed and cuddled without worrying about moving too much or making a noise that woke our daughter up. The bags under my eyes started to reverse course and we were both in a much more chipper mood. 

Sunday night our daughter woke up every hour screaming. At first we thought maybe another tooth was coming in so we would sooth her and put her back down. Monday night the same thing happened. She didnt have a fever or a runny nose so it probably wasnt a tooth. Was she regressing? No way, not happening. I want my bed back. 

We resigned to take turns, one night my wife and the next would be mine. That leads me to tonight  it was my turn. I had some work to catch up on so I was up late already. My eyes were getting blurry and stinging from being open so long and staring at a dim laptop screen when I heard the first wails. Ugh. I was halfway down the hallway before I remembered that I was already holding my daughter. Chills went up and down my spine.

What was crying in my daughters room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love me some ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glory holes. SWEET!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got yourself a classic United States GVMT conspiracy! I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should ask for your money back. Is there a number to call? They usually have a money-back guarantee for products that don't live up to their name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am trapped in my bed and I need help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember waking up knowing something was off. I usually dont move in my sleep but that morning I was twisted and wrapped horribly in my sheets as though I had awful nightmares all night long. Nightmares are usually the dreams I can remember vividly but my mind was blank. 

I was afraid to open my eyes so I laid in bed for an unknown stretch of time trying to breathe evenly and determine why everything in my head felt jumbled. I cant explain it but I could *see* my covers wrapped around me. There were stains that I had never noticed before, microscopic snags all along the bottom from my toenails rubbing across the interwoven threads night after night. 

What the hell was going on?!

A sensation began building in my body; similar to when a song really moves you and you get a shiver all throughout your body and want to cry. Within seconds it was too much to handle and I ripped the covers away from my body in an effort to stop it. Light flooded my mind, blinding me physically and mentally. The agony was indescribable! For those who have light sensitivity during a migraine, magnify that one thousand fold and you might understand the mental anguish I was under in that moment. 

My hand shot out in a search for the covers I had just rejected wholeheartedly. Just as I felt the last shred of sanity slipping away my fingertips found and clung to the edge of my comforter. I rolled and pulled at the same time. My body buried itself deeply in the dark confines of cotton layers and I trembled in pain and fear. 

Just when my heart slowed to a more reasonable pace and the superheated blood began to flow away from my temples my phone rang. Again, it is impossible to describe what I was hearing because it wasnt just hearing but *tasting*. Each note of my ringtone had a distinct taste to it. Maybe if I had a more cultured and sophisticated palate it would be easier to describe but I am a pretty bland eater so tasting my ringtone was an explosion of new flavors to my taste buds. By the third ring my mouth was watering and my stomach gurgled and growled for breakfast. 

Tenderly I moved my hand along the bed to try and find my phone. It was a horrifying experience. My fingertips kept scuttling across old encounters with my ex-girlfriend and as I moved past each one I could almost recall the exact event that left it behind. Right before I reached my phone I even saw the exact spot where my first girlfriend had her first period. I know I had cleaned these sheets a million times since then, using stain removed and hydrogen peroxide and the whole nine yards. I always thought the stain had come out, but I was wrong. I was seeing in a whole new way.

Finally I found my phone and hundreds of bacteria names came flooding back to me from biology class. It was COVERED, every square inch. I shuddered at the thought and brought the phone close to my face. I had to open my eyes to use it. An ultra-bright, fabricated light exploded into view and I quickly dropped the brightness down to the minimum. 

If my description of feeling and hearing are terrible just wait until I try to tell you about what I saw. An intense pressure pounded against my eyeballs with every image I took in. Each key I pressed, each app I opened, each new image crossing the screen had a different pressure and *feeling* to them. I can feel the difference between a 1 and a 2. Ones are soft and gentle, begging for attention like a little puppy. Twos feel happy, strong. Everything has a different feeling to it. 

So here I am hours later, hiding under my covers with my phone on mute and the screen brightness as low as I make it, trying to make sense of what the hell happened to me while I slept. Somehow my senses have swapped? Blended? I dont know if that is the right word. I dont know what I am going to do when I need to pee or eat or drink but I dont think I can take another episode like before. I need to figure this out. 

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The church is merely a building. The power is within the individuals. If no one truly believed any of the sermons it would not really matter where they were. 

Also, she said her lips once spoke the Lords prayer but murmured something else at that time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that makes it better! All is forgiven.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 1800+ words you give me only one. Oh lordliv you dastardly devil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think sweet Ophelia has the strength to shove roses through a skull so my guess is the soft-spoken lady has some power, whether occult or otherwise, based on the "murmuring of something else" you mention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it something in the cookies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see that one coming AT ALL. Very nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA USA USA USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have been saved by my glasses more times than I know. I've got some really nice snowboarding goggles so I'll keep them handy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad I am not in that family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I KNOW I have encountered these before. Thankfully never infiltrated by one but I will be extra cautious from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it because I care! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to knowwwwwwwwwwwwww! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, figure it out. Do it for Mother Russia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me answer your question with a question. What motivated you to write in the first place?

Got your answer? GOOD. Now hold on to that and don't let anyone dissuade you from continuing. If you enjoy writing, if it is an outlet for you, a stress reliever, a way to unload your cares and fears, whatever it may be for do not stop. 

Even the greatest writers in the history of humanity have harsh critics. They only became great because they didn't give in to the critics in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's pissed about a bad student so she is trying to kill her in her mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Icky :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really have any limits aside from my ability to write it. I've tried to branch out more and touch on other subjects but not many have had much success at least as far as up votes go. 

Personally I think one of my least voted is my best submission, but that's besides the point. I suppose I'll find my limits as I progress as a writer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A kid give you a rotten apple this year? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your parents definitely seem to want you to know about this. I am wondering if they were forced into silence all these years and planned this whole event in a means to uncover the sinister truth and escape the clutches of whoever silenced them. 

Keep going, keep digging (not literally), and find out the truth. Hopefully in the process you will exonerate your parents and can be reunited.

I hope they are not actually the cause of this and I also hope they haven't been killed. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falling into Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say sometimes love slowly grows on you. Years of spending time with a friend or colleague at work getting to know their habits and hobbies and quirks. You know every freckle and mole, every hair style they have tried and what tie they will wear based on the day.

Other times it is love at first sight. It hits your right in the face and you fall deep into love. That is the kind I have. It is beautiful and sweet and surprising and terrifying.

Her name is Elena and she is the most beautiful woman in the world. Even with a bloody nose and torn clothing she is simply radiant. 

Her nose broke when I crunched my palm into it and dragged her into my van. Her clothing tore when she struggled and fought the whole way from the van to my cabin.

As I look down at her and smile from the top of the pit I call Love I just know she will finally be the one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stick to the highways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is funny how other users encounters can jog your memory. A few days ago I read a great submission by u/darthvarda and by the end of it my mind was sending off alarm bells. Like Navi bobbing around in the air telling Link *Hey, Listen!* a memory came to the forefront of my mind. Id like to share that memory with you all today.

In 2014 my wife, good friend, and I went to Ireland for the Feast of Tabernacles. I wont bore with you all of the religious details but suffice it to say I am a religious man and it is an eight day celebration where we get together with members from all over the world to worship God and fellowship with each other. It is the highlight of our year because we get to see friends and family that we might not see at any other time of year due to money or time constraints. It is also a time to meet new people and make new friends. 

My wife and I knew that we were going to try to start a family in the next year so we really wanted to have a huge, last-hurrah kind of Feast before a child made it more difficult to do the long over-sea flights. Anyway, we always wanted to go to Ireland so when the site opened up we were the first to register and, thankfully, we were accepted. 

Our good friend Tim (who goes to our church) is part Irish and thought it would be a great experience so he tagged along with us on our adventure. He is a single guy with a good job so he said he would rent a car and we would be able to drive all over instead of being stuck doing the tours that our church sets up. For those who have done group tours you know why we wanted to skip out on them. Old smelly buses filled to maximum capacity lurching along bumpy streets at a slower than snails pace.

Renting a car was a mistake. 

We made a connector to Chicago OHare and from there directly to Dublin, Ireland. The flight was overnight and uneventful, but gorgeous. I had never gone out of the country (going to borderlands in Mexico really doesnt count) so I was thrilled to fly over the ocean and across the island of Ireland. I stared out the window the entire time! We landed safely and got right into our rental car to head west. For those unfamiliar with Ireland, Dublin is pretty close to the middle of the eastern coast. There is a highway that cuts directly across the country called the M4/M6. This is the route we took to Galway.

We were exhausted by the time we crossed the island but excited to see a cool new city in a cool new country. There is a show based out of Galway that Tim watched so he wanted to check it out and the university there. We poked around, found an *amazing* breakfast place right on the bay and after a few hours of walking and taking pictures we headed back into the car to drive south along the coast to the Cliffs of Moher. We stopped at castles, caves, all the amazing things that we planned out months ahead of time. 

Nothing disappointed! Everything we did and saw and experienced was the most amazing thing, until the next place, and then the next. How could a place be so beautiful? Anyway I am rambling so Ill skip ahead to when the unnerving encounters begin. We spent an entire day on the west coast doing stuff and now had to drive back across the country to our hotel in Ashbourne. Ashbourne is a little city to the north of Dublin so we had quite a ways to go. 

At this point we had been awake for 30 hours straight and feeling incredibly worn down. My phone was dying so I could only use it sparingly for GPS (I had a wall charger but not a car charger) but we had a paper map and used that with great luck so far. Looking back this whole thing could have been avoided if I just took us into the Dublin circle, M50, and then taken the Ashbourne exit but I was trying to save us the cost of the toll and some time so I mapped out a path through the suburbs. 

What I didnt realize, and you may not either unless you have experienced it first hand, is that some of the roads on the map only exist during certain times during the year. Sometimes they are flooded out, sometimes they are closed off so that herds can move freely between pastures. And sometimes the road is just so narrow you would do better classifying it as a hiking trail and should have no business being marked on a road map of the country. 

As I am sure you are now guessing some of the roads that I chose to go on for our merry little shortcut ended up being non-existent or too narrow to go down. As soon as our first road failed us just outside of Kilcock we pulled over and assessed the map, trying to get our bearings and see what we needed to do. Upon finding a suitable new route we headed off. It is now just past 11PM and the streetlights are very sparse. Reading road signs is incredibly difficult due to the fog that has rolled in and we are in a new country with no real directional bearings. We somehow went the wrong way and end up in Enfield so we turn around and once past Kilcock we find ourselves on a new road that leads us to Maynooth. Crap.

Maynooth was east and we needed to go north. How the heck did that happen? The fog is really settling in on us now and by the time we pass Kilcock for the third time and make it into Enfield for the second we are getting frustrated and just want to get to the hotel. It was about this time when I began to notice the people. No one seemed to move or change since the last time we were passing through. I shrugged it off, reasoning that most people look the same outside of a bar, and we turned around to try again. 

It is past midnight by this point and the headlights arent doing much for us against the fog. We keep trying a different fork in the road but somehow end up at the same three places: Maynooth to the east, Kilcock in the center and Enfield to the west. Our tempers are flaring up and our stomachs are growling and the map is starting to become illegible from all the folding and unfolding. The fourth time we pass the same bar I get that feeling again, this time because they all seem to be looking at us as we rumble on by. I am sure if you witnessed the same car go by a few times in the span of now almost two hours you would probably look as well but what got to me was the fact that their faces seemed to just blend in to the fog. Like they were part of it. I witnessed no life in their gazes and the hairs on my body stood on end. I kept this all to myself so as to not freak out my wife (she is pretty much the most easily scared person on the planet) and instead issued a silent prayer. 

It wasnt a long prayer, or even a particularly eloquent one. It was just desperate. Tim, who had been driving this entire time and was starting to really lose his composure veered off onto what looked like a very county, very non-helpful road. We went up a hill, down the hill, and began a long ascent up another. As we rounded the corner a man materialized in front of us with a dog on a leash. I cant say for sure whether or not he just appeared or it seemed that way because of the fog but one second he wasnt there and the next he was. His dog sat down without a single command and he waved to us as we slowed to a stop next to him. 

We began to ask for directions to Ashbourne but he was already giving them. They were perfect. He had us going on tiny little roads, some looked like driveways, two gravel ruts with grass in between, but without fail fifteen minutes later we were greeted with a welcome sign to the city. 

Another few minutes of driving led us to a Chinese restaurant that also served pizza and after that our hotel. When it was all said and done we had been awake for almost 40 hours straight. Ive never slept better in my entire life. 

I am not sure what is was that we experienced that night. You hear stories of evil forces trying to separate you from your faith and make you doubt, make you waver. Maybe that is what was going on. Maybe we were directed out of that forever-loop by an angel. Or maybe it was just a foggy night in Ireland and a really bad map. Either way I urge you to always stick to the highways.

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooooooooooooo please :( give her a chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The former, however it wasn't executed well enough. Thank you for the comments! Always learning, always improving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Maybe my small revision helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I definitely need to revise it. It is funny how it can be so clear as the author yet not clear to anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is nothing like a mother's milk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *suckle*

*suckle*

*puuuUUrrRRR*

"He loves his momma, yes indeed. Such a sweet, innocent face. There isn't a thing more beautiful than those rosy red cheeks and pert pouty lips glistening with sweet milk and mothers tears." 

*suckle*

*suckle*

*pop*

She cringes in pain. He always suckles so hard and pulls away so fast. Nipples swollen and chapped, not quite bleeding yet. 

"I'll be back for lunch. "

*footsteps move toward the door, it opens and closes*

*chains rattle and clink*

"He loves his momma, yes indeed. Such a sweet, innocent face. There isn't a thing more beautiful than those rosy red cheeks and pert pouty lips glistening with sweet milk and mothers tears."

*sobbing*

*rattle*

*rattle*

"He loves his momma, yes indeed. Such a sweet, innocent face. There isn't a thing more beautiful..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as a cat plays with its prey... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are hope. You are courage. You are strength. You will succeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are welcome! I have a few stories on nosleep if you are interested :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh? I've never played the games so I'll have to look it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I'm glad you liked the story

2. I woke up last night around 2am and the thought popped into my head. No idea why. I definitely could expand on it but I kind of like the mystery of it as a single moments look into something sinister. 

Maybe I will, maybe I won't. We shall see how many more 2am thoughts I get :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your brain. It is beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok cool that makes sense. I am brand new to this sub so you know, don't want to go breaking rules right away :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start to masturbate furiously. That oughta straighten out the little creep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you naughty rule-breaker, you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to but you know, no "Part 2's" allowed ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh the way she eats that apple... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You were saying?](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/56rsx2/we_cant_go_back_into_space_until_logan_masterson/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These kinds of things frustrate me so badly. Please stop championing things that you are not practicing on your own. You give a bad name to those who do but don't have the same voice as you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Matrix. I kept rethinking everything about life. Is this real? *Is this real?!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are in desperate need of a car/bike/Wheelie shoes. Anything but Lyft. I have a feeling you'll be seeing Sheri sooner than you'd like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have now added a (hopefully) more improved and easier to follow set of links at the top of the posts as well as a link at the bottom of each post to the next part. The only one that will not link to the next part is the one I did not write and therefore have no control over. It is "13" in the top list. Come back here to be able to move to 14. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human - the other pink meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize for the confusion. This is the "end" as it follows Patient 314. There is a side story that a friend wrote which is the "related" link and then there are past entries by Dr. Feldman that give background information to the facility and its roots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The end of his life, but not the end of his usefulness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perspectives change when you are tricked into killing your own mother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. I have no started working on it yet but I think I was to rearrange some of the sequencing to make it flow better and fill in more backstory, details, etc.

What do you think of the title options? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be. You might be in that room some day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hit home with me. Not in a "I murdered my wife" kind of way but I understood the hopelessness he felt. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome work with the bot. This is a great way to find stories we might have missed. I am enjoying this Sub a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha Steve might throw the reader for a loop, that is for sure. Thank you for the feedback. I'll keep it in mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure why but I almost vomited when I read this. It just got to me. Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate to this so badly. When I get into a new hobby or video game or book I become obsessed and I don't want to stop until I have finished the game or book. I don't want to do anything else except that new hobby. My wife HATES IT so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tour Guide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On your left you will see ten complete strangers living in a room. They will remain together in the room for one week or until only one person is left. Inside of the room is one chair, one bed, and one book. Typically there will be one homosexual, one criminal, one hippie, and one corporate executive among the ten people. Of course we have done studies were each individual was of the same job type, sexual preference, religion, and so on, however the results seldom vary. On average a group lasts thirty one hours. Interesting side note  when we put ten cult leaders together in the room they lasted longer than any other group at eighty seven hours.

As you can see this particular group is entering the eleventh hour and already groups have formed. Ah, subject 10 has begun fighting with subject 8 over the book. Lets see what happens, shall we? This is the third fight over the book already between these two. It could get ugly this time. Oh my, subject 10 broke a leg off of the chair and is waving it at subject 8. You may want to look away, the rage in her eyes is  ok yes she drove the chair leg into his neck. 

You would think that knowing they were being watched would change their behavior but it doesnt. We just hate each other so much, dont we? Now if youll step this way and look to your right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool concept! Thanks for making this. Just a quick comment about the bot - the link to the subreddit was incorrect. Here is what my message looked like:

Congratulations! Your story, Patient 314 has a name - Part 2, has been selected with a Bot Score of 130.0, to the NoSleepers subreddit.
This subreddit is designed to find the hidden gems on NoSleep. You can visit the subreddit at /r/NoSleepersI am just a bot

The "I" in I am just a bot was part of the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure not a problem!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the top of the story there are links. Click on "related" to view 315's story which outlines his ability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have withstood many things these past few weeks. Sometimes a man just need closure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little advice and feedback please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello my new friends. I have been lurking on NoSleep for quite some time enjoying all of your stories and just recently began writing my own. I just submitted the final section (for a while anyway) to my Patient 314 series and I am going to begin turning it into a short story to publish. If you are unfamiliar with it go take a [look](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/) and then you, too, can offer advice! That link is to the first part.

My *first question* is to those familiar with the story what do you think is the best title for the short story? I have a few options.

Patient 314 (obvious, well-known, boring)

Inhuman Potential (the one I am leaning toward the most)

Maybe you have thought of one better?

-------------

My *second question* concerns the linearity of the story. I am pretty sure I want to change things around in the book so that it makes a little more sense as you read it as opposed to the order in which I posted it. What do you think?

Please let me know! And if this is the wrong place for my question send me in the right direction. Thanks friends! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks will do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to post at about the same time every day but now I just post whenever I am done. I figure if people like it they will find it regardless of the time of day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 has a name - Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Chapter 1** | [1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/) | [2]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/) | [3]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/) | [4]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/) | [5]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/) | [6]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/) | [7]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/) | [8]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/) | [9]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/) | [10]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/) | [11]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u0d4q/site_2/) | [12]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u7lf7/patient_314_final/)

**Chapter 2** | [13](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u9s1m/hide_seek_with_dr_feldman/) | [14](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5vt6ud/patient_zero_origins/) | [15](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5w0734/thanksgiving_with_dr_feldman/) | [16](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wotm6/patient_11/) | [17](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x4373/patient_98_the_surgeon/) | [18](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5y1fk7/patient_314_has_a_name/) | [19](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yhiy6/patient_314_has_a_name_part_2/)

-----------

Spring is a beautiful time of year. I had never witnessed it first hand before so to you this revelation might seem a bit odd but we all have little times like these in our lives, right? When we stop and smell the roses so to speak. The cruel, cold death of winter faded before my eyes as new blooms opened and greeted the warm sun rays. Skinny trees began to fill out with new foliage that provide cover to the nests high up near the tops. 

Our train sped along in the general direction we needed to go and I sat back enjoying a process I hoped to witness more than just once. This was my spring  a new life ready to bloom.

Sandman snapped me out of my reverie with a question. *Do you have a plan?*

I do, I said. But I cant tell you what it is, and you need a plan of your own that I cant know either.

We both need plans. But neither of us can know each others plan? Why?

I chuckled softly before explaining. Zero can read minds, yes? And presumably has perfected using whatever he gained from my DNA by now, yes? So therefore he can read our minds, know our plans, and quite possibly kill us without even moving. Not only that but he has a device that inhibits my ability to kill him with my mind or read his thoughts.

Sandman just stared at me for a moment before punching the wall of the train. So basically we cant beat him and we are just walking towards imminent death? Great.

I laughed hard at that. I mean really laughed. He probably thought I was utterly insane, like the Joker in the original Batman movie, because I just kept laughing. Tears filled my eyes and my stomach ached. It felt good to laugh. Wiping away the tears and the smile on my face I allowed myself a somber tone once again.

We can beat him. We will beat him. But you cant know how I am going to do it. Where did Matt tell us to meet him?

Sandman pulled out his phone and pulled up a message from a few hours before. *I dont know how much longer I can hold out here. He gets closer every day. Im hiding in the subway systems under Cincinnati.*

I sat in silence the rest of the way pondering what the most effective scenario might be. More accurately I stared out the window watching trees and hills blur by while hoping I looked like I was deep in thought. 

Does Matt know Im alive?

No, Sandman said. He just thinks I am coming to try and help him escape.

Good. Dont tell him anything. If Zero is catching up to him we need to use Matt as bait. Well need to meet Matt in a place that will ensure Zero is there when we get there. How do we do that? He is in the subway. Is he just jumping cars all the time? Lets bring up a map of the subway.

Sandman grabs his phone and types away for a while before a concerned look crosses his face. The subway has been abandoned for years. It is just Matt down there hiding like a rat.

My face must have lit up like a Christmas tree when I heard that. Even better. All alone, no witnesses, no worries about innocent casualties. How long until we can get there, do you think?

----------------

The train came to a gentle stop at the end of its track and we stepped off. As soon as my feet hit the dusty, worn-down platform the train vanished. It didnt speed off in the opposite direction. It simply vanished. I put my hand out and groped around for the door frame I just passed through and my fingers wrapped around the cool metal. Convenient.

Sandman was shaking his head in a way that suggested he should expect such things and not be surprised anymore but cant help it. We exchanged broad grins and walked a few miles before hiring an Uber to take us into the city.

We ate a quick bite at a food truck while we waited for an opening to slip down into the subway entrance that was blocked off. Once no one was paying much attention we ducked under the boards and made our way down the wide stairs. Graffiti covered the walls leading down and I assumed continued on throughout the whole tunnel but light only made it a few feet beyond the last stair. 

Do you get signal down here? I asked.

The phone lights up and he nods to me.

Tell Matt to meet us in this tunnel and to cover you in his goop so you look like one of his creations. Zero wont think to read your mind and thus youll be safe. Once you are covered just mimic what the others do. Got that?

Sandman nods again, this time with less conviction.

We head further into the tunnel until we reach a fork with three other main tunnels converging and I hopped down into the track to hide and wait. A faint light lets me know Sandman got a message back and soon he peeks his head over the edge in search of me. 

Matt is on his way and Zero and about twenty Faceless are hot on his trail.

Perfect, hide up against the wall and wait until you are inked. Try to think of nothing, literally nothing. The fear is evident in his eyes so I give a thumbs up and whisper I promise we will be ok.

His head slowly retreats and a few faint footsteps later we are immersed in silence. A car horn honks now and again on the streets above. I reach out with my mind and try to implant confidence and strength into Sandman. Soon murmurs and footsteps reach our ears. Each noise echoing lightly toward us. Then louder, louder. More steps, more echoes. It sounds like hundreds of people rushing toward us. The footfalls are crashing off of the circular walls now, pounding through me. My heart begins to race, rattle, pound, thump, revolt against me. Then silence. 

I hear a whisper, then another. Now a steady march of footfalls echo in unison toward us. Zero.

I make my way cautiously around the curve of the recessed track hoping to end up behind Zero as he faces off with Matt and his black army. 

Tired of running, Patient 315? It is my voice, with a sneer to it, and slightly deeper.

Instead of responding I hear a large commotion of motion caused I can only assume by Matt and his minions. I peek up over the edge to gauge the right time. Inches from my face are the heels of Zero! I contemplate grabbing him and pulling him down but the noise above me sends my heart racing once again and I can feel my strength fading. Did Zero just clutch his chest for a moment? 

Gathering my strength and courage I take a step back and leap up behind Zero, my hands grasping firmly to his jaw and forehead and a satisfying snap silences everyone. Faceless turn to me, Matt drops to his knees gasping for breath, Sandman shakes free of the inky gunk covering his body. All at once the Faceless run toward me and drop at my feet. Strength flows from my heart to my fingers and toes. 

No one said anything. After all of that what was there to say? I nodded my head, scooped up Zero and began to walk away.

Harrison, what are you doing? cried Sandman.

Research.

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The red pill or the blue pill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it wasn't your face, not yet. You didn't let them change you completely and for that I admire you. Could I have been strong enough to repel the temptation that awaited? I know not. But you did. 

Make the most of your new debt-free life and do some good. Pay it forward, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am confused about that as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I got back, u47284u had sent me a message saying, "Where'd you go? Hope nothing strange happened." I ignored it and asked what it was HolyMoses did. He said, fine, he'd tell me.

WHY DO PEOPLE IGNORE SUCH THINGS?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the constant support!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When whatever happens happens I'll definitely share. Or Zero will if we fail, I suppose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whose?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that is what I'm referring to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm topless ladies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! I can't say my life is much different yet but hopefully soon I can have a somewhat normal existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. It feels good to be interacting with you again, my friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harrison, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was coming here to suggest Tommy Taffy as well. Good call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'll buy that for a dollar." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't possibly answer that question. If I could I would be able to admit it to myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how does it feel knowing you slept on the grave of a murdered woman while the serial killer watched you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He saw me look and then opened the jacket. I don't remember anything after that. 

That must have been some penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the warning! I shall promptly remove all mirrors in my home and flip off everyone who thinks I look unkempt or have a booger hanging down. It is all about survival, yall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be a manticore or gryphon since it has wings. Do sphinx have wings? 

I wonder if it came from the rock or came to the rock because of what the rock is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it is only visible via a mirror. Either way you need to settle this once and for all. Noodles is there with you. Charge that door and figure it out, yo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You somehow managed to break every law of horror movies/stories. Achievement Unlocked!

I truly hope you are safe and they catch this guy/demon/entity. Good luck OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is some sort of conditioning going on here. When he saw the guy in the mask he started laughing like crazy. You need to try to get more information out of Klay because he clearly knows more. If the man who recruited him bragged every day I am certain that he mentioned something, anything, that would be helpful. 

For now you could use the info of over 300 buildings to see if an individual or company owns that many buildings along the east coast. 

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 has a name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Chapter 1** | [1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/) | [2]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/) | [3]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/) | [4]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/) | [5]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/) | [6]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/) | [7]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/) | [8]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/) | [9]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/) | [10]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/) | [11]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u0d4q/site_2/) | [12]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u7lf7/patient_314_final/)

**Chapter 2** | [13](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u9s1m/hide_seek_with_dr_feldman/) | [14](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5vt6ud/patient_zero_origins/) | [15](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5w0734/thanksgiving_with_dr_feldman/) | [16](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wotm6/patient_11/) | [17](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x4373/patient_98_the_surgeon/) | [18](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5y1fk7/patient_314_has_a_name/) | [19](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yhiy6/patient_314_has_a_name_part_2/)

--------------

I awoke in a haze and wracked with pain from head to toe. I havent felt like this in how long had it been? Days? Weeks? I honestly have no idea how long I was kept in that room. 

There was an extreme pressure on my wrist. I was being pulled, dragged actually. Unbearable light penetrated my eyeballs and the squeak of my bare heels dragging along the clean linoleum floors sent horrible pains through my eardrums. It was almost too much to bear, however I had come too far and endured too much to give in now. 

Mashing my eyelids together to block out the light I gathered my strength and pushed off of the floor while twisting. The grip on my wrist loosened, then broke. I had taken my captor by surprise and didnt hesitate to capitalize on it. My hands leapt forward and groped for purchase, finding a familiar medium to mold. With a twist the neck snapped and strength flowed through me. I opened my eyes and let go of the Faceless tasked with my disposal. 

I took in my surroundings, trying to determine where in Site 2 I was. Eventually I just wandered around until I found the central loft that I was familiar with and headed up to the top. Fortunately I ran in to a few more Faceless along the way which helped build my strength back up. At last I came upon a large door that opened up and beautiful, natural sunlight filtered down from ten flights above me. I climbed up the metal stairs and was greeted by the train that brought me from Site 1. 

A sound caused me to duck and dive behind the nearest cover, which wasnt much, just a metal railing. Someone was poking around in the train. I couldnt quite make out the face but I didnt recognize his features as anyone I had encountered during my experiments. He was young and moved with an uncertainty as if he wasnt quite sure what he was looking for. I sat crouched down and watched as he made his way to my end of the train. If he was going to exit out of the train he would spot me instantly so I moved, low to the ground, over to the doors and waited for an opening. 

It was at this point that I realized how stupid I was being. Why not just read the guys mind and see what he wants? I focused on him, searching for the information I needed. He was from Reddit! It seemed like so long ago when I was posting my experiments to that site. Feldman must have taken over my account and continued posting. Why the hell would he do that? Ego, I guess. Anonymous notoriety? Karma? That stuff is a bit addictive once you get a taste. This guy knew just about everything that had gone on with me in that place. 

I broke the connection and stood up. At that exact moment he lifted his head up from the control panel of the train and we made eye contact. I didnt have to read his mind to know he peed his pants a little. The look on his face was enough. 

**314** - Its ok, I know you are on my side. You know me as Patient 314.

**Reddit Guy** - I, uh, umm hey. How can I be sure you are you and not Dr. Zero?

**314** - If I were Dr. Zero why would I be hiding in my own train station? And if I were Dr. Zero I would have just sent up a few Faceless to kill you or bring you down for testing. 

**RG** - I suppose that is true. I guess we will just have to trust each other, right?

**314** - Right. Why did you come here? More importantly, how did you find it?

**RG** - It is kind of a long story but there are a lot of people rooting for you. Feldman and Zero are monsters and we all want to help. I figured I would try to put some pieces together. Hey, umm, I dont really want to call you Patient 314 so whats your name?

**314** - My name. Yea that is probably the one thing you dont know. [extends a hand] I am Harrison. Nice to meet you.

**Sandman** - Im /u/Sandman9913. Lets get out of here. You have a lot to catch up on. 

Sandman handed me his phone with the Reddit app open and I began to read all of the posts that Dr. Feldman and later, Dr. Zero, made on my account. 

------------------------------

I cant begin to describe what I felt as I read about what had happened to me. Surreal just doesnt cut it. I never knew the doctors thought process during the testing and that was quite enlightening. The guy was smart, Ill give him that. The origins threw me for a loop, though. Area 51? Aliens? I am sure there is a lot more we dont know about and maybe one day Ill come back and try to learn some of them.

I admit it. I cried when I read about my mother. That sick bastard screwed with my head more than I thought was possible. The one thing that helped as I read each entry was the comments. So many people hating on Feldman and Zero. So many hoping the best for me. Sandman went so far as to search for me and another guy even challenged Zero. Not smart, Ill admit, but admirable. After reading everything I just had one question for Sandman.

**Harrison** - You read that last entry right? 

**Sandman** - Yea I read all of them, why?

**Harrison** - At the end of it Zero killed me, or at least he thought he did. What made you think Id still be alive?

**Sandman** - I dont know, man. I guess I just couldnt believe that after everything it would end that way. But, like, why didnt you die?

**Harrison** - A very good question. I am not sure if I truly know the answer but my guess is that Zero wasnt very thorough when he absorbed my information and my condition made it seem like I was dead. For all intents and purposes I do die each time I get stimulation overload but for whatever reason the end result of death doesnt come. Maybe I cant die, not fully. Maybe I am already dead. [I look out the window of the train, watching the scenery fly by] So where are we headed now?

**Sandman** - We are going to find Zero and save [Patient 315.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yhiy6/patient_314_has_a_name_part_2/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't put that information here but I can PM you if you would like to set up a consultation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at those coordinates on Latlong.net and you are right, just wilderness for miles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not see that coming. Ugh.... now I am going to be freaked out by my daughter when I get home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm crunchy dill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not ALL people. Just everyone but you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your wish is my command.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might just do that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he was dressed as a common farmer to the area. I believe him to have been a good spirit/angel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most certainly!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your PM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah! I'll try to figure out those symbols and get back to you. Good luck and go shower my man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
