<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7254</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right in saying there's no proof that a higher power has helped history at all. But I like to think of all the horrible things that happen as opportunity. 

Example: My dad was diagnosed with cancer a few months back. My mom said, "This made me remember how much I love your father." You go through daily life, thinking, yeah, I love my SO. But that was a push to get her to really remember everything he does for us. Plus, he's almost cured now. So this has given him the opportunity to say, "I kicked Cancers ass!" Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean the God(s) have helped very little or religion has helped very little? Just some clarification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that is something I hate as well. Some sects of Christianity, for example, really do just that and makes me mad. It seems they forgot Jesus's number one rule: love everyone. They cling more to the Old Testament laws than the ones Jesus described. Last time I checked, women, gays, blacks, etc. are all a part of everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atheists of Reddit, can you please tell us all what problems you have with religion? Religious people of Reddit (whether you be Christian, Jewish, Muslim, or Pagan, it doesn't matter) can you explain any misconceptions or confirm their problems? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 01:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am religious. However, I love learning about all peoples beliefs. Let's have a civil discussion. No hating. No harsh words. Let's learn from each other. No one has all the answers. 

EDIT: keep in mind when I answer some of these things with some of my beliefs, I may use God and Love as synonyms. I essentially worship Love. Which means I simply try to live a life of Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My question: Has anyone actually made it through the game without dying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 19:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw an achievement on XBox for making it through the game without dying. I'm not gonna even try for it. Has anyone gotten it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What funny thing makes you horny? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 18:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to tag [serious] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Xenomorph v. The Hulk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 21:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most relieving moment you've ever had playing a video game? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is called a Rear-Naked Choke. You learn it in Judo, Brazilian Jiu Jitsu, and several other grappling arts. Very effective. Hold the choke for about 10 seconds, they lose consciousness. About 20, they're dead. 

TL;DR: you should take up BJJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 05:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came from the North Korean version of the man himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 02:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hangin wit dat hoe Mary Magdalane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 02:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smite humanity I don't agree with. Appalled with modern interpretations... Right on the money. 

"Love everyone."

Last time I checked, gays are a part of "everyone" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 02:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that would mean Jesus is a vampire. He's drinking his own blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that according to the Bible, Jesus only got mad once. In the Temple. He proceeded to flip over tables. 

So next time someone asks you, "What would Jesus do?" Remember that flipping tables is a viable option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would Jesus do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 02:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let it begin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood what's the big deal about that? Isn't it polite to thank someone for spending their money on you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, let me redraw her then lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/Dl5Aa15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was his/her name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This work?

http://imgur.com/N1v7HEC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I feel like drawing something. Can you give me an idea? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something crazy. Anything. I'll upload it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 16:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will someone please photoshop a Brazzers logo on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 05:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sub is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cartman would fuck

Shit

Up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An army (5000) of orphans vs. 20 nuns armed with rulers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy how even people with Down syndrome can learn to kick ass

http://youtu.be/kgYjeHsuHac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you nearly fuck up your future? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DILDO! DILDO! DILDO!

In the voice of the Minions from Despicable Me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Fuck you particles with mass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the biggest middle finger of the universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 05:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/cutefemalecorpses

For the record, don't click on that. It's horrible. Just thought it was relevant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The anal rapist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 04:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first cartwheel kick in a Taekwondo match. Landed it out of nowhere. Didn't even know it happened till I watched the video. 

"Dafuq? Did I just do that?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 19:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say you should ask for their blessing. That way if they say no, you don't have to look at your girl and say, "your parents said we couldn't get married..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. I've never heard of G cups. I thought it only went to DD. You've skipped E and F. 

Do they hurt when you run or do you like.... I don't know how else to say this. Are you in danger of knocking yourself out? Not being disrespectful at all lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You always hear how guys want monster dicks, but I assume it would make sex nearly impossible unless you were sleeping with a professional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mind me asking how big we're talking here? Like, if they're big enough you can't sleep on your back or run, I'm imagining some monster tits lol. What are the dangers of running with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women are beautiful creatures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men with micropenis/a huge penis, and women with tiny/huge breasts, what are the pros and cons? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: Shrek is Love. Shrek is Life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM IMMORTAL!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter, died having sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any time Jesus took a dump, was it technically a holy shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jess take the wheel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Satan is an awesome Satan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What word can you replace in a religious song title to make it NSFC (Not Safe For Church)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 17:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite urban dictionary entries? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Shelby's vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She saved my life. 

I suffered from severe depression and anxiety, as well as ADHD and Asperger's syndrome, though we didn't know about the latter till a year later. 

I was in fourth grade, and after being bullied horribly for a good portion of my life, I was home alone one day. I went into the kitchen, saying I was gonna cut my throat with a knife. 

Didn't go through with it for whatever reason. Ran to my room, cried. Prayed to God, "Why are you doing this to me! I hate my life! I just want a friend."

Two weeks later, this girl in my class sits down next to me while I'm reading Harry Potter and starts a big HP conversation with me. I'm startled she's talking to me, but whatever, she'll leave soon. 

Same thing happened over next few days. I ask why she's hanging around me. 

"I want to be your friend stupid," she said with a big smile. 

She remained my best friend even now that we're seniors in high school. She helped me deal with a lot of my issues with Aspergers, like teaching me social stuff. By being my friend, she gave me a reason to live. 

I got a crush on her in fifth grade. Realized I loved her by the end of eighth. I stayed in love with her till a little over a year ago. I loved her for eight years. I still love her, just not *in* love with her. 

We've already decided we're not ever gonna stop being friends. We never dated. She currently has a boyfriend. And I'm happy for her. She's my best friend. 

TL;DR: Give autistics a freaking chance people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the kid on his lap. 

Keep in mind I have Aspergers Syndrome and ADHD. When I was 5-6, it was particularly bad, and I wasn't on medication and hadn't even gotten the diagnoses yet. I sat on his lap, noticed the elastic holding the beard to his face, and ripped it off. Shouted, "YOU'RE NOT SANTA!"

TL;DR: Made a bunch of kids cry in the mall, and I believe I saw tears from Santa as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That... Is pretty weird.

That being said, I'd try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most creative/worst thing you've ever eaten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 18:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides my mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 03:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it like to be boring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by holding in a fart too long. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 02:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first opportunity, I let it out. 

All at once. 

It's not bleeding, but it hurts like a motherfucker.

TL;DR: I nearly rent my butthole asunder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 21:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't mean it's what I want to do. I will study physical therapy, but my dream is to be a fighter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'll pee in a public restroom if necessary, but I'll never shit in one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no luck in Isolation. I play with friends. It's the only way we can actually get anywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutting sausage with a butter knife. 

Well there's your problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro, Colliseum was my first game. I'm now forever enamored with Eeveelutions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have yet to actually play it, but I've seen my friend. It's just about good old fashioned decapitation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stabbed myself with a butter knife once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooooo much decapitation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World War III is imminent, you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instructions unclear. Brought food to restaurant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I last played Alien Isolation... Sorry guys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last video game you played is now reality. Is the world better or worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umbreon is the shit, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Predalien </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my preferred college had that. I don't think it even has a wrestling team. But it has a fantastic program for Bio and Athletic science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already plan on studying those subjects. For exactly the reasons you described. My parents want me to be a physical therapist, but I don't think I can do that. That's not what makes me happy. 

The idea of being an athletic trainer appeals to me more, but I'd prefer to be the athlete. 

I've decided I'll go to college to make my parents happy, but I'll train MMA on the side to see where it takes me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And out. And in. And out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really scared, just don't want to go. 

I don't think I can handle much more school. I just want to follow my dream of being a professional Mixed Martial Artist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll often look at doctrines of different religions, Christian and Pagan, and find the similarities between them. Then I formulate my own beliefs. I'm a very different kind of Catholic lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with amputations or who were born without limbs, what do the rest of us take for granted? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly administered by Wolverine (if you're in to that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, let me rephrase that:

I love discussing philosophy, but I know very few philosophers. I mostly spend my time thinking and end up making connections between many seemingly separate aspects of existence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bitch Irene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philosophy. I love it when I find that person who can actually follow my train of thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jizz in my Pants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manly as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And cries during...

I feel so dark now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only person who never uses public restrooms? I only poop at home. Any time I poop, I also pee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are playground STD's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would probably be a win for everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed it last year in my Bio II class. "So wait, we were ALL assholes at one point?"

Teacher laughed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then there's that one girl. 

Sure, other girls you might have fleeting ideas of what it would be like to have sex with them, then you go back to simply appreciating their beauty. 

But that one girl. 

That girl that seems to make everything better. 

That girl where the idea of sex and love are completely inseparable. 

That girl that you feel the need to protect with your last breath. 

That girl who you want to cry on your shoulder. 

That girl who would let you cry on her shoulder. 

That girl you wouldn't care if she saw you cry. 

That girl who makes you happy and sad at the same time. 

That girl that makes you sad because you know she deserves better than you. 

That girl that makes you happy because she chose you anyway. 

That girl. 

The one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm not talking to anyone and I'm sitting there staring into space with a deep thoughtful look, I come up with things that belong on /r/showerthoughts

Seriously, I love philosophy, I love the idea of questions that just really make you think. I love finding meaning in the most insignificant details. There must be meaning in everything. From things like religion and mythology to science and art, I love combining them all into one cohesive subject. I find the things that link them all together and my thoughts snowball from there. 

I think we can blame it on my ADHD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans are deuterostomes. This means that during pregnancy, when the cells are dividing, the first orifice that develops is the anus. So technically we are all assholes at some point in life. Some people just develop further

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get rid of the other guys evolutionarily with four simple words...

YOU WANNA GO BRO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. He solved the problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier this year I was in a martial arts tournament. In my fight, I used a kick called a wheel spin kick. It's essentially a jumping spinning kick that lands with a heel to the head. The guy backed up, front kicked up the middle. The force of my spin combined with his kick equalled immense pain. Ref stopped the fight to let me recover. He looked at me and said, "I know you're not ok, but are you ok?" 

Thank God for my cup. I finished my fight and won my division in the tournament. 

TL;DR: I got power-nutted and dropped like a sack of potatoes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And women always take our in-come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless one of the girls insults the other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 05:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What logic? We do what's fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 18:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [VIDEO] A Shadow of Mordor Video where the decapitated Orc says something hilarious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 07:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember where I saw it. The Orc said something along the lines of, "I will only come back stronger" after being decapitated. If you know what I'm talking about, please link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know those feels :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's further down in the thread lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight, we raid Ikea. They have our precious ammunition. After that, the used sex shop. Biological warfare is the key to our success. Bastards won't know what hit them till they're up to their necks in crabs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who wants twigs and berries anyways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad cow disease  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you say you're female? *eyebrow raise*

Upvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 04:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tag-team Redditting. Very nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Jesus will help with this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wastelands by Linkin Park

Should instill hope I believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend showed me the Cumbox post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is not a lot of peace was held that day. I've never seen that happen, but I really do imagine things would be awkward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best pic/gif of corndog(s) you've ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kid back in school were you glad got expelled? What did he/she do? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 21:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 15:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean like a fridge box. The one he lived in. He ate his house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 04:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was about 10, on Halloween I was trick or treating. My parents told me to stay away from this one culdasac (spelling?). I later learned this is because drugs were sold down there. Didn't listen. Regret it. 

TL;DR: Looked through window on Halloween, saw fat man jerking it while wearing bra and panties.

Edit: OH! Best experience! Sorry, just reread that. Thought it said weirdest... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 04:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, it makes it less heavy and stressful. Knowing you've got your friends there and you can turn to them to help figure out problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you suck the least at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 04:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice I didn't say good at. What do you suck at, but could be worse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 04:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to New York when I was 11. Saw a homeless dude eating his own box.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 22:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little over 3 years ago, freshman year of high school, I started martial arts training. It has absolutely changed my life. I had very little self esteem (though more than I had in the early years of my life) and martial arts gave me a ton of confidence. 

Of course, we all have to start somewhere. You're not gonna go to one class and suddenly be Bruce Lee. It takes time, effort, and practice. It's a fantastic way to fill your time. It's somewhat addicting. 

You get fitter, you learn self defense, you have fun. It's awesome. Plus, sparring sessions, whether you do a striking art or a grappling art, boost your confidence. Something primal about combat that all humans understand and get an adrenaline rush from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's your idea for an... Interesting alien? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Describe your extraterrestrial and get creative. /u/awildsketchappeared I would appreciate your help please :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean... Other places? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Release the Xenomorphs!

*chaos ensues* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like you :) upvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would eat a ghost chili quesadilla. That way, when they fry me in the electric chair, they have a hell of a mess to clean up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are about to be executed. What is the means of your execution and what do you eat for your final meal to mess with the executioners the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meal can either mess with them before or after the execution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the darkest Family Guy joke? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one moment that made you question why you watch it or that made you stop watching it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 01:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic question my knucklefudge friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 00:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please elaborate on what Alpha/Omega and knotting porn is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What questions do you have about a weird fetish? People with weird fetishes, can you answer these questions? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 00:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 00:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they got the vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 22:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they've just made the graphics a little better. If you look at the first series and at Yu-Gi-Oh! Zexel, you see a big difference. Kinda like the pokemon anime then and now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mines not a Pokemon card, but a Yu-Gi-Oh! card. It's a Ghost Rare "Galaxy-Eyes Tachyon Dragon". 

I hadn't played the game in years when last year my little brother comes up to me and tells me how awesome he is at Yu-Gi-Oh! I laugh, dust off my old deck, and promptly annihilate my brother. 

I started helping him build a better deck, decided to collect some of the new cards myself. In one booster pack, the dragon was there. I say, "Dafuq is this?" Do my research. Very rare copy. 

Edit: Galaxy-Eyes is also a very good card. Hard to summon, but once it's out, you essentially dominate most people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 17:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here comes Bridezilla! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 23:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes flashy works very well. Capoeira is far flashier than TKD and is very effective. Many people that I've fought in TKD don't often use the flashy stuff because it does sometimes leave you vulnerable to counterattack. I personally love the flashy stuff. I'm good at landing the flashy techniques and have a good idea for my range. You see Olympic TKD fighters use these advanced techniques because they're very technically sound with the basics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 20:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you got the lack of hand strikes idea. We work on them almost as much as kicking. 

Yes, there are complex advanced kicks, but they all stem from the basics that you learn in Muay Thai: Front kick, roundhouse, side kick, back kick, axe kicks, cresant and spin kicks. 

You learn the basics, then when you've got them down, you learn the advanced stuff. The advanced kicks are somewhat applicable in MMA, but yes, unless timing is right, takedowns will be successful. Really the advanced stuff are used more for conditioning. If you pull them off in a sparring match, extra points. 

Great for developing speed and power. Learn to react and counterattack effectively. 

The list goes on and on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly makes you say it's ineffective? Something about technique?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BDSM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try looking at Olympic TKD sparring. It's crazy what those guys do. There's a reason it's an Olympic sport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friends=missionary
Family=cowgirl
New acquaintance=doggy style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minute to win it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is no art is better than others. They all have strengths and all have weaknesses. There is more than one way to do everything and they can all be equall as effective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened on your wedding day that makes you cringe? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: guys, I'm so sorry. A lot of this stuff truly makes me cringe. Keep them coming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THESE MOVIES MAKE ME SO MAD!!!! I LOVE THEM SO MUCH!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
