<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to beat a ban? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will and we haven't even see a GOP plan yet. Just like we haven't seen the promised new travel ban.

Trump is so lost it's almost laughable, except people's lives will be ruined by his ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't asking him to be President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world is a big place, collectively it can bring the US to it's knees. Trump will lead us there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't do either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Trump will believe that and flip out. This is a roast not a serious event. We'll just play the tape of him bashing Clinton at a charity event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do in the TV industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you attack someone who is not in attendance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SNL ratings have gone through the roof thanks to Baldwin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants a war, I say give it to him. It's one he can't possibly win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has exceeded all the orders Obama did in 8 years. He'll have to take credit for destroying the environment and our water supply. 

He will be impeached and it will come from his own party. They just need to get enough on him to be sure he can't come back at them. He's a vindictive little bastard who can't stand being wrong. 

Where the hell is the new travel ban he promised last week? I would have thought he had one since he went and played golf. Everything he's done so far is a negative.

Eventually he will get the shits of his military advisers telling him how wrong he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Anyone who is an American citizen who doesn't think that Trump is their president understands we have a constitution and the fact we have no dictator. This clown can't do anything with legislation, he relies on executive orders. He doesn't want to be questioned.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who remembers when Trump attacked Hillary at a charity luncheon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a roast, not an attack. Most people can tell the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many Republicans don't believe he is their President. Do you believe the huge crowd at the women's march was all democrats?

You seem to have a real problem with black folks.

Trump will be hit with protests everyday of his life, many from Republicans who have got the shits of him as well. 

Can't wait for him to fuck up our healthcare system. Even the cops are starting to turn on him as he does not represent them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure paint with a broad brush. Are you defending the shooters? What about the people who get harassed at malls without knowing if they are US citizens or not. It's not so isolated. We have 10 million legal Muslims in this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've already had people shot after being told to "get out of my country". Uneducated Trump supporters can't even tell who belongs here and who doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has also radicalized his followers. Anyone walking down a mall who looks "different" is at risk.

Someone will die at Standing Rock before it's over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driver shot dead on Highway 4 in Antioch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't help notice the cops at Standing Rock were a lot more forceful when Trump gave them the go ahead. This will be a record year for lawsuits against police officers. Thank Trump for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure would be with all stations televising it live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calls for Trump to be replaced by Alec Baldwin after boycotting White House press dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.businessinsider.com/r-trump-decides-to-skip-white-house-press-dinner-2017-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to address nation sandbagged by record low approval rating: NBC/WSJ poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repubs promised to do just that on day 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longtime diplomat criticizes isolationism in retirement speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Trump adviser: Ryan should be replaced if he can't execute on ObamaCare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does all that have to do with the fact we have racist cops?

Can't see why they removed my comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played sports in HS with plenty of cops. Nigg@r was every other word. Cops have gotten away with murder for decades, it will only get worse as Trump emboldens them. Trump may lose many of them as they are finding out he doesn't really support them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be a youngster, this has been going since the 60's and beyond. Racist cops are everywhere, I know many of them personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never mind, I read that as "orgasms".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is spending his political capital and costing the US friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A look at the economy Trump inherited, which he calls a mess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worried of Trump Effect in Europe, Mr. Ehler Goes to Washington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you screwed up when Fox News turns on a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 13:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, the Judge that initially blocked the ban was appointed by GWB. I'm aware you  are in love with this little dictator but we are a democracy.

He won't be President for long. Pence is a creep but at least he isn't mental.

What exactly has Trump done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you didn't hear his ban was overturned and his labor guy didn't make it. His national security guy got fired.

Least effective President as hundreds of key jobs go unfilled. The crazier he gets the harder it will be to fill these positions. 

Rasmussen is right wing propaganda. Only place he is number 1 is in protests held. He's headed for impeachment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at 39%.

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/donald-trump-us-president-approval-rating-one-month-historical-low-bill-clinton-a7586931.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's pissed off most everyone. I'd say it's probable. Could be ISIS, maybe a woman or even someone with a bow and arrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans will turn on Trump when the real Russian story comes out.

You may be right, the second amendment people may get him before he's impeached.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had to withdraw the Labor nominee.  Republicans would not confirm him.

Impeachment is close at hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That number will go up under Devos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top staffs have been gutted, the people who know what they're doing. Of course the secretaries and janitors are still there.

Cabinet appointments are not automatic. He gives us lunatics and we reject them. He has the majority in Congress and still loses some of them-BAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit has nothing to do with it. National polls show this. Even many Republicans think he is bat shit insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's common knowledge.  Assange will end up in prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not like this. This is what happens when you put someone in charge of an agency they have multiple lawsuits against. Many agencies are dangerously understaffed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikileaks just threatened CNN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> State dept was gutted recently. EPA also gutted.

https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/state-department-trims-its-upper-ranks-as-tillerson-retools-personnel/2017/02/17/d6e6ee64-f52a-11e6-b9c9-e83fce42fb61_story.html?utm_term=.a058d7222b44 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is purging the agencies of all experienced workers. They will indeed collapse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie's done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence is bad but, but he is not mentally ill. Some Republicans are already calling for impeachment. They will support it if he commits a crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as long as he is around. He'll be impeached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The court said otherwise. Trump could not support the ban with facts. Trump banned only countries he didn't do business with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Muslim ban that wasn't and the Obamacare repeal that isn't happening. Plus Flynn and the labor guy that withdrew. The Russian ship off Connecticut is also worrisome since they have dirt on Trump. 

Stay tuned for more winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total chaos. A good month for the Russians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that have to do with how the IRS works? Want you home repossessed stop paying your real estate taxes. IRS is easy to bargain with, even to the point of having 80% of your tax forgiven. The IRS simply doesn't want your home. Fact! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlikely, paying taxes late can be strung out for years. The IRS is not in the real estate business. They are very slow to foreclose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By your rules we have to deport Trump's wife.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have read this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still illegal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, know my kid's greatest dream is to be a coal miner /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These people being here aren't harming anyone. This is a mentally ill president having a fit because he didn't get his way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can let someone live here for 30 years then turn around and deport them. Trump is pitching a fit. The courts are going to be jammed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most have family here, this is where their life is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seriously equaling being here to rape and murders? What happens in the mass raids, which Trump said he wouldn't do, is we inevitably end up deporting people who shouldn't be . Then they come back and sue our socks off.

I am amazed at how afraid of the world Trump supporters are. Hell, I don't even lock my car or home when I leave. 

The whole deal is Trump is pissed off his ban didn't fly and now he's throwing a fit--CHILDISH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We also handcuffed a 5 year old and questioned him for 5 hours. No, it was not proven fake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right, the government keeps their money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I donate to local charities that support them. When I give to a food bank I don't designate to whom it can go. If they're hungry they can have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump pays nothing. Immigrants also pay into SS which they will never get back. They also pay sales taxes on things they buy. They are not a net drain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kellyanne Conways dangerous game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 years later?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These illegals pay more taxes than Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The massacre at Fraggle Rock"..LOL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In emotional speech, Streep renews harsh criticism of Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What scares you about these people? Why shouldn't children in this country be allowed a visit from their Grandmother? The Grandmother that we turned away came to see her Grand-kids for the 1st time since the Iraq war and died on the return trip.-BAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly how freaky Conway is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is one hell of a national security risk, but then so is the entire Trump family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free speech is happening. They are telling them they have rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These people are their relatives, dunce. You are indeed fucking the legal immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the next headline to hit. Oops, look what we did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in your home without a warrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, "I want to see your warrant" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to do if immigration officers come knocking at your door </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a ploy to stop people from protesting against him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> California wants nothing to do with a Trump America.  California will not go for Trump's decreased regulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And we need to protect our farms from foreign competition as well. Avocados are a great example. There's no reason to let Mexico flood us with Avocados when they are in season at the same time in California. 

Avocados take a lot of water to grow. Something California is in short supply of.

You might have trouble selling that food prices need to rise.

Be careful what you wish for.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He couldn't support banning those countries with data. The ban was seen as religious, which violates our Constitution. He was also banning people who should be legally allowed in this country. The law was totally flawed and rejected by 4 judges. It didn't help him that he did it by executive order. The court also rejected that he had the power to do that.

Obama increased vetting, he didn't ban people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American workers are overrated, to use Trump's word. 

If Mexican's go back, the food will rot on the vine. Do you think today's IT guys will pick it?  Even if he reduces that work force, farmers will be forced to bid for the labor that remains and food prices will skyrocket.

You seem awful naive. Be careful what you wish for! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask the courts who rejected it. It was seen as a Muslim ban, which violates the US Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is an idiot. He is not respected by those in the military. Loose cannon would be the best description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Election results are not economic data. 

Yes, people would starve to death as amateur farmers. China could be joined by many countries. Again we are the second largest exporter in the world. Exports are critical to our country. Poor old Donald had to ask how a strong dollar affects them.

Our corporations will be hurt by the best minds going elsewhere. American workers are inferior. They lack a work ethic employers look for. There biggest worry is is it break time yet. You will be disappoint by the manufacturing jobs he brings, if any.

If anyone does return to the US they will bring the best workers in the highest paying jobs with them.

Be careful how many Mexicans you piss off, they pick your food off the vine. That next strawberry could be tainted and Trumps is cutting inspections. 

Fortunately, Trump will go down with Flynn and the Russians. This is something even the republicans care about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is no economic data then it is indeed speculation. 

If people had to do that they would starve to death.

What would happen to Boeing if China didn't buy from them? You fail to understand the value of exports to American companies. The US is the second largest exporter in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any boost by Trump is pure speculation. Earnings will drive the market. Obama's last economic report was excellent. Let's see if Trump can keep up.

Trump's import taxes could tank the market if countries retaliate, and they will.

I wonder if Trump knows the US can't feed itself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has taught us not to respect women. Look for this here

Violence is already happening in the US as Trump encourages violence against the Muslim community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump had nothing to do with the stock market. Obama's latest economic data did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try and make this one legal, Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flynn may be the one to take down Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't keep the trains we have now on the tracks. This is dangerous as Trump decreases regulations and consumer protections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with the fact that Trump has greatly scaled back his tax cuts when confronted by advisers who explained economics to the man. Your cut won't even touch the inflation this man will cause.

Best thing he could do to change that is quit making his shit overseas. His plans will cripple US corporations if other countries retaliate.  Without exports our corporations won't survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impeach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't even understand the picking grapes reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm insulting you for not understanding the difference between words and actions. Go back to your dreams in la la land. No point in talking when you aren't listening. Have a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't understand what I tell you because your face is stuck in a book.-SAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't listen to people's words unless they back them with actions. People toss out a lot of great words but don't live them. Go cuddle with your dictionaries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexicans vow to fight Trump by jamming U.S. courts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I have to define reality to you. You're such a nerd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, you chose to ignore it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You voted for violence in America? I think you mean you voted for hate. This will be the norm.

Deplorable that you laugh at people getting hurt. Amazing, but expected from a trump supporter. Impeachment is near.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trump, he has thin skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Words are just words, actions are far more important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is deplorable. They've removed the website to advise parents with kids with disabilities to find help. They don't come more deplorable than Sessions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has too since he criticized Obama for playing golf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I judge racism by how someone lives, not by some textbook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where? When? What will they pay? Will they provided benefits? That last one is crucial since trump is canceling everyone's insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been proven she worked as a model before she became legal. There's no question she came here illegally. 

 You and I disagree on the definition of racism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too little pay for me to bite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration is already doing that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The_Donald needs no defaming. They self defame. Stop the spam please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why read them when he can just hear things on the Internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
