<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9815</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was my goal too for my 10k yesterday! How did the run go in terms of km splits? Were you able to maintain a consistent pace for each one? 

I started out on track with a 29 min 5k, but then lost steam for 6-7 and tried to make it up on the back end but just couldn't get the energy to break 60 min.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried to PR my 10k time in anticipation for the 15k I'm running this weekend. So I picked a relatively flat, relatively beautiful lake to do loops around. Missed it by 1 minute and had to stop early (was hoping to get in 8 miles to satisfy my half training) because my hands were freezing. It was low 40s so I was just wearing a hoodie and the rest of my body was fine, but I could barely feel my hands by the end of it. 

Also I can't figure out how to get my Estimated Bests to appear on my Strava profile. The only one that shows is my 1k time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a long commute, so I'm up at 6:30 to catch a 7:00 am bus to be at work on time to then get back t o my city at 7:00 pm by bus. It's hard, and exhausting. I get in three miles after my bus let's me off though because that's the distance from the stop to my home. If I didn't run from the bus I'd probably run to the bus in the morning to just get those 30 minutes in. And if that wasn't possible I'd probably try to squeeze in some time at lunch time. Usually running for about 20-30 minutes gives you more energy, makes you feel better all round, I'd say just find some time in your day where you can sneak it in, and see how it makes you feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished **Swing Time by Zadie Smith** today. I've gone back and forth on whether I like it or not. Zadie is extremely verbose towards the end. Pages of a single paragraph verbose, but I like what she's trying to say... mostly. 

**The Conscious Parent by Dr. Shefali Tsabary** Just trying to be a better parent. Though this is pretty common sense stuff so far. 

**They Can't Kill Us All by Wesley Lowrey** this is due to the library tomorrow. it's only 200 pages so I might be able to finish it. (I haven't even started it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McHugh is pitching? I guess we'll see how dead his arm is still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of our minor league catchers ever work out. I have hopes for Stubbs. I don't want him to go the way of Perez, Nottingham and now Heineman. Too bad this wasn't Stassi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quintana plus a throw in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved my MS Band 2. But the strap kept tearing so I finally just got a refund  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't think we should treat any political with such reverence. Draining the swamp should mean being critical of everyone. But I agree with you. Bannon does seem more problematic, but Trumps public persona seems like an inhibition for any nefarious plot he's had so far  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Cardinals still get an honorary mention because of the hacking thing. I probably hate then more than anyone except the Rangers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he could have replaced overrated with quiet or overshadowed. He's right that with Altuve and Correa (among others) it's easy to overlook Springer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not betting against Trump just suggesting he isn't some infallible mastermind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think at some point we need to stop giving Trump credit for his failures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puerto Rico would win as soon as they became the 51st state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't anyone want to see Mike Trout?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! and yet some people still think Fowler and Ozuna (who isn't even playing CF anymore) are going to be better than him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banh Mi? That's all I can think of. I love Asian food, but when it's sushi/Vietnamese/Filipino every day and weekend it makes me miss Mexican food. I'm the only non Asian/non white person in the family and it's weird sometimes definitely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Highline is great if it's really cold or bad weather for running. All other times you will be starting and stopping as the path isn't wide enough to pass people consistently. It's supposed to rain tomorrow so you might get lucky with a space to run.

When I tried last week the extension up to 34th street/Hudson Yards was also closed because of snow pileup. Not sure if that's cleared.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I'm trying to convince my wife to go to Yankee stadium for the series here but it's Mother's Day Weekend. so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like both Busch and Wrigley have similar dimensions and are a little more shallow themselves compared to MMP and Coors. So maybe that contributed to it as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While everyone in r/baseball continues to ignore Springer and leave him off their CF rankings completely, I thought it'd be great to spread some love here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Springer: the Astros underrated Super Star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Trout's the hipster weatherman right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that makes him better than guys who are plus defenders (Kiermaier) and guys who are above average defenders with above average hitting (Springer   Yellich)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imo you are way too high on Fowler. He's average to bad defensively in Center. Not including guys with high defensive upside seems weird. Springer and Yellich are also moving over to center and project higher than a lot of guys you included here. 

Edit: Ozuna will be starting LF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Eager to be asleep. I have a cold. 
* Hopefully getting brunch at a an Ecuadorian place. My in-laws are Asian, and living with them has been different. Bought tortillas for myself and they have repeatedly asked "what do we do with these?" and called them pitas. 
* 91 - 71. I'm ready for a 90 win season. Tiebreak Jose Altuve with 7.1 fWar. Near Trout levels this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read "Where'd You Go Bernadette?" by Maria Semple, it's not quite as dark, but the main character is unreliable/pessimistic/skeptical/depressed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 27:40 5k yesterday on my run commute! This is only the third time I've broken 30 minutes in my life, so I'm pretty happy with that and how my training has gone this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Positional Power Rankings: Right Field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you get like 10 for $1 so that makes it worth it right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle keeps breaking Felix Hernandez's heart! They have to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my biggest paranoid fear, that someone will just lean into it because there's no one around to witness their vehicular manslaughter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone done the [Walkway over the Hudson](https://walkway.org/) Marathon or Half Marathon? I'm thinking about signing up before the price increase on April 1, but I'm running a half marathon April 30th (so about a month an a week before) and don't know if it's worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why people think America is the worst.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Callahan is more of a minor character in Salem's Lot. It's not spoiled per se but you did get a glimpse of the climax. I'd say it's definitely still worth reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jose Altuve, who is not tall

I see he got the necessary height mention out of the way quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be 1B but Gurriel could be serviceable there. Otherwise I'd say the Rotation isn't a weakness so much as an unknown at this point. But we have Musgrove, Martes, and Paulino (almost) ready to fill in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna have to put a * on that pr.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can switch places with the Brewers! An interstate rivalry will be 100x more fun when it happens inter-division.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks. this makes the most sense. I guess I never thought about it, but you probably aren't going to go around saying my territory, or my commonwealth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah probably also speaks fluent Spanish. So depending on the context he could have been interviewed in either? I've just never thought about nomenclature for PR, and wondering if calling it a country is the standard

Edit: But I guess they're just in LA, so maybe I am being culturally dumb to a certain extent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. US losing makes the WBC more enticing for smaller countries to participate in. PR looks pretty unstoppable though imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just read through this. Correa refers to PR as a country, and I've never really thought about this too much. Do native Puerto Ricans call PR a country? Or is this possibly a direct translation from the Spanish pas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I feel the argument is often used to misrepresent the current political situation. It isn't saying our current conservative values are valid because conservatives are older and wiser. Someone who is comfortable with gay marriage today won't become more conservative as they age and become uncomfortable with gay marriage. It's just a conservative talking point to validate their outdated politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tbf he has Russell and Crawford tied but the Cubs with more bench WAR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Correa Tops Fangraphs SS Positional Rankings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Positional Power Rankings: Shortstop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but if we make them a State we absorb their powers? (plus their debt yippee) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can the rest of us in Mainland USA counter their Super Saiyan powers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm was assuming overtraining as well. My HM is in 40 days and I'm stuck between taking some rest and feeling like I might not finish well, and just rolling into the HM exhausted and not finishing well. 

Partially why I'm wondering if a run where I generally feel like garbage is still good for fitness maintenance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are all runs beneficial? I'm in the middle of HM training and doing 20-30 miles per week with slow build ups each week. (I'm currently at 26. But I find myself having one "off" week where my per mile time shoots up by an additional minute, and then the alternate week is back into my comfortable training zone. I've been doing about 5 runs per week. 3 at 3/4 miles and 2 on the weekends at longer distances usually 5+.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just meant in the sense that he's been part of the denouncement of Indian Point. Which makes sense since it's in NYC's backyard, but also I imagine provides a large portion of NYC's electricity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just got elected the most historically unpopular President but was running against a similarly unpopular presidential candidate. At this point the campaign means nothing to his future success and the ability to sway future voters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can find is that he's putting funds into supporting the two [nuclear power plants upstate](https://www.governor.ny.gov/news/governor-cuomo-directs-department-public-service-begin-process-enact-clean-energy-standard)

But according to NYTimes he's replacing the Indian point energy burden with [Mr. Cuomo said the state would invest in wind farms and other renewable energy sources and add transmission lines to carry hydropower from Quebec.](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/09/nyregion/cuomo-indian-point-nuclear-plant.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If AMLO runs this will be his third time around and after the first time when he set up camp in the Plaza and had his alternate government, will people really be devastated by his losing? Tbh after so many failed attempts AMLO seems like he's the one who is failing the party, and he needs to step aside to let someone with less baggage run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the more conservative as you age bit has been mostly debunked in favor of your political beliefs just cementing in your mid twenties. Which makes sense, older people aren't inherently conservative, they just appear more conservative in relation to the modern day progressiveness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because the media is largely liberal leaning? So you see people who feel antagonized by both the liberals and the media for being told their beliefs are out-dated or bigoted. I'm not saying I agree with that, but I think you have a lot of previous hard working Americans who were the center of attention not finding themselves displaced by multiculturalism and globalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which for me begs the question why is it so important for individuals to try to shape the GOP/Conservatism into something it's not, rather than move in a different direction? If you're Pro-LGBT but Conservative either hold your party accountable or move off in your own direction. Especially if you're claiming that's the direction of new conservatism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I think you're overestimating the influence of YouTube stars (and also conversely celebrities) I'd wager that less people vote according to their favorite celebrities than that.

And you're attempting to create a movement that isn't Conservatism. I'm obviously struggling to understand this and needed to read "Strangers in Their Own Land" by Arlie Russel Hochschild to get a better understanding of this Great Paradox (as she calls it), but even she admits that deeply conservative Tea Party voters are looking for a more representative voice than big business interested GOP/Conservatives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually kind of fascinating to me. Politics didn't inform my choice at all, but I went to NYU, super liberal super big school in the middle of New York Values NYC. So that definitely impacted my politics. It'll be interesting for you to see how moving from a super liberal state (depending on county I'm sure) to small town Montana will inform your world view.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we'd need a bit more demographic information for any question to be meaningful but I'm curious if the current political climate impacts your college application process at all. It didn't for me in 2008, but now you have more of a backlash against the insular liberal elites, and snowflakes being raised on liberal campuses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you need to find a new word for the movement outside of Conservative. By definition being conservative is either against too-quick progress, a slow rumination on issues before adoption, or a pining for the past circumstance. Yearning for the past is not "punk" in anyway. There's absolutely no way that Conservatism is anti-establishment. Case in point Tami Lahren (or however you spell her name) losing her job for being Pro-choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be misremembering this but didn't AMLO run on a continuation of Calderon's aggressive policy towards drug cartels and corruption? I know that you added the bit at the end about Federal versus state level politics, but isn't this still an issue on the Federal level? I'm thinking the crack down of farmers who are making opium/marijuana, the conversation around legalizing the production of substances per Calderon's comment to Obama about ending the drug war and legalizing to take the power away from cartel's (this may have been Fox). I agree to some extent that Trump will take have an impact, but wouldn't the failed/mixed success against demilitarizing towns in the North also play into the conversation? I know Pena Nieto eventually brought back the more militant approach to the cartels, so I'm not sure which party has the better solution here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you remember what you felt politically in 7th grade? I know that I was in Middle School around the time of 9/11, so I felt firsthand the impact of overly fervent patriotism and calls for defense of freedom etc and while I did make the argument defending Bush's war by citing FDR's Four Freedoms speeches, I saw myself shift dramatically away from that in high school and then in college. I'd say that the only way 7th grade politics becomes cemented, is if somehow Trump politics becomes popular.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I live in a progressive state, in a super progressive city, and the one thing that the Governor (Cuomo) and Mayor (Deblasio) seem to agree upon is that the Indian Point Nuclear Power Plant should be closed. With no conversation as to alternative locations or updating the plant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more accurate to say that Trumpism and new conservatism is attempting to move the conservative position towards being supportive of gay rights. You can't gloss over Mike Pence, conversion therapy, Transgender bathroom bills, or Kim Davis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about environmental issues! Hopefully this does become more of a bipartisan concern, but as of right now we could see a shift away from more traditional forms of energy and production towards cleaner/safer energy sources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What didn't you like about The Regulators compared to Desperation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorite: Rose Madder, Roadwork are the  two I re-read the most

Least Favorite: Salem's Lot, From a Buick 8 (Or can we pretend this one doesn't exist?), Dreamcatcher  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a bar, Greenwich Treehouse, which was showing the US-DR game the other day. It's on Greenwich off 6th ave. Not sure if they're showing this one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree with this as well. They're both fairly culpable in the situation, I was mostly disagreeing with the assertion that Nick cheated because Amy became herself but it looks like OP might be at a point in the book before the turn. So I can see why they think that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. I think this book is a classic example of the Eyes Wide Shut argument I get into a lot. Your perspective will depend a lot on who you side with/feel compassionate for. And for me that was mostly Nick. How far are you? This is a book you probably don't want to have spoiled for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real Amy is the one who is manipulative and will do anything to destroy other human beings. Nick didn't cheat on her because she became the real Amy, he cheated on her because he had deeply personal issues going on in his life and he wasn't able to confide in Amy. Because Amy was perfect. Amy was everything a woman should be. Etc. That's why you had the big reveal in the end about all the individuals she framed, set up, ruined their lives. It was a game to her, so that her life stayed exciting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros remove catcher Max Stassi from 40-man roster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WP: You are the last person on Earth. To feel less lonely you collected shop mannequins as a substitute for friends. As you walk past one of them you hear a faint 'help me' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was insane. I knew this. Not in the classic situation of if you know there's a problem, then you can fix that problem. I had lost my mind. Understandably I thought.

After discovering I was the last person in my town of McAllen, Texas, I took a road trip around the United States and Mexico looking for others. Five years of dusty broken down towns, dwindling food supplies, and the transition of diarrhea to solid waste as my body adjusted to each town's water supply, and I was back in my hometown. Alone, and crazy.

Naturally I filled that void talking to myself and the inanimate objects that were all that was left behind of any other humans. 
Everything had something to say. I discovered that even in my garden the fruit and vegetables would chat loudly and without end. Sometimes about me. Often about me.

I needed reinforcements against the others, those not privy to arms and legs, so I began stealing mannequins from storefronts. My theft didn't go unnoticed, but I had the best lawyer in town who was able to argue before the judge that I was mentally incompetent, and so everyone just looked the other way as I went about my harmless crime spree.

My vegetable garden was still fiercely judgmental of my lifestyle, but I suspected it was a demoralizing effort to get me to stop eating them and their families. I didn't stop; I was a monster.

In the winter my mannequin compadres would bear the brunt of the elements due to my laziness in bringing them inside. Their voices grew harsh and scolding.

"You'll never amount to anything," One said.

"You have been a disappointment to us," Ten chimed in.

I ignored them and began to suspect that I might have self esteem issues that were exacerbated by the friends that I chose to surround myself with. I called my parole officer to discuss adding mental health services to my service plan but he was unavailable and I didn't have the persistence to try more than once.

Limbs quickly lost their cohesion, and my army of friends began to look like refugees of war. Eleven began to scream wordlessly and I had to take his head off and bury it in the yard.

It was then that I lost the trust of the rest of them.

I would watch them from my sliding glass doors and wonder at what they were plotting. How would they attempt to be rid of me?

I kept this vigilance up until I began to hear the quiet whisperings as they carried into my home.

It was inaudible and would stop when I slid the door open. In order to protect myself I snuck up behind the clique, now happily talking about the change in weather, the flowers blooming, and their growing friendship with the vegetables, and placed a battery powered recorder in the tall grass.

The next day I retrieved my device.

Hours of silence spun from the tiny micro-cassette with the occasional exaggerated shout, my voice, coming from the home, or directed at the clique of mannequins. My voice was varied, playing games to fill in all of the voices of my garden, and to hide the deep loneliness that was rubbing the veneer off my protective insanity.

Then as the tears slipped down my face, a daily occurrence, I heard the faint outline of "Help me."

It was a woman's voice. Not mine. I curled up under the table and rewound the tape.

"Help me," I said along with the recording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bacon v. Tacos: Losing team wears the others baseball cap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you vote against Team USA though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was insane. I knew this. Not in the classic situation of if you know there's a problem, then you can fix that problem. I had lost my mind. Understandably I thought. 

After discovering I was the last person in my town of McAllen, Texas, I took a road trip around the United States and Mexico looking for others. Five years of dusty broken down towns, dwindling food supplies, and the transition of diarrhea to solid waste as my body adjusted to each town's water supply, and I was back in my hometown. Alone, and crazy. 

Naturally I filled that void talking to myself and the inanimate objects that were all that was left behind of any other humans. Everything had something to say. I discovered that even in my garden the fruit and vegetables would chat loudly and without end. Sometimes about me. Often about me. 

I needed reinforcements against the others, those not privy to arms and legs, so I began stealing mannequins from storefronts. My theft didn't go unnoticed, but I had the best lawyer in town who was able to argue before the judge that I was mentally incompetent, and so everyone just looked the other way as I went about my harmless crime spree. 

My vegetable garden was still fiercely judgmental of my lifestyle, but I suspected it was a demoralizing effort to get me to stop eating them and their families. I didn't stop; I was a monster. 

In the winter my mannequin compadres would bear the brunt of the elements due to my laziness in bringing them inside. Their voices grew harsh and scolding. 

"You'll never amount to anything," One said. 

"You have been a disappointment to us," Ten chimed in. 

I ignored them and began to suspect that I might have self esteem issues that were exacerbated by the friends that I chose to surround myself with. I called my parole officer to discuss adding mental health services to my service plan but he was unavailable and I didn't have the persistence to try more than once. 

Limbs quickly lost their cohesion, and my army of friends began to look like refugees of war. Eleven began to scream wordlessly and I had to take his head off and bury it in the yard. 

It was then that I lost the trust of the rest of them. 

I would watch them from my sliding glass doors and wonder at what they were plotting. How would they attempt to be rid of me? 

I kept this vigilance up until I began to hear the quiet whisperings as they carried into my home.  

It was inaudible and would stop when I slid the door open. In order to protect myself I snuck up behind the clique, now happily talking about the change in weather, the flowers blooming, and their growing friendship with the vegetables, and placed a battery powered recorder in the tall grass.

The next day I retrieved my device. 

Hours of silence spun from the tiny micro-cassette with the occasional exaggerated shout, my voice, coming from the home, or directed at the clique of mannequins. My voice was varied, playing games to fill in all of the voices of my garden, and to hide the deep loneliness that was rubbing the veneer off my protective insanity. 

Then as the tears slipped down my face, a daily occurrence, I heard the faint outline of "Help me." 

It was a woman's voice. Not mine. I curled up under the table and rewound the tape. 

"Help me," I said along with the recording. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Mike Fiers has a good game but no one is watching is it still a good game?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted to read this article but that autoplay video ad in the corner distracted me. Does it go away? I tried closing it and it just gave me the option to move it around or make it bigger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryce Harper or Manny Machado? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same predicament as you. the 5k Runner has an old blog about it. It's still mostly rumors. 

https://the5krunner.com/2017/01/06/garmin-what-next-after-the-fenix-5-something-interesting-or-forerunner-930xt-635-or-240245/

March/April should be the release date for new 240/245 but I don't know if that's looking all that likely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roger Clemens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the Ultralight. I can't speak to that one specifically but the brand has been good to me. Depending on your need though it looks like the Ultralight doesn't have a chest   waist strap in the front like the Daylite does, and the Daylite also has snaps that compress the pockets and keep your items snug. I would just be worried about possibly overpacking the Ultralight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend the Osprey Daylite but it might be a little out of your range. I've had only positive experiences with the bag. The zippers did pop out once when I overfilled it, but I discovered it was my fault for not clipping the sides in. They also have a cheaper bag without the internal laptop pocket the Osprey Ultralight. (I don't know why one is lite and one is light.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you find a 15k or 10-miler? I'll be running my second HM ever this April and couldn't imagine running one a month later. I was wrecked after my first. 

But if you're trained and don't go all out on both of  them you should be fine I'd imagine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't stretch, but I probably should. I run commute after being cramped up in a 2 hour Coach bus ride. 

Taco: I'll never not be partial to slow cooked, shredded lengua on a corn tortilla with pico on top and a lime on the side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Hate U Give" sounds like Diary of a Part-Time Indian to me. Exploration of a controversial issue that some can easily dismiss as self-fulfilling because of presence of drugs + alcohol in the community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made this exact argument to my wife. I don't need to smell like flowers for the benefit of pedestrians if it's visibly clear that I'm exerting myself! 

She didn't buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say we could go swapsies, but Chicago/St. Louis/Pittsburgh is probably more intimidating than Seattle/Texas/LAA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how far you got, but definitely keep reading. The book excerpts about Lincoln are weird and off putting in the beginning in my opinion. (Heck the entire book might be in the beginning.) It takes awhile for the main characters to really get into a groove, and for the William Lincoln story to take off. But once I really dipped into the world I loved it. It's charming without getting too moralistic. 

I read a review where they described Saunders as being able to evoke compassion for the most degenerate and forgotten of people, and by the end of Lincoln in the Bardo he accomplished that for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Great. Had my best meeting (all in Spanish) so far at my new job. 
* Broke my quads running hills. 
* I have a HM in April that I'm both excited for and dreading. So much like the Astros in April.

PS. I can't decide if it's worth the 120 to get MLB.tv like I did last year. I'm procrastinating my purchase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does he actually have time to play this season?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you in the sense that I really almost desperately wanted to see what happened with the Reverend in take 2. I did however like [spoiler](/s "the scene where they go and save the girl from the crashed train car/regular car if I forgot the details. That was a pretty adequate ending to me, and gave a nice progression for the two of the main characters. The former sharecropper/free black/slave walking with Lincoln out of the graveyard was a little too on the nose for me though.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this has been posted yet, but saw it mentioned in Fangraphs' catcher [rankings](http://www.fangraphs.com/blogs/2017-positional-power-rankings-catcher/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros catching duo, the best in history of organization? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a really thorough review on Goodreads about how it's not that substantive that's been keeping me away. But I really want to read about Buchanan, so I might just dig in to this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just signed up the Scarsdale 15k impulsively. It'll be 4 weeks before my spring HM. Running in the Lower Hudson Valley has been giving me a near constant set of sore quads due to all the sharp inclines. I'm hoping the Scarsdale race is (relatively) flat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2014 Houston Astros' Opening Day Starter! He's the rebuild go to now it seems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best One-Two Punch in Baseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to reduce my plastic consumption to zero if possible, and I'm looking mostly to work around a post run Gatorade situation. I've tried Nuuns tablets but am not a huge fan of the carbonation and would like the ability to buy in bulk/wholesale if possible. Does anyone have any recommendations? I could probably just buy Gatorade powder, but I'm sure there's a healthier option out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VS Naipaul often challenges the colonial beauty/dark facade with his novels. Indians/South Asians in Africa had an interesting place in post-colonial times and there's rich literature from that time. In addition to any Naipaul novel (A Bend in The River is most applicable of what I've read though), I would highly recommend The In Between World of Vikram Lall, by MG Vassanji </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be my final week with **Team of Rivals by Goodwin** I'm absolutely loving the insight into Lincoln's presidency. I paired this with Lincoln in the Bardo and it gave me an even deeper appreciation for the man. If anyone has an James Buchanan biography recommendations I'd really appreciate. I'd really like to hit the bad presidents. 

**Swing Time by Zadie Smith** Will start this tomorrow. I'm nervous that it might be more On Beauty than White Teeth

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wasn't that like the penultimate chapter though? It didn't appeal to me either but it took up such a small space that it didn't affect the rest of the book for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I think it started out slow I very much liked it and when I think back on it, it ages well. It reminded me of The Semtex Girls and almost all of CivilWarLand, just truly bizarre scenarios looking at the human condition and response go tragedy. Etc. While the scenario could have used some flushing out it was the sharpness of the four main characters, the Reverend, and then the two boys/men who accompanied him, and Lincoln that really sold me on the book. I got a little emotional towards the end with the climax for the Reverend. 

But im also reading a Lincoln biography so I might have been more inclined to this personal and weird view of a big event in his life. 

Edit: On the back of my book jacket, Zadie Smith said Saunders was the funniest satirist since Mark Twain and tbh I'm not sure I see how that applies to this particular novel. So that bugs me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for this I hope McHugh throws several no hitters. Preferably against the Mets! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A TR vote is to be expected, but the Astros feel like vanilla ice cream. Nothing too offensive about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second highest vote total for the Astros? What are legitimate reasons to hate the Astros  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes and includes a very graphic image of a child in a woman's uterus. I was red starting this on the subway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I spend my entire life reading about Lincoln and the people around him. Team of Rivals has me pining for a good Salmon P. Chase bio.

I'll add this one to my list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audiobooks are my friend! Though yesterday I did have to carry my library haul through the final half mile of my run. 

I'll add those to my list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Sleepy. Basically finishing up Lincoln in the Bardo by George Saunders. What a weird but delightful book. 
* More reading. Hopefully finishing Team of Rivals by Doris Kearns Goodwin during some long runs. 
* Favorite presidential biography? Bonus points for presidents who sucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to quibble this isn't really 2nd person point of view though right? Because we have a first person narrator in the story who is communicating to someone else also in the story. In my opinion a true 2nd person point of view operates as if the narrator is using the singular 2nd person and the reader is the intended target of the pronoun. "You went to the shopping mall so you could buy some oranges." 

I think the usage here is great though because it has the ominous first person, interrogating or cajoling some unseen off-screen individual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a joke account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiers has had just the one relief appearance I think? The one that was like a day after he got traded and he got shelled. (Although he may have had some relief appearances in the playoffs in 2015 which probably weren't terrible.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cyclones already releasing their jersey designs https://instagram.com/p/BRvnJ1ygGJ4/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> boo why do you hate cities with good BBQ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the Mets are successfully turning the tables and eliminating AL Teams. Every AL team eliminated is another "Fuck the DH" whispered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were whispers that marriage was initially servitude for women. Of course people are decent and love is not a modern invention, so not all marriages subjugated women, if they ever did. My parents married out of love. I married with what was possibly a combination of love and being tired of guarding the secret.  

I am a person who is easy to make intimate relationships with, and therefore subject to painful attacks of guilt when asked about my favorite color. I cannot share it with everyone, but I can easily feel bad for keeping it to myself. There have been friendships lost because I've lied about it, and in the subsequent moment when the other individual attempted to use that knowledge, and it did nothing; they became upset about my betrayel, I became upset about their coercion, and the whole thing fell apart.  

Marriage, at 35, was my escape from that. Nobody would think to steal away the control that my wife had over me. There are unwritten societal rules, and manipulating a spouse is one that few people are willing to break. There is no real adultery since one spouse holds absolute control, or in most cases both spouses go through a period of exerting control over the other and then get tired of the manipulation.  

In my case I haven't told my wife my favorite color in the 20 years since we got married. We are locked in battle. At first it was easy, thinking that we would reveal our favorite color to the other in the natural course of things. We were married now, and it was a sign of trust to reveal to the other your control word. It just never happened with us.  

The last five years my wife has been passive aggressively hinting that she'd like to take control. There are the constant comments about our failing marriage, the thinly veiled eyebrow raising at the overall blue of my wardrobe and any purchase which further color codes me, and the whispers in my ear when she thinks I'm sleeping.  

We have been through them all. A steady torrent of the color spectrum runs through my head as I drift off to sleep.  

My chest has grown heavier and my heart beats when I'm around her. I don't know how to tell her now that we've become locked in this war of attrition.  

I don't know how my preference will affect our marriage, or if she'd even believe me.  

I don't have a favorite color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might I recommend the works of [Pankaj Mishra](http://www.pankajmishra.com/) who admittedly does not write from a Western perspective but offers up a history of how Western democracy was formed and influential thinkers (such as Rousseau. whom he disagrees with). What I like is that if you come up in the Western system there is a certain level of exceptionalism that gets bred into you, and Mishra is helping me see American liberty and exceptionalism with a little bit more of an outside perspective. 

Otherwise I would recommend any of the classics: "Common Sense" by Thomas Paine, "On Liberty" by John Stuart Mill, "The Four Freedoms" by Franklin Delano Roosevelt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this Peacock's last stand?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
