<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject276</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way she phrased it made it sound like there are whistleblowers or moles near Trump, no?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I'm happy about this, doesn't this kind of happen everytime someone new is in power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I want to believe there's a sliver of a chance he might veto this, I highly doubt it. He's not going to reject the Republicans after they've all been butting heads for so long. He needs them on his side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is not for starting witch hunts against specific users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not exactly a secret that there was a pretty large influx of users from that sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politics are spammed in this sub by both sides. There was a heavy influx of people following the election who were sick of the corruption. 

The "we already knew this" line is mostly used when the same article is posted 15 times over 3 days. 

This mentality is alienating users, new and old, because you *think* they're shills. No, it's not "obvious" unless they're following the same shit you seen in the politics sub. People who don't even come close to fitting in that pattern are still called shills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's becoming a completely meaningless word now because anyone who disagrees with someone is being called a shill. 

If it's really obvious they're shilling, you can report them to the mods and they'll handle it. Plus, calling someone out directly could probably get you banned here, regardless of whether or not they actually are a shill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People sent here to derail our conversations

I honestly can't fucking stand this thinking on this subreddit. Are there shills of some sort? Probably. But the majority of us are free-thinking people with no agenda but our own opinions. Someone disagreeing with you or tying the conversation back to *the current President of the US* if it's applicable and relevant **does not automatically make them a shill**. 

Seriously, when everyone on this subreddit has the same opinions and stops creating discussion or debate, this sub will be dead. I've seen more posts than ever before discouraging people from voicing their own opinions or ideas because "if they don't believe exactly what we believe, they're a shill".  

I was called a shill two days ago because I told someone that their argument of "autism being caused by aborted fetuses in vaccines" had absolutely zero evidence to support the claim. The shill calling is out of fucking control on this sub, and it's incredibly annoying for those who have been here well before the political shit started taking over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so excited for Saturday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People can make fun of MLS as a league, but I think Schweinsteiger just genuinely wants to contribute to a team and be appreciated. I'm happy Chicago were able to pick him up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to find out how easily your Representative was bought by ISPs? Now you can. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys know what's really fun? Matching up [this list](https://www.opensecrets.org/orgs/recips.php?id=D000000461 chamber=H party=R cycle=2016 state= sort=A) with those who voted yea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're correct, my mistake. This number is regarding the appeal. 

[Here is the actual voting recorded](http://clerk.house.gov/evs/2017/roll202.xml) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying, but with the obvious lack of any actual security most of these people have on their confidentials, it's probably easier to just hire someone to hack them directly if you're that desperate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number 2 is so important. It is now easier than ever to back up everything on your phone, from contacts to photos and apps. If you're mugged, the worst you should lose is just the phone itself. Your life is not worth fighting over a $600 electronic that will probably be replaced in a year or two anyways.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, more recently it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Additional source if this one isn't your cup of tea](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-nunes-idUSKBN16Z2TZ?il=0).

Asked whether he'd tell committee members who gave him intelligence reports indicating President Trump's team was incidentally surveilled, Nunes replied, "We will never reveal those sources and methods," 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nunes won't reveal sources to Intel Committee members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corporations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find how your Representative voted [here](http://clerk.house.gov/evs/2017/roll200.xml). If they voted yes, do your best to be sure they are not re-elected. They do not deserve to represent you or your fellow constituents. Those who voted yes *do not* care about you or the people they claim to represent. 

Edit: Another user pointed out that what I have linked (and what's linked in the article) are regarding whether or not the appeal should be tabled. 

[Here is how all Representatives voted](http://clerk.house.gov/evs/2017/roll202.xml). 

Final vote was 215-205. 15 Republicans said no. All 215 yeas were from Republicans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House of Representatives votes 232-184 to do away with Broadband Privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 231 Republicans said yes. 189 Democrats said no. 5 Republicans and 4 Democrats did not vote. Not a single Republican voted no. [Source](http://clerk.house.gov/evs/2017/roll200.xml)

I hate the "party lines" thing, but it has never been more apparent that the House Republicans could not care less about the people they're supposedly representing. Those that voted "yes" do not deserve to be re-elected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Ryan tried again to ask her question, Spicer said, I appreciate your agenda here.  At some point, report the facts.

Jesus christ. She *is* trying to report the facts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get out of here with your perfectly sensible logic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DePaul University student shot during attempted robbery near campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of corporate money allowed in politics is astonishing. Most people don't even bat an eye at it anymore. Some of the most clear cases of corruption and the only thing we can do is vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP are you ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 children died and around 30 were hospitalized. It was the fault of the national health agency. A bacterial contamination during the procedure is to blame. The vaccines themselves were fine. The babies died or were hospitalized for sepsis. Symptoms all aligned with what you see in a bacterial infection. 

[Source that is slightly more informative](https://www.google.com/amp/s/amp.cnn.com/cnn/2015/05/10/health/mexico-vaccine-deaths/index.html) 

From Mexico News:

Health officials believe the truth is that the vaccines were fine, but contamination by the bacteria, which was identified through blood tests, occurred at some point during the vaccination procedure.

The Hepatitis B shots were the one common vaccine among all those who became ill, but an analysis by Cofepris, the Commission for Protection Against Sanitary Risk, found there had been no other cases of adverse reactions in the application of 100,000 doses from the same batch of vaccine throughout the country since last October.

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After doing a little searching, I found a couple people said Washington's blog "has been taken over byJewish mis-directional influence".  I'm not familiar with either source so I have no idea what that means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ridiculous that this doesn't have an independent investigation yet. Everywhere you look this has conflicts of interest.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truthfully I don't and never have really watched her much, but I do really appreciate how well sourced and evidence based all of her topics are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police investigating 2nd shooting on Eisenhower Expressway in 10 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it tiring being so angry all the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a message of any sort, more of just your own opinion. But to each his own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to make this a copypasta? Why do you keep reposting this exact comment in different threads? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The heroes we need, but not the ones we deserve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't even notice that. I only noticed the date when I got to the end of the article. Whoops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is over two years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex Christoforou

 Living the dream in Moscow.

lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my shift doesn't end for another 22 minutes and I thought I'd get one last "vaccines don't cause autism" argument in to really make sure I earn my paycheck.

/s

Seriously? Disagreeing =/= shill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone disagreeing with what you're arguing because there's no evidence to support the claim doesn't make them a shill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That section goes on to discuss the "growing proven connection between autism and vaccines". There is zero proven connection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Connection Between Aborted Fetal Tissue and Autism

You lost me here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like you're missing something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who have the same urges and are actively trying to suppress them? Support coming from knowing they aren't alone and have a community to turn to for help can do a lot of good for people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's being stated that the community can help *prevent child abuse*.

That is a very different thing than "helping children".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your title is entirely misleading and misrepresenting the article. 

They're people with mental illnesses who are seeking help from others who suffer from the same illness. They've admitted they're wrong and are actively trying not to act on their urges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in the article does it say that? The entire article is about pedophiles who have created a community where they can help each other to not act on their urges. 

The goal of the organization is to offer support to pedophiles who want to live virtuously and to raise public awareness about the fact that such pedophiles exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. government watchdog to review Mar-a-Lago trips, Trump hotel profits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you were around before the election, you have no idea what this sub used to be like. You can say it's "apolitical" now, but based on the submissions in the last year we all know that's not true anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a sitting president and administration with a ridiculous amount of "coincidental" ties to Russia, and people still go back to this shit? It wouldn't change anything even if it were true.  

Edit: you people are fucking hilarious. The guy quoted in this article was already proven to have changed his story, job title, and actual level of involvement many times over the last few years. The guy first turned to a white supremacist group to  get this idea out there. He's probably one of the worst people to listen to if you're actually "looking for truth about this topic".    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the amount of cops that are in and out of that place everyday, I don't know if this guy is ballsy or an idiot. Or both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beverly 7-Eleven Robbed At Gunpoint, Police Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the special weather statement regarding the dense fog, it should ease up late morning to early afternoon, but probably won't be completely gone for awhile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 46 Dogs Rescued from Korean Meat Farm Arrive in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even after all this time, he's still fighting for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some real assholes in this thread. I don't care how much you're "pumping into the economy", it doesn't give you an excuse to be an asshole. Just pick up after yourself because it's the courteous thing to do, especially in such a beautiful and welcoming country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Brooks had an awkward leg movement. Hoping it's not the knock he had before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost feel a little bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?" 

Lads, it's ~~Liverpool~~ Honduras </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Against USA? Taking a player out with an injury. Against Honduras? Swipe with the foot and a late dive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale of one to Milner in the game against City last week, how bad would you rate it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WORLD CLASS PLAYER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bar I'm in just started doing karaoke while half of us are watching this game and the other half are watching the Wisconsin game. Kill me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's so sad :( great goal to give USA the lead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're telling me. I've been drinking the last 4 hours thinking this game was supposed to start an hour and a half ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the Ireland v Wales game today I don't think I can handle anymore murders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's so much bullshit in this comment I don't even know where to start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The art institute is one museum that I think is definitely taken for granted by some. Honestly it's one of the best in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelievably embarrassing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably the most pompous comment in this thread. 

1. Not everyone has an option to work from home. 

2. Not everyone can rely on working from home or having family watch after your child so you don't have to pay for daycare.

3. Some couples genuinely cannot afford to have children. During a child's first year, provided your child is healthy and has no medical issues, it's going to cost an average of $12k. 

4. You don't have to have children to "offer something to society other than tax dollars". 

5. Those who realize they're too financially unstable to have children at the moment are being responsible and actually doing us all a favor. 

Being a mother does not give you a right to be a judgmental asshole.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mortgage - $7k-$9k/year (PMI)

Utilities - $3.6k/year

401k - $7k/year

Car Payments - $4.5k/year

Groceries - $2k/year

Insurance - $2k/year


These are conservative estimates. Where am I supposed to fit a child that costs $12k/year? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police said the victims told them they were picked up outside two different Chicago bars after ordering Ubers, driven to an undetermined location in Skokie and sexually assaulted in the vehicle.

Always, always, always check the license plate before getting into any Lyft or Uber, guys. Don't be afraid to ask the driver their name to confirm it matches with who is supposed to be picking you up.

This shit is scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Impersonating Uber Driver Sexually Assaulted Women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's bullshit. Why bother having an appeal system when it clearly doesn't work? Ref was right to give a red based on what *he* saw, but the replay clearly shows it wasn't as dangerous as a quick glimpse would show. Yellow, definitely. Leaving it a red is the wrong decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good year to start supporting Fire. We might actually finish above last in our conference this year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Schweinsteiger knows Pauno's wife. That would truly be the scandal of the decade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was true. He met with Fire's head coach Pauno some odd months back. It was actually hilarious, the way they were trying to leave separately made it look like they were trying to hide an affair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely. I meant it's more that you can't exactly look at MLS as a "league to retire in" and put in 25% of effort because you're going to fail miserably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, I meant clear from my previous comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a douchebag, what the fuck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, you still have a chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you rejected by MLS?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our current owner is absolutely awful and one of the direct reasons for the club's downfall over nearly the last decade. There were rumors of the club being sold last season but it never amounted to anything. Honestly, with the way the club has progressed so far this season, it makes me think Andrew Hauptman is much more hands off this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention how things like altitude changes with frequent flying affect your body. Don't think most people realize how large the US is, it's not exactly like you can take a train to get you to your next game. You're really traveling more than you're playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be nice to see him play regularly again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who hurt you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly talking about individual players and not the PL as a whole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny because there are certainly players in the PL that couldn't play in MLS because of how physical it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fucking shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fucking shit it's happening. 

It's happening. IT'S HAPPENING.

EVERYONE STAY CALM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's shitty.

My coworker was roped into doing the free training session when she signed up at her new gym. My coworker, who very visibly has CP, was just looking for a way to stay active. The trainer told her virtually nothing for 30 minutes, then gave her a goal of deadlifting 200 pounds in 3 months. In her words, "I can't even hold a cup of coffee in my right hand, how the fuck am I supposed to deadlift something double my weight?" 

He then tried to charge her for 3 more training sessions. 

Some places just really suck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be more surprised by people thinking he would stay if they're relegated. He'll be picked up quickly somewhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame, Alli is talented but his behavior and reputation are going to follow him throughout his career if he doesn't grow out of it. For example - Diego Costa is known for two things: 1) Being one of the top strikers in the league and 2) being a cunt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be so sure about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just said it's unfortunate to admit that Vardy has received pens the same way that Alli did this game.

Why do Spurs fans always resort to talking about last season? That's one generalization that seems to be true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunate to admit but Vardy has received quite a few pens from just slightly dragging his leg the way Alli did. Not completely unheard of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same to you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> talking out of their ass

90% of r/soccer. 

It's going to be a good match, but I won't pretend that we're going to have it easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spurs fans.

*Alli gets legs tangled in the box, penalty given*

"You simply can't do that, clear penalty for Alli, no doubt about it."

*Davies kicks Tadic in the knee in the box, absolutely nowhere near the ball, no penalty given*

"Well you see, the velocity at which Davies had his foot matched with the distance of which Tadic's knee was moving per second.... *Blah blah blah*... And that's why he didn't deserve a penalty".

Christ it's unbelievable with them sometimes. 

And the calls of diving from Spurs fans is hysterical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They honestly make discussions unbearable sometimes. The mass downvoting yesterday in the match thread was ridiculous. 

edit: lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That whole game was phenomenally shit as far as calls made or missed. Really don't understand how some refs are able to keep their jobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckin nailed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to have you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/Politics - Trump

r/Soccer - Diego Costa

r/t_d - Hillary Clinton

r/RickandMorty - False hope about Season 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want to say I really appreciate how civil the match threads tend to be in this sub. Makes everything much more enjoyable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm under the impression that it's part of a large "against racism" initiative happening right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Seattle, 

I hope you're treating Harry Shipp and Joevin Jones well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> June 10th is right around the corner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I DIDN'T HAVE MUCH FUN YESTERDAY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude, i feel you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you guys just chanting Holy Shipp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, looking at the replay you're right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Robles just watch that go in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are going to make it an exciting game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta say I think the ref has been pretty spot on tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been like 2007 Britney Spears but slowly making a comeback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT'S THE FUCKING SEATTLE I LIKE TO SEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks mostly ok now, I hope

Edit: Yeahhhh I spoke too soon. Sorry, guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to see what's happening in the last third? Fuck you, here's my face!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do people hate more atm, MLS live or Facebook Live MLS games? BTW, don't forget to send me emojis and leave your comments below! You might get a shoutout!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao that girl fighting with the guy over the scarf in the Red Bulls section </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao I just read that too. I miss Shipp like crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure he's saying nothing but words of endearment to his team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad luck Jordan Morris

Wins Rookie of the Year

Has one bad first half in the next season

"Dude sucks" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can get creative with lip reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is this "4chan"!? We'll never know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have been beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Army propaganda  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lagunitas Little Sumpin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm certainly not going </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think it's going to be a great game, at least for the first 60' or so. You guys are looking pretty solid this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit, it started out like a really bad breakup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that applies to 90% of MLS games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we do that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably just waiting for half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle have just been scary this half. Lots of good chances. Hoping they can actually double the lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks, me too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll give this to myself, don't worry](http://imgur.com/gallery/sy9lVl4). It's the thought that counts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually try to give people the benefit of the doubt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
