<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8607</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, 29 million people still lack health insurance, 63% of Americans say they can't afford a $500 emergency expense, almost half of all workers earn less than $15 an hour, more than 70% of all college students are in student debt, every major city is in an affordable housing crisis, there will be more hospitals than nurses by 2022, 1 in 3 black students drops out of high school every year, the water in Flint is still poisonous, the water in California is still missing - and the President spends all his time (okay, one *third* of all his time) golfing on luxury greens, tweeting about a glorious wall that will somehow make everything great again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why they put the numbers on your vest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Sanctuary Cities' Promise Legal Fight After Sessions Threatens Funds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore Mayor Vetoes $15/hour Minimum Wage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore Mayor Vetoes $15/hour Minimum Wage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Vicious Attack on Black Communities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new NYPD officer sheds tears of joy at her graduation ceremony [OS] [1024x682] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably not that nuanced. The poster was made for a competition sponsored by graphic designer Herb Lubalin in Avant Garde magazine, calling for posters of the theme ["No More War."](https://www.flickr.com/photos/uniteditions/7419680134/in/faves-lubalincenter/) Joe Simboli submitted [five posters](http://www.simbolidesign.com/posters_war.html), which he said were only meant to reflect the insane nature of war and "not meant to be a political statement", in his own words.

Personally, I think it's great as a metaphor for small actions being part of a bigger picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong, 1996 [1200x809] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Visa Changes Hit US Nursing Supply From Canada, Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America Is Getting Richer and Sicker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pull! Joe Simboli, U.S., 1968 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump cuts food aid while kids starve. And how do you bomb Ebola? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you dare to struggle, you dare to win. Fred Hampton [500x398] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sending a signal for help, by Aaron Whitehead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was a much more intense Rogue One poster in Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lady doth protest too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailer for PBS FRONTLINE's 'Battle for Iraq', aired January 31st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map of uranium deposits around the world [OS] [723x558] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You chose to butt in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like they've been prototyping the Switch for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Bathroom bill' to cost North Carolina $3.76B </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Paypal**

A state Commerce Department analysis shows officials expected a planned Charlotte PayPal operations center to contribute more than $200 million annually to the state's gross domestic product  an overall measure of the economy. By the end of 2028, the state expected PayPal to have added more than $2.66 billion overall to the state economy, according to the March 2, 2016, analysis.

But shortly after House Bill 2 was enacted, PayPal CEO Dan Schulman announced the company was backing out of the 400-job plan because of the law.

***

**Deutsche Bank**

Using the same model, the Commerce Department estimated that a Deutsche Bank project in Cary would pump about $47 million annually into the economy once fully staffed at 250 jobs in 2017. The September 2015 analysis predicted a total impact of about $543 million by the end of 2027. But the company announced it was halting plans because of the law.

***

**CoStar**

The AP used figures from North Carolina and Virginia to conclude that CoStar's decision not to put its facility in Charlotte will cost North Carolina at least $250 million.

CoStar's CEO had recommended Charlotte to his board and was preparing for final negotiations for a site there when the board backed out because of negative publicity over the law, according to a September 2016 email exchange between Charlotte Chamber of Commerce and city officials.

***

**Voxpro**

The AP analysis valued Voxpro's decision not to come to the state at about $52 million based on figures from North Carolina and an interview with the CEO.

The company was in negotiations to bring hundreds of call-center jobs to the Raleigh area, but chose not to because of the law, founder and CEO Dan Kiely said in an interview. The company chose Athens, Georgia; Kiely said the company will employ 500 there.

***

**Adidas**

The AP used figures from North Carolina and Georgia to compute a value of about $67 million for the decision by Adidas not to choose North Carolina for a factory.

The shoe and apparel company was considering a High Point site and visited about a week before the law passed, according to state economic development emails. 

***

**Sports events, concerts, conventions**

The AP conducted more than a dozen interviews and email exchanges with tourism officials and planners to determine the state lost more than $196 million from sporting events, conventions, concerts and other events. Cities researched include: Asheville, Charlotte, Greensboro, Raleigh, Manteo, Wilmington, Durham and Fayetteville. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian opposition leader due in court after anti-corruption protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a snowy Saudi Arabia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse, they're cracking down on their own people. It's barbaric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will she shake hands? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "First step is to get rid of everyone's pension benefits. Then, make everyone work in an open plan office." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense - they're more shark than man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he's still a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We export $5.7 billion and import $14.5 billion in goods to and from Russia ever year - a multi-billion dollar deficit. We're already giving Russia tons in money, we should invest in their political freedom too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the Christian missionary who denies the existence of climate change shouldn't be the one telling doctors already trained in medical school how to do their jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "The more you tighten your grip, the more star systems will slip through your fingers." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "make everyone like you"

I thought you meant the billionaire cabinet by this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Battle of Yavin, if you will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now Republicans want to literally put words in doctors' mouths for them? Talk about conservative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU of Maine Offers Support to Local Law Enforcement Resisting Trump Threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rene Mederos was the artist who made this and many other posters / screen prints in the same (psychedelic?) style. They all look pretty great, and a lot of them are about Vietnam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Next time you should try learning about the history first
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *known deaths. There was huge stigma against diagnosing AIDS, especially in heterosexuals, and activists had to do their own research since the government wasn't going to. Next time you should try learning about the history first and then google "how many minutes are in a year" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_Will_Absolve_Me

It was the name given to Castro's speech made in his own defense at the trial for his role in attacking the Moncada Barracks on July 26th 1953, the start of the Cuban Revolution (hence "siempre es 26 / it's always the 26th"). The poster commemorates that 20th anniversary (see the Roman numerals in upper right) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gran_Fury

http://hyperallergic.com/42085/aids-art-activism-gran-fury/

https://www.theatlantic.com/entertainment/archive/2012/01/how-aids-was-branded-looking-back-at-act-up-design/251267/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  source is unreliable

they believe in climate change, don't they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man is a walking product placement. And now the whole government is too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's common for prosecutors to press multiple charges for the same killing in order to cover all possible arguments. [This is the full indictment of the defendant.](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/2648133-Jason-Van-Dyke-Indictment.html) If he's convicted at all, this officer will probably serve multiple sentences or portions of them concurrently, which is also common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *Each time a man stands up for an ideal, or acts to improve the lot of others, or strikes out against injustice, he sends forth a tiny ripple of hope, and crossing each other from a million different centers of energy and daring, those ripples build a current which can sweep down the mightiest walls of oppression and resistance.*



[Robert F. Kennedy](https://youtu.be/QbtxTh_A92s?t=55s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also a reference to the Marlboro Man, and the surgeon general's warning on cigarette packs. Something distinctive about the gay rights groups of the AIDS era was they used the aesthetics of commercial advertising in a lot of their posters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  50,000 fewer votes

...

 "All those votes went to Blacks! None of them were cast by Whites!"

Black people were 6.5% of the eligible voters pool in 2016, but cast 12% of the actual votes in 2016. Who's not keeping up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the middle of World War II, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His mouth should be fined for carbon emissions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rich or poor, black or white -

Health care is a human right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bad police shoots are not racially influence, they are a lack of training.

These are actually related, not opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just goes to show having better aim doesn't mean doing a better job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it was White people didn't show up at the polls for Hillary in November, and White people who are regretting their votes now. The percentage of non-hispanic Whites who vote in general has actually declined each election since 2004. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WARNING: While Bush spends billions playing cowboy, 37 million Americans have no health insurance. One American dies of AIDS every eight minutes. ACT UP, U.S., 1990 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Americans Killed by Police in 2017, but Trump Dominates Headlines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They misinformed us, and told us Quanice was shot three times in the chest. We later found out through the death certificate that, that wasnt true," she said. Quanice was on his knees when he was shot in the head and in the chest. I think thats important when anybody wants to say that he was this dangerous robber.

 Hayes said her son is the victim in the case and that he was painted by police as a robber or a car prowler.

 All of which is not a reason to be executed in the United States of America or the state of Oregon, Hayes said.

...

 Police spokesman Sgt. Pete Simpson told The Oregonian/OregonLive on Wednesday that he didn't know the total number of officers at the shooting scene, but confirmed the presence of one K9 officer and one officer with less-than-lethal ammunition in addition to Hearst.

...

 Unlike the "petit" jury, which is used to determine guilt in a trial, a grand jury consists of 16 to 23 jurors who are not screened for bias. The purpose of the grand jury is not to determine guilt or innocence, but to decide whether there is probable cause to prosecute someone for a felony crime. The grand jury operates in secrecy and the normal rules of evidence do not apply. The prosecutor runs the proceedings and no judge is present. Defense lawyers are not allowed to be present in the grand jury room and cannot present evidence, but may be available outside the room to consult with witnesses. The prosecutor and the grand jury members may not reveal what occurred in the grand jury room and witnesses cannot obtain a transcript of their testimony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago officer who shot black teen 16 times faces 16 new counts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother Of Teen Killed By Portland Police Calls For Federal Investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smile for the laptop :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in America she'd already be black because of the systemic racial inequality in America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condemn me, it does not matter. History will absolve me. Cuba, 1973 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Have you perhaps considered the vast economical and social (no to mention cultural) differences between single European countries and the entirety of the USA?

The differences in social and economic terms aren't that large between most of America and Europe. You could travel between the US and Europe and find us all dealing with fairly similar problems economically (unemployment, urban poverty, immigration, automation, austerity, etc) under almost identical conditions of general social stability (compared to say, Honduras), and even media consumption habits (look at our internet penetration). 

America is much more different *legally* and politically [compared to the countries of Europe,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_national_legal_systems#) and is one of only three in the world to guarantee an explicit right to bear arms (Mexico and Guatemala being other two - notoriously safe in gun violence). And among fellow descendants of the Britsh Empire, we definitely have the loosest and least consistent set of gun laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago doesn't actually have super strict gun laws, and Chicago police have said themselves the laws are too lax. False facts aside, America is 25 times deadlier in gun violence compared to Europe and it has more citizens incarcerated than any other country in the world. The state of crime and gun violence in this country are both pretty big examples of American exceptionalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Government and non profits spring into action

-Systemic poverty, prohibition, and gun law reforms pass

-Lol JK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're definitely in the news though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are awake at different times than America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That says it was posted less than an hour ago. This will be discussed for a lot longer than hour, so this is really quite early.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People shouldn't "politicize" this killing for bragging points, but at the same time violence is the product of systemic problems that can only be solved by systemic (political) solutions. 

You're right the media should treat all victims of massacres equally, but they won't, because not all news is equally profitable. And in the end, the media can only point out the problems that politics has to solve.

The worst kind of politicizing though is the gossiping kind - it doesn't seem outwardly political, but fixating on the character of victims or perpetrators of violence doesn't stop a flawed system from producing more of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever notice how almost all these spree shooters are heterosexual men, usually rejected by women at some point in their lives? I mean, almost *all* mass shooters in the history of mass shootings and school shootings have been men or boys. The tendency to kill has less to do with race - men of all races kill - than it does with gender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Waits for Red States to get their shit together.*

*Dies.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could choose not to be stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how you get citizenship dummy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not how law abiding works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unsurprisingly, the anti-immigrant "citizen" knows next to nothing about the legal system.

It takes several layers of *approval from Homeland Security* to move forward with your citizenship application, not the waiting of x amount of years. 

There are several categories of citizen applicants, and a quota system is used to determine who can continue. That has nothing to do with years of residence. 

Amongst men without professional degrees married to US citizens with American children, there were about *800 approvals* granted last year, out of 200,000+ in the same category waiting.

There are shorter lines for the wealthy and higher educated, because American values, with a total of more than 4.4 million people waiting in "line" to take the oath of allegiance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes this presidency is failing, but the real blame is on everyone but Trump!" - the author
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Trump tweet posted from Transportation Secretary's account: 'SUE HIS VERY SOUL' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even within baptism by water, there are differences. Some believe you must be fully immersed in water to be baptized, others don't. Fun fact: the part of the Jordan River Christ was baptized in is now so polluted, it would be a health risk to try getting baptized there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with Latino in quotes? You think you can tell from a distance who's illegal and who's not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tear off the mask of the fascist provocateur! U.G.T., Spain, 1930s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also pretty fucked up to Latino students to make them think they're surrounded by white people who want to deport them when they're not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prosecutor: Targeted killing of black man in NYC 'most likely an act of terrorism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump urged to condemn white US army veterans racist murder of black man in New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
