<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9704</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem senators on working with POTUS on drug costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to say one positive thing about Donald Trump, no matter you love him or hate him, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actual real life scientist disproves the association of CO2 with Global Warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Well get you one of these times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going home for they day, can you give me some inpriring words before i leave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol t_d alt account,  I only have the one :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no I am having fun, i wanted to see your commitment. You sir are committed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context for anyone who didn't see Carson's speech:

http://www.bing.com/videos/search?q=obama+calls+slaves+immigrants view=detail mid=4787F7A4707D00EC69CD4787F7A4707D00EC69CD FORM=EWREVC mmscn=wnmp ru=%2fsearch%3fq%3dobama%2bcalls%2bslaves%2bimmigrants%26form%3dIE11TR%26src%3dIE11TR%26pc%3dLNJB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a word scramble and I cannot figure it out, can you help me?

A Trump Donald liar is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, what do you think of President Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally an original thought around here!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok...Thanks! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I follow him on Twitter. I like Bernie, I just want him to have some positive messaging. He isn't a Democrat but he is acting like one with the trump reactionary shit. 

There is a black hole of positive messaging that he could fill, in my opinion. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are missing the point of what I am saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not saying he has to say pro Trump stuff, just does he have anything to say not related directly to Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must be fun at parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie's got nothing. I was hopeful he could translate his message after the election but instead he has nothign to say but anti-Trump stuff. It's too bad.

Imagine having him still speaking about his ideals rather than just gaslighting the anti-Trumpers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly I cannot wait to see what he says. Donald Trump does not own illegal action by the CIA, but he is President. So he has to denounce the leakers and pledge to catch them. But, and this is a big but, this is a real opportunity for change. We have an atypical President who doesn't own any of this, he is a new comer and has pledged drastic change in many areas. This is an area that obviously desperately needs change.

It's no secret that the President has not been fond of the CIA and man as Americans we have a real opportunity here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they stopping the investigation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never said it shouldn't be investigated, in fact in this same comment chain I have said I have no problem with an investigation twice. 

I am simply saying there is no actual evidence of any wrong doing. Trumps campaign met with people, which campaigns tend to do. Clinton's campaign chairman owns a lobbying group with heavy ties to Russia. 

The very same Russian ambassador who was supposedly Session's contact was sitting with the Dems during the State of the Union speech. This guy is fucking everywhere, so now all of sudden it is evidence for a conspiracy between Trump and the Russians. Come on. 

It is all narrative and little substance. I am shocked that seemingly intelligent people will bite into this bait so hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol just saying it is good to get away from what the corporations are saying. 

Watch what Secular Talk Kyle says about it or Ben Shapiro on his daily show. There's nothing there. 

Don't compare me to Jones, you're the one pushing the Russia conspiracy theory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol don't slander Republicans on my word, I am no Republican. You're clinging to a dead narrative. 

It's ok though, it is certainly easier to make personal attacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That it is a sham narrative? The lack of evidence from those who claim it to be true is the best evidence.

Maybe the best way to approach it is to ask, what do you think happened or what crime did Trump and his people commit? And then what evidence for that is there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with it, it's better than media conjecture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather than pouring through your collection, what do you think is the single most damning piece of evidence, and of what crime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not telling myself I am listening to others. 

Conservative commentators and progressive commentators who are not MSM think it's a sham. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. We need our govt to be accountable. I'm just don't think anything will turn up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw, it is a sham narrative and only people who really want it to be true are buying into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone shares your level of outrage. many people see the Russia narrative as being pretty obviously over blown. Not just Republicans and Independents either, there are lefty and Dem commentators saying the same. 

So this isn't a big deal really and the whole Russian Narrative is collapsing. Go re-read any NY Times article about, about half way down they go into how none of the 'evidence' is conclusive and could be due to numerous factors. 

It's all a sham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering there has been no evidence found of collusion between the Trump campaign and Russia, why is this so surprising? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a good one. It is an anonymous source which I frankly think there have been too many of in this whole damn narrative. So probably not. 

https://heatst.com/world/exclusive-fbi-granted-fisa-warrant-covering-trump-camps-ties-to-russia/


While looking I did find an interesting article from National Review about the whole Russia narrative


http://www.nationalreview.com/article/445522/russian-election-hacking-fbi-not-investigating-trump-campaign
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think at least one was denied as well? Something happened seems like a good description.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky they couldn't stop him from backing out of the TPP. 

I guess we'll see how it goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the Rs should do it either, and now we have both getting nothing positive accomplished? That's party before country if I have ever seen it. Both corporate parties have become more of a hinderance than a help at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, why would it matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a real opportunity for Bernie to have positive messaging and to continue the momentum he may have gathered from the campaign season. Instead he is just like all of the corporate Dems with nothing positive to say for the country, just negative nancy shit about Trump.

It seems like the perfect opportunity for a Dem or left leader to emerge with positive messaging and a willingness to work with Trump for the better of the country. But instead we will just see a reactionary party with nothing to offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, what attacks on scientists are happening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bad enough for what? There is no evidence of a crime, is there?

Or is it just bad that he is potentially 'friendly' with Russia, even though his UN ambassador and Secretary of Defense have both spoken  out against Russia in their respective rolls.

I guess I am missing what is bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Russia acted, without any collusion from the Trump folks. So we can all stop with the Trump is a Russian agent conspiracy theory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday
http://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/video/full-clapper-no-evidence-of-collusion-between-trump-and-russia-890509379597
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they couldn't find any actual evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI and James Clapper have said they have found zero evidence. The mystery is really how is this even still a story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, thanks. I went and got my reading comprehension hat on, and your comment still deserves criticism.

Let me know when that solid evidence gets here. They haven't found any yet. So you are proposing Trump is planning for when the evidence is so overwhelming to have his supporters go after Obama? But they haven't found any evidence after months of trying. 

So i guess you don't have access to more information than Clapper or the FBI...just a conspiracy theory that should come true any day. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now Trump supporters will simply claim that Iraq has no issues and shouldn't be on the list.
I wonder how they change their minds so rapidly and intensely.

You are proposing what they will claim, and then questioning how quickly they have changed their minds. So you are wondering about something that you made up. This is a Straw man. I actually looked this up and reference it all the time because people were using the term at my work a lot and they were using it to mean like a wire frame...

A Straw man is a simplified or misrepresented argument you use to easily defeat. It is made of straw, i.e. it is easy to knock down. This has been a popular tactic to criticize Trump. 

Here from wikipedia
A straw man is a common form of argument and is an informal fallacy based on giving the impression of refuting an opponent's argument, while refuting an argument that was not advanced by that opponent.[1] One who engages in this fallacy is said to be "attacking a straw man".

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Straw_man

So maybe your's was half a strawman since you didn't quite knock it down, but a strawman still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if you stroll through posts on the sub-reddit it is constant. Misrepresenting Trump supporters, casting them all as X or Y simply because they support our President is silly and I like calling it out. 

Half of the 'conversations' around here have close to zero basis in reality and it is a circle jerk of epic proportions. So as someone who supports our President I want to point out the straw manning.

You're right though because I am not really contributing to the conversation so I am actually doing similar thing to what I am criticizing...Damn you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but there is no solid evidence, even after months of wire tapping. That's a big piece of the story. James Clapper, who is no Trump ally, even said he saw no evidence of Trump/Russia collusion. 

So unless you have access to more information than him, I am wondering what solid evidence you have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well with so many people peddling the Russian Conspiracy theory, i am not surprised CNN assumes Trump is pushing one as well. 

The only thing that seems to be on contention is is Obama ordered the Wire tap since there is significant evidence that one existed, after multiple attempts to obtain the warrant. 

Even James Clapper is saying he saw no evidence of collusion between Russia and the Trump campaign. The FBI has said the same. So the wire tapping is the new story, and the Russian angle is being blown out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part is all the people who are now admitting there is no evidence of Trump campaign collusion with Russia, most notably James Clapper. 

I am interested to see what comes of the investigation, especially since  there are already journalist providing evidence that the 'taps' existed and there were multiple attempts in the FISA court to get them. 

Crazy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to be clear you are asserting what 'Trump supporters' will say and then refuting your own assertion. This is Strawman 101.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to see the evidence if he has it. This would be pretty bad in my opinion. I mean he is the POTUS, if there is evidence I am sure he can get his hands on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for linking the article. It is mostly about a proposed plan from Trumps lawyer, which based on the actions of Haley at the UN and Mattis at a NATO conference, this plan is not happening. 

If this is all about Russia wanted better relations then we shouldn't immediately close the door, especially if we can get Putin to act more in line with international standards of decency. 

The sanctions stand, Haley has condemned Russia's actions in Crimea and we have not seen any suspect pro Russia anything, beyond them talking. Which is not unusual given past campaigns have spoken to Iran and other nations. 

If Trump was compromised by Russia I am not sure what to expect to see really. Maybe taking actions that only help Russia? Leave NATO? It's a good question that I am not really sure how to answer. 


    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it. 

You make some good points, I would have to go back and confirm that Flynn and Sessions discussed the same things. Do you have links for that?

So if I am wrong and Sessions wasn't acting as a Senator but as a campaign aide my original question stands about what is the end game? I got hit with so many responses at once on my comments I am hoping this is referencing the correct thing? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yes. I'm working, was there something you were waiting for a response on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pelosi has been so quick to criticize and judge, it would be a same if we started going after her. I mean what career politician doesn't have over one hundred million dollars of net worth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I am a Russian internet troll so obviously my allegiance is with Lord Putin, but I get your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are so good at judging other people, I wonder if you ever give yourself the same level of critique. You can make it about what an idiot I am, that's fine my wife does it all the time too but don't act like you somehow have actually proven a point. It is really just a sign of weakness of your argument.

Glad i could at least entertain you. Have a good day too!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they were my words surely you could actually reference them though right? I am sure it is easier to debate the straw me anyway, you can build in whatever weaknesses you want. It's cool man do you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course since the were the two major candidates, but they are different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am? Are you talking to me or the strawman of me you have created?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be, depending on what is actually true and what is not and what was discussed. 

Russia attacked HRC and the DNC, not America. I mean from the CIA's own report they say it was likely this was more against Hillary than pro Trump. 

I guess we will have to wait and see, but I will not except the current conspiracy theory as fact on this sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet. 

Thank you. My Russian to English translator acts up sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, much of the speculation comes off as conspiracy theory but as long as we all admit that we are speculating. You may have a cooler head but i see a lot of people stating fact that Trump is a Putin stooge, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Lets see what comes out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a Sessions fan boy, I do not like many of the career politicians we have. I am just saying people are jumping on the corporate narrative when they should be skeptical of all sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, what facts did i deny. It's ok if you don't want to talk but don't pretend it is because I am claiming the sky is red. Relying on character attacks is evidence of a weak argument, not a strong one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not have a problem giving my opinion, and I do not think it is comparable to your 1979 example. Maybe if you provided an argument for it rather than simply stating it as fact then we could discuss that. I would make a more recent comparison of the Obama campaign talking with Iran, which I am not outraged about but it is a closer corollary than the made up example of Reagan. 

Why would people talk with Russia? I don't know we would have to ask them. The NY Times article that originally broke the story about communication during the campaign said they may not have even known they were and that it could have also been during their normal course of business. 

The FBI deputy director also reportedly told Preibus that the story was BS, why would they do that?

I posed my question to you because there is supposedly a massive conspiracy between the Trump campaign/administration and Russia and I am wondering what the end goal is?

There is so much conspiracy theory being mixed in with the facts at this point it is getting crazy. 

So back to you, why is this worse than meeting with Australia? Do you know what they discussed?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you think their scheme is? Whats the end game of all these nefarious meetings? 

I don't know your history but surely you were outraged at past campaigns talking with foreign officials? 

Does it matter that the FBI and House Intel Committee head say there was no collusion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't get stuck proving a negative. What do you think they talked about and how do you think it was a meeting that went against the best interest of the American people. 

The implication is that there was some wrong doing, correct? What was it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh. I do not think it is Ironic considering the the corporate politicians no matter the side all oppose him. Whether it's McCain or Pelosi they are career politicians who have become multi millionaires while serving the public. Look up how Harry Reid made his millions, because it is all dirty dealing and abuse of power. So the irony is supposedly informed citizens in a Politics sub reddit jumping on the corporate messaging. 

The dislike of Trump has made people willing to jump in bed with self serving professional politicians and corporate media who have no interest is helping or serving the American people. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, some of us know all too well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the dirty part is an opinion at this point, there is no evidence of it. So, by extending the same logic we can make a similar argument across the board. Especially since the FBI and House Intelligence chair keep saying there is no evidence of wrong doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Flynn is the only one to lie about it, right? And that was lying to Pence. I think, honestly, because of the media frenzy Flynn felt like lying was the best thing to do to try to help all the Dem speculation to go away.

So for the one guy, it seems like it was a bad mistake and he resigned...which is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect Democratic voters, everyday citizens, but...The Democrats Inc. are quickly becoming an old and obsolete party. They are not offering any positive messaging or plans, the whole party has become a constant reaction to Trump.

I have similar criticism for Republicans during Obama. There corporate parties are in a constant pissing match and all we end up with as citizens is piss soaked clothes. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is in reference to Sessions? Did he say he didn't speak to them about campaign business, or he didn't speak with them? This is an important distinction for the claim.

So far I will trust the FBI saying there is no link, and the head of the House Intelligence committee saying there is no evidence of the campaign working with Russia. Everyone making the claim they worked together has to make many assumptions to reach that verdict.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it reaches anywhere near the conspiracy levels I see around here and from certain journalists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to know what he looks like, look for the heavy set old Russian man sitting with the Democrats during the State of the Union.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then get ready to need a lot of prison cells because many members of our government have met with Russian officials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is everyone who talks to Russian officials a traitor or only people you don't like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are any of our reps talking top Russia? Why was the Russian Ambassador sitting with Democrats during the State of the Union address? Why have an ambassador or any Russian official at all in the country?

How many of these questions have the same answer? Why was it so unimportant before but now it is a sign of a treasonous President? 

Why was it ok for Obama to make hot mic promises to Russia during the 2012 campaign?

Why was it ok for John McCain to lobby Russian officials for campaign contributions?

If we are going to make talking with Russians evidence of some grand conspiracy then it is much bigger than Donald Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there is no evidence that he is involved with Russia. It is purely conspiracy theory at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Investigating Donald Trump, F.B.I. Sees No Clear Link to Russia

https://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/01/us/politics/fbi-russia-election-donald-trump.html

House intel head: 'No evidence' of Trump campaign contact with Russia

http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/321350-house-intel-head-no-evidence-of-trump-campaign-contact-with-russia

They have been investigating and find no evidence, and then repeatedly state there is no evidence. This is getting ridiculous because it is now being put on the Trump administration to prove a negative.

But maybe if we keep talking about it and speculating people will just think it's true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ask journalists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, again, we're only 1 month in.
Yes, which is why everything should be tempered, praise and criticism.

Damn, Trump chasing wealth and Bannon chasing Power is a compelling image. I don't think they are fascists but if I did or wanted to write a book about it that seems like the best description I've heard yet.

I am trying to find details about VOICE, but it looks like he first mentioned it lastnight. 

I mean I voted Trump and I still support him. I don't call him king, and I think that is just a colloquialism that has come out the group of supporters on Reddit. I like the Trump community here, it is actually a fun subreddit if you like Trump.

I guess time will prove one of us right, but in the mean time thanks for chatting! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a big Carlin listener also. You are right about my response to his latest episode. I am glad he is saying it thought to keep me honest in my approach to it. I was a little surprised at Dan's over all response given his desire to break from the common mold of our political system. 

Even if you're right about them having fascist intentions, which obviously I disagree with, I don't think they would be able to pull off a fascist qoup of America. The executive branch while too powerful, as we have both agreed, is not powerful enough to take over the Nation. There is plenty of Trump dissent in the communities across the country that there does not seem to be the Nationalist fervor required to go along with some sort of Trumpian take over.

And what would be there goal? He ran on ending foreign interventionism, and reducing governemnt regulation. What would be the goal of a Fascist America under Trump? 

It is actually an interesting thought experiment that I wish I had more time for right now.

My believe in America, which i say often without explaining means believing in our foundations in personal liberty and the Consitution. Maybe I am applying it too liberally to Trump, but not Bannon, in my view.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't mean to imply you were an Obama defender, just that authoritarian has been par for the Presidential course. 

If they start shutting down people who oppose them, in the media and politically then we should worry about them being Fascists, but from what I have seen Bannon and Trump believe far too much in America to be fascists. You cannot support American principles and be a fascist. 

So far I have seen no fascist indicators.

As for the Boy Scout quip, this was my favorite part. I think that the people trying to draw a connection between Trump and Hitler are being disingenious. Dan carlin made a great point about history repeating itself recently on Dave Rubin's show. He spoke about how we recognize the humanity in history and we can recognize systems but that does not mean we will get the same results. I am parphrasing and probably horribly. 

So I may have over simplified with my Boy Scout example, in which case I was doing exactly what I am arguing other people are doing with Trump and Hitler.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personal thinking the connections to fascism or authoritarianism really start when you look for it. The cub scouts can be similar to Hitler Youth if you really want to make a case for it. 

I also think the powers of the Presidency appear amplified if you don't like what their doing, but the Presidency has been gathering power for a long time now. I thought it was pretty authoritarian when President Obama killed an American citizen without due process but I don't think he was a full blooded authoritarian. 

We are probably just split on this, and that's ok with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I misspoke, I meant it is not brought up by Trump, but his detractors. There are racist assholes that support him for sure, there are racists assholes who oppose him too. This conversation can turn into a black hole real quick. 

What have they done that is fascist or authoritarian so far though? I was just reading about how Trump is trending less authoritarian than Obama.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. It seems like you are applying your biases to other peoples words to be honest. As an American citizen you should get a gun and learn how to use it. But as long as you are focusing the conversation on race you are only making the situation worse and not actually helping anything.

You are obviously not willing to have a conversation though, as indicated by name calling and firm ideological statements. 

I will say if someone makes a distinction that distinction is important, wether or not you choose to ignore it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe some of them, but not the majority. I cannot defend every Trump supporter, i actually think he has a wide variety of types of supporters so to try to fit them all into one box doesn't work. I am consistently called all sorts of labels around here that do not match me simply because I defend Trump. This is not conversation.

Bannon definitely ties traditional christian values to his view for America, there is no denying that. I think this is an important discussion to have actually as a Nation because there was a tradition of Christian values for a long time in the country that has been slowly erroding...rightly or wrongly. But again, this has nothing to do with race, but more ideology. 

To have an honest discussion about Trump and Bannon we should address it they way you are now, not by making it a race thing. I see the attempts to discuss the two of them in terms of race, by either side, as a major impediment to having a real honest conversation.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, I don't know. But the fake market is helping my real retirement saving right now. In our office we try to keep an eye on it and shift stratgey for when the Market slumps. Who knows what Trump will do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i read an article about him referencing Evola, you know i found it interesting because we should not shun people from reading and referencing all sort of thinkers. But if he acts on it like the Italian Fascists acted on it then we may have a problem. But Bannon isn't President either.

To be honest, I read stuff that is intellectually interesting that I do not agree with 100% all the time. Lenin's the State and Revolution is something i will frequently reference but that does not make me a Socialist/Communist by any means. 

I really have not seen anything fascist come out of the administration yet, and having heard Bannon describe his own ideology it could be inspired by pieces of Evola...but he is not a mimic of Evola. 

The only time I see skin color brought up it is by people criticising Trump, not by him and not by Bannon. I recently re-watched Trump's New Deal of Black Americans for a discussion i was having with my brother and in the first five minutes he outlines it as a key part of his America First strategy. The implication being that Black America is a key part of America in Trump's view, which is contradictory to the White Nationalist claim.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the comment was about people from Asia, not Asian Americans. Which is less about race and more about non-Americans which you can take umbridge with, sure, but it is not a White thing...it is an American thing.

When taken out of context the comment does sound a lot worse though. I have read a lot about Bannon and watched his speeches/interviews. He never talks about White, but consistently speaks about Americans. He is also talks a lot about Christians, which again you can take umbridge with, but its never a skin color thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At no point did he deviate from the nationalist-populist ideology his administration has adopted 

The article never actually mentions white nationalist anything. He is a Nationalist for sure but White isn't part of the label. 

Saying it is white nationalism is an obvious attempt to turn non white people off to him but it doesn't come from Trump, it comes from commentators who don't like him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 401k has been on a steady climb which is great, but your right all the growth cannot continue forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nit-picking is so desperate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part about the Russia conspiracy theory is it can be tied to everything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. How many Trump supporters have you observed  in the wild.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol why attack people besides Trump for his decision. Seems like a low blow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but we can do both. Maybe in America our state should focus more on renewable and slow the subsidies of fossil but they aren't mutually exclusive, to start. 

This is a big plus for Musk being friendly with President Trump, he keeps the renewable conversation in front of mind if leadership. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we honestly don't know how much of fossil fuels is still available. With that being said I agree with the sentiment that we should be investigating and investing in alternative energy, even if just for its game changing capabilities. 

In essence we should do both, use fossil fuels and invest/investigate alternative energy. 

As a nation it serves our best interest to do both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Democrats what do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
