<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8068</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going out to the lounges, and the nightlife in general has a sense of adventure to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Niv Mizzet, the Firemind]] + [[Mindmoil]]

There's [[Curiosity]] and [[Teferi's Puzzle Box]], but Mindmoil feels more like an Izzet spell than the other two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a fun series, especially for a swords-n-sorcery junkie like me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't there a movie from the 90's called Warlock? Anyone here seen it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Land Fit for Heroes by Richard Morgan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tor's got them collected in a single volume, plus there's a new one called Wurms of Blearmouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rank 'em

1. Sojourn

2. Homeland

3. Exile

You can try the Sellswords Trilogy too. That and Dark Elf are Salvatore at his prime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite training sequence would have to be Bruce's recovery in The Dark Knight Rises. We don't see much of it, but the stakes were what made it enjoyable - you get me invested in the threat posed by the antagonist and the training sequence will be much more enjoyable. I was practically cheering for Bruce's return to Gotham and subsequent thrashing of Bane.

I can't think of anything in the fantasy genre, written, that really stands out for me. Much of what I've read in terms of training tends to have just been the character going from lesson to lesson. I never felt like there was any sense of urgency or danger, so these I tended to put aside for longer stretches of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.) I'm enjoying it

2.) They were proud of my love of reading

3.) No

4.) Elric by Moorcock

5.) The Crippled God

6.) Yes

7.) Probably R'hllor - dragons, fire, and Asshai sound like fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragon Stomper here. Blood Moon cripples the Eldrazi, but if I miss the Moon effect, Imma get curbstomped by the Eldrazi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play the dragon shell and have an uphill slog against miracles. Sneak and Show hurts, too. So does nic fit, since that one doesn't care about nonbasics and can run out some big critters and planeswalkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just straight mono red sneak with a couple of gambits if you wanna play high risk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next eight years are gonna be fun.

edit - thank you based centipedes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 06:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should capitalize on the safety pin craze, if they haven't already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if someone like SSJ3 Gotenks could've pulled off the save, or Mystic Gohan, in keeping with the idea that dead guys can't keep dropping out of the sky to save the Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could anyone have thrown that spirit bomb, or does Goku's powerlevel influence its strength? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it, I think Homeland is still a better experience for the new reader. To each his own, of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yourself, Sam and Lord Grimdark have mentioned the early Drizzt novels, so the contribution is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Silent Blade, originally book one in Paths of Darkness is a good read too. Sort of a mini setup for Servant of the Shard, book two in the Paths of Darkness Quartet and book one in the Sellswords Trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think The Silent Blade is the strongest of Bob's Legend of Drizzt entries. I remember thinking it was a fairly deep look at the characters, in the context of the novels that had come before.

edit - Origins Award, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I like Urusander and Hunn Raal. They seem alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roland Deschain and Elric for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get the best of both worlds with Malaz: one of the marines and her squad broke the language barrier by executing tax collectors and decorating the bars with their heads (they were doing a bar crawl lol). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did some geopoliticking in Pirate King in the sense of the common folk of Luskan getting caught in the crossfire between Drizzt's guys and the Pirate High Captains' flunkies. Lightly sprinkled compared to Martin and co, but it made the book enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked 3/4th of the Neverwinter books. Neverwinter (Book II) didn't need to be a full novel imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martin has a good context for the characters that do that, too. But it certainly isn't the predominate vibe in modern fantasy. The characters just act like people. Some are concerned with the rat race, some wanna have a good time etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave it three books. I felt that book three should have been book one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took them as palate cleansers between Malazan series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Pirate King* is the closest Bob's come to a good exploration of the D D standard of heroes taking down the big bad guy. Among the fandom, it has some of the lowest ratings while more battle-centric novels like *Siege of Darkness* tend to take the cake where ratings are concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick with his Sellswords Trilogy. You'll find his best talents being used to their fullest in that set of novels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this neck of the woods better than the Six Duchies. Stronger worldbuilding at play than in the first two Fitz trilogies. I haven't read Liveships, so I can't compare them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be that the Bakers are Osmund Saddler's family and we're playing as Osmund the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strelates, Napads and the chainsaw thing with the bone-saw were the best of the new BOWs imo. Raskal doesn't compare to the Regenerators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they don't like the anthem and what it stands for, they can leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly wasn't a tool when Barry got elected. Went to classes, same as usual. Continued through em same as usual even though I disagreed with President Obama on a number of issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait,

didn't Bernie say he was willing to work with Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Drizzt. The Dark Elf Trilogy - its about a character going on a hero's journey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP I had problems too, but mine were night and day from yours. I didn't find any of your problems in the text. Mine was mostly pace and character related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Leftrin and Thymara. Sedric's started acting like a twat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only in the game for Team Dragonstone tbh fam. The setting didn't really hook me until ADWD when we got more of the mysticism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dany is a f*cking idiot. She needs someone like Daario to help her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malazan Book of the Fallen

The Dark Tower

Elric Saga

Vlad Taltos

A Land Fit for Heroes

Broken Empire

Red Queen's War

Black Company


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't feel like the fate of the world was at stake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it practical. Vampires are inherently magical, so drinking blood = jacked up immune system.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote Legacy!

Standard for Prison!

MMGA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if there's black in the 75, then it is Green Black.

Lololol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't lol. 3 colors is 3 colors boyo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any Skreds running around at the modern event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't recall, really. A lot of Toni Morrison, something called Melanctha, some other random authors sprinkled throughout. It was an easy A, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like a pile of fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 19:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds better than the woe-is-me stuff I waded through in my college lit classes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved NoK, but found the other Malazan Empire novels to be a dropoff in quality. NoK felt like Ian doing his thing, while the others felt like Ian trying to do Erikson's thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 09:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Night of Knives is great. Everything else up to Assail is a poor imitation of Erikson and a massive dropoff in quality from NoK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 09:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the art in the LCG from FFG. I think GRRM has signed off on most of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 08:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Best Served Cold** does it for me. Fun bunch of miscreants with plenty of laughs along the way.

The names in TH are pretty good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 08:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish fake news would stop overhyping the apocalypse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 08:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> downvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kali the dragonborn - he gets high off the chemicals released by the human body during moments of high emotion. So he works as a headhunter for hire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...Trump saying mean things keeps them from doing their job? How does that even work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it well enough. The FM are f*cked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our man Trump is busting ass for the people. Love it! Meanwhile, the DNC has tightened its hold on Bernie again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 15:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took the EMP gun Batman had in TDKR and threw the EMP device into the melee weapons' handles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LDAR 7 kingdoms your tour is over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP how does Standard Showdown differ from your regular standard FNM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 02:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just assume my political affiliation and or identity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhea of the Coos. Nasty old bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first standard deck was Fires of Yavimaya.dec. I can confirm this.

edit - I see you Rebel, Dromar-Go and Nether Spirit players downvoting this comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fellowship dynamic is what I enjoyed most, I think. It reminded me of Two Towers or Return of the King where you have the fellowship of heroes doing into the dark land to deal with the darklord. Its the earthier motives that worked for me - "no money, no honey," keeping Colonel Flag alive because if he died, then the squad would die - as opposed to standing up against a nebulous evil simply because its "what's right."

I did find Croc lacking in backstory - nothing there but a mobster that got run out of Gotham. I was hoping for a little more, maybe black market organ trade or something like that. Seems fitting for someone prone to cannibalism.

I do hope the sequel plays more geopolitics - the comic's strength is the way it interweaves stuff like metahuman teams with geopolitics. The Jihad is a group I'd like to see tackled in the sequel - they attack America for war crimes we comitted in Qurac (Iraq analogue) and have a nifty set of superpowers. 

On the Marvel end, how well received was Shane Black's Iron Man 3? Having seen most every MCU movie sans Dr Strange and Civil War, I would say that Marvel has yet to top IM3; I would've added this if Mandarin had his magic rings or we got a cool extremis dragon like the one from the comics. Fang, I think he's called there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works for me - sounds closer to gardener than outline. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the only thing they left out of Boomerang's character in the movie is that he's a womanizer (though in the movie he helped them scout out Enchantress and Incubus's spell rig). In one of the comics he tried to trick some college coeds into doing a "model shoot" while the squad was trying to uncover some secret society hiding beneath the college.

I like beer, brawls, and women, so I found myself liking Boomer. Smith and Harley were the mains, though you can also throw in Diablo for his backstory as a gangbanger and Flag. Albeit with Flag his story is mostly told through the way he acts around the squad at the beginning vs the end.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like you could offset the women covering themselves thing by having something in there about how they want to minimize sun exposure to keep their women from developing skin cancers.

Just shower thoughts on my end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has Pat ever said whether he's the outliner or gardener type writer? Its something GRRM came up with. GRRM is the gardener. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red doesn't play by the rules. Its chaos baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can randomly screw you. Its red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 07:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the kind of fantasy we got in the original three Devil May Cry games. Great hero, fantastic designs, fun soundtrack. I still replay them to this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 07:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Book Series:

The Malazan Book of the Fallen

The Dark Tower Cycle

The Chronicles of the Black Company

The Elric Saga

Conan the Barbarian

Movies:

Conan the Barbarian (1982)

Suicide Squad

Hellboy

Hellboy II

Solomon Kane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viashino. They should become red's mainstay mini tribe. Combine their bounce effects with [[Pandemonium]] for maximum fun. You can also go [[Zirilan of the Claw]] + [[Dragon Tyrant]] with [[Blazing Shoal]] thrown in if the dragon ends up in your hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes are the ones that roll up their sleeves and get what needs done, done. It isn't all that interesting - just common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 11:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chick in my class loved SS...she said she kept waiting for it to turn into a trainwreck lol. I think I preferred SS slightly more than BvS because of it all being due to Waller being a dick. That and I been itching for a good fantasy movie ever since Hellboy II years ago, and SS delivered there.

But I did like BvS more than BB or TDK (and the Burton/Schumacher movies), but not more than TDKR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Qyburn is there to serve as an extreme counterpoint to the Citadel's supreme maesters. Marwyn, more likely than not, will end up as the happy medium between the unethical Qyburn and the science-oriented-yet-excessively-conservative maesters in the citadel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invasion [[Terminate]]. Favorite plot point in that block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah yes. The very first build cropped up late 06-into 07. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that Blood Moon build using [[Seething Song]] to power out the T3 [[Stormbreath Dragon]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 06:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DRAGON STOMPY**

Hehe always nice to see that deck in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 05:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hobb and Thrones? Try Memory, Sorrow and Thorn by Tad Williams. Along with Hobb, its a series that inspired GRRM to write ASOIAF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot and character are the meat of it. Worldbuilding is the window dressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got burnt out on the bridges thing.

I would say Wu, the setting for Malaz, the setting for Conan or maybe Mid-World from the Dark Tower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demons are psychic projections of the Primeval Dragons' ambitions, desires, and passions. They tend to take the form of weapons while angels often appear as armor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea. I'm only on Guns. The Amazon reviews for the Merlin cycle average a 4.5 for what its worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He fucked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corwin from **Nine Princes in Amber** quickly became one of my favorite characters in the fantasy genre. I'm liking his development in **Guns of Avalon** too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Blood Moon]]

Huehuehue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's that beach house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qyburn wanted to pursue his research. Serving the Brave Companions gives him the freedom to do so on the downlow. Ingratiating himself to the ruling family gives him the legal clout to continue his research without worrying about codes of ethic etc. I think that this is it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play with her arse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Company had more politicking than I expected, so there's that too. 

I have to recommend **The Farseer Trilogy**: Assassins, psychic bonds with wolves, dragons, and zombielike enemies with courtly politicking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it bad if I didn't struggle through them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 08:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say that I've seen Arale outside of the previews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're thinking far too much for this series, and I say that as someone that loves DBZ because he grew up with it. Comedy trumps all here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sounds like an earthly version of Zeno. Tiny, unassuming, could beat the tar out of everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comedy.

The rules are malleable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pride, mementos of past battles, personal choices, take your pick OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "An individual is free to have whatever they want, provided they have the power to obtain and keep it"


"Everyone seems preoccupied with the meaning of life. Red's not, because red already knows the answer. You see, your heart tells you what it needs to be fulfilled. All you have to do is listen to it and act accordingly. It's not a mystery."

"Green is the one color that doesn't want to change the world because green is convinced that the world already got everything right. The natural order is a thing of beauty and has all the answers to life's problems. The key is learning to sit back and recognize what is right in front of you."

The quotes I've pulled are most relevant to me, so looks like I am in the Jund. These are what guide me as an individual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs.

If there's potential, capitalize and hope you strike it rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i honestly figured Stein had hoped this would reveal some of Hillary's dishonest tactics where the votes are concerned. That or we get to see a three-way schlonging when the votes for all 3 are still for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gatewatch Saga also brings in a host of new problems - our main heroes feel like they came from a Saturday morning cartoon. At least the Weatherlight folks and Urza's nine titans felt a little bit more genuine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still run a BBE shell that replaces my 4 BBE with some mix of Huntmaster, Olivia, and Kalitas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
