<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8546</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Women Are Harassed Out of Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend wants to not kill these plants and has enlisted my help/Reddit account to try to identify them so she can look up care instructions. Any tips for identifying them would be much appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for help ID-ing these 4 succulents. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [W. Europe] [Indoor] Succulent house plants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isolated coral reefs are not healthier than those in more densely populated areas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shown photos of real scientists, people judged feminine women more likely to be teachers or journalists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rapid, low-temperature process adds weeks to milk's shelf life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say you're "operating as product designers, ethnographers, social scientists, and machine designers." How's that balance been? As engineers, how are you approaching the social sciences aspect? Have you consulted with social scientists?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U1 area isn't exactly going to relieve this, but I'd say riding on the bike path down Frankfurter/Karl-Marx Allee at rush hour is akin to driving on a highway almost the whole way. Tons of cyclists, all going different speeds yet somehow also clumping together. I actively take less direct routes to work when I bike to avoid the bike traffic on that street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was so excited to post this here (was going to go with Reuters--short and sweet, since the headline is basically all the info anybody has on this), and so disappointed that it was already up as a RT link. They must get a shit-ton of traffic from posts like this. I refuse to click through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Questionable study design aside, these results are hardly surprising given the research on nature and its mental health benefits. Here's a [good example](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4204431/). Here's [another](http://news.stanford.edu/2015/06/30/hiking-mental-health-063015/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anybody who wants to read this somewhere other than Russia Today, here's the coverage from [Reuters](http://www.reuters.com/article/turkey-security-education-idUSI7N1A3004) and the [Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/turkey-bans-all-academics-from-travelling-in-latest-post-coup-measures/2016/07/20/f3498b44-4de5-11e6-bf27-405106836f96_story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, I totally missed that sentence and skipped right to the figures on cost. For those whose reading skills are as bad as mine: 

"...the Senate of Berlin has embraced the Radbahn and is in the process of passing a provision to finance the project." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 10:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really clear whether this has any kind of city approval or buy-in, but would be great to have!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plan to build a bike highway under the U1 elevated track. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 10:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, though improvements to infrastructure lead to more bikes on the road, which means drivers get better at driving around them (and driving around bikes gets included in drivers-ed). Also cyclists ride more safely when there's infrastructure to accommodate their needs.

Some cities have non-profits that offer free classes on how to ride more responsibly/safely, like [Bike New York](http://www.bike.nyc/education/classes/). Nowhere near the scale you're right we need. But definitely helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bicycling needs two things to be safer: better infrastructure and better policing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AIDS deaths are falling in most countries worldwide, but the rate of new infections increased in [74] countries over the past decade  including Egypt, Pakistan, Kenya, the Philippines, Cambodia, Mexico, and Russia.

The studys being announced at a [press conference]( http://www.healthdata.org/events/conference/international-aids-conference-2016) right now, and will be published in The Lancet HIV today. 

Edit: Here's a link to the study: http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanhiv/article/PIIS2352-3018(16)30087-X/abstract 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rate of new HIV infections increased in 74 countries over past decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice for early career researchers on building an academic reputation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 12:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 11:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Here's the answer: [Research collaboration between scientists in the UK and other EU countries](/answer). More info [here](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/uk-scientists-rely-on-the-eu-and-dread-brexit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wieviel Geld wrdet ihr bei einer Hochzeit schenken? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich gehe bald auf eine Hochzeit. Braut und Brutigam sind beide Freunde von mir, zhlen aber nicht unbedingt zu meinen fnf besten Freunden. Wir sind alle gerade mit dem Studium fertig, also berufsttig, aber verdienen auch nicht auergewhnlich viel. Ich war noch nie bei einer deutschen Hochzeit. Wrde in meiner Heimat 50-100 Euro schenken und denke, das wre auch in diesem Fall angemessen. Aber die Frage bleibt: 50 oder 100? Knnt ihr mich aus einheimischer Perspektive beraten? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, other outlets did a much better job covering this research. [How the professionals do it](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/07/12/upshot/surprising-new-evidence-shows-bias-in-police-use-of-force-but-not-in-shootings.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NYT, who [also reported on this](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/07/12/upshot/surprising-new-evidence-shows-bias-in-police-use-of-force-but-not-in-shootings.html) , ran a piece where the researcher who did the study [answers some of their readers' questions about it](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/07/12/upshot/surprising-new-evidence-shows-bias-in-police-use-of-force-but-not-in-shootings.html). A really interesting behind-the-scenes look that shows how many factors can affect results in a study like this.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I wonder if the ability to do this after birth impacts the way animals relate to the world around them as adults.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious to know how the mothers were selected for the study. Anybody have journal access?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7th grade science teacher loved cockroaches. Kept them as pets in the classroom (not that weird for a science teacher), and would let them crawl all over her while she taught (weird for anyone).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 17:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tried to be friends for like a week. Weren't compatible (she like to party and came home drunk every night, wasn't my scene). We stopped hanging out, but were civil and friendly to each other until she moved out at the end of the semester to move in with a friend. Nobody else moved in, so I got a double to myself second semester of freshman year. Everybody wins!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can Pack Heat at the Republican Convention But Leave Your Nunchucks at Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 17:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Embassy official put a staple in my passport right through the part that says not to perforate it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a log in half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fried in a mixture of oil and butter (buttery taste with a higher smoke point) in a seasoned cast-iron skillet. Over easy to the point the yolk is *barely* starting to solidify on the edges, but is still almost completely runny. Edges of the white starting to brown/crisp. Seasoned with salt and pepper before flipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How scientific culture discourages new ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 17:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Submission Statement

I had been aware of the notion that scientists don't want to challenge the leaders in their fields, and also that innovative research often appears in journals with lower impact scores (at least it always seemed that way to me), but never considered the phenomena in conjunction with each other. Surely then there are more than these two things, but other factors slowing down innovation. The flawed peer-review process? Limited actual commitment open science (beyond lip-service)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How scientific culture discourages new ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 17:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I missed it! Am at work in Mitte. We just had rain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 00:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong that that was carelessly worded. I don't really see it as critical to the core arguments, though, which center on the ways *some* states make things harder on top of that. 

I think this is intended for an international audience, since he mentions that elections are state-run and that voter registration is a thing. I read this as him explaining that election day is on a weekday (as opposed to on a Sunday, when many other countries hold elections). But yeah, you're right that that's only an issue in states without early voting. I'd be happy to scrap the whole damn system and just have everyone vote absentee!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 00:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, early voting and no-excuse absentee voting (including mail voting) are great. If they existed everywhere, this would be much less of a problem. The problem (at least in terms of the cost argument) isn't with those states, it's with the 13 others you mention. 

Every citizen gets a vote. That's how democracy works. It's not everybody in 75% of the country gets a vote, plus the people who can afford it among the remaining 25%. The 37 states you mention illustrate that it's possible and reasonable to put mechanisms in place that make it easier, not harder, for people to vote. That's what the article's calling for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More easily than dogs, according to the guy spearheading this whole thing. Apparently they have to make sure they imprint on a human right at birth though to make them "gentle enough," which seems prudent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not saying it's unreasonable to prove your residence and status, he's just saying there should be multiple ways to do it.

Let's do the math: even assuming there's no fee to get a copy of a birth certificate, marriage certificate, and ultimately license, you'd need a day for each if you're traveling to different offices that are far away. Even if they're close, maybe you can't just get an hour off work, maybe you either work a whole shift or you don't work at all. At minimum wage, that could be $60-180 in lost wages just to get your ID. Plus another $60 to miss work on election day (and then maybe the person covering for you--likely someone from the same socioeconomic group--isn't voting). Throw in the logistical challenges of getting all that done if you don't have a car? Forget it. 

But let's say you do have a car, and it was just $60 total in lost wages, spread over the time it takes to get an ID and go to the polling place on separate days, if you're living hand-to-mouth, that's probably not $60 you have to spare. $60 is a week's worth of food for your kids (maybe two). I'd chose feeding my kids over voting any day. But I shouldn't have to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 23% of all US workers, and 9% of full-time workers don't receive any paid vacation at all. So yes, most people get some. But that's still a lot of people not getting any. 

[Source](http://cepr.net/documents/publications/no-vacation-update-2013-05.pdf) (p. 4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of jobs don't offer any paid vacation (especially minimum wage jobs). Though it's often possible for these employees to schedule unpaid vacation, people working in these kinds of jobs generally can't afford to miss out on that salary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine you're trapped in an avalanche, and a paw breaks through the snow. "I'm saved" followed by "Holy shit, it's a f*cking wolverine."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They can be trained to sniff out humans specifically, and can learn to do so in as little as a week; the programs founders say theyre actually smarter and easier to train than dogs, which are used currently to find avalanche survivors. 'Anything you can train a dog to do, you can train a wolverine to do, five times quicker,' Miller told Outside." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Wolverines are being trained to rescue people from avalanches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this change in principle, but I find it kind of icky that they named an Asian woman "Dr. Orchid" given how often Asian women are compared to "exotic flowers" in an objectifying way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the intimate look at daily life for (at least some, urban) people in N. Korea. The somewhat familiar carriage interiors really drove it home. Must have been so awkward to take those photos. Don't know if I could have pushed past that feeling of awkwardness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 14:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We already have probiotics for our bodies, so why not our homes? There's so much knowledge already about harmful microbes, but as we learn more about healthy ones, it'll make sense to really curate those in our environments. Parents with newborns could even get microbe kits to introduce certain bacteria and fungus into their homes to build strong immune systems, prevent allergens, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. See hint 7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, (7th) [more about the work than the people](/hint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 12:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But local authorities think theyve come up with a solution: a prosthetic penis."

"From now on, Heracles will wear his own anatomy only during special park ceremonies. Afterwards, he will be once again dis-membered, says Phelippot." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a statue in France has been retrofitted with a detachable penis because people kept stealing the regular one. Authorities store the penis for safekeeping and reattach it for special events. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 12:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 10:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would watch the hell out of that YouTube series. Glad your colleagues are amused--I once had to attend an HR seminar about fostering a good work environment. It was stereotypically bad, with advice that included talking about hobbies, with the caveat that we should NOT talk about "inappropriate" hobbies like pole dancing class. The general consensus afterward was that people who do pole dancing as a hobby are awesome and we would want to know about it so we can congratulate them on their awesomeness, HR be damned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 09:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. You'll want to hide that under an answer tag, by the way. That way people new to the thread don't get any unwanted hints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 09:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but (6th) [Academia is the right place to focus](/hint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 23:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York City has a chief rodentologist. Which makes sense, but I never thought of anybody having that job until he was all over TV talking about how hurricane Sandy flooding would affect the rat population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We too had four lovely days in Bernkastel-Kues. The weather was tolerable.* The house had everything, great that there were two bathrooms for six people. Thank you for the very generous offer with arrival and departure. 

The six people from Wuppertal, Remscheid, and Velbert

*Literally: "One could live with the weather."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of late to the conversation on this, but I wanted to share something I read in [this interview with a NASA scientist](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/celebrating-womens-contributions-to-science) that has really stuck with me. It's just great advice: 

"My advice to young women is to have determination and not take things personally, especially negative feedback. Know that you will make mistakes and people will call you out on them. When this happens, its easy to take it personally and let it lower your self-esteem. Criticism doesnt mean youre not a good scientist or engineer! You need to have determination: learn from it, correct it, and continue to work hard; then you will earn respect from your colleagues."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Closer, but still no. 5th: [At least not import of goods. Has more to do with knowledge.](/hint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Edit: 4th [It relates more specifically to a certain branch/industry/occupation type](/hint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
