<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject721</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what did you guys think of Monte Carlo this year? Also a few rules questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit; mistyped the title, only 1 rule question -- just meant to type that I had a few questions in general.


I kind of lost interest in rally last year and didn't watch any, and I think I only caught maybe half of the 2015 season.

Decided to resubscribe to WRC+ the other day and watched the first rally. Really enjoyed it, I think it's going to be a great season. I wasn't aware of all the changes; namely bigger turbos. New manufacturer is always exciting. Generally, I never cared for Ogier. He's a fucking phenomenal driver and I respect the hell out of him, but he was always very impersonal and just gave off a douchey vibe IMO but this year he actually seemed like a pretty cool dude. Felt super bad for the Belgian going out like that, he was doing so well. Ott Tanak did pretty damn well too; last I remember of him was the "Titanak" when he accidentally went off a cliff into a river or something. Also, where's Mads this year? I saw he's doing some other rally; is he out of WRC entirely or just not participating in MC? Looks like Kris Meeke inherited his hardware problems :P and also why is Mikkelson in WRC2 / racing a Skoda?


Lastly, if a driver does not finish an individual stage in a rally, how is their overall time "scored"? Like say a driver basically totals his car on the last stage of day 2 but is able to compete and finishes on day 3. Do they just assign the Slowest time for the stage they didn't finish? Or is it a weighted average, or...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Great Hunt] Newcomer's thoughts on TGH, just finished book #2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted the other week having blown through the first half of TGH and wanted to share my enjoyment... guess I'm back.

---

**Broad strokes**

Awesome. I'm amazed at how quickly I finished this book, as someone who is still fairly new to reading for fun. Rand squaring off against Ba'alzamon was way more satisfying this time than EotW. I felt sincerely terrible for Egwene; being a damane seems terrible. Reminded me a little bit of the "Reek" chapters in ASOIAF. Overall though, I loved how much we start to learn about The White Tower and The One Power and just everything. The Ways are cool and the Black Wind is terrifying. Nynaeve's trial to become an Accepted was my favorite part of the whole book, I think. Can't wait to go crawl into bed and start #3.

---

**More specifically / Points of Interest**

I feel like I totally missed the ending to Chapter 48. Min finds Rand and then Lanfear, a Forsaken, just pops up out of nowhere to say "Hi" and then disappears. *What?* Like the Forsaken serve The Dark One, no? Why didn't she just fuck up Rand's unconcious body. Also, I need to go back and find a description of Selene, absently-minded wondering if they're the same person... I have nothing beyond my distrust for Selene / her absence in Cairhein to link these two as one, but I also can't think of a reason it might not be true. And would anyone be able to sum up what I should know about Lanfear by this point? Like the name rung a bell before "Forsaken" was dropped but I could only think, "I recognize that name." 

There are just so many characters, I can't keep them all 100% straight.

Is Liandrin the Black Ajay? I don't *think* so, but yet again I feel like I'm forgetting a detail from before. And what she did was definitely a [dick move](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rWY47bW8K3s). **Please don't spoil who IS, if it is not Liandrin**.

---

**Final question** -- does anyone know if the [WoT Re-Read Blog series on Tor.com](http://www.tor.com/series/wot-reread/) is safe from spoilers? I don't want to accidentally have something ruined / pointed out. Obviously stay away from the posts for the books I haven't read yet, but would it be a bad idea to look at the posts for each book as I finish them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started noticing an unpleasant noise under acceleration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started noticing this fairly quiet noise. It only seems to happen above 40 mph. Doesn't matter the gear, RPM doesn't seem to matter either but it's tough to tell for sure. I can hear it on the highway at 2.5-3K RPM or on the street at ~2K or below.

Haven't really had the time to investigate it unfortunately, but as soon as I put my foot on the gas, even the tiniest amount, I can hear a kind of faint "airy" noise. It sounds to my **non**-expert opinion like it's having trouble "breathing". I popped the hood but couldn't see anything obvious.

It hasn't been *especially* cold, a little above freezing for the most part. I had winter tires put on recently and thought my brakes sounded different / feel more while braking, so I've been paying extra close attention to every little noise. Not sure if this this something I just never noticed, or if it's actually a new noise.

Is there a way I can look up to see if my vehicle is still under the factory warranty? It's only got 19K on it, but it's a '14... Not sure when the 3 years is up. Also, any ideas what I might be hearing?

I'll try to get a recording today after work but with just a cell phone I think you'll get nothing but wind noise... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does your ADHD medication effect marijuana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I don't care about competing with other drivers, is there a reason Not to mod my car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Fiesta ST and I only got to partake in 1 autocross event in my region last year. 

When I have the money, I'd like to buy the Cobb "Stage 3" kit which includes an improved rear motor mount, intercooler, exhaust system, and an AccessPort which comes with an array of engine maps preconfigured.


So this would push me into a different class. But if I don't care about being the fastest / winning, is there any reason I should **not** do this? I just want to have fun, that's all I care about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No spoilers: Do you think it'd be feasible to actually skip the first book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little over half way through book #2 and I've been talking to my other Reading friends about how much I enjoy it, despite how much I struggled to read #1. It took me three separate tries to finish the first book, though I'm much more into reading now than the last 2 times I had picked it up. 

So they're a little apprehensive because of my experience with EotW. We're all into epic fantasies, starting with A Song of Ice And Fire, then Mistborn and Stormlight, but now we've all branched off into reading our own things.

Just curious, do you guys think one could still appreciate the series if one only read a synopsis of the first book? 

While it is slow, the pacing did a good job of building a sense of fear and paranoia amongst the characters. I think a lot might be lost without actually reading about Mat's dagger, as well as the relationships / dynamics between all of the characters. Particularly Nynaeve as she feels very strongly about *everything*.

On the other hand, because it's 14 friggen books, I think that there's enough to come that it wouldn't make such a huge difference if you skipped #1. But again, I'm only half way through #2 so what do I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did women do (or use?) before tampons were invented? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Great Hunt] Just finished Chapter 23 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. It took me so much to push through the first book. Overall I liked it, enough to continue cleaely, and I'm glad I did. 

Nynaeve's entire "test" was cool. I don't much care for the Lan love arc, it seemed to come out of left field in the first book -- for both characters -- or maybe I just really am that oblivious? So the third arc was a little cheesy I thought, but then she just says "To hell with you, and hell with your Ass Sedai rules" and fucking portals her way out. And then finally the Amrylin.

I just thought it was a really fucking cool and "rewarding" chapter. I'm enjoying TGH so much more than EotW and this chapter just really sealed the deal.

I told myself I was going to alternate reading something by Jordan and then once that's finished I'd something by Sanderson until I've finished both. But I just ordered book number 3, so we'll see about that.

None of my friends have read WoT and I just needed to freak out after that chapter.

Oh and also I accidentally saw l a thread titled "Does anyone else not like Nynaeve?" or something like that. I didn't read it, but 1/2 through book number 2 I can definitely get it so far. 

She has like 3 modes: Overbearing mother / Condescending-tone mother, Hate Aes Sedai, Random love interest out of nowhere. I just want to yell at her, "You get to be a badass wizard. Shut up and say thank you!" OK maybe not 'Thank You' after having to leave behind her home in that second Arch, but you get the point! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about dog tag silencers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this is the wrong sub, but I don't know where to ask this. 

My brother was in the national guard and passed away in November. I started wearing his dog tag, and then over Christmas my mother gave me this beautiful necklace pendant with his ashes. 

I want to wear them both, but any time I move at all they clink together and it's very annoying. I looked around for dog tag silencers, but all I can find are this style: 

https://img1.etsystatic.com/000/0/6638710/il_570xN.292084419.jpg

These don't work for me as the pendant can and does clink against the exposed metal. 

I've temporarily solved this by wrapping the dog tag in paper, then putting the silencer on but this is not a very good solution. I shower with them on, and obviously the paper won't hold up. 

**Question / TLDR:** Do they make dog tag silencers which **fully** cover it? Ideally I want something like what I linked above, but with a clear plastic that goes over the "body" of the tag itself, rather than just the edges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone used udemy before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've *heard of* udemy but I don't know anyone who has paid for their services / educational materials. 

They have a 52-hour course on C#   Unity on sale right now for only $10.

I've got a degree and work as a programmer using C#/.NET primarily, and I've followed an array of tutorials on Unity's website and a few random series I've found on YouTube. So it's not like I **don't** have a foundation. But I do have ADHD and I think a more structured approach to dabbling in game dev might help me more than trying to find random tutorials online, or dicking around with an original project only to get overwhelmed and give up within a month.

Just wondering if it's worthwhile? This is the 'syllabus': [link](https://www.udemy.com/unitycourse/?utm_source=facebook utm_medium=udemyads utm_campaign=NEW-FB-PROS-TECH-Dev-NY-UnityNY-EN-ENG_._ci_258316_._sl_ENG_._vi_TECH_._sd_All_._la_EN_._ utm_term=_._ag_Unity-NY-LAL-US-2P-Combo-_._ci_258316_._._pi_1454876351219091_._gi_all_._ai_18--65_._an_n4m3nj_._lo_United%20States_._ k_clickid=d807dd1d-9746-47f2-8548-8200721a74fa_115543800).

The reviews seem positive /shrug. Their mobile site seems extremely slow, so that's marginally concerning but it could also just be my shitty phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Eye of the World] Issue with the ending / Anyone able to explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished book #1 over Christmas weekend. Overall, I enjoyed it. The first half was so very slow but when they finally get to Caemlyn it really starts to pick up. But then the last few chapters when they go to the Eye just felt... I don't know what the word is. Not *rushed*, but something like that.

Aside from Lan   Moraine, the rest of our party is mostly defenseless. Yea they've been practicing with their weapons, but they've had almost no real experience.

Then Rand just suddenly goes Beastmode and severed Bazalmon's dark tether thing and now he's dead and everything is OK. Our teenaged sheepherder just squared off with the big baddie and it felt so anticlimactic, premature, hard to believe and so on.

I'm 1/4 of the way finished with The Great Hunt, so obviously I enjoyed it enough to keep reading  (and know more about the Dark One than at the end of EotW) but I periodically think back to the end of the first book and just don't "get" it. It felt like if you watched The Matrix and movie transitioned from Neo training with Morpheus in the dojo after he's first brought into the real world, then jump to Neo facing off against the group of men with the Merovingian in the second movie -- in terms of prowess / strength gain.

I just can't help but think that Rand should *not* have been able to do that so soon or so easily.


Is this a sort of RAFO thing, or is it just like, "Yep he's a badass because the wheel weaves it"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning on a very limited budget? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to learn to watercolor but I've got a seriously limited budget this month due to some unexpected expenses. Anyways, this is what I have:

* $5 approximately a thumb's width across for painting miniatures. Not sure what the bristles are made of.
* 5.58.5 inch Sketch pad (so, not meant for paint obviously)
* $4 Crayola set of watercolors

I know that a good artist can make a nice painting even with some pretty poor quality supplies. However, I also fully realize the importance of using quality supplies and the difference they make -- I simply just don't have the money to fund the hobby.

Anyways, I have two questions: 

* Should I even bother trying to learn with these very limited resources, or would that just be an exercise in frustration? 
* If you guys think it *might* be reasonable to give it a shot, any tips? Controlling the water on the brush and having just these dinky little ovals of paint is really difficult and time consuming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what breed this guy is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to handle my relationship wth my nephew since my brother passed away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Familial Details: My brother passed away in November. He was going through a very rocky time with his wife, who wasn't exactly high on my list for a Sister In Law. They were separated and my brother was living with my parents, but they weren't legally divorced yet. They have a son, my nephew, who will be turning 4 next spring. I live ~450 miles from all of my family.

---

I was home for Christmas last week and my parents went to visit their grandson on Christmas Eve but I didn't go with them because I don't much like my sister in law's family. But also because I just didn't have the strength to see my brother's son.

I never really had any relationship or interactions with my two uncles when I was young, and now that I'm older my aunts all got divorced and I don't see the uncles anymore, ever. I didn't want it to be that way with my nephew, I wanted to be a part of his life -- especially since I don't particularly want kids of my own. Maybe be the cool rich uncle who spoils him, or just help keep him on the right track as my brother wasn't the smartest, nor his wife.

But now... I've just been feeling confused or unsure of what to make of my relationship with my nephew. He's still family and all, but without my brother, combined with the distance, it's different somehow. I feel selfish for "withdrawing" because I don't like my SIL and her family but I don't know what to do or anything.

Any of you guys been through something similar? Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it OK to get sterling silver wet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 21:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pendant that is meant to store ashes. It is sterling silver.

Is it OK to shower with this on? I've never owned a piece of jewelry in my life. Wikipedia says it's a fairly non-reactive metal so it sounds like I should be fine but what do I know... I'm also concerned about water getting *in* it.

Edit: Thanks for the input everyone. Appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TFW you ask your parents for a lighter for the first time, in a state that just legalized. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Headshops in the suburbs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm home for the holidays and forgot my glass pipe at home. I'm near the tri-state border; Oxford/Webster/Dudley/Charlton/Southbridge area... Any suggestions on where to buy a pipe? I'd rather not have to drive all the way into the city but Google is failing me. I can't believe there isn't anywhere to buy a pipe out here.

I saw [this thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/WorcesterMA/comments/5g6iy6/headshops/) posted earlier this month, but that seems to all be *within* Worcester. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need a dog, you guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] How to pronounce "Ogier"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with the French last name Ogier, but I'm sure that's not how it's supposed to be pronounced in WoT... So how do you pronounce it? 

I'm *almost* done with Eye of the World, just got to Caemlyn and it seems like the word is only going to get used more frequently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frozen chair lifts in Sweden (source in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Question about Arcanum Unbounded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked up the hardcover today. I've read everything Mistborn and everything Stormlight.

I intend to read everything Sanderson has published, but haven't yet started any of his other stuff.

Should I avoid reading the non-Scadrial/Roshar stories in AU until I've read the other books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corolla owners: How is your Winter driving experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend bought a 2014 Corolla LE Eco last year. It has about 30K miles on it.

Last winter he complained about how poor it handles on the snow, how light and floaty and slippery it feels. This weekend we got a light dusting, probably 2" max. I commented to him how I was surprised that my Fiesta ST had no issues, as I figured with all that torque and lightweight it was going to be bad. Don't have the money for winter tires this year.

He said his Corolla was already slipping last night, before all of the snow had even fallen.

For those of you in colder / snowy climates, how has it been?

Also, I was wondering what tires come stock on the car? I found measurements, but couldn't find brand / model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about OEM wheel measurements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have an '03 Touring, [this style](http://i235.photobucket.com/albums/ee132/Boma1982/IMG00122.jpg).

I'm trying to sell the wheels and someone asked me:

 What is the hub hole diameter size in the middle of the rim?

But I can't seem to find the measurement. Just stuff for the lug nut pattern, offsets, or tire /wheel width... Does anyone here know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's the FiST hold up with a proper track day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an HPDE school near me that has Novice classes available for the 2017 season at Watkins Glen International in New York.

For those who have taken their FiST out to a proper track day, not just autocross, how is it? I'm concerned about it overheating primarily. But any other concerns?

I did this once, two years ago in my 350Z but it was actually pretty intimidating and I was a bit out of my element. But now that I've done some autocross, and will have done more by the time this event rolls around I'll be more confident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Largest wheel / tire size? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really really don't want to spend the money on winter tires this year. I have the winter tires from my 350Z in the attic still. I'm not sure of the measurements off the top of my head but I want to say they're on the stock 18x8.5" wheels.

I suppose buying wheels with the FiST's bolt pattern might be equally as expensive, if not more, than winter tires, but assuming that is cheaper, can these tires fit the FiST OK?

I've had no luck trying to sell them on Craigslist to fund new ones of appropriate size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My coworker refuses to every remotely consider the possibility he's wrong; how can I talk to my boss about this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a software engineer and I've been at my company for about 2 year and have been employed in my field for 4 years since graduating. Database work is by far my weakest skill and I greatly prefer programming applications.

Yesterday, a coworker of mine on the Database team mentions to me a recent update I made to one of our modules isn't working right. Half of the data that's supposed to be written to a file is missing. After some tooling around, I identified that the data I was receiving from the DB was in the incorrect order. I tell him this, and he tells me that it's in the right order when he generates it on his end blah blah blah it **must** be an issue with how the code deals with hundreds of thousands of records in memory and I'm not doing something right.

Because DB work is my weakest skill, he's been employed here way longer, and has been working in the field in general way longer than I have, I take his word for it. Spent literally all afternoon researching what could be going wrong, then for shits and giggles I decide to run the DB code on the DB itself... Sure enough it's in the wrong fucking order. He didn't even bother to check. I called him over and showed him exactly where the data was wrong in the application side code and he assured me it was correct in the DB.

(If you're asking yourself, "But /u/subject721 why didn't you just check the DB in the first place? Could have saved yourself hours of effort" it's because the DB code that runs takes a solid 20+ minutes to execute and if I let it run while I'm trying to figure out what's wrong on the code side then it'll take even longer, so I took his word for it trusting his experience in the field)

I get it -- we all make mistakes. I'm not mad his script is broken. But what the fuck, he didn't even try to confirm what I told him I suspect to be the issue before dismissing me.

And this isn't the first or even the second time I've had a problem with this guy. Shortly after I started working here, we did a production update and a module I worked on was no longer working. "Well it's got to be something the code is doing". It took me a while to determine the cause of the problem was because he simply lost the database scripts I gave him. Normally I'd just email the files to the DBA, but since I was new at the company he specifically instructed me on where to upload the files to our network where he maintains a list of all the DB changes. But somehow he lost the file, and even though I was like "I'm pretty sure this is just running the old DB script" he was insistent he didn't miss anything and that I missed a something in the actual code for the update.

There was a third incident as well, which happened sometime between these two incidents but I honestly don't remember the details. Another co-worker, who is also relatively new at the company, has shared a lot of my frustrations with this guy and has some other complaints of his own about this dude too.

I really wanted to talk to our boss yesterday at the end of the day, but I decided not to. I was frustrated and probably wouldn't have articulated myself well. Hell, I don't think I would be any better today.

Have any of you guys had to deal with an over-confident coworker who refuses to even *consider* he might be wrong unless you jump through hurdles proving it? What can I do / how could I talk to my boss about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about Polymorph </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This spell is worded so poorly.

My party last night got into a pretty big battle when our Druid polymoprphed the creature into a harmless rabbit then killed it.

I was like, "I'm pretty sure it doesn't work that way" then we re-read the spell and there was a bit of confusion but we just let it ride.

For next time though, if you turn a monster into something much much weaker, kill that thing, it turns back into the original form with an amount of HP lost equal to the HP of the thing it was turned into right?

Like say it has 50 HP and you turn it into something with 5 HP, kill that 5 HP then it reverts back to it's original form at 45, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What RPM does yours idle at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a '14 with 17K miles on it. Recently, maybe a week or two ago, I started it up and it would not "settle". The RPMs were slowly changing between 1-1.5K

I let the engine warm up and drove to work without issue.

More recently, it was idling *really* low. 700-800RPM, the car was rattling like it was going to stall. Again, got to with with no issue.

The other day it was at a steady 1K while I let it warm up... So what's the deal? Should I be concerned? This is my first turbo charged car, is an inconsistent idle normal?

What does yours idle at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short stupid question about drive-through car washes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is the difference between a Touch car wash or Touchless? I'm a pleb that uses drive-through car washes but even though I ask / pay for touchless, they still drape all those things over it. I've never done non-touch, so I don't know if those use additional, more aggressive machines?

I've been contemplating plastidipping my Fiesta ST. The wiki on /r/plastidip says not to use Touch car washes, but I'm afraid even the "touchless" ones will still be bad for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get involved in local and state politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 26, moved to NYS 3 years ago but only became an official resident of Buffalo a year ago. I am registered to vote and will be doing so next Tuesday.

While voting in the Presidential election is certainly important, I think it's arguably more important to get involved in local and state politics... But I have absolutely no idea where or how to get started.

Trying to google around provides an array of websites but none of them have any real, "good" information. Mostly just dates for when to vote, but no real information on candidates or policies or... Anything.

Can anyone here help? Where can I get information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it equally difficult to engine swap 2 front-engined layouts as it would be to swap a rear / mid into a front engine car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that recent 458-GT86 video floating around, this question popped into my head.

I wasn't sure if the orientation the engine is the same for mid or rear engined vehicles as it would be for regular front engined vehicle.

So basically, in a FR car, is the forward-facing part of an engine the same as the forward-facing part on a MR / RR vehicle?

If not, how the hell do you even do something like this? Can you simply just... Turn it around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we move this UI element so it doesn't block the preview window...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if you swung an impossibly long stick in an arc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brewers Tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked up the Brewers a little while ago. Running a Tapper, Hooper, Spigot, Scum, Friday and whoever else list is quite straight forward: Knock 'em down and murder their stupid faces.

I tried playing Esters for the first time last week. I think I ran Esters, Mash, Scum, Friday, and Stave.

Felt like I had absolutely no idea what I was doing. Played against Morticians. Scalpel, thankfully. Struggled to keep the ball and don't think I ever scored, though we didn't get to finish the game as my opponent got wife aggro.


I just picked up Quaff last night and I'm eager to try him out, he seems like he's going to be a lot of fun wrapping and pushing my opponent a million inches.

So, yea, any tips for Esters / Quaff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for staying on a diet / healthier living? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just so damn impulsive and live in the city so I have countless food options in a quarter mile radius from my apartment.

It's so fucking difficult to buy groceries, cook a decent dinner, not walk around the corner too the convenience store and get something deliciously unhealthy.

Any of you guys have any tips for dealing with dieting frustrations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My motherboard is slightly(?) defective; what are the implications? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 weeks ago my 5 year old computer shit the bed. I replaced the motherboard, CPU, and RAM. I bought an EVGA Z170 FTW edition, i5-6500, and 8GB of DDR4 RAM.

In the BIOS, my computer was reporting only 4GB of RAM in one of the banks and then just said "unrecognized" in the other bank, and Windows was *highly* unstable.

I RMA'd the RAM and bought some 2x8GB kit of PNY memory from Best Buy just to hold me over until NewEgg processes my replacement.

Well, BIOS only reports 8GB now and Windows is still unstable. Can't run any applications, can't shut down, can't open the task manager -- can't do anything other than boot to my desktop reliably.

Did a fresh reinstall of Windows using the built-in repair utility in Windows 10. This fixed my usability issues! Now Windows runs perfectly. But my computer is still only detecting 8GB of RAM.

I *really* don't want to disassemble my PC, RMA the motherboard, wait for a replacement, and re-build the whole thing.

I'm wondering what are the implications if I were to just deal with my computer as is? Obviously I'm shorting myself on my memory, won't be able to take advantage of dual channel etc. but is there really any other problem? I'm concerned if something more serious goes wrong in the future, then who knows what...

I did download the latest chipset drivers from EVGA's website, but I haven't upgraded the BIOS. Full disclosure, I've never flashed the BIOS before and I'm afraid of fucking it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumb question about Charge rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A	model	may 	not	declare	a	Charge	 if	it 	is	currently	engaged	by	an	enemy	model.	A	model	may 	not	target	an	enemy	model	that	it	is	currently	engaging 	with 	a	 Charge.

Can someone explain exactly what the second sentence means?

I found out yesterday that my local scene has been playing this very wrong.

 We've basically been reading it as "May not target a model with a Charge if it is currently engaging" -- as in, if Seenah and Obulus are duking it out, I couldn't charge Obulus with Jaecar because he is engaging Seenah.

I know now that is incorrect.... So what exactly is this rule saying? Is that too prevent shenanigans with models that have Counter-Charge? ie "You ended your activation and now I get to Counter Charge even though we're both engaging"?

Furthermore: If I have Counter-Charge, it **does** trigger it my opponent's Charge fails to get them into melee, right?

**Edit** Re-reading it, it's basically just saying you can't charge a model you're already in melee with. So in my situation above, Seenah can't charge Obulus because Seenah is already engaging Obulus. Is that correct?

**Double Edit**: Thanks for the clarification everyone. I have no idea how we got it so wrong this whole time! It's definitely been a "least favorite" rule, glad one of the guys noticed this. I've been gimping Seenah so hard this whole time!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to catch / break upon receiving an XmlHttpRequest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My web application sends an ajax request to the server with an object that has 4 million characters in it.

This results in an exception being thrown as the default max length in the JavascriptSerializer class is roughly 2 million characters.

So the server gets the request, tries to deserialize the data and it crashes before my Controller receives the method call.

I've looked at an array of SO threads which suggest adding a key to my web.config file but this did not solve the problem.

Anyone know what I can do?

Chrome Dev Tools are able to break once a request is *sent*, but that doesn't do much good for me since the problem is server side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help picking out a motherboard / CPU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 14:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a $300 budget and need a new motherboard and processor as mine shit the proverbial bed on Monday. I had a second-gen i7 with an LGA 1155 socket.

The cheapest board [on Amazon] compatible with my current processor is $160 made by some brand I've never heard of; Tyan. So it seems like I may as well spend a bit more and get a new CPU unless someone has a better idea.

I would like to retain the DDR3 RAM I have currently, and I have a strong preference for an EVGA branded board. I've had terrible luck with Asus products over the past 5 years. Current board is MSI and it's been OK but a little wonky since day 1.

I was looking at these two motherboards:

https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00K8KPXUO/ref=aw_wl_ov_dp_1_2?colid=3DAHR1QKZQG6Q coliid=IMBMAQ8KTZ156 vs=1

https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00K23BW70/ref=aw_wl_ov_dp_1_2?colid=3DAHR1QKZQG6Q coliid=IMBMAQ8KTZ156 vs=1 th=1 psc=1

But I don't understand what the difference is. Amazon's product details blow ass, and NewEgg is blocked at work. Are there just charging more because it's branded gaming, or is there some actual difference?

Looking at this processor:

https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00CO8TBOW/ref=aw_wl_ov_dp_1_1?colid=3DAHR1QKZQG6Q coliid=I3TWS9HVO5UA8G

If I go with the "gaming" motherboard I've exceeded my budget a more than I'd like.

Use: 1440p gaming, software development, some RDP usage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is this car in the winter with All Seasons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid I'm not going to be able to afford winter tires this year, maybe. I've got some All Seasons on it right now, haven't experienced Winter in the FiST yet. It's so lightweight and easy to spin the wheels in excellent conditions, how is it in bad conditions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married women of AW, have you ever said "Don't get married" as a joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AskMen, what do you think having ADHD is like? What sort of behavior do you think someone with ADHD exhibits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PC reboots itself before it finishes posting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Computer is about 5 years old:

* i7 2600k
* 8GB RAM
* 1TB HDD
* 500GB SSD
* 120GB SSD
* GTX 970
* 750W PSU
* Windows 10

Computer was running OK yesterday, an extended session of Deus Ex: Mankind Divided didn't cause any major issues, though the UI was being weird in the game (icons on the hotbar not refreshing quickly, that sort of thing) but no outstanding issues.

I booted up this morning and after a few seconds it just reboots itself. I let it it do this for about 5 minutes and eventually I got a screen that said it couldn't use the overclock settings and let me get into the BIOS... But I don't OC any of my hardware. Tried rebooting and back to square one.

I unplugged my GPU, all my drives, reconnected the main mobo connectors and booted it back up. Didn't restart itself.

No onboard video so I plugged in my video card and a monitor and it booted up again, except my monitor wasn't getting power (ancient house, likely something screwy with the outlets because if I swap outlets the PC still works).

Plug everything back in to my desk and it's restarting itself again. I unplugged drives, USB peripherals, everything I could but it's not staying on.

Unfortunately I don't have a spare PSU to test with or anything like that.

Any ideas? Thanks.

Edit: Replaced the PSU, not that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few stills from the Wilde Flowers video I thought looked neat [2560x1440] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 09:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I [26M] think my roommate [23M] is becoming schizophrenic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TL:DR** Craigslist roommate who is likely depressed and abuses alcohol / marijuana was sent home from work for "saying crazy shit", said he can see colors with meaning, auras, and the he's moved things with his mind. He also said he will "give a week's notice, but is going to show us how connected to the earth he is". My other roommate and I are concerned both for our own well-being and his health. Wtf do we do?



A few months ago my other roommate [27M] and I had to fill an empty bedroom in our 3BR apartment, but didn't know anyone so we grabbed someone off Craigslist.

He seemed OK, a little odd, mumbles a lot, a little depressed / lonely but has a decent job and a GF and doesn't cause problems, and at the end of the day we just need someone to pay rent.

Couple months go by and me and the other roommate definitely agree this guy is weird, he's said he's moved stuff with his mind while meditating but we kind of just chocked it up to him being a massive pothead.

The past 2 weeks or so, my roommate was saying how Craigslist guy has been acting really weird, that they've had some weird conversations. My friend / older roommate is working becoming a guidance counselor and the CL-dude knows this so he's kind of confided in him a bit and we've tried to get him to see an actual professional but he can't really afford to.

Then yesterday, I guess his GF got a call from his boss telling her to come pick him up because he's saying "crazy shit". She dropped him off at our place and he told her he was just going to get some stuff then go to her place. He never went to her place, so she started panicking. I guess the cops were looking for him, as well as some mental health crisis group.

Eventually he shows up at our place and that health group swung by and did some sort of assessment, talking to him. Despite saying he can "see colors with meaning" and "auras", apparently they thought he was fine and did nothing.

Then later that day, my two roommates were talking again and he described himself as "blue, and a little orange, but trying to get rid of that". He also said something about how he thinks it's all connected, the universe, my other roommate trying to help this guy, a "no smoking" sign we have in our living room (he's trying to quit cigarettes". Then most unsettling of all, he says "I'll give you a week's notice, but I'm going to show you how connected to the earth I am".

My roommate asked if he should be concerned, by he said he won't hurt anyone / himself, and we mostly believe that... But still, WTF. At the very least we're both extremely uncomfortable.

This dude clearly needs help, but we have no idea what to do. I'm not comfortable with him living with us, but no idea what to do. How could we kick him out? We're on a month-to-month rental property, but if he's unstable who knows what he might do.

My sane roommate's GF knows someone who was diagnosed with schizophrenia and she said this guy's behavior is very similar to the other person before he "snapped", so we think it's that / sounds similar to what I've read on wikipedia but we obviously don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to handle family drama / stress when you can't help? [Long] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do drivers mean when they say they "try something new" in regards to driving style? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ostberg has been saying how he's trying it a "different style for tarmac" and expects to be losing time while practicing.

I've done autocross /HPDE's, I know racing isn't easy, but at the same time I know so little. What could a professional driver be mixing up, trying differently etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anything I can do about a rusty blade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newbie fencer, took 7+ months off between the first time I took lessons and starting up again.

My foil, helmet, jacket and glove were in my bag in my closet for the duration of my break. Noticed something brown on my jacket, from rust on my blade.

Anything I can do / should I be concerned? How can I prevent it from getting worse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple newbie question about parries (Foil) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a beginner course a year ago and then continued fencing for about a month or two after that, then stopped.

I just signed up for beginner classes at a different, cheaper school a few weeks ago and just thought of a question after we practiced Parry 4's and 6's last week.

Is the idea to deflect the blade **and** keep the bout going, or do you not really care if you deflect the blade so it connects off target? I guess all that matters is denying your opponent the touch, but while practicing with one of the guys last week he kept hitting my arm when I'd try to parry 6.

I'm left handed and he is right handed,  he was aiming for my chest and as I'd try to push his blade out of the way it often resulted in my arm taking the hit.

As I said before, I guess so long as they don't score a touch then good enough, but I kept thinking that if this were an actual bout that would get really tedious having to halt every single time. So am I doing something wrong, or is this just kind of normal / part of learning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the benefits to the various tire sizes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is, why do you see like 20 - 22" wheels / tires on really exotic cars? What is the benefit of tires **that** big compared to, say, 18" that you'd see on a more normal performance car?

I know tire width helps grip, obviously, but how does the diameter come into play? Simply just more rubber to "share the load" and prevent them from getting worn out too fast?

Then on the other end of the spectrum why do you see such small tires on rally cars? 15 or 16" are quite common there. Is that just because of requirements dictated by the governing body? ie "must not stray too far from OEM sizes" or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there somewhere I can legally purchase a digital download of DTP's Retinal Circus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can find are blu ray's on amazon and I don't have a blu ray player :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Issues trying to stream an mp3 with my web application </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a web application using C#, .NET 4.0, MVC and RazorViews.

On a page within our site, we have links to a variety of audio files, primarily mp3's.

If the user has something other than Windows Media Player set as their default media player, they are able to stream the mp3 straight from our website. VLC Player does this perfectly.

If they have WMP as their default player, however, the application launches and pops up with the following error:

 Windows Media Player cannot play the file. The latter nigh not support the file type or night not support the codec that was used to compress the file.

This can be resolved by simply downloading and installing a third-party codec and then it will work with WMP.

But if you look at the wikipedia entry for WMP, it says streaming capabilities have been improved with version 12.

Am I missing something? I've tried googling around but a lot of results just recommend using all sorts of third party solutions, using different media players, adding a media player control to a desktop application, or were answers about how to go into WMP and stream something manually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BoM Spoilers] Question about the ending... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished reading about a week and a half ago, and my roommate just finished reading tonight. We both were a little confused about two major things:

* How / When the Lord Ruler hid the bands? Namely, did he hdie these before Vin killed him, or did she not *actually* kill him?
* Maybe I need to re-read HoA but didn't Vin remove TLR's bands when she killed him? So what were *those* that he was wearing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just found out Blind Guardian's setlist for their US tour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely missed this, in a blog post on their website Hansi announced they're playing Imaginations From the Other Side in full this year.

I was literally just saying to a friend the other day, "I'm excited to see them two years in a row but I didn't love BtRM so I hope the setlist is different enough." So that's definitely different enough.

Not my favorite album of theirs, but I've never had an opportunity to see a band play an album in its entirety so I'm super excited now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First autocross event last weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my first Autocross event ever, this weekend. I've done an HPDE a year ago at Watkins Glen International in a 350Z which was insanely fun, but I felt a bit out of my league. This autocross event was much better for me.

I was so slow, but it felt good seeing seconds drop off each lap.

Here a playlist of 5 of my 8 runs.

http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL8zklCxSqdGVSeRdi_9kgxnrOvDkMgefe

 Unfortunately my GoPro died before I could record my fastest laps, but I went from 57 seconds on my first lap down to 46 seconds by the end of the day. 34 seconds was the fastest time of the day, and the other FiST at the event did a 0:37 run so I clearly have a ton of room for improvement but hey I'm content with 17^th out of 20 in my group.

A few photos, as well; https://imgur.com/a/BPHN3

Have another event in 12 days, I'm super excited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autocross yesterday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my first Autocross event ever, yesterday. I've done an HPDE a year ago at Watkins Glen International in a 350Z which was insanely fun, but I felt a bit out of my league. This autocross event was much better for me.

I was so slow, but it felt good seeing seconds drop off each lap.

Here a playlist of 5 of my 8 runs.

http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL8zklCxSqdGVSeRdi_9kgxnrOvDkMgefe

 Unfortunately my GoPro died before I could record my fastest laps, but I went from 57 seconds on my first lap down to 46 seconds by the end of the day. 34 seconds was the fastest time of the day, and the other FiST at the event did a 0:37 run so I clearly have a ton of room for improvement but hey I'm content with 17^th out of 20 in my group.

A few photos, as well; https://imgur.com/a/BPHN3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was just at an art festival, bought this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it mean for something to have a "finite, non-zero temperature"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pet Peeves in D D? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just curious, what are some things you guys encounter while playing D D that annoy you?

For me, one of the biggest things is Rogues who check goddamn every openable object for traps.

I think it interrupts the game, narrative and general "immersion" to constantly have to roll a skill check every single time the party goes through a door to the point where it honestly annoys me. Admittedly, in my current campaign we have *two* Rogues, but someone is *always* describing how they're going to open a door and rolling for it. I just think that, as a role-playing game, if your character feels compelled to check every single surface for a trap either they're a really shitty thief with no intuition, or have a mental disorder.

I get that DM's aren't just going to say, "Hey there are no traps in here" because it they *don't* say it then you'll know there are. But it's just so tiresome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Tough Hide work with wrapping? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say someone attacks a model with Tough Hide.

They pick a 1 Damage result and a 2 Damage Result.

Do you reduce the damage from each result by 1, or do you reduce the sum of the results by 1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for filming from within a vehicle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 19:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got an autocross event coming up this Sunday and I wanted to record it. I'm probably going to have one camera on the passenger side door window in the cabin, and another probably either on my roof or maybe mounted to the passenger seat pointing out the windshield.

A year or two ago I tried to do something similar. I had a coupe and I put my camera on the cross bar in the back. I didn't know about the "Spot" setting, so unfortunately the video came out terribly and you couldn't see out the windshield.

Can anyone provide any other tips other than using Spot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WoR] Question about Syl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 19:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just downloaded the Stormlight Companion Book and under the "Named Spren"  it has this entry:

 Sylphrena, better known as Syl, is an honorspren bonded to Kaladin. She embodies the charateristics of her type of spren, being changeable and playful, while also urging Kaladin to embrace the ideals of the Windrunners. **She bears some relationship to the Stormfather, who seems to feel responsible for all windspren and to have forbidden them from entering into bonds and making new surgebinders**

So, I don't get it. Syl is an Honorspren, but then it says the Stormfather feels responsible for all Windspren. Do Spren start as one type, then for unknown reasons become attracted to something in the physical realm and start to bond, then change their "type"? Based off the 'entering into bonds' it sounds like that might be the case?


**Edit** Under the Stormfather's entry we have this line:

 As one of the three spren who can bond with humans to create a Bondsmith ...

So maybe it's more limited. Only Spren of types X,Y,Z can become A,B, or C? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone use the Bridgestone Potenza RE760 tires? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking at TireRack as I need to replace a tire, decided to check a local dealer first and they had this tire that was not listed on TireRack's website (at least, not when shopping by my model).

http://i.imgur.com/hn4oSpF.png

It has a *significantly* higher tread wear **and** they're cheaper?

Has anyone here used these, and if so how are they?

Looks like they're just even performance tires, but at the end of the day it is my DD-- willing to sacrifice performance for something that'll be better in the rain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever just think, "I really don't give a shit" when talking to your parents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TWoK] What is Syl referring to? Chapter 43... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chapter 43 - The Wretch

"Maybe you should have fought them, then" she said.

"I thought you didn't like killing?" Kaladin replied

"I hate it", she said, growing more translucent, "but I've helped men kill before."

---

I've finished reading WoK and WoR. A co-worker is reading WoK now and she just told me she was devastated when Syl said this. I completely forgot about the line! But having read both books, I cannot recall any context for this.

Can anyone here shed some light? I'm not sure what physical page it's on in the book, by the book in my Google Play Books account it's on page 726 of 1202. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WoK] What is Syl referring to in Chapter 43? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some more rules questions... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can Tapper make a handful of attacks, take out the model he's engaging, then Old Jakes and Charge? I know you can Move then Attack or Attack then Move, but I don't know if Charge is different.

---

How is the order of operations resolved for a single Character Play? For example, if Stave uses his Heroic, can you Push the model, then after the Push do damage? If this kills Vileswarm, where does he explode? Or if the model being hit has the Ball, from where does it Scatter-- before or after the Push? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick etiquette / rules question [Foil] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got into fencing last year for about half a year, so I know the basics but far from an expert.

Just watching USA vs UK in the Olympics right now and it sounded like one of the announcers said "You can block with your arm since that's not a valid target."

It sounded like they're implying it's common tactic to actively use your arm to block your flank.

Now, from a sport point of view, that *sort of* makes sense to force their point to hit an invalid target, but from a sword fighting stand point that's obviously really stupid to actively put your body in harm's way (though I suppose the arm is better than the flank, if I had to pick where to be stabbed).

It'll still pause the action since it's off target, but is it considered "a dick move" to actively try and "block" with your arm, or does no one really care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WoR] Question about the Heralds / prominent character at the end of the book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 15:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've generally been assuming the Heralds are reborn as "regular men" who discover their powers in life. If you read the descriptions in the WoK prelude, some of them around very similar to Kaladin, Dalinar, and Shallan or maybe Jasnah.

I was discussing this idea with my roommate yesterday and he made a good point that this might not be the case because Nin / Nalen saved  Szeth after he died.

If Nin / Nalan knows this name, then it stands to reason the Heralds "permanently" exist despite being able to die, right? Like it's not as if they get "reincarnated" into someone else-- they just come back as themselves.

So I'm thinking I'm completely wrong about my original assessment. Are all of our characters, Kaladin, Dalinar, Shallan, Renarin, Jasnah and possibly Szeth simply just "regular" Radiants who would be a member of an Order headed by one of the Heralds?

I guess I'm just having trouble trying to understand the "hierarchy" to the whole Knights Radiant / Heralds thing, and I'm thrown off by the WoK-Prelude implication that the Heralds cannot truly die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick rule question about Stave... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lob Barrel states:

 All models hit suffer a [4] Push directly away from the
centre of the AOE and the knocked-down condition.
This Character Play may only be used once per turn.

Now, the way I understand this rule, regardless of where the model is in relation to the center, if it's hit, it is pushed 4".

I played my Brewers for the first time against a relatively new player and he was pushing models equal to the difference of 4" and [models' distance from the center]".

So if I only just barely clipped a model with the AOE, he'd only push it 2.5" because because it's a 3" AOE, 1.5" radius... 1.5 + 2.5 = 4.

I'm *quite sure* this is not correct, but I can't find anything explicitly stating otherwise.

He was pretty salty the entire night when he learned that a charge doesn't have to be  **directly** towards a model and that Tapper can Old Jakes himself (was insistent that 'friendly guild model' means another model until I showed him Hearne's Heroic which explicitly states 'other guild model', and even then his argument was it could've been erratad in season 2) so I was just like, whatever I'm not even gonna argue it.

Edit: derp, the definition for a Push clearly states "pushed up to the distance shown".

I was looking for AoE rules and stuff :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumb question about SSRS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company has a web application written in C# / .net 4.0 and it uses Razor Views and MVC (`System.Web.Mvc` version 4.0.30319), as well as Crystal Reports.

We're looking to switch over to SQL Server Reporting Services.

I've started doing some research online, and it looks like accessing the reports through a URL is probably the easiest / best bet given we're using MVC... But I still don't really understand it-- I'm not the one in charge of creating the reports or anything on that end.

Do I literally just create the URL based off parameters the user selects and open that URL in a new tab?

Like I'm not able to get a working demo up and running yet, so I don't know what I "get back" from the URL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just picked up the Brewers; in what order do you usually activate them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the general strategy is "swarm a dude and kick him while he's down".

Do you charge in with Tapper, knock down on the Charge if you don't get enough successes for Commanding Aura, then just unload with him? Then just follow up with Hooper and Spigot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whoever did the Phantom Brave port should do everything else NIS ports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming it must've been two different teams that handled PB / Disgaea 1.

Disgaea had some issues out of the gate but it's only gotten worse.

This PB port on the other hands feels pretty much perfect. Whichever team / studio who did this should handle all of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if two identical objects were placed together close enough that they gravitational pulls effected one another? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clunking noise in reverse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I bought my '14 with 11k miles and it's up to 12.5k now.

This week, I started hearing a pretty loud clunking noise when I shift into reverse and then start to go.

Haven't had an opportunity to investigate it myself, but looking around online I found this thread:

http://www.fiestastforum.com/forum/threads/4550-dear-gearbox-please-stop-clunking/page7

Overall it sounds like it's not necessarily an uncommon occurrence / might not actually be anything wrong... But it's been a while since that thread was updated--wanted some more recent opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of Casket's Legendary / Seenah's Trait? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 16:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still pretty new to GB, playing against the Morticians with my Hunters last night.

It was probably the most fun game I've played, ending when he Icy Sponged Casket and managed to finish off Egret, securing the final 4 VP he needed for the win.

I understand Legendary Plays are once-per-game, but does Casket seem a tad too strong to you guys? Both Character Plays are really good, his Traits are extremely strong (admittedly, all the Light Footed Hunters are well equipped to deal with his bullshit) and then you have Casket Time. Oh and also he generates an Influence for the team.

Compare this to Mob Favorite on Seenah. He's a good model, but he generates no Influence, has a Playbook-Result-Only Character Play (admittedly it is very strong)  that requires 6+ successes to be used.

In the ~month I've been playing 2-3 games a week, I've gotten Mob Favorite once.

Admittedly, I'm sure a lot of this boils down to me not using Seenah to his maximum effectiveness but it seems pretty difficult to actually get Bear Hug with any reliability. Yea he rolls 11 or more Dice on the charge, but more than half of those need to be successes, after armor, for Hug to go off.

Now I suppose you're saying, "If you're charging something that isn't Snared you're doing it wrong", which is pretty fair. This was the first game I didn't run Hearne, and I didn't have Zarola either so my only real opportunities for Snare were Theron and Chaska/Jaecar traps-- and against the Morticians with Puppet Master *and* Lure, those Traps are more of a liability than anything.

Just wanted to see what some more seasoned players thought? Different models, different roles, but with some minor overlap... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook in the web browser getting less and less usable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like many others, I don't use the FB apps because they require an obscene amount of Privileges.

But lately, using the mobile site in my web browser has been getting worse and worse. If I try to edit a post, I can't move the text cursor. Today, I'm completely unable to even post in a Group page. I tap the 'Post' button and nothing happens.

Tried Firefox, tried Chrome, reset my phone.

I can't view messages from mobile anymore, either. If I clicked the chat icon, it launched the Play Store to download Messenger. I used to just be able to hit Back and it would take me to the browser and I could access chat that way but that no longer works.

It's like ever day they purposefully make the mobile site less and less usable to force people to download their shitty fucking apps.

Has anyone else had these issues? I'm on a Nexus 6 / Project Fi / Android 6.0.1


Not necessarily looking for a solution per se, I'm mostly just curious if anyone else is having these kinds of problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about leaving the pitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say you're at full HP and then get pushed off. How much do you come back with next round?

Someone told me you come back with an Icy Sponge (or two) worth of HP, but I thought I read somewhere that you had come back with however much you left with.

Can't find the rule for it, now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *Why* does this car shit brake dust like it's its job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it, brakes create dust. It's going to happen. But I've never seen a car so good at spraying down its entire body with the stuff.

Is it the OEM Pads themselves, or is it something to do with the actual design / oversight off the car itself?

Is there something that can be done besides buying different pads? If not, how effective of a solution is that-- does it really make an improvement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12K miles on the car, new a new tire-- could I get away with only buying 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tire has a leak, brought it to a tire shop and they showed me it's already been patched twice, poorly, and that they won't do it a third time (I bought it with 11K on it).

I *really* don't want to buy 4 new tires, but I know you're supposed to keep them all with the same tread "level".

Should it be OK to only replace the front two? It's the front passenger side with the leak.

I should mention I do want to do autocross next month, so that might be a concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion: "Support Heroes Only" Brawl Mode for when Ana launches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 05:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was one of the most fun Brawls I've played, personally. Maybe it's just because I really enjoy playing Zenyatta and Lucio. But either way, I think it'd be a cool way to introduce new heroes -- some Brawl mode centered around their class in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dealership overpaid on my lien, bank gave me a check for the difference. What do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I traded in my car last month. I was unable to get an exact figure for a "10-Day payoff", so I told them the immediate balance if I were to pay off the car that day.

I'm assuming the dealership probably padded the value I gave them, to account for interest. 

Yesterday I received a check in the mail from the company I was financing my old vehicle with a small, but not insignificant, amount of money.

Do I call the bank and explain? They could cancel the check and issue one for the dealership, or they could just tell me it is in fact mine.

Or should I just keep my head down and cash it and then it the dealership contacts me, give them the money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Handful of rules questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Q) What is the definition of "condition damage" (pg 16)**


Example, if someone dies to Seenah's Bear Hug's Bleed damage,
		does that trigger 'Mob Favorite!' ? I'm guessing no.


----


**Q) How exactly do Icy Sponges work? How many do you get?**


This is my interpreation after reading it 3 times:

* The first time, you only heal up to [IS1] HP.
* The second time, you can heal up to [IS2] HP [which you'll obviously do instead].
* Third time and beyond, you can still only heal up to [IS2] HP? 

I guess this would make the most sense -- we can't have our athletes *dying* now can we?


----

**Q) Do Dodges / Pushes ignore intervening models?**

Someone told me Yes, they ignore them (can't stop 'on top' of them, of course) but you can freely move around them. Reading the rules, ti seems like it's specifically **terrain** that doesn't impede these re-positioning effects?

----

**Q) Can Theron Sun Strike himself, then Pin / Arrow an enemy for 1 MP?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rules Question: Killing an ally -- does the enemy get VP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say Egret's Flurry ability also takes out an ally.

Does the enemy get VP for this? I assume not, but I couldn't find the ruling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picked up the Hunters on a whim; anything I should know in particular about 'em? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 03:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I know pretty much nothing about this game, other than the fact that a lot of people on a local FB wargaming group and drumming up a ton of interest.

Went down to the LGS today, saw the Hunter starter box and picked that up as well as a giant bear and some dude with bear traps. Hoping to go play a demo game tomorrow.

I was just hoping someone could tell me a little bit about the Hunters? Steam Forged's website isn't exactly spectacular lol.


Edit: So I was actually *really* surprised everything I bought cost me $180... but is the entire faction only 8 models? Did I literally just buy *an entire faction* for under $200? That alone is refreshing. I'm so used to Warmahordes -- which isn't half as bad as Warhammer -- so I was expecting "battle box and a few solo / characters" expensive ($100 tops). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to recover the metallic-looking bits on the steering wheel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Title should say "How to **Remove**" not recover :(


Why the hell do manufacturers insist on putting reflective surfaces on the steering wheel?

Anyone here know how to remove that silver bit around the horn?


http://images.cdn.autocar.co.uk/sites/autocar.co.uk/files/styles/gallery_slide/public/ford-fiesta-st-7.jpg?itok=RL9vx8bn

I'd love to just plastidip it black or something not fucking reflective. Every day I drive home from work with the sun to my side and it just blasts off that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Roadhog's right click work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 23:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that after a distance it disperses the blast, but what if an enemy gets hit by it before it explodes?

Does it deal all of its damage as a single instance? I assume not, because then why would you ever let click. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to open a link in a Private Tab when the "Open With" menu lists a web browser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, if I click an imgur link in reddit is fun i have the option of opening it with the Reddit Is Fun app, I have the option to open it in the Imgur app, Chrome, or Firefox.

Is it possible, from this menu, to open my browser with a Private tab, rather than having to copy the link, open my browser, open a private tab, Paste and go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New-To-Me car might have a leak; dealerships responsbility or mine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 23:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought at '14 FiST on Saturday. They put air in the tire when I went to go for a test drive and stupidly I didn't think anything of it.

Tire pressure sensor came on this morning when I went to go to work... If I have a leak, am I on the hook for the replacement or is it something they have to cover? It's been less than a week, pretty new car, still under warranty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Web developers, do you prefer to debug JS code in Visual Studio, or the dev tools in the browser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing a lot more JS development than ever before, recently.

When I launch my application, I can't debug through Visual Studio-- only with the browser dev tools can I. New to web dev, I thought this was a limitation of our code because a firm in India just rewrote our code base.

For many things, I really like these tools provided by the browser. Then I found out if I launch my app in IE, I can debug via Visual Studio. Again, for certain things, I like some of the features available in VS. Both have their pros and cons.

Just curious what you guys use? Again, it's all pretty new to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what a sequel should be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone in WNY? Looking to get started / few questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a 350Z and did a HPDE course at Watkins Glen International last year, which was a ton of fun.

I unfortunately had to switch to a Fiesta ST, now I'm looking to do autocross.

I found my region website; wny-scca.com

Looks to decently active. I wanted to try and talk to people first / meet people before I get started. So.. anyone in the Buffalo area? How is the crowd?

----

As far as autocross itself is concerned, how stressful on the car is it? Would I be doing once per month in my DD?

Obviously, it's much lower speeds than Watkins Glen, but I'll still be at high RPMs the entire time. Not as hard on my brakes, but I'm sure they'll still get quite the work out.

Would I need dedicated tires / brake pads / fresh fluids each time? I'm afraid I'm under-estimating the wear and tear autocross can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to protect paying when you're forced to park under a tree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live down town, on street parking. The streets are lined with trees, the kind that just love to drip sap all over the place.

I just picked up a Fiesta ST this weekend with the gorgeous tri-coat Molten Orange color. Is there anything I can do to try and help preserve the paint when I've little choice but to park under these trees?


Edit: just noticed the typo in my title. Should say "paint", not "paying". Stupid phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Installation time for the Cobb stage 3 package? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a lot of reviews online talking about the quality and results of this package, but nothing really about how long it takes to install everything.

I won't be buying it soon, but just so I can plan-- roughly how long does it take to install everything? I'll most likely be paying to have it done (no tools / not a mechanical person / on street parking; no drive way) so I'm just wondering how much more it'll cost than the price for the parts itself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumb questions from a new owner / new to Ford in general; adjusting the seats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just picked up my 2014 Molten Orange FiST yesterday and I love the car! These recaros are insane, they hug you so well. But the headrest feels a little wierd, like they're angled *forward*. I don't often put my head against the headrest, but when I do it's very unpleasant, like I have to angle my head downwards.

Is there a way to adjust this? The dealership didn't have the user manual, but I find a 2016 manual online. But what they show doesn't seem to match up, at least not with the recaros. I assume it's a difference between the regular seats you'd get in a non-STR trim Fiesta.

Also, the guy at the dealership told me the lever on the side of the seat adjusts it up and down, but when I crank it makes a teeny tiny adjustment forward and back, even though the seat also has the manual bar to adjust the seat underneath. Like this lever just lets me "fine tune" what that bar unearth the seat allows. I definitely feel a little higher up than I'd like, I'd love to find out how to lower them...


Also, do they pipe in noise into the cabin via the speakers? I know they should be taken with a grain of salt but in the [Regular Car Review](https://youtu.be/gw-3zLZheII?t=5) he says they are. But a buddy of mine who owns one says they're actually not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to buy a FiST, dealership has a Focus RS on the lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pulled in and saw this black beast sitting there. I'm an hour away from the nearest major city, in cow town. Really surprised to find one here. Sorry for crappy photos; it needs to be cleaned and is tightly parked between other cars

https://imgur.com/a/xN88R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most likely buying my FiST tomorrow; what to look out for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a few months back asking about what you guys didn't like about the FiST in an attempt to persuade myself *not* to buy one.

Unfortunately you guys sucked at making the car sound un-appealing :P

Just found a 2014 with 11K miles and recaros for $18.7K online; going to the dealership first thing tomorrow.

Is there anything in particular I should look out for that might indicate I shouldn't buy it? Looks clean in the pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just looked at the event schedule for the venue back in my hometown and damn near pooped my pants... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/SVJafRm.png

What a month and a half to be alive, damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $15K for a 2014, 15K miles-- too good to be true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a Focus ST that's about 5 hours away. It's a 2014, Recaros + moon roof. 14.5K miles and the dealership is asking $14.9 on Autotrader.

Sounds too good to be true, no? Looks OK in the pictures...

Edit: balls. Reconstructed title. Missed that at the very end of the description :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This game ruined Fallout for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think the wait has broken my friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 23:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire from crash at WRC Portugal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do dealers offer more money on the trade in rather than reducing the price of the car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone loves their FiST, but what are some things you DON'T like about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of doing something financially stupid and trading in my Honda Fit for a FiST.

While I absolutely can afford to do this, it's still kind of a dumb idea so I guess I'm sort of looking for reasons not to go trade in my Fit for the FiST that's spec'd exactly like how I want one from a nearby dealership. So, what complaints do you have with the car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Blizzard be wiping accounts for release? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Smoke when you're behind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a pretty average 3-point-something K MMR player.

I realize that at this level, smokes are one of the most heavily under-utilized item in my matches and I rarely see them beyond a Lycan or Ursa picking it up to solo smoke.

When we have decent offensive vision, I try to encourage the team to gather to smoke and go for a kill when I can and usually this works well.

Periodically, I'll be losing a game and someone urges we smoke and try to get kills... When we have zero offensive vision, and minimal or no defensive vision. I've always felt like this is absolutely a terrible idea; we're already behind, unexpectedly walking into the whole team will probably be a disaster.

I feel like it's a waste of time; we're not farming, we don't know where we're going, and we don't know what we're going to find if anything.

I suppose it varies from game to game, team comp to team comp, but am I wrong? Is it a decent idea to smoke and hunt even if you don't have adequate vision?

Generally speaking, how should one handle such a situation? I'd much rather simply try to get up some defensive vision and farm, let them come to us under a tower or fail to find a pick off of their own in our jungle then try to go on the offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 North American tour (w/ Grave Digger again) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 19:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the hell do you love yourself? At what point are you content with your efforts and proud of something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been diagnosed with depression, take medication for it and see a therapist. One thing I've come to realize is that I hold myself to impossibly high standards and dismiss any compliments because I feel like the other person doesn't know the whole truth, both in my professional life and personal life.

While talking with my therapist, I cited a recent example where a coworker said I was a good guy and a good programmer. But I don't believe it to be true because he works in a different department, and while my software might meet his direct criteria, under the hood there's a lot that could be improved (which he doesn't see; only the end product).

She said that because I don't respect myself, because I'm never content with anything I do, it prevents me from ever really respecting others as well.

While I don't fully agree with that entire sentiment, she is mostly right. I do realize my expectations and standards are unrealistic, but despite my best efforts to lighten up, to be nicer to myself or more forgiving of my mistakes / shortcomings, I can't seem to really "accept" or internalize these views. I can't really believe them.

At what point do you say, "OK, I've done the best I can and that's good enough for me"? How do I stop *always* searching for things to improve while simultaneously dismissing everything else? Bleh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kangaroo attacks car (warning: very loud) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 16:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think the new Armlet is insanely powerful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 16:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played a few games last night, once against a Wraith King who picked up Armlet first pretty early, and a second game where my roommate grabbed it on Legion Commander.

5 Additional free armor is bonkers. It now gives more than a max rank Frost Armor from Lich. Combined with the new Armor aura from towers, and the increased base HP / HP per Strength, you can get very fat very early.

Admittedly, these are only 2 All Pick games with minimal thought put into team comps, we could've done more to deal with that Wraith King but he just felt unstoppable. The Legion Commander game wasn't bad, but we all played poorly and it didn't go well.

We do have that new component for Medallion, blanking on its name, which could help to mitigate some of all that new armor, but damn.



I also didn't realize how much it's gotten buffed over each patch. In a year and a half since 6.82, the cost has dropped by almost 300g between Recipe cost reductions and the components themselves getting cheaper. I think this item has always enjoyed a good bit of popularity, but I really think it's going to explode in popularity this patch.

What has been your experience with the new Armlet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers Everything) Theory about Tyrion's origins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we know Dany is a Targaryen. The leading fan theory is that Jon is, as well.


I haven't been super into ASOIAF since finishing the most recent book a few years ago but now that the TV show is back on I'm a bit excited again. So I don't know if there's a leading theory on who the third Targaryen is-- the house crest is a three headed dragon after all.


Tyrion was on the boat with "Griff" aka Aegon after leaving Westeros behind. But they've been separated for a while so as far as I know his status is Unknown. Please correct me if I'm wrong there.


I was talking to my coworker today, he had this theory that Tyrion is actually a bastard Targaryen, and these were his supporting arguments:


His mother was in King's Landing in the year 272 and one of the Targaryen's ruling at the time made comments to her, asking if her body was ruined from giving birth to the twins

Tyrion was born in 273, a year later (so, depending on when she was in King's Landing it could have been only 9 months)

Tyrion was described as a hideous baby with "a monster, with a tail, monstrous huge head, thick black hair, a beard, an evil eye, lion's claws, with teeth so long he was not able to close his mouth, and both male and female genitals." (From westeros.org). Sounds a lot like a dragon to me. This could be a way for people to say he's a Targaryen, without committing the offense / insult of directly calling him one. I also just found a note saying that Dragons are neither male nor female, which is also significant considering the description mentions he has both genitals.


Building on that, this story was brought up in both the book (I believe Cersei tells Tyrion), and in the show (Oberyn described his disappointment that Tyrion was simply crippled, not a monster, when he visited Tyrion in his prison cell before his Trial for allegedly killing Joffrey). So clearly this description of him must be somewhat important to the audience, whether we knew it or not.


And in the show he's already in Dany's good graces. So that's a plus.

Thoughts? Criticisms? Corrections?

I never heard this theory before, it seems fairly sound. Though I'm not sure what would become of Griff / Aegon if he lives. Guess he's not a sibling of Dany's, but rather the nephew of, so she'd still have claim to the thrown over him. Or maybe he'll die in the books and just never appear in the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spoilers All: A theory my coworker has about Tyrion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would I still be able to enjoy the Vive with very limited open floor space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bedroom is about 9x10. Between my larger L-shaped desk, Full mattress, dresser, and an assorted pile of stuff from various hobbies my room has very little open space.

I was just wondering if that's actually a problem for the Vive or VR in general? I'd like to buy one some time this year but if most games use Room Scale or otherwise expect me to be able to move around much, that would be a deal breaker.

On the other hand, how long is the cable? The adjacent living room is much more spacious. Perhaps if I could wander around there, without having to relocate my PC... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does my RawImage render over all of the Text items belonging to this Canvas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 22:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this [`Canvas`](http://i.imgur.com/58mfqI1.png) containing 3 `Text` objects and 1 `RawImage`.

My [`RawImage`](http://i.imgur.com/muhmD8V.png) is like so.

But when I run the game the image appears over the text. Doesn't matter if it's first or last in the hierarchy.

I'm sure I'm missing something really dumb, but I can't figure it out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you opt out of the ability to call / text over WiFi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 15:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company is finally granting WiFi access to employees. I'm psyched to no longer need to use my own data to stream music, but I dislike the idea that they could intercept text messages.

Is there a way to disable that feature of Project Fi? It'd be nice if I could just toggle it as easily as you can your WiFi or Bluetooth settings from the pull down tray.

Using a Nexus 6, if that makes a difference.

Edit: Got in touch with support, this isn't possible from what they told me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does your company / team keep track of issues, tasks, projects and how big is the team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my first job out of college, I worked individually with small businesses developing custom software for them. Solely responsible for all aspects of development. As a very disorganized person (hardcore ADD and just not organized in general) this was not a good role for me. They'd kind of just email me stuff and I'd try to work on it. Having direct contact with the person or people who make the end decisions was helpful, but yea overall this just wasn't good.

At my next job, we used a bug tracking system called JIRA. Most of my work was pretty simple and overall this worked fairly well. It was also a very large operation. 15 UI developers, 10 back end developers, a few DBA's plus managers for each team.

At my current job, we use a different tracker called Mantis, but it's more or less the same. But for the nature of our business it's not as effective. Or perhaps it's just how we use it. Here, it's me and one other developer plus our boss, and a single DBA though we do some of the DB work too.

---- 

 At my last job, I worked on a single software product. At my current job, we have a few different products under one umbrella all part of separate Solution files (.net dev) but they all share a singular Login solution and that routes them to the correct "module" based on their login credentials. There's also a few other projects completely separate to this "main" product line.

I often find myself having to go back and forth digging through emails, bug postings and calling / talking to my boss and it just feels like a lot of overhead to get all relevant information. Coincidentally, I was just creating an Excel document to track all of my stuff when my 1 coworker just messaged me saying she also wishes we had better documentation (she started this job 2 weeks after I did and she has pretty much identical work experience as me).

So, what does your company do? Do you think it works well? Any suggestions for me? I want to propose *something* to my boss, but I need to come up with a better, easy system. But I'm afraid of introducing more beauracracy, especially when something like this can usually fall apart very easily unless everyone is on board and uses it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been getting a lot of relatively neutral comments on my beard, does that happen to you guys often? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about rev matching / riding the clutch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 15:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you downshift and blip the throttle a little, should you **only** do that when the clutch pedal is fully depressed? Or does it not really matter because it's generally a pretty quick action to shift and give it a tid bit of gas?

I've been driving stick for a while now, 6 or 7 years but my first car had the transmission die. I got an '03 Corolla from my mother, who has driven stick her entire life, with 85K on it. Then around 100-110K I was cruising home on the highway and the transmission just up and shit the bed. I wasn't changing gears or anything. Always wondered if it was something I did in the ~20K I put on it, or what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does your employer know you have ADHD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 16:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed in middle school wth ADD. Last year (well over 10 years later) I got re-diagnosed, after college when I was afraid it was effecting my job.

When I got re-diagnosed, I was also diagnosed with depression which wasn't exactly a shock to me. I've been taking the ADD medication for about a year. I've been taking antidepressants since last August, but I had multiple, multi-week interruptions in January and at the beginning of this month. This most recent time, I was also off the anti's as well.

Needless to say, my brain chemistry was all kinds of fucked. I had a bit of a breakdown at work and talked to HR because I was a giant mess. I told her about my mental health issues and that I was (unwillingly) off my medications. I didn't want to do this, but thankfully it's a small business that actually gives a shit about their employees. She asked if my boss knew (he didn't) and asked if I would like to keep it that way (I said yes).

I've been contemplating letting my boss know though. He's not a micromanager at all, so it's possible he didn't even notice a difference in me lately but my work definitely hasn't been up to par.

So I want to let him know that if he had any concerns, he can lay them to rest as I'm back on my medications... But if he didn't notice, well, I'd rather not bring attention to it then.

I think I'm just tired of having to "hide" a part of who I am because it is so often misdiagnosed, especially in today's youth. Most people just don't understand, can't understand. It's frustrating.

Do you guys tell your bosses? Do you think I should? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your biggest case of Buyers Remorse, men? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 15:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddy of mine just texted me this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 14:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Affordable Action Cat (I didn't notice my mistake until it was too late) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 06:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/xSgJopE.jpg

**TL;DR** The joke was "Affordable Care Cat" was a type-o someone made and I wanted to draw it. But I accidentally wrote "AAC" instead of "ACC", the initials, and didn't realize my mistake until I had completely finished.

---

I've been slowly teaching myself how to draw over the past month or two. Very slowly. I've always been a cut above average, I think, but never took the time to learn to get better. I'm trying to change that as I learn how much my ADD, depression, and simply my own poor mental attitude impacts my work and I'm trying to correct this. Instead of crumpling up a picture as soon as I make a mistake, roll with the punches. Finish it. You'll never get better if you quit immediately and it's unrealistic to expect perfection the first time. Why do I subject myself to such standards?

This is me trying to lower my standards, in healthy ways. This is the first drawing I've done in a week and the first time I've tried to draw something "cartoony" rather than as accurately as I can.

 A person in my buddy's office accidentally mistyped the 'Affordable Care Act' as 'Affordable Care Cat', and it became a running joke and "mascot" for the day and I wanted to draw the cat... but yea, fucked up on lots of things. Most importantly, I wrote "AAC" instead of "ACC" which I didn't even realize was wrong until I finished. Thought it was funny and figured maybe I'd share it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> '01 330ci with 200K miles -- how expensive would this be to own? Would be my first German car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to get a second car, $7K absolute max. I found a pretty nice looking 2001 330ci for $4900 on Craigslist, but it has 205K miles.

I'll only be driving this vehicle on the weekends in the summer (I live in Buffalo), can't imagine it'll see more than 4K miles per year. I have zero mechanical skills, no tools, and on-street parking so I'll likely be going to a mechanic for any and all repairs.

On the upside, since this would just be as toy, any repairs won't Need to be addressed... But at the same time, if I'm paying for a toy, I want it available when I want it.

Other options I found was an '87 350E with 88K miles for $4K and a n '87 325is with an undisclosed amount of miles for $5500. I'm not familiar with what the difference between the two is to be 100% honest with you guys, but at the very least I can say that an E30 is kind of a "dream car" of mine-- I'd love to buy one and learn to wrench on it. Nice older car, lots of room in the engine bay, minimal electronics.

What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking at 2 BMW's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a 1987 BMW 350E, black, 88K miles, manual transmission-- asking $4K

An E30 is one of my "dream project cars. I have zero mechanical knowledge and would love to get something to fix up and learn on so this might be a good option.

The second car I'm looking at is a 2001 330ci M-Sport in white with I *think* 200K miles but the post is written weird; it just says "205k fromNC to NY"-- can't imagine what else he's referring to. Also manual. $4900.

------

I used to own a 350Z but sold it for a number of reasons and thought I could be a mature responsible adult and deal with a boring practical car so I bought a new Honda Fit. And I really don't like it.

So I'm looking for a new car to drive 2-3 days per week, tops, in the summer. Still use the Fit probably Monday - Thursday.

What do you guys think? I want a fun RWD sporty car. Something I can throw into corners.

I set a filter on CL for RWD, $7K max. After scrolling through a hundred early 2000's Mustangs I found these BMWs and a 300ZX (though it's not the TT model I believe so I'm much less interested-- also frankly the 300's are my least favorite Z car).

Looking for something that won't break the bank. I suspect the '01 will :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do some websites automatically log me, but others only populate the login and password field? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just lazy programming? I'm a developer myself but I've never really developed an "actual" login system. Anything I did in school was pretty basic, and any job I've had doing web dev that sort of stuff if already in place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long is an average match? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 15:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game has been in my radar since it was announced, but I haven't paid much attention to it and was on the fence.

Buddy just said he was going to buy it for me, in just curious how long is an average match? I love DOTA, but sometimes I just don't want to be in a game for 30-60 minutes.

I like that Hearthstone and Heroes if the Storm are like, 20 minutes tops. Is this going to be another "quick game"? I assume matches will be shorter, but I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am utterly incapable of receiving / accepting compliments. What the hell is wrong with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 14:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always struggled with my own self esteem / confidence, both in my personal life and my professional one.

I have been diagnosed with depression and ADD, currently not taking the medication for either because I've been having trouble with my nurse.

A few months back a girl told me my haircut looked nice and my immediate reaction is, "Yea I know it looks terrible, but thanks for trying to make me feel better about it". I mean, i just smiled and said, "Thanks", but in my head that's what I was thinking. Or any time I'm walking around the city if I see someone smile in my direction I assume I'm unaware of something. Is my hair sticking up? My fly down? Eh, I'm just a goofy looking son of a bitch, whatever.

A few weeks ago, a coworker copy-pasted a conversation she had with another coworker to me. The other guy basically said to her, "I respect /u/subject721, he's a great programmer and a good guy" yet I feel completely the contrary and reading it kind of makes me feel... Hollow? Fake? I feel like it's not true, and because he's not a programmer himself I don't feel like his comments are valid. Also I got laid off from my last job, and the job before that shortly before I quit my boss spoke to me and expressed concern he felt like the quality of my work then compared to when I started had dropped (and I would agree).

Yesterday, I received a message from one of my two best friends. Known him for probably almost 7 years now, since college, but I moved away almost 3 years ago. The TL:DR was basically, "I miss you and look up to you" and I just feel guilty. He also struggles with depression / ADD (though has been steadily medicated for a while) and I've always felt bad moving away, I feel like I could have helped him more. But I think we also had a sort of co-dependent, somewhat unhealthy friendship. I mean we did absolutely everything together, went everywhere together etc. and as much as I love the bastard, I think our unhealthy tendencies fueled each other's bad behaviors. Combined with other things I didn't like about my social life and my career, I had to get out of that state. Moved 400 miles to live with my other best friend.

The other day, I showed my other best friend (my roommate, now that I moved away from home) something I had painted and he's like, "You did a really good job on this" but all I can see is parts that came out wrong, things I don't like etc. He kind of yelled at me when I pointed out what I screwed up on, he just said "love yourself!". I know he's right... But I don't know how. I feel like I'm not capable of it.

I just have this habit of dissecting everything, looking for flaws, things I could've done better, things I don't like. In everything I do-- from looking in the mirror, to my job, to my hobbies. I'm relentlessly unforgiving and nothing is enough but I don't know how to stop or change. Like picking at a scab. I just tumble down these rabbit holes of negativity, but instead of fixing or changing or improving those things I don't like I just let them be.


I talked a little about this during my last session with my therapist, but she's been busy with clients and I haven't been able to schedule appointments as regularly as I'd like. Also March was just an absolutely crazy month and I had a lot of stuff I wanted to talk about in addition to that... But yea... I'm just so tired of actively rejecting compliments, disliking with everything I do, but I can't seem to stop it. What the fuck is wrong with me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, what are some really nice, comfy shoes? Non-sneaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I desperately need a new pair of shoes. I have 2 pairs of nice dress shoes, sneakers for the gym / physical activity. My "daily" does are some more "dress-looking" cheap pair I bought at Walmart years ago, when I used to work in a restaurant. There plain, black, fake leather looking.

I prefer that sort of style, like casual dress shoes if that makes sense? But I have no idea what are actual quality brands. I have bad feet and I'd like to actually get something good instead of a random cheap pair from wherever, but I have no idea what brands are actual worth the money... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are the motors in electric vehicles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised to see the Model 3 is RWD like the Model S, but I was wondering where the motors are? Are they compact enough they can be kept near / over the rear wheels to keep some weight over 'em?

I realize that's an issue with traditional ICE vehicles, wasn't sure if the same is true for electric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides some form of Ad Block and NoScript, what are some browser plugins you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 20:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it "noticeable" if you have a 144hz monitor but don't have a GPU capable of cranking out that frame rate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 21:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be buying a 144hz monitor from NewEgg but I only have a single GTX 970 and in some more demanding games I doubt it's ability to deliver 144 fps.

I've never seen a monitor higher than 60 Hz in person, so I don't know if they lag out or anything weird if a game is only running at 60 fps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What're you guys up to this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no Easter plans... Or any plans at all. Supposed to be nice this weekend so I was thinking of going to the zoo maybe but going alone might be boring.

I dunno, I want to get out but nothing sounds particularly appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fostering an interest in STEM in a young child? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 14:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine has a four year old son who she's said has expressed interest in maths and sciences and she was looking for ways to try and encourage this.

I looked around for programming tools for kids, found a project by MIT called Scratch and a few other resources on code.org but most stuff seems to be more geared towards kids 8+.

Anyone here have any advice? I have no kids of my own, none of my friends do either so I don't really know what "level" a four year old is on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We recently paid another company to rewrite our application... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 02:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does your ADD / ADHD effect your hobbies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 16:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been diagnosed at a fairly young age (I honestly don't remember, middle-school maybe?) But I stopped taking the medication after a year or two. I'm out of college now and A year ago I got re-diagnosed because I was afraid it was effecting my job, now I've been taking it regularly and seeing a therapist.

Lately I've been "hobby hopping" a lot. I find something new, I get really into it, surf the internet for information / content, start to do it, then before long I'm disinterested.

In the past 6 months I got really into fencing, drawing, game development (I'm a software engineer by day), going to the gym, play video games, reading... But before long I drop most of these hobbies for one reason or the other.

Honestly I find it frustrating, but I don't know if I'm just going through a sort of "self exploratory" phase in my mid-20's, if this is common with ADD, both, or what.

Any of you guys find yourself constantly jumping from one thing to another, but not in an immediate sense like typically associated with ADHD? More over the period of a few days, maybe a week or two.

It's just been tremendously frustrating lately. I feel the need to do stuff, I feel like I'm capable of really "doing something" with my life... I just can't stick with anything long enough to do anything, and I don't understand why I can't keep things going for long :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any of you dudes hook up with a friend in an Open relationship? How'd it go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you pay OTD for your FiST? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago I thought I could do the responsible thing and buy an efficient, boring ecobox. I picked up a Honda Fit, but 3.5 months later and I'm just so unhappy with it.

I was looking around online and a dealership near me has 2 brand new FiST's in, one for $20K and one for $24K. I really want the $24K one (Molten Orange, sun roof, better seats) but that might not be in my budget.

Fortunately for me, because I JUST bought a new car, I really don't need a new one-- so they can't "pressure me" or anything, and they're a high-volume dealership chain. One of the largest in the region, so maybe they're OK with smaller margins. I'd say the chips are in my hand. But I'm curious what you guys paid for yours, compared to MSRP?

Would it be realistic to hopefully talk them down to $22, do you guys think? Between the loss on the Fit, it's really not a *smart* decision, but I could afford to and the smart decision doesn't make me happy so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boss bought an i8... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 17:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/28us6Sv.jpg

Sold his 911 earlier last year, but he still has his Z3, X5 and whatever his wife drives. Must be cool to be rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've completed half of the tutorials on Unity's website, but I don't feel even remotely capable of starting my own project. Where do I begin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've completed the Roll a Ball, Space Shooter, Survival tutorials and I'm about half way through the Tanks tutorial.

But I feel like all of these just show me things Unity are capable of. Providing me a handful of assets and scripts and telling me how to hook things up together doesn't actually teach me anything, I just feel like they are cool, quick tech demos meant to sell their product ("Look how fast and easy this!") rather than actually teaching me anything.

I have almost 4 years of real world business programming under my belt, as well as my BS in software engineering, so it's not like I'm just some dummy who picked it up on a whim and expected everything to be great-- I understand the depth of what I'm getting into here... But I'm really struggling to get started.

Like beyond moving a ball around a flat plane I just feel like I have direction on how to start actually doing anything.

Ultimately I want to build a SRPG sort of like FF Tactics or something along those lines-- 3D grid based map, 2D sprites, turn based action... But beyond slapping a few planes around, again, I have absolutely no idea where to go from here and all of these tutorials don't really *teach* me anything I feel like.

Like from a software dev point of view, I can loosely break down the systems that need to be developed: a system for generating maps, moving things along fixed paths on a grid, loose combat systems, selecting units, issuing command to each unit etc etc... I just have absolutely no idea how to begin, even on the most basic level.

Any tips? Please? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resources for understanding game architecture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I posted a few weeks ago about my troubles as a professional software developer trying to motivate myself getting into Indie game dev, having picked up Unity for a few weeks on multiple occasions.

I've poked around with Unity a little bit some more since then, but the other night me and a close friend from college seriously discussed game development and it's something we both want to do, so we're going to sit down Sunday and come up with a few short term projects and goals, and discuss my idea for a "real" project that I'd eventually like to have actually published in 5-10 years.

Anyways, the purpose of this post is simply to request suggestions for material pertaining to games from a more "software point of view". Stuff about the architectural development of a video game. I mean I understand OOP and business software (~3.5 years professional experience + college) and while a lot of it carries over to game dev, it's also a very different beast.


**TLDR:** Anyone have any good recommendations for reading in regards to the real "engineering" and mechanics side of game development? My "dream project" is a strategy / turn based RPG, so anything related to that would be ideal but I'll take anything really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've all made mistakes in our lives, but what was the biggest mistake your parent(s) have ever made? How did you deal with it / it effect your family? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad travels for a living, and in the weekend he drives for a bus company just taking groups wherever. This weekend he was taking a college team from Boston to somewhere in Kentucky, dropping them off and then taking a rental car back home. Then next weekend he drives the rental back out there, picks up the team with the bus and brings 'em back.

Or at least that was the plan, anyways. Saturday evening I got a text from my brother telling me Dad is in jail, he got a DUI and totaled the rental.

What the **fuck**. My mom is pissed, hurt, disappointed... We all are.

They can't afford his bail so he's been in jail for a few days too.

I'm just genuinely speechless. A combination of "how fucking stupid", "you are royally fucked", " what are they going to do about the house", "what is Mom going to do" (he's had issues with alcohol in the past, but nothing this bad)

So... Anyone else experience some colossal parental fuck ups? What happened / how'd it play out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a trivial feature you miss from a car you no longer own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 15:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if Nissan still does this, but my '03 350Z and my roommate's '03 Maxima you could hold the Unlock button on your key fob and it would lower the windows.

It's trivial, but I actually really miss it now they the nice weather is starting to come back. Especially since only the front Driver side window is automatic in my Honda, so I still have to hold the button for my front passenger side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question(s) about Meld Into Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play a Dwarf Cleric of Light and recently got Meld Into Stone.

I've always just used the spell in a more gimmicky fashion; using it to avoid paying for a bedroom in an inn and things of that nature. My DM said to me it wouldn't "interrupt" my Long Rest, so hey why not!

Anyways, so last week in the campaign game, I decided to eat a mushroom that shrunk my Dwarf down to Tiny sized and I melded into a small rock after instructing the Dragonborn Barbarian to throw me at an enemy and shout, "my Clerics name, I chose you!"

Unfortunately, I failed my Perception check to hear the Barbarian-- I planned on simply un-melding and chucking a Fireball at a group of enemies. So the DM just had him make an improvised ranged attack with a small Boulder, and both me + the target suffered the damage. Then on my turn I jumped out and finished my plan.

Anyways, I was just curious on how you guys might rule this sort of use with the spell? Has anyone here been used as a projectile before? Any other fun uses for the spell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what release(s) Riverside had planned for this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just looking at their website and they had a blog post the other day saying they've cancelled all their concerts this year following the death of their guitarist (turns out it was sudden cardiac arrest) but "plan to continue with their releases Late Spring / Autumn 2016"

I don't think they were working on a new album since LF TM just came out last Fall, but maybe I'm wrong.

Anyone know?

Edit; link to the post in question: http://www.riversideband.pl/en/news/item/statement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two year old bindings broke after 3 uses, anything I can do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 15:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I folded my rear seat down. When I try to lift it back up, the bottom of the seat lifts with it. How do I fix this? ('16 Fit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds really dumb but I can't figure out these seats.

I folded the rear passenger side seat down two weeks ago and only just tried to upright it again. But when I do, the whole seat lifts up with it so it's stuck in this folded position. Tried to separate the two but I can't get it to come apart.

Is there a button I'm missing somewhere...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just figured out why Mayor Lewis comes by your place every night to pick up the stuff you put in your bin (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's on his way home from Marnie's.


I did the quest days ago, but it didn't dawn on my until just now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the last thing that startled you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 17:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to leave my apartment at 7AM this morning for work, to find my downstairs neighbor curled up in a ball napping on my stairs / leaning against my door.

Definitely did not expect that, jumped back a little bit. She was drunk / hungover and apparently locked herself out lol.

I generally don't scare easily, that was the first thing in a while to get me. How about you guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the hell do Gates work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 22:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I placed one, it seems like I have to left click then right click and I can walk through? Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys, what sort of stuff is on the walls in your house / apartment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 19:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new Fit "chugs" a lot in first gear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 15:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a brand new Fit the week before Christmas and I've put 2500 miles on it.

Often times when I start out in First gear, the car kind of "chugs" as if I'm not giving it enough gas, or like if I abruptly took my foot off the clutch (and then pressed it back in and let it out too quickly again).

Is this normal? I've been driving stick for probably about 6+ years now.

Initially I thought it was temperature related, mostly happens in the cold, but even after a 20 minute drive on the highway it still does it when I get off the highway and come to a redlight.

Again, it doesn't happen every time but even if it's 30% of the time that seems like it's too frequent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men, what are some good non-competitive physical activities / sports? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 22:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago I signed up for Fencing lessons and I've been having a lot of fun with it but for a handful of reasons I've decided to stop attending class.

The biggest reason is that I don't want to spend the time it would require to "keep up" with my classmates when it comes to drilling and sparring.

I tried rock climbing when I visited a friend in a different state, but the only gym near me sucks. I've lost a lot of weight since last time I went, maybe that would help, but we'll see.

I also went snowboarding for the first time in 9+ years the other weekend, which was fun but is expensive :/

I dislike the gym, but have been making myself go. I'd much rather some sort of activity, or activities, for exercise instead. Just need something I can do at my leisure, yet still preferably with people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mothers of AW, did your sexual needs / desires change after having kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I enjoy fencing, but I'm seriously bad and I don't particularly like my clubmembers. Kind of want to quit? What do you guys think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started fencing in October. Full disclosure, I was tremendously depressed and started taking antidepressants and seeing a therapist + counselor a month or two prior.

I initially signed up for class for a few reasons:

* get back in shape to go snowboarding in the winter
* meet people
* just generally try new things

I do enjoy fencing, I had a lot of fun with the beginner class and there were 1 or 2 decent people my age, and honesty I think it did a lot to help "kick-start" my confidence / help with the depression.

But lately as I've joined the Intermediate class I just feel like I'm not keeping up, holding others back during drills and just generally get my butt whooped in bouts. I don't mind losing, but I don't feel like I'm progressing. And perhaps most importantly, I fucking hate directing and the coach often has us do directed bouts. It's partly tied to my confidence issues, but even that aside I just don't like it and am not good at it.

I'm supposed to have class tonight, but lately I just can't get motivated to go. If I could just do my own thing, hey cool whatever I don't mind being bad. But like I said, when I consistently fuck up drills and such I just feel bad for messing up the other dude's "rhythm".

Then just in general, half the class is highschool students and the other half is generally younger college kids (I graduated a few years ago) and just don't really "get on" with anyone there. The coach is a decent dude but even that is pretty shallow.

I dunno, I feel like I want to quit but I also feel like my reasons for doing so are kind of weak, if that makes sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that it's been out longer, what do you honestly think about Windows 10? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been a fan of Microsoft, using their OS just because it was familiar to me and I play PC games. I work in IT and know how to use a computer, all the complaints "non tech people" have of Windows have never been a problem for me.

But their business practices in general over the past 5-10 years have really turned me off from the company and this weekend I finally slapped Ubuntu on my new 500GB SSD. I intend to give it a solid month of use as my primary OS (DOTA 2 honestly runs *better* than it did on Win7) and if I like it I'll upgrade my Windows partition to 10 and keep it around just for games that don't work on Linux-- that new Quantum Break game looks cool but requires Win10, so that's why I plan on keeping it around.

So for those who have already adopted 10, really, how is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Person Quadrocopter Racing is going to be a thing; arguably belongs there? I thought it was cool (from /r/multicopter ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 04:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a programmer, I love gaming, but for the life of me I can't get into game dev. Any tips, tricks or advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my BS in software engineering, I've been employed in the industry since graduating but mostly just do win forms / web dev.

I've dicked around with Unity and followed some of their tutorials, but I can never seem to finish anything, don't have enough ideas to build a game on my own, can't come up with a project in excited about etc. etc.

Lately I've been exploring other Creative hobbies and I kind of want to revisit game dev but I already know what's going to happen; aspirations will be too high, I won't even come close to meeting them, get frustrated and call or quits after 3 weeks.

I realize very few games are created in such a short window, barring random weekend game jam projects, but I've just always struggled with this sort of motivation / discipline.

Do you guys have any "exercises" to help you keep on trucking and follow through with things? I would really like to finish a project one day, I don't care if it's successful or not, but yea...

Edit: Should've probably been more clear; while I know what a game jam *is* my skillset isn't even at the level where I could participate and even contribute. Yea I write code, but I'm just not even familiar enough with the tools to really do anything. It's like each time I re-install Unity, I need to go look up the absolute basics all over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single men, what are you up to this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 15:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have anything going on this evening aside from going to the gym (just started this week, ow my limbs). Saturday I've got open sparring for my fencing class then in the afternoon I'll be playing boardgames all day with a few friends / acquaintances. Sunday I'm hoping to go to the mountain. I haven't been snowboarding in at *least* eight years. Don't really want to be home as my roommate and his girl will be shacked up in his bedroom all day / weekend.

Got Monday off but have no plans. Guess I'll need a recovery day after trying to step up my physical activity level.

Other than all that, I've been trying to cut back on smoking weed. I generally smoke every day, but I've stopped this week to prove to myself I don't need to do it or anything. But sometimes it's just nice and I think I want to this weekend.

How about you dudes? Any plans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be realistic to consider buying a house with $80K debt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 16:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick facts:

* 25M
* Single
* New York state (WNY)
* $62K/yr with a pretty stable job
* $63K in various student loans ranging from 3.4% - 8.8%
* $14K owed on a new car (2%)
* Contribute 4% to my retirement account

Currently, I rent a 3br with two other dudes. This costs me about $400/mo between rent + utilities. $240 on my car payment and about $1,000 in student loans. Plus all the other expenses; car insurance, groceries, spending money etc.

I want to start considering buying a home and ideally I'd have enough for a small down payment by the end of the year. Where I live houses are extremely cheap, but the taxes are high from what I've told and I don't really understand them.

You can get an OK starter home with 2-3 BR, 1BA and maybe a garage for around $70-100K depending on the region, but this would also be like an 80 year old house.

You can get a much nicer, newer home (~40 years old) for 150-200K.

I'd much rather buy a good home I plan on living in for a long time, rather than buying a cheaper, crappier "first home" with the intent of selling it and getting something nicer in 10 years. But this of course would be much more expensive month to month. And it'd be more difficult to come up with the down payment for a $150K home than an $80K one

I've tried googling property tax codes for the various suburbs but I seriously don't understand what I'm reading. School zone taxes? Other taxes based on the value of the house? Etc...

Then there's insurance, saving you for when something breaks, general spending money and so on.

Can anyone here tell me more about the "real" cost of buying and owning a home? A coworker said I should probably expect to spend $1000 more per month than I already do on my rent. Is that realistic?

I do plan on setting up an appointment with a realtor, I imagine they'd be able to give me the best, most accurate information but I also don't want to waste time if it's pretty obviously a bad idea or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get some input on starting up going to the gym again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 22:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, so a year ago or so I lost about 50 pounds almost exclusively by dieting. I started walking about it 3 miles most days per week this past summer, but the winter / holiday season and a sort of "relapse" in my personal life and I put 15 pounds back on. So I went from 215 -- 165 -- 180.

I said enough is enough and went to the gym yesterday for the first time in well over a year. I did about an hour of weight lifting. Hit a few upper body machines and a few lower body ones.

My predicament is a fairly busy schedule. On the week days, I can only go to the gym Monday, Wednesday and Friday. However, I have a Fencing class (just started a few months ago) on Thursday evenings, and open sparring on Saturdays.

So my plan is to do weights on Monday so that my body is isn't a limp noodle during fencing, and to do Cardio on Wed + Fri.

Saturday like I said is fencing and evenings I'm generally busy with friends, then Sunday is recovery / chores so I don't want to do anything then.

Right now my main goal is weight loss. I'm more of an endomorph, even when I was in really good shape (regular "extreme" sports + track + ate healthy) I was never lean, always just been kind of a thicker dude.

Currently I'm 5'8", 180 and I want to get down to 160, then from there bulk up a little bit maybe around 170ish.

Just wanted some more experienced peoples' opinions: should my planned exercise regiment be effective for my goals, assuming I can curtail my poor eating habits? If not, what do you think might be better, while maintaining respect to my fencing days? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Mine] Trying to make the best of a very small, cramped room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 18:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a book about drawing at a [6] when I see Snoop Dogg on a fuckin book cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 04:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on trading in a brand new car for a slightly used one that's more fun? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 16:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you guys will be more biased towards getting something Fun, but i thought I'd ask. Just before Christmas, I bought a new Fit. I test drove a handful of other cars in the market but ultimately decided on the Fit for 3 reasons:

* Awesome MPG 
* Neat fold-up rear seats, the car is crazy spacious for a compact
* Brand New was in my budget (I know you lose a lot of money and often times this doesn't make the most sense, but I wanted something with a perfectly clean history that I did not have to worry about)
* Thought I'd do the "responsible" thing and forego a toy because I have $63K in student debt and live downtown / on street parking, didn't want a car I really care about in case it gets damaged

So, those are my reasons. Fast forward a little more than a month and 2,000 miles later, I don't *hate* the car, but the A pillars are goddamn awful and it's just such an anemic, boring lifeless box. I miss driving something fun, something I look forward to getting into.

Car was about $18K, around $20K after tax and fees. I put about $6K down on it.

I checked cars.com and autotrader and I've found a few Fiesta ST's for $17-18K.

I'm wondering if anyone here has done this? How does it work? Should I try to privately sell the Fit, pay off the loan, get the title, then buy the Fiesta?

Or would I be better off / easier to just trade in the Fit? I know you lose ~10%, but it's brand new so hopefully they wouldn't fuck me too bad on trade in? Or am I just being dumb and still "getting over" my 350Z? I miss being able to pass cars when needed, accelerate as I desire, take a corner without feeling like it's going to roll over on me.

Edit: I think you guys are right. Considering my financial situation, I'm just going to sit on the Fit for a while. Plenty of time to own a car I really like when I'm debt free :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about PP's Masterwork model(s) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't really Warmahordes related but I don't know where else to post it.

This seems to be the only model they have:

http://privateerpress.com/masterworks/captain-victoria-haley-statue

And googling around I found forum posts from 2013, so did PP just sort of abandon this? I've been out of the game for almost 3 years now and this was the first I heard of this when fishing around on their website looking for Widower's Woods news.

So, is this the only one? Do we know what other models there will be? Or... Anything? I want an 8" Gaspy statute, damn it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opeth - Atonement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me, or has NewEgg declined in quality over the years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 15:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I built my first PC almost 10 years ago, and every time I've built one I order almost exclusively from NewEgg.

Recently, my roommate ordered a 27" IPS (Asus) from NewEgg and it had a dead pixel. He got the, "talk to the manufacturer" run-around for a bit before NewEgg finally sent him a second one... Which also had problems. More, "It's out of our hands, talk to Asus" from the rep. In the end he did get a third replacement from NewEgg and that's been OK.

Just last night now I went to buy an SSD + new monitor. The monitor was $41 cheaper on Amazon, and Prime eligible. The SSD was the same price. I wanted to open a NewEgg card and put it on that so I could finance it 0% interest, and NewEgg doesn't charge tax in my state whereas Amazon does.

Anyways, so I contact their customer support and they said they'll price match the monitor, but their price match is not a refund but rather simply they give you store credit. I was on the fence about buying two monitors, but the rep told me they cannot price match multiple quantities. So I'd still pay that $40 premium for the second one if I wanted it. In addition to NewEgg store credit being nearly worthless to me, as I rarely ever buy from them between Amazon being as cheap / cheaper, free 2-day shipping, and I have an Amazon card for points and they actually sell other stuff so I'm far more likely to use the credit with them.

Additionally, they're Prime eligible so I'd get free two-day shipping or $4 one day. NewEgg said they'd give me free 3-day shipping.

Ultimately, I decided to pull the trigger and just get one as I really don't *need* two.

So I sign up for the NewEgg card, check out and place my order. Give the order number to the sales rep to process the price match guarantee and he tells me the sale was cancelled. Stupid me, I forgot to change my Shipping / Billing info, it was still saved to my old address and the card I just opened had my new address. My mistake. But the rep wasn't able to modify that info and try again. I had to cancel the order, and place it a second time with the correct info. And now I can't place the transaction because my credit is exceeded because of the failed transaction previously. Call up their bank and they can't do anything for me because it's such a new account they don't have it in their system yet.

I fully acknowledge that last part is entirely my own fault, but honestly I have to say the whole experience wasn't great. Between how much they've stepped up their spam promo emails, the issues my friend had and a less than great experience trying to make an $800 purchase I've lost a lot of respect for them.

Anyone else feel NewEgg has gotten bigger but not better over the years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, how do you handle obvious physical flaws / "the elephant in the room"? Particularly with regards to dating / dating profiles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 11 years old or so, I knocked out my front tooth in a rollerblading accident. I had it reinserted, got braces, then when those came off the tooth came with it. Issuance wouldn't cover it.

For a while I had a fake tooth attached to my retainer, but as I got older I stopped wearing that because it was uncomfortable, difficult to clean, and generally just really inconvenient.

I was extremely insecure for a while about the missing tooth, American culture loves a pretty smile. I've gotten over it mostly, but not completely.

I find I don't really know how to "handle" it though, I've tried making jokes about it but usually don't get many laughs-- maybe the jokes are just bad, but I also wonder if others pick up on my insecurities about it and maybe I'm just making it awkward. Do I just ignore it unless asked?

It's particularly a problem I'm having with dating, I guess. I've never been explicitly told that's why someone wasn't into me, but I'm sure it doesn't help my case. Also, I don't know how to talk about it on a dating profile. I want to be upfront about it, don't want to be like those people who have nothing but photos of themselves 50 pounds lighter. But at the same time, I feel like I'm kind of gimping myself by throwing it out there.

Maybe it wouldn't be so bad if I had a cool story to go along with it, but oh well.

Any of you guys have thoughts on this issue? Or, if you have any obvious flaws that sort of command attention like that, how do you handle it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking of renting a car to drive the Pacific Coast Highway, has anyone her done this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 15:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in dire need of a vacation lately, and I was thinking maybe in the Fall this year I'd like to drive from WA to CA. Ideally, fly in from the east coast, pick up a car in WA and drop it off in CA. Is that doable, or do you have to actually drop it off where you got it / at least in the same state? Additionally, what's the likelihood of renting something with at least a V6, convertible and manual? I can't imagine a lot of rental places would meet those three criteria.

I was planning on doing maybe 5 days, seems like that's ample time for the drive and to make stops whenever, but I could make a full week of it. Get in on a Saturday, leave on a Sunday.

I've looked around online but all I can find are galleries / articles about peoples' trips rather than any actual information to plan the trip...

So, if anyone here has done this or is knowledgeable about it, I'd really appreciate hearing anything you have to say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about Quetzalcoatl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quetzalcoatl says, "Haunt and Locust Swarm now deal their damage in half of the normal duration."

So if Haunt deals 4000% damage over 12 seconds, does it now deal 4K over 6, or 8K over 12?

Additionally, how does this tie in with that Passive that makes things last "almost forever"? That's so vague.

I guess however you split it, the math will come out the same but I was just wondering if there's any more trickery going on there + with Jade Harvester dealing 150 seconds worth of damage than one might immediately think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which effect of global warming is the most immediately threatening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historians, can you tell me about your favorite conflict or event that you studied? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 21:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
