<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2562</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a great experience, actually! The ground was soft enough to feel natural and the ball rolled true, which you can't say about most park grounds. It bounces a little higher in the field, but that's easy to get used to.

The only problem is, on a hot day the ground gets very, very hot. The rubber pellets used to bed the artificial turf absorb the heat from the sun and throw it right back at you. It can be sweaty work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone tried to film Father John Misty's concert at the Sydney Opera House, he grabbed their phone and did it for them. Twice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 23:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone played cricket on a synthetic outfield? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 15:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cricket club starts the season this weekend with a match on an entirely synthetic ground - that's outfield included, not just the pitch as we're used to here in Australia. It's something that happens far more often in the football codes.

Does anyone have experience playing on synthetic outfields? What should we expect? Any tips appreciated, as it's sure to be quite the change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 10:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Cockerill, who wrote this piece, was writing as Associate Editor on FFA's official site from 2012-14.

Not much of a surprise he's taking his former employer's side, even if under the sheen of 'independence' at another publication... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 13:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all your fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taylor Swift tweets permission for ageing theatre actors to dance to 'Shake It Off' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 09:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
