<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3293</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 06:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's Beautiful
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 07:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> salad greens, collards, and kale could be planted
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend is raising funds for her comedy, support the morale of the people!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 12:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name is Sarah Jean Anderson and she is hilarious and she's trying to take her comedy to the next level. Here's her  [indiegogo campaign](http://www.indiegogo.com/projects/birthday-bizniz-booster-for-big-fat-starving-comedian-sarah-jean-anderson). Please help spread the word!! Thank you guys!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adventure Time (Sarah Jean Anderson) needs our support!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 12:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An old high school classmate of mine is a great artist and comedian. She needs help taking her projects to the next level! check out her [indiegogo fundraiser](http://www.indiegogo.com/projects/birthday-bizniz-booster-for-big-fat-starving-comedian-sarah-jean-anderson). I think she is rad and if you do too, please show her some love and spread the word on her  indiegogo campaign!! Thank you guys!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 07:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check with local farms!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 02:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you eaten them before?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I say go for it, but continue to be thoughtful, cos it'd be awesome to pull it off! Get heavy duty bike tires, they'll be better, I promise! And five chickens is probably too many for your particular set up, as there is stress in being kept in a tiny area with that many other birds. I'd say maybe 3 at the most would be more than enough for one person! Also maybe raise the chicken area into your sleeping area ever so slightly, to avoid the bottom of the chicken coop from dragging on the ground in rougher terrain. Also, chickens love sprouts, so you can feed them those too plus the bugs, great thinkin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 19:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for checking in! My mom says he's had a few cards come in the mail and she says he's been smiling a lot when they arrive and he has taped them up on his bedroom wall. I know there's not always quick solutions when someone is feeling blue, but I think it has cheered him up a lot to be hearing from all these people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 05:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're great! I sent you a PM! Oh and he loves monkeys ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 05:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thank you!!  I live in Oregon too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 05:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he'll love that! Thank you!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 05:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, good idea!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brother with Down Syndrome... (cross-post from r/getwell) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 05:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here we are in 1990](http://imgur.com/RSZBWEO)

[Here we are in 2010](http://imgur.com/FKgrdM5)

My brother Jared was always the happiest little boy. He loves singing and reading. His favorites are snoopy, clifford, and whinny the pooh. A few years back, my family began to notice a difference in Jared's behavior. He wanted to sleep all the time, started having bed wetting accidents and has significantly decreased his speech and interaction with others. He was diagnosed with depression by a specialist in the area where my parents live. Here's the thing: his symptoms started when my other brother and I moved out of state to go to college. And my parents say he only really smiles and talks when we call or when we visit. It breaks my heart and I know it's making my whole family sad for Jared.

My out-of-state brother and I have been sending Jared letters and little homemade gifts and we also make sure to do facetime (like skype) every week to help him put a face to our far away voices. 

Anyway.. I found this subreddit today and I thought maybe some of you might want to send him a letter/drawing in the mail. I set up an email address for him too(jaredrocks@zilladog.net). His reading is at a 2nd grade level, so he really likes videos and he loves music. He would love to get a video of you playing a song, or just saying hi to him. I know he's lonely, and I think a little love from ya'll might cheer him up. 

Thanks for sending love. It means the world to so many people.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 23:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll love that! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 23:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! He loves animals too so I know he'll be happy to see your ferrets
! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 23:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he'll love that. I'll let my mom know to help him check his email today, as he has some messages from some internet friends! :)
PS: thanks for the compliment, I actually feel a lot of guilt being away at college because I know it's hard on Jared to have his siblings away from home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offer... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 09:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll send homemade cards, pressed flowers/leaves, photos, art, trinkets well wishes, etc to anyone. PM me with requests. I really like this subreddit.

Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 09:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he would love that!! He likes a lot of music, but a song that always makes him laugh is "Pop Goes the Weasel". He also loves the Beatles, and lots of Disney tunes. He has a keyboard and a guitar that he likes to plays! Thanks! I'll PM you...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 07:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be awesome! It makes us really sad too, but I think things like this would really touch his heart. Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 07:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! Thanks for that! I think it will cheer him up just to have some internet interactions with people. Thanks for taking time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Brother Jared has Down Syndrome and has been diagnosed with depression (more info in text) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 05:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here we are in 1990](http://imgur.com/RSZBWEO)

[Here we are in 2010](http://imgur.com/FKgrdM5)

My brother Jared was always the happiest little boy. He loves singing and reading. His favorites are snoopy, clifford, and whinny the pooh. A few years back, my family began to notice a difference in Jared's behavior. He wanted to sleep all the time, started having bed wetting accidents and has significantly decreased his speech and interaction with others. He was diagnosed with depression by a specialist in the area where my parents live. Here's the thing: his symptoms started when my other brother and I moved out of state to go to college. And my parents say he only really smiles and talks when we call or when we visit. It breaks my heart and I know it's making my whole family sad for Jared.

My out-of-state brother and I have been sending Jared letters and little homemade gifts and we also make sure to do facetime (like skype) every week to help him put a face to our far away voices. 

Anyway.. I found this subreddit today and I thought maybe some of you might want to send him a letter/drawing in the mail. I set up an email address for him too(jaredrocks@zilladog.net). His reading is at a 2nd grade level, so he really likes videos and he loves music. He would love to get a video of you playing a song, or just saying hi to him. I know he's lonely, and I think a little love from ya'll might cheer him up. 

Thanks for sending love. It means the world to so many people.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 01:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out this [site](http://pc-pdx.com/show-guide/) for inspiration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 00:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once counted 30 horse comments in an hour when I took my Dane to the Portland Saturday Market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 21:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out 100 paintings for 100 days by Foot Ox @ www.footox.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FOOT OX - TINY ANIMALS [FOLK PUNK] [RARE] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 21:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 21:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teague Cullen, of Foot Ox is making these mixed media pieces to raise money for future music projects. Check out his music here: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=16ziwHQRawo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 Paintings for 100 Days  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 21:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 06:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at those paws!! Any new pictures?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 07:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still do this as an adult. Boosts the immune system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 18:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cat hates you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 08:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is he damn it???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 08:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible, as I am currently pulling it off. However, it's certainly not easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 03:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then pay your own bills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 05:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can help boost her self-esteem by trying new things together and being encouraging and honest. Don't be passive aggressive and also just be yourself and be patient. Trust is something that is built and it's not uncommon for girls her age to have insecurities. Maybe try talking with her about the roots of her insecurities and tell her about a few of your own insecurities. Everyone has them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
