<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7184</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE spending time with my squish but why the fuck do I need to defend myself for wanting to go out in the real world a few days a month? 

You don't.  Ffs, I couldn't wait to go back, whereas before I had BabySpawn I swore I wanted to be a SAHM.  Nope.  No way.  The only person you have to please is **YOU** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> works from home for a legit w2 paying tech company

So um, are they hiring?  Am serious.  Please PM me. =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am forever getting shit for not putting BabySpawn in a jacket but literally I am the same as you - it's like 10 ft from my door to my car.  And, like you, I cover him with a blanket   put on a knit hat/gloves if it's really cold!  Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I usually delete the Redditor's address after the package is marked delivered.  B/c I could see myself doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, what?  She was raped then you instantly wanted to have sex with her?  Dude, are you sure YOU aren't behind this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying, you can't DDOS someone w/o a LOT of resources.  I hope you have another plan, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big part of me wants to download this, and yet.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a cool website, www.skinnytaste.com, that you might be interested in.  They have a 30 minute meal section, (  possibly a crock pot section, too.)

I recommend for you either a FitBit (you can log your calories on your phone, or online) or My Fitness Pal (but I think I read that didn't work well for you) - or even just a regular old copybook that you write down what you eat.  Honestly that was the biggest game changer for me was seeing all the shit I was eating all day written out.  It wasn't enough for me to struggle to bend over to tie my shoes or shave my legs.  It wasn't enough that I couldn't fit into any of my clothes anymore.

Personally I am doing "Transformation 360" which involves a lot of meal prep and no exercise required.  (I prep lunches for me   my husband on Sunday nights,   breakfasts the night before.  I take something out of the freezer for dinner the night before, too.)  I don't go to the gym (though I do run/play sports).  It primarily focuses on portion control/no carbs.  If you're interested, send me a PM!

Otherwise, good luck with everything :3  I hope you find a program that works for you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is really stupid, b/c Neopets HAS a FaceBook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Google Chrome, and I added UBlock Origin.  It's much better than AdBlocker for WoWHead, and it's much improved the site's performance :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idc who set this up, it's cute :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks, I was looking for some kind of pun :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warm, Cuddly Toes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opened that link at work.  Thanks T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get it ._. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually in awe that all fit on her license, when they can't "Mary Angela" on my mom's...(They always cut off the "a", leaving her as Mary Angel.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm going to post the fantasy version on sleepspell and change it slightly to make them humans for nosleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought he was going to harvest yours and add it to some kind of collection _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to VF before during the day and at night...This is so, so true.  It's beautiful and eerie at the same time.  I've felt the man w/ the bandages by those fake cabins, too.  He's lost and needs help.

Also, I've heard people say "crick" in NJ, too =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I knew it.  Super creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol nooooo.  I mean, I wouldn't care if he was 11 and doing that; by then he's fully capable of going downstairs and watching TV and hopefully not causing a fire :P  I'm impressed with 3, though.  I think I'm going to start training from now, so he's got it well in hand by then ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey soooo if you somehow end up doing old content WoW raids (I assume for xmog) plz msg me :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really? It's 5:30AM WHYYY :*( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BabySpawn is just about 15 months old now, and for the last week or so, for some reason he's decided that 6:30am is a great time to wake up screaming at the top of his lungs.  (He used to sleep until about 8:30-9am before, and had been doing this for a very long time.)  Just when I thought it wasn't going to get worse, IT DID and he decided to wake up at 5:30am screaming bloody murder today.  Well, I guess we didn't need to sleep for 2 more precious hours before work.

Not sure why my previously beautiful sleeper has gone rogue, but omg plz don't tell me this is forever /3  Please send all the coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really respect you.  Back then, I was (must have been, I don't know for sure) feeling these effects and as much as I wanted to talk about it, I literally was not able to make myself.  I didn't know what Reddit was back then, either.

So, if nothing else, I give a shit about you.  Your doctor will, too.  

As far ash your DH - maybe he's trying to downplay it b/c he's worried and doesn't know how to handle this.  Or he truly doesn't understand just how you're feeling.  Whatever the case, I hope you feel better =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sending you good vibes and positive thoughts* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't feel guilty in the slightest.  Everyone needs a mental health day once in a while ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that avatar.starried place?  I miss it...I had so many signatures I made stored there.  ALL GONE :*( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you can do medium if you can get through it quickly enough to get the bonus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH GODS I hate it when that happens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this was me last night as I was rushing to get it done before soccer xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tea.  Not a fan of chocolate cookies or cakes very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I match for myself!  I just wear the cuter sets when necessary ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *High-fives fellow WoW-lady!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I'm a female, and YES I play Dungeons   Dragons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to take the time to quest, you should take the time to read the text, too.  B/c the storylines of the quest are so creative most of the time.  It's a main reason why I will go back and take my time when leveling an alt.  You really do miss out on a lot of the story if you don't read them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would try to install the game directly from WoW's website.  The disks don't work correctly (for me at least) anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's dishonest, b/c after all it's your toon and you did the achievement on one of your toons.  I think most people just ask to link achievements like that as a quick way of seeing your skill and that you know the fight.  I wouldn't kick a player for doing this; only if he was not performing the way he should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure DKs are very good.  At least, that's what I see in my guild for what you're looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen him since then, but I haven't seen Tommy, either because he's still home recovering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's Tommy Taffy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess?  The teachers really appreciate the time to relax, grade papers, whatever.  I remember our teachers watching us, too, but I'm not complaining, because it gets me a job :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tommy's Little Brother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I am a 23-year-old recess supervisor at a local school.  I normally use Reddit for all kinds of cute things, like little crafts to do on rainy days and fun snacks to bake for kids.  A friend told me about this place, and encouraged me to share my story.  So, here it is.


I have been working at this job for two years, and I honestly love it.  I love kids, but as I havent found that special someone yet (not to mention that Im still kinda young, haha) I knew doing something involving children would be a great career for me.  Im working my way through college to be a Kindergarten teacher, so this recess supervisor job is a great way to get my foot in the door.  I figured that the staff would already know me, should a position open up once Im finished my degree.


Plus, being a recess supervisor is pretty easy.  Watch the kids play, make sure they arent beating each other up or doing anything especially unsafe, make sure they dont wander away unsupervised.  Occasionally get asked to be a judge or referee for a pickup game of kickball.  Rarely get invited to join in.  Its only for a couple of hours a day, too, so I have plenty of time to get my schoolwork done.


So, anyway last month I noticed two new little boys in the school yard.  One was about eleven or twelve, and the other was maybe five or six.  Both had the same sandy blonde hair and blue eyes.  I could only imagine that they were related; most likely brothers.  The older boy was being tailed by the younger boy.  I noticed that they were loners, not really playing with the other kids, but I didnt think that was too strange because they were new here.  The older boy read a paperback book during recess, while his little brother mostly skipped around him and played in the dirt.  Older Brother didnt acknowledge Little Brother, but again, I know how that goes, being the youngest of three.


For the next week, this same thing repeated until it seemed Older Brother made a few friends and would join in a football game.  Younger Brother still hung by his brothers side.  The older kids all ignored him and I thought that was sad.  I even saw a couple of times when Younger Brother was wide open for a pass, but Older Brother didnt throw him the football.  He didnt even glance his way.  When this continued daily it sort of broke my heart, even though Younger Brother didnt seem bothered by it.  He always capered happily around Older Brother.


Yesterday, Older Brother got tackled a little too hard during their football game.  I ran over and saw that his arm was bent at a weird angle, so I called an ambulance.  As we waited I tried to make him comfortable.  I pointed to a boy in red and told him to get the school nurse, and I pointed to a boy in blue and told him to let Mrs. Reynolds, the schools secretary, know what had happened, so she could call this boys parents.  The rest of the kids pressed close and I waved them back.  Little Brother was sitting right next to Older Brother.  I smiled at him and said that everything was going to be okay.  Little Brother looked at me with huge eyes.  Older Brother scrunched his face up in pain.  I talked to Older Brother, who told me his name was Tommy, trying to distract him from the hurting until help came.


By the time the ambulance came, the rest of the kids were back in class but Little Brother still lingered.  I didnt mind him staying by his brother, and I guessed that his teacher would know his brother was hurt and thats why hed be missing from class.  Once the ambulance took Tommy away, I stood to the side with Younger Brother for a few minutes until their mother arrived looking very tired and frazzled.


I told her not to worry.  I told her the hospital where Tommy was being taken.  I pointed to Younger Brother sitting on the curb.  Your other son is right there.  I tried to talk to him, but he just wouldnt answer me.  He just wanted to hug that football.  He might be in shock, but I told him his brother was going to be just fine.


The mother looked at me like I was crazy.  What are you talking about?  Is this a joke?  Itsits not funny.  Tears formed in her eyes.  Tommys little brother died a month ago.  W-we moved to get away from the bad luck.  Her voice trailed off as she turned and headed to her car in a fog.


I stared after her open-mouthed.  When I turned around to look at Little Brother, he was nowhere to be found, but I could see the football hed been holding lying on the curb where he had been.  Confused and worried that Little Brother had run off, I checked into this with Mrs. Reynolds.  Tommy did not have a little brother or any siblings enrolled in school with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here expecting mushrooms.  Was pleased to find sunflowers instead.  Loved this.  Thank you for sharing, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats to everyone!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not see your original post, but ffs...I have no idea what I would do if I saw a parent literally beating his child.  It's one thing, I guess, for a slap if the kid is misbehaving, but literally beating the shit out of a child?  I'd like to think I'd *say* something, but I...wow, I have no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Adds this to my metal library for when BabySpawn is older*

I love you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, I'm so sorry that you're dealing with this.  Your husband seems like a real dink :(

I agree with /u/poidipoidi though, and I speak from experience.  You need to let your husband take care of the kids, even if it's not the way you want him to do it.  Like, mine would bathe BabySpawn if I asked, but he doesn't do it like I do and it would make me nervous.  I sat myself down and I thought, well, sure it's not the same as I do it, but at least he's DOING it.  I need to be happy that he's participating in his own way.  He's not doing anything *really* wrong or bad, just not my way and I have to realize that's okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have literally never heard of a "fill your hole" in rule.  I never even thought about it before.  Actually when we were kids we'd look for the pre-dug holes and dig them out more so we could bury ourselves in them.  So I mean, I guess they were kinda filled in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I hear you.  If I was a rich person, I'd def go crazy on my people xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your loss, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would prefer the stories have more "book-like" titles sometimes.  B/c I totally don't understand why some of the titles I've seen are not considered click-bait.

I don't need the title to give me a summary of the entire story.  "Omg I Saw a Guy in the Woods and He's Scary and Idk What To Do" - why not "The Guy in the Woods" - kind of want to know more.

Nothing against any authors, but it seems that click-baity titles get more upvotes.  Idk.  Ultimately it doesn't matter to me.  I'm just giving my thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Strip down to your underwear and arouse me bitch".

Well that escalated quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long has it been between the power getting cut to your daughter's death?"

How did Gale know it was his daughter?  Matthias never says this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Killed My Best Friend [Plz Critique/Is This Horror?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was my best friend, and I killed him.  If I am to be honest, I must say the truth, even if it hurts.  I must give this confession now, before it is too late.  Only the gods know when it will be too late.

Dolan was a blonde haired, blue eyed farm boy.  Me, I am a brunette half-angel.  Back then my wings were pure white.  We met each other by the blessing of the Sun God.  We were both training to be Paladins of the Light.  We, along with several others, heard the call and decided to dedicate our lives and Souls to Him above all other gods.  Paladins are special warriors that are adept at weaponry, but are also able to call down our chosen gods powers to assist us in small ways.

We made our way through our training with little problem.  We helped each other learn our spells, and I helped Dolan master some more complex swordplay.  When we were to graduate and adventure on our own, it was only natural that we decided to travel together and spread the word of the Sun God to all who would listen.

And so it was, for several years.  In my eyes, we were just two best friends.  Nothing more.  I never saw that Dolan wanted more than this.  I never had a clue.  I guess I did not know him as well as I thought I did.

Then came that fateful week.  We arrived just after dark to a small village in the middle of a forest.  It was not marked on our maps, but that was not unusual for us.  Oftentimes little villages would spring up out of nowhere.  We were welcomed by the villagers with open arms, but one villager in particular caught my attention.  When the villager and I made eye contact, I could feel an unfamiliar yet not unpleasant tingling all over my body.  I blushed faintly.  From the moment I saw him, I knew hed be something special to me.  

He had blonde hair so light it was almost white, pale skin, the small and pointed ears of his Elven race, and hypnotic green eyes.  The first night he kept his distance, standing in the back of the crowd as we spoke about who we were and why we were there  to spread the teachings of the Sun God.  Though I tried to look at everyone in the crowd in turn, my eye was constantly drawn back to that man.  When we were done our introductions and headed toward the villages only inn for the night, Dolan was looking at me strangely.  I had no idea what could possibly be wrong, so I imagined he was just tired from our travels.

The next week went by pretty uneventfully.  Other than my blossoming friendship with Lucius, that is.  He would always meet up with Dolan and I in the evening.  Dolan would make some choked excuse and head off most times, but I happily stayed and talked to Lucius.  He told me all about his life, and how he came to be in this village.  Finally on Friday he confessed his feelings to me.  I was ecstatic!  I ran to tell Dolan that I thought it would be a good idea to invite Lucius to travel with us.  After all, Lucius had been extremely interested in us and our Sun God.  Lucius had even said that he was considering becoming a paladin as well!  I could be his sponsor!

Unfortunately, Dolan did not take the news so well.   He cried and screamed and begged, saying that he loved me, that I should be with him, and not to trust Lucius.  Dolan insisted that Lucius was hiding something.  I began to get angry as well.  I had told Dolan before that we were and would always be just friends.  That we could be nothing more.  I left the inn room after that and lingered downstairs in the common area for a while.  I never saw Dolan leave the room.

Sighing, I decided to head toward the clearing in the woods that we had come across before we entered the village with the idle thought of hoping that Lucius would show up.  That was probably foolish, because it was well past midnight, but sleep was going to be evading me for a while.  Maybe I would just sleep in the clearing itself

I knew something was wrong the moment the small clearing came into view.  The moonlight streaming down and filtering through the maple tree leaves seemed innocent enough, but I noticed that there were no sounds.  No scuttle of animal feet as they foraged for food.  No sweet music of crickets chirping.  Nothing.  The air itself seemed to hold its breath, as if waiting for me.  Instinctively, my hand fell to my sword as I walked forward, fully on the defensive.

Slowly, I edged up to the clearing, but didnt quite enter it.  Crouching behind a rose bush, the scent filling my nostrils with a heady feeling, I saw Dolan standing over Lucius, Dolans sword drawn and dripping with Luciuss blood.  Gasping softly, I hesitated for only a moment as anger washed over me.  Before I could react, Dolan drew breath to speak.

You lied to her, and I will expose you for the villain that I know you to be, Lucius!  You may have blinded her, but not so with me!  I will show her the truth, and your terrible plotting will be revealed!  Dolan shouted.  Then muttering to himself, he said, And she will love me for it.

Chuckling softly, Lucius drew a deep breath, and a new light lit his eyes.  You are more of a fool than she is, you know.  You have no idea, absolutely no idea, what you are dealing with, do you, boy?
	
Dolan clenched his sword tighter and moved toward Lucius.  In a flash, I was on my feet and running toward my friends, pulling my sword out of its sheath as I neared the two.  Expertly, I parried Dolans downward slash and stood guard in front of Luciuss fallen form.  Behind me, Luciuss eyes glittered.  What in the Nine Hells are you doing, Dolan?  How could you go so far as to openly attack Lucius?  Are you so blinded by your own feelings that youd sink so low?  My voice was all steel.

Dolan stared into my face with disbelief.  Still, you doubt me?  You would protect thisthing, this abomination!  Why should I ever lie to you, Crystal?  I only want to keep you safe!  You know this is true.  You know how I feel  you know I love you!

Watching the moonlight fall on Dolans hair and face, something inside my stomach tightened and I faltered for a moment. Dolan, I began, my tone soft.  I  Behind me Lucius coughed feebly, and I snapped back to reality.

Lucius was going to die, unless I defended him.  The elf I loved was going to die, because of another mans jealousy.  No, Dolan.  Love is not this way.  You have it all wrong.  But I respected you, once, and because of that, I will give you one chance to walk away.  Just go.  Do not look back, and do not ever try to come into my life again.  I have made my choice, and I am happy.  If you cannot be happy for me, then it is time we went our separate ways.  I brought my sword to bear in front of me.  I have always been the better fighter, Dolan.  Please dont make me force you to go.  Please, just go for me.

Tears started streaming down Dolans face, and seeing them made me begin to cry as well, but my grip on my sword did not waver.  Eyes on the blade, Dolan took a step forward and extended his hand.  Crystal, take my hand, and we can go together.  Leave him, you dont need him.  Hes a *vampire*, the very personification of that which we strive to destroy.  Come back to me, and come back to the Sun God.  He took another step forward and gripped his sword tighter.  Lets take care of this together.

Tensing, I swore under my breath and took my own step forward, but what happened next is forever unclear in my mind.  The next thing I knew, my sword was plunging downward into Dolans chest.  Everything seemed to slow down in that instant.  Dolan was falling.  My hands slid from my sword and moved to catch him as he fell to the ground.  Dimly, I heard laughter  was that Lucius?  did he trip me?  no, of course not, thats just being silly.

Numbly, I fell to the ground beside Dolan, his warm blood colouring the ground, my hands, everywhere, it seemed.  Slowly, Dolan turned his head to me, and his fingertips brushed my face, leaving a small bloody trail in their wake.  Y-youare so stubborn.  Im s-sorry I couldnt keep you safe this time.  Im sorry I failed, Im sorry I love His hands fell from my face and his head fell back, vacant eyes staring at the uncaring moon.  Anguish unlike any I had ever known ripped through every pore in my body, every fiber of my being.  Even my wings felt too heavy to carry me away.  I nearly blacked out from the rending pain that coursed through my body.  Time passed weirdly, and I felt a cold hand on my shoulder.  My confused mind groped for an explanation.  Ah, Lucius.  My love, come to comfort me, to tell me it was not my fault, that everything was going to be okay.

It never gets old, you know.  It always gives me a new thrill to see it.  But I think this time was my favourite.  The hand moved to my face and wiped away Dolans blood from my cheek.  It was Luciuss hand, I noted.  Turning slightly, shifting Dolan to the ground, I stared.  Lucius licked the blood from his fingertips like a spoiled cat.  Well of course he was totally right, dear.  You really should listen to your friends more carefully.  And hey, I dont want you to think were not still friends.  Im pretty much all youve got in this world now, because I dont think your precious Sun God will want the likes of you back after a murder-

Accident.  My interrupting voice was level.  It was an accident.

Oh no, I saw it with my own two eyes in vivid, delicious colour.  You slaughtered him.  You took one step and drove your sword right on through him without even hesitating.  Definitely not an accident, my dear.  Lucius laughed cruelly.

My patriarch will hear me out, he will understand!  He will help me through this, he will!

Oh, I highly doubt hed want to see you right now, looking the way you do.  But I must say, those black wings are so much better than the way the used to be.  White was never really your colour, girl.

My wings?  I turned my head slightly and moved my left wing into my vision.  The tip of it was black, and it seemed that the stain was spreading upward at each passing moment.  I sobbed.

Well, now, dont think youre all alone in this.  I have plans for you, and so does someone else Id like you to meet.  Now, dont be all worried about this, Im pretty sure that you and my boss here will be the best of friends.  Lucius stared me dead in the eyes.  In fact, Id bet my eternal life on it.

Whimpering softly, I stared at the blood on my hands.  Lucius pulled a cloth from his back pocket and wrapped it around his hand.  Placing a foot on Dolans chest for leverage, he pulled out my sword and dropped it, steaming, onto the grass beside me.  Ill just take care of this for you, help you out here, okay?

Slowly I nodded, still unable to comprehend all that had happened.  Where did I have to turn?  Where else could I go?  Lucius was right  my Patriarch would be horrified at what had happened.  Even if it was an accident, clear as day, he wouldnt want to hear it, wouldnt want to listen.  No, there was no place for me in town any longer.  Better to go with Lucius, meet this boss of his.  Who knew what kind of Demon or Devil would be a vampires boss, butPerhaps he would take care of me.  Hide from the Sun.  The dark was safer.

It wasnt until years later that I realized how foolish and childish that hope was.  I killed my best friend, and lost my innocence all in one breathless minute.

*****

/u/kneeod sent me here; I'm excited to get everyone's feedback.  Basically looking for critiques to this writing in general, and if this story is considered "horror" enough for NoSleep and similar forums.  If not, what can I do to make it more horror?  Trying to go for a psychological angle of horror here; this woman believed she was pure and good but lost it all.  Tyvm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to do that.  Thank you so much =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's over 500 words.  Could I post to one of the other forums, then post a link here for review?  Idk, I don't want to waste the mods' time, but I do want to submit here if it would fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Quite Sure/Other Popular SS Writing Forums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a story that I want to post to NoSleep, but I'm not sure if applies.  It's high fantasy, but I think it could be horror as well.  Basically it's about a woman who accidentally kills her best friend, betraying everything she stands for in her life.

If this isn't "horror" (I was thinking it may be for the psychological element of the story...and not to mention the antagonist is secretly a vampire), what other subreddits could I post this to?  I tried the search bar, but I've found that my fav boards come from others' recommendations.

Thanks =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but if you view the comments section, users post that info :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?  "They" claim I will miss the tiny baby days, but I'm really extra 100% sure that I won't miss poop under my fingernails.  Not even a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, if I ever have #2, I wasn't going to breastfeed but THIS like, all day.  I think I might have to rethink it ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stories like these break my heart.  I wish I knew you irl, I'd give you so many real life hugs =/  I'm proud of you for taking that step   moving forward.  You don't need horrible people like that in your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sending good vibes to you and your family :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accurate.  Can confirm.

Source:  Am 100% Italian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !RemindMe 9hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a link to a dress w/ doggies on it for the dog exchange.  I said that it was very expensive (it's like $75.00) but it was just an idea of something that I'd wear, if my Santa was lost.  I said that I didn't expect him to buy it for me, but it's an example of how quirky I am fashion-wise :P

Is there anything similar to what your Ron match asked for?  If your match asked for Season 1 of Parks   Rec, can you maybe instead send a comic book or book?  (If such a thing exists, idk, I didn't sign up for that one b/c I was pretty clueless on who it even was ._.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can sign up to be a rematcher for this round of exchanges.  While you won't get a gift, you will be able to buy one for someone who's original Santa fell through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoy when it's like if you press A, then B, C will light up and do a powerful attack! type rotations.  This way, if I have to move for a mechanic, I'm not screwed and I won't have to start a whole rotation all over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I completed the "defeat" on normal, I didn't realize I had to click on Khadgar when I was done collecting the eye, so I completed LFR and was able to complete the quest that way.  Have you checked on WoWhead?  (Yes I know that site is questionable right now, but it might give you some insight.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a Special Santa :O </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my matches is a person who was shafted in a previous exchange.  (I had no idea it actually *told* you when you received a match like that.)  So now, I'm extra excited.  Has this happened to you before?  Have you done a little extra to make up for the missed exchange?  How did you make it special?

Thanks, guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the time I could muster a decent scream I felt myself becoming part of something else.

I've figured it out.  OP has been assimilated and is now one of the Borg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, just curious here - how does potty training work when you're that young?  Asking you b/c you clearly have experience, and I find that interesting!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be able to shrink the pic with some CSS code.  But I'm at work so I can't look Neopets to try to figure it out for you :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats :)

I tried this once but I was not able to complete it b/c the person selling the item I needed wasn't online.  Never again.  So I'm living vicariously though you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first was as a rematcher for Halloween 2016.  Though my giftee was an utter failure, I didn't let her deter me.  I signed up for Secret Santa 2016   as a rematcher again, and this time BOTH my giftees (  my santa) really were terrific.  I try to be creative with what my giftee mentions.  I have received snacks in non-snack exchanges (I got lots of snacks in my scarf exchange!!)  I don't mind getting snacks, but you might want to ask your giftee b/c he might have dietary restrictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time someone asks, they get delayed another month :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put my dog's name for the who's a good boy bit...though he's really more of a "I toe the line to see what I can get away with" boy lolol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excited as always.  My Santas were amazing last time around,   I can't wait to pay it forward for this batch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14.5 mo old BabySpawn: WAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!

B/c I wouldn't let him play with the electrical sockets/surge protectors/wires that connect our computers.  Wtf is wrong with me, guys?!  I'm such shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ewww.  For the record, I wasn't like that as a teen.  I can't imagine xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I post that quite frequently, and I'm glad to explain why.  It's specifically directed to my brother   SIL.  Constantly they (well, tbh, it's *her* 99% of the time) want to hang out/double date/spend time together.  Me   my husband's work schedules NEVER change.  SIL's doesn't change.  My brother's rotates.  I told them to pick a date *any* date they want.  THIS after literally 2 years of "trying to hang out" even once.  I understand that yes, sometimes things come up.  Things happen.  But when, 100% of the time we have **SET PLANS** to do something, and YOU bail, then welll, like I said - You make time for those that you really want to make time for.  I'd rather her just say she doesn't have time or that she doesn't want to (I suspect it's this) rather than constantly bitching out on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?  I thought it was "That Face When" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lol'ed for real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Chomby Knit Turtleneck Sweater to User 'koolkidz12345'.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  Sorry I missed this earlier.  Sometimes on mobile I have issues.  Or it might be me ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Rav to User 'panikingdisco'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Halloween Aisha Balloon to User 'lasix'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Orn Codestone to User 'innerslowdance'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Neatly Stacked Ice Cubes to User 'kahlen369'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Dainty Ink Frame to User 'puppylove2664'. Click the button below to continue.

You have given Pumpkin Ink Frame to User 'puppylove2664'. Click the button below to continue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Main Codestone to User 'andromedric'. Click the button below to continue.

You have given Main Codestone to User 'andromedric'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Main Codestone to User 'k4tsumata'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Zombom Pillow to User 'hc_pillow'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thank you very much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Shadow Chomby Plushie to User 'lalalawhateve5'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Red Neocola Token to User 'artusativ'. Click the button below to continue.

You have given Red Neocola Token to User 'artusativ'. Click the button below to continue.

You have given Red Neocola Token to User 'artusativ'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Captain Scarblade Crunch Cereal to User 'boundingwarfs'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very  much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given 101 Uses for Old Gears to User 'paperxthinxhymn'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably going to the movies tonight with my bestie.  Possibly have a beer or two afterwards, but who knows?  I'm old and I can't stay up late anymore xD

**Gifting:**  Wishlists!

**Seeking:**  Random Silliness, Active Neofriends, Nerkmids, Neocola Tokens, http://items.jellyneo.net/mywishes/stealing_heaven/

**UN:**  Stealing_Heaven

Will be gifting when I get back from breakfast ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
