<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that probably means he won't be impeached. Gonna be a long 4 years, not that it wouldn't have been anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when we thought the wall was just a talking point for a guy campaigning with the expectation of losing so he could start his own news network with Steve Bannon? Man. Good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the windscreen. At one point he used this mic though. He might still.  
[Neumann TLM 102 MT Condenser Microphone, Cardioid](https://www.amazon.com/Neumann-TLM-Condenser-Microphone-Cardioid/dp/B003HGJAL4)  
[Source](http://equipboard.com/pros/pewdiepie/#microphones) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John McCain is the ultimate example of what millennials hate about the old guard in this country. All talk, no action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But like Ipecac for someone who's swallowed poison, it's important that every citizen of the United States read this article and/or know and understand it's contents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Comrade Congress will always choose  party over country.  
"Red before Dem." It's a damn shame. Trump could break 250 years of democracy for good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was nothing wrong with Flynn talking to Russia about sanctions, then WHY DID HE AND THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION LIE ABOUT IT TO THE FBI?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi truck hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gettin' real sick of this whole "fake news" phrase. Fake News exists, but news that you simply disagree with isn't it. Obviously most people get that, but Trump's followers are a special kind of brainwashed. They're not Republicans, John McCain is a Republican. Lindsey Graham is a Republican. Trump is dangerous, and he's not representative of most conservatives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W-9LafoA9lI)  
Well, now I kind of get why my parents didn't let me play this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jonathan Taylor Thomas won't even voice adult Simba? Sorry. That's just blasphemy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You pay for your library card, and you pay taxes to keep the library going. You don't pay to join Pirate Bay or taxes to fund it. It's not as simple as OP makes it sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a better mobile link? This one is phone cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSao2wXgcuk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yeah, that's the one.](https://youtu.be/XjkFUWoRQG8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Little Donny" is no longer just an Upright Citizens sketch. Really hope this takes off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's just weird. Good though, I guess. Cut costs. Drug tests don't work anyway. People can lay off pot for a few weeks, they can lay of the others for a few days (usually). As soon as that test is done, if they want to use, they do. Just don't let it affect your work, I say. And don't smoke weed in the guard house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most hospitals do pre-employment drug screening. If you're cleaning carpets, your check probably isn't coming from the hospital like a stock/supply clerk's would, you're probably contracted through an outside company. If you're not, color me surprised on all fronts, but in *most cases* in the U.S., hospitals/clinics screen employees (but not necessarily contracted employees). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny you should say that. I'm an operations manager and had to call the security company that contracts with our company today to let them know one of their guards was reported by another guard for rolling joints and smoking at the guard house. I went over there and it was a complete hot box. He tried to say he'd been smoking a cigarette. I was like "dude, I just finished my 20s, and I went to college. I know what weed smells like. You couldn't wait until you got home?" So frustrating how stupid some people can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...it's a hospital. Yeah. They drug test you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that he *wants* to be a dictator, it's that he didn't know there was a difference between being a dictator and being a democratic President. For all he knew, with his lack of civic knowledge, the President was just another newer, fancier word for "king." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 22 when Hot Rod came out, and it was a staple for my college friends. It effectively ended the Old School/Wedding Crashers/Dodgeball era of comedies for us, and it was far superior as a comedy anyway. I quote Hot Rod more than I probably notice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's not Mario, that's just a fat guy and a woman being paid to act slutty on him so he'll buy whatever she's selling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fall dominoes, fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tom Hanks Pro Skater 4: Grind, Forrest Grind!](http://vignette2.wikia.nocookie.net/uncyclopedia/images/8/8b/TomHanksProskater4.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20070919004012) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **President Trump has made it very clear that he expects the Russian government to de-escalate violence in the Ukraine and return Crimea.**  

-Sean Spicer, White House Press Secretary (2/14/17)  
   

**We don't give back our own territory. Crimea is territory belonging to the Russian Federation.**  

-Maria Zakharova, spokeswoman for the Russian Foreign Ministry (2/15/17)  
  
  

edit: formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP senators are split on whether to investigate Flynns Russia ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to, good god I want to believe, but I don't see the smoking gun for the salacious video here, and the fact that Trump campaign officials had contact with the Russian government is SO much more egregious than a pissing video (hey, to each his own in the bedroom), but this is the United States. And a story like that isn't sexy enough to garner impeachment in 2017. In 1976, sure. In 1998, yeah, even lying about a blowjob got you impeached?  
But in this new political climate? Barely, and I mean barely, a story of the month. We need a smoking gun. The NSA/CIA will have to publish specific names, specific conversation transcripts, and hopefully some sort of audio/video evidence. When you bring down a giant, you don't bring him down politely. You destroy him and everything he touches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the White House didnt get its story straight on Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Then: I Would Have No Problem Banning Lobbyists. Trump Now: Youre Hired! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lock him up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, not every weekend. The weekend/day after inauguration he stayed in DC. But yeah, every weekend since that he's played golf at his resort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, paid Goldman Sachs speeches. Simpler times. Thanks, racists and politically uneducated people who thought burning the whole system to the ground was somehow better (or a good lesson) compared to the status quo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, apology not accepted, I guess? But thanks for admitting you discussed sanctions with Russia. In the words of one of the biggest reality TV stars ever, "YOU'RE FIRED!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're from the Highland Park area, your life shouldn't suck too bad. It's all good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $100.00 says even if we do hang on to it, nothing happens and the mainstream media/masses stop talking about it within 31 days. Paypal preferred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sucks the most is that this is so much worse than Nixon lying about Watergate for the Trump administration, but in 1 week we'll be on to a new scandal, another the week after that. This will be forgotten by the masses in a year or two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goon  
Mutation V5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want the parents to put down their phones and hug their kid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing about tanks you have to keep your eyes open to. Sometimes, they just spawn where they're not wanted, with no direction from any nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe W's tax cuts wouldn't have had such a terrible effect on us if we hadn't been at war, but we were at war, and he did cut taxes, so coupled with the deregulation of Wall Street with the repeal of Glass-Steagal (by President Clinton at the end of his term), yeah, Bush did fuck us up into a recession. But Clinton helped a little there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal appeals court maintains suspension of Trumps immigration order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, like when Kelly Anne Conway say an alternative fact is an ok thing to spout out, she's technically telling the truth, because she does it so often that her brain actually believes what she's saying? The brain is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that analogy once before, and it's absolutely accurate. We've got the angry, uneducate guy with 5 beers in him at the end of the bar as President now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't reason with them. This logical explaination for why we use the phrase "extremists" rather than tying a religion representing millions of peaceful people doesn't add up in their echo chamber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump Effect is energizing people to pay attention to politics for more than just the last 6 months of an election, to get to understand the 3 branch government, who their Senators and House representatives ([there are 2 houses of Congress, people, and they're all elected by you every 2-6 years](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_elections,_2018)) are and whether they like their senators or not, so many things. And in 4 years, 4 more years worth of liberal-leaning millenials pissed off about Trump's racism, stupidity, narcissism, and ignorance will be able to vote. And they will be the most informed 4-year block of young voters in American history. If Trump's deplorable behavior  can energize the youth to vote for the first time in American history, he will have unintentionally done 1 thing right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Problem With Donald Trump's Reported Late-Night Call to Mike Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. A good trailer that doesn't give anything away. I'm actually excited about a movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Chattanooga, TN for a time and can tell you without a doubt, the city itself is about as progressive as any other city in the Southeast, but the surrounding area is about as conservative as any other area in the country. Getting Bob Corker out, even after his gaff over the VW plant where he lied about VW pulling jobs out of the state if the employees unionized, it'll be a chore. There's no realistic challenger at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Senators Vote to Formally Silence Elizabeth Warren </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not offended by homosexuality. In the '60s, I made love to many, many women, often outdoors, in the mud and the rain, and it's possible a man slipped in. There would be no way of knowing." -Creed Bratton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could have been a President, but being the leader of a cult is much more profitable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet they'd have laughed harder at some point in life if they'd never been raped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A letter to GOP voters: Youre being conned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A constitutional expert explains the issues at stake in Trumps travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our democracy is broken. We are a plutocracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be so disappointed if I thought I was going to hear Frank Sinatra go "Chugg-a-Chugga Chugg-a-chugga choo choo!" and found a Wilson Phillips CD instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Obama also got to speak in Westminster Hall. That's where The Queen, Nelson Mandella and The Pope speak.  
Bill Clinton and Ronald Reagan didn't get that honour (they got The Royal Room). The Bush boys weren't invited to speak.  
edit: honour (thanks, I like to imagine, my more well-read British friend). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job, Steve Bannon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kerry, Panetta, ex-CIA officials tell court Trump order will endanger troops in the field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it definitely shows how little value other people's lives hold in their minds compared to the profits that are there to be gained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [So, Republicans, a question if I may...](http://i.imgur.com/rvQh7FM.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I read Supreme Court nominee Neil Gorsuch's book. It's very revealing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can't though. That's the problem. I don't mean there isn't an argument to be made (I cant think of one), just that Trump doesn't have the ability to make that argument. He doesn't understand how to debate, he only knows how to throw temper tantrums and lash out. He's the "nuh uh!" kid that didn't believe the earth was round "because I don't." He's the "because I said so" parent that doesn't explain to their kid why what the kid did was wrong when they punish their child.  
Trump understands how to rule as a dictator where whatever he says goes, but he doesn't know how to work with others or express himself thoughtfully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump lashes out at so-called judge who temporarily blocked travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
