<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1467</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/totallynotrobots   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The micro soft B gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks to me like a .22 that was made as a military training rifle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [yup](http://www.independent.com/news/2012/aug/16/did-charles-manson-live-santa-barbara/#commenttoggle) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think goon rather than stooge would have been my choice of words as goon carries more of an implication of violence. 

Nice post though, I have been feeling dis-harmonious all week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if this is important with brown rice also </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I for one will not miss him, the vast majority of the people on his site were criminals and bolsheviks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read my response? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say there were many, many issues that brought us to this state, a right wing media that has brainwashed their followers to the point where fact and fiction mean nothing, a working class that feels ignored and shat on by elites, and the many avoidable fuckups from HRC and the DNC. Also there is the fact that mass immigration of low skill, low education workers from Mexico affects blue collar workers differently than it does university educated folks and many of the educated classes refuse to acknowledge this and prefer to just accuse of racism anyone who wants to discuss problems associated with immigration.

Also quite honestly "progressive" ideas are often represented to the rest of the country by people that are a little... well lets just say they should shut the fuck up. If you look at the vids that made Annaliese Nielsen and Zarna Joshi famous on the net you may see what I mean. There are too many immature ideologically rigid jackasses that think they can impose their crap on others and seem to live for the chance to pose as virtuous. 

If progressive folks dialed it back a bit and calmly clearly and rationally worked on the factual basics of race and gender issues instead of being on a constant search for ever more pointless and minute crap to criticize people for it would help.

What does not help is this "all whites are racist, only whites are racist" crap and nuts saying if a straight man will not have sex with a transgender woman who still has a penis that there is something wrong with him and all this crap about cultural appropriation. Who gives a fuck if some white guy has dreads?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good crane guy costs a lot, a bad crane guy costs a fortune </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Tut) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad, sad killing. reading the comments in that article gives me cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an older bachelor, thank you for your service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> silicon valley oligarchs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This means more men are going to stop sharing info with women at work. and like most of the loony left ideology it will drive a backlash from the loony right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do not have quarters or dollars, they use ... Krogers I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer "give me a pig foot" sung by Bessie Smith, but it is more of a drinking song than a dying song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We trained him wrong, as a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a lot of California Democrat politicians he seems to feel that a constant, never ending series of gun laws aimed at making law abiding gun owners into criminals is a good thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of it is that regressive leftist activists overuse these terms to the point where they can be perceived as just noise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are just trolling us, you know well enough those are all American words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a young one](http://imgur.com/a/DNTsn) I saw behind my house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tractor abuse is a serious issue, please call someone!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angry ram [is popular](https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=angry+ram) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only imagine how many stabbys there are in Scotland, some can trace their lineage back to Stabby McStabface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/asiangirlsbeingcute   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might ask in /r/deaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a style that says he has been in the big house and expects to go back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, a shark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! This is normal and natural. Do you know who uses metric crap? Bolsheviks and Bonapartists that is who. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never have drifted down a bayou stream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn Beatles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carpet sharks are [an actual thing](https://www.google.com/search?q=carpet+shark source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwj2n5yczqPQAhVq0oMKHb64DWkQ_AUICCgB biw=1300 bih=625). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a glorious time to be a damn Okie, Meanwhile, in California where I live gun and knife laws suck ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 06:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed will get you through times of no diamonds better than diamonds will get you through times of no weed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some info [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3bv0xl/were_battlefields_cleaned_up_after_a_battle_in/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 02:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart people that is who. A new tank starts depreciating the minute you drive it off the lot, and since they are built like tanks, a well maintained previously owned tank is a real bargain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, everyone should install a panda bath in their yard, watching them come around in the morning is so rewarding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did not buy her a drink first either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/bitchimarubberbus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobs are all about [physics, and math](http://imgur.com/a/b8vt4) NSFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More of a Santorum thing I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck did you just fucking say about me, you little paralegal? I'll have you know I graduated top of my class in Harvard Law School, and I've been involved in numerous  pretrial conferences, and I have over 300 peremptory challenges. I am trained in jurisprudence and I'm the top lawyer in the entire county. You are nothing to me but just another defendant. I will wipe you the fuck out with evidence the likes of which has never been seen before in this court, mark my fucking sworn testimony. You think you can get away with saying that shit to me over the Internet? Think again, appellant. As we speak I am contacting my secret network of colleagues from the ABA and your subpoena is being served right now so you better prepare for the consecutive sentences, maggot. The legal decicion that wipes out the pathetic little thing you call your disposable income. You're fucking indicted, kid. I can litigate anywhere, anytime, and I can get you convicted in over seven hundred ways, and that's just with my oral argument. Not only am I extensively trained in legal theory, but I have access to the entire arsenal of the United States legal library and I will use it to its full extent to annul your miserable ass off the face of the continent, you little shit. If only you could have known what billable hours your little clever comment was about to bring down upon you, maybe you would have pleaded nolo contendre. But you couldn't, you didn't, and now you're paying for your tort, you goddamn idiot. I will shit jargon all over you and your appeal will be dismissed with prejudice. You're fucking guilty, kiddo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, I believe all the secession and anti-federal lands stuff is promoted by the wealthy class to raid the western states for its resources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Read this](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daryl_Davis) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Clinton was not part of any hateful, radical, toxic, social justice feminist movement.

While that is true I think it is a part of Trumps win (not the main part, but a part) that people look at the internet and news and see "SJWs" behaving terribly, expressing their hate for white males, their contempt for rural blue collar whites and blocking off freeways people use to get to work and paths and bridges students get to class.

They look at this and expect nothing but hate and self-righteousness from the left. Trumps win was a backlash against many issues and this is just one of them

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not engage with crazy when you can walk away. 

Unless the crazy is a threat to others which was not the case here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ronald Wilson Reagan

R1o2n3a4l5d6 W1i2l3s4o5n6 R1e2a3g4a5n6

666 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One good thing about this whole kerfuffle is a rise in the use of "grifter" in common speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 01:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dnde est la biblioteca? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks like the snake neighborhood of snaketown on snake island </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am under the impression he is a bit more open about his views than he was in the 80's and 90's, anyone else old enough to remember if this is so? I think the [rise of Trumpet](http://trumpdonald.org/) has emboldened him a bit.

Also from his Wiki " In 2002, Duke pleaded guilty to defrauding supporters by falsely claiming to be impoverished and in danger of losing his home in order to solicit emergency donations; at the time, Duke was financially secure and used the donations for recreational gambling" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to see similar knives do a search for Kard knife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You serious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 04:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You misspelled gollem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, he ran like a little sissy boy, do you think Teddy Roosevelt would have run? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lobster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were to go back to American revolutionary war or Napoleonic war times a sergeant might be armed with a spontoon or similar polearm, this could be used to defend himself in close combat, or could be used to direct fire. 

  If he was carrying a longarm he might be paying more attention to reloading or sighting at an individual instead of being aware of the big picture of troop movement and directing the troops under his command.

   I think all of this can be applied to the question at hand plus having a fully automatic weapon in the hands of an NCO meant that it would be carried by an experienced soldier that would use it to its best effect in placing or replying to an ambush instead of spraying in a panic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  personal relationship with stimulants like cocaine and amphetamines

He looks a little chunky for that though.

Snifff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a [shake and bake meth lab?](https://www.google.com/search?q=shake+and+bake+meth+lab tbm=isch imgil=pgNELFKRImaT2M%253A%253B0y4zV_SfUGxFiM%253Bhttp%25253A%25252F%25252Fsowegalive.com%25252F2015%25252F05%25252F15%25252Fcontractor-charged-with-making-meth-in-home-under-construction%25252F source=iu pf=m fir=pgNELFKRImaT2M%253A%252C0y4zV_SfUGxFiM%252C_ usg=__4mT72EOOtWsq-QbOiZEPLUkN6V0%3D biw=1326 bih=625 ved=0ahUKEwig2dKKqJLQAhVorVQKHVV5ChoQyjcIPQ ei=_i0eWKDiLuja0gLV8qnQAQ#imgrc=_) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but if you sharpen an axe properly, as it should be done the edge will last much longer while chopping would than if you sharpened it to a shaving edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 04:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see cash for keys mentioned a lot in the landlord sub, it is a bitter pill to swallow but if you are in this as a business you may have to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/ND48h </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 23:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I pretty much came here to ask if he caught the roadrunner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He makes mainlanders look polished, worldly and sophisticated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My neighbors late husband was a handyman and after she passed I was helping clear out their stuff and I found two GE hundred year bulbs. They where made for GE's hundred year anniversary and are engineered to last a hundred years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 07:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> velociraptor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Smiling down from heaven!!!](http://imgur.com/a/fJp79) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting in a legendary thread, watched the game at McDonalds with a bunch of seventy year old guys; luxury!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they have breasts!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they walk and peck from day one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All cats are grey at night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find many similarities in her mindset to people that believe they are the victims of gangstalking. there are websites where these folks gather and they even have their own subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I cannot disagree with most of what was said there I think adopting a less strident tone would have been better. Articles like this should be about converting the opposition, not insulting them and you do not win people to your side by telling them over and over that they are stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had known you were so sensitive I would have been more considerate of your feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a poultry forum some guy was wondering why his turkey hatchlings all died. he did not give them any food or water and just assumed that the mother turkey would feed them somehow which is not how poultry works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interruption in the cotton market fucked them up big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a sign we are in for a cold winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 07:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean shady, do I look shady to you? I am a legitimate businessman, nothing shady about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish Ernie Banks was alive to see this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are assuming he is going to be working for the benefit of this nation, from all I have seen of him he is just too self centered for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dog gets any fatter his face will need a circumcision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  handful of moles

You misspelled "shitload". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your comment so you should add me as a co-author. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard that SRS originated with goons from Something Awful coming here to troll reddit. Any opinions on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a kind of sword that not much is certainly known about, They used to be be attributed to the Berber regions of North Africa and they are still called Berber swords but the majority opinion seems to be that they originated in the Dominican republic. [More info here](http://www.vikingsword.com/vb/showthread.php?t=10636 page=1 pp=30 highlight=berber) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully she will be cited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got banned from there last night, [totally worth it](http://imgur.com/a/cwVjM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeds the fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair I am sure they are very small brothels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
(((Breitbart))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not want to destroy the republican party, just reduce it in size enough that you can drag it into the bathroom and drown it in the bathtub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There [is a hole there](https://imgur.com/a/0RY1F), you just do not see it from this angle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 14:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conspiracy that dare not speak its name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you hippies got haircuts and jobs you would not feel like protesting so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The grift that keeps on grifting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I see some redditor calling another a fucking idiot, I immediately think you are twelve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Documentaries are metal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These foolish republicans do not realize that office is merely a clever decoy!

The real office for the the democratic party is in the big field behind my house, right next to the tractor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know ordinarily I greatly enjoy arguing  with folks both left and right on the internet but in your case it is kind of difficult because you are just all over the place in an undecipherable word salad.

Like this; " after Obama became president and didn't condone BLM even after the insane shit they've done,"  did you mean to say "condemn" instead of condone? And this " no one is talking about things that haven't happened" Is that not the point of this post, things that have not happened? It would help your rhetorical style if you would make short concise points instead of trying to fill the page with text, is English not your primary langauge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want that truck, damn I miss my truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Obama took away all my guns!! Oh, wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please, the idea that this is typical of Hillery supporters is bullshit and you know it. this is just stupid hoodrats who view Trump badly because he started his campaign with characterizing Mexican immigrants as rapists and drug smugglers. If he had tried courting the Latino vote they would probably be out assaulting Hillery supporters because that is how hoodrat gangsters conduct themselves politically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You poor soul, try Bing she is a real slut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 05:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flat tailed little fuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
