<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 09:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Tucker and Dale vs. Evil? You really remind me of Dale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 02:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Way's run not come earlier than that? I guess it just seems like we had shitty Deadpool for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 02:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm just an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 01:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a lot of fun. I just can't figure out how to write reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 01:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way I see it is, for example, most Rebirth stuff is appreciated.  Most people like it, but there is a pretty large crowd who aren't fans. If this comes up (as it always seems to), people are usually understanding and these comments get a fair amount of respectful attention.

Whenever I see someone say anything about Tom King that isn't positive, people seem to get personally offended and those comments go straight to the bottom of the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 23:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it is a children's movie, its not unreasonable for an adult who watches movies regularly to be able to see where the plot is going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cop guy looks like Bob Odekirk so much in some of those pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, I think the recent Howling Commandos run lessened our chances of a new monsters book.

I tried so hard to like it, but I just couldn't, and I was definitely not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, Deadpool started out as a tragic character that had comic relief. The point of his character before the early/mid 2000s was to be sort of depressing but still cool and funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom King is the most circle jerked writer on this sub lately, so yeah, lots of love for SoB. Not to say its not deserved, King is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit that makes so much more sense, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is Daniel Craig worth? What can't he do that he could do with another $150? Not a lot, I'd imagine.

Also rather than have Caville play Bond, let's get another Man from UNCLE instead! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That part alone was enough to sell me on the movie.

Actually that part alone was my favorite part of going to see Suicide Squad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  one of the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been reading this or Daredevil, why is Matt evil now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 03:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Jackson said he's working on Tintin 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw man I'm gonna have to miss Rocky Horror because I'm gonna be out of town that week. Nosferatu and Halloween should be fun though.

Stadium 11 is showing Young Frankenstein on the 5th if you're into that.

Anyway, thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as the last Indiana Jones movie came out eight years ago and for some reason fucking Tintin 2 is in production, you got your wish and no one else did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone knows what the fuck you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you guys! I went to the pre-show meet and greet in Bend, Oregon recently and was awkward as hell because I didn't really know what to do. Brian, I just wanted to say it was awesome that you came up and introduced yourself to my friend and I, it was pretty unexpected and really cool of you.

My question is, at the show, Nikki was singing a song and everyone was supposed to shout at her to make her uncomfortable, I think? Do you get stage fright/are you shy, or was it just for the act?

Anyway, thanks for making such great music! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's take Refn's silence as a yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Halloween activities for minors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19. Halloween as an older teenager kinda sucks. Too old to rick r treat, but too young to drink (legally). I'm looking for stuff for my friends and I to do leading up to and on Halloween.

We're gonna hit up EZ Orchards and Bauman's for sure, and probably some haunted houses (suggestions there?) when they start opening this next month. Other than that, I can't really think of much.

My mom was telling me about how they used to have Halloween themed dances around here in October (non school functions) that teens could go to but I don't think they still do that.

Do you know if there are gonna be any classic horror movies screened anywhere around? The Dallas Motor-Vu is playing Phantasm next weekend so there's that, but I haven't heard anything else. I know in the past, there was a zombie walk and CCT had a Halloween show, but I wouldn't know where to look for stuff like that. Also I think it would be fun to visit some "haunted" spots but I don't know if we're interesting enough to have any around here.

Any other ideas? And no need to suggest just going to a party Halloween night. I can drink whenever, but I want to do seasonal stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  people are saying this looks great

What the fuck even is this place anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he meant Liam Neeson and was so confused and entertained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **WHY DO YOU HAVE THE KILLING JOKE SEPARATED FROM THE REST OF THE BATMAN BOOKS AND IN THE MIDDLE OF THE MARVEL BOOKS YOU MONSTER** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nocturnals is so goddamn good. I read at least a couple stories every October, because it has such a strong Halloween tone. I wish I could get the omnibuses in print but the first one was like $200 last I checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 04:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I'm just happy I can help support my current favorite game developers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much everyone we've seen in the MCU  Dr. Strange's magic  Thanos with Infinity Gauntlet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many fan service easter eggs in those games. Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 06:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  lmao fuckin shredded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 06:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And Doom is different from normal since Secret Wars so Bendis can't really write him out of character.

Bends, uh, finds a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are probably buying SS comics to try to figure out what the fuck was going on in that movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Heart of Darkness because its a really interesting story, and it kind of created that popular "going native" arc.

Is Conrad's other work really wordy or just shitty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we gonna get to see how many points each character got in total? Also I like how this devolved into 'Top 10 Characters' from "Top 10 Heroes" haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 04:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Launch the game, start a match, and tell me what it says in the corner of the screen there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was Kitty Pryde being involved with Starlord and GotG so bad? I'm not *real* familiar with these characters so I know I'm missing something, I just don't know what (unless its because she should be with Colossus instead, which I get). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck did you got to school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it because I like his character but for some reason dislike reading stuff outside the main universe.

But he does seem to be pretty pointless right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Kyle the most as a character, but I was never really too into the whole White Lantern thing.

I really like Hal, but I can see why you wouldn't. Guy would be the asshole of the group, but provide more diversity in personality which is always good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 07:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my God Idris Elba as JS would be amazing.

What I really want is a Green Lantern team up movie, with Hal and Guy and John, and maybe even Kyle but without all the complicated stuff that comes with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 07:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I take it there's no reschedule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm guessing he means the John Stewart GL but John's a hard-ass military man, which I can't see Mos Def doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched Heat again a few weeks ago for the first time in a few years. I saw Pacino punch him and I was like "What the fuck?" and had to rewind it because why was he even there for such a short amount of time.

Edit: Also, have you seen [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fv4D0o41Aj8)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't expect too much and you'll probably like it. Had a few cool plot points but for the most part it was a little generic and cheesy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Rod

The Nice Guys

Mallrats

Goodburger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't happen to know what issue this is, would you?

Doom's my favorite so this is fuckin awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Adrien Brody line from The Darjeeling Limited is weird because it makes me more sad that *he wasn't able to save his*, rather than the kid dying, which is kind of horrible but also kind of ingenius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn that whole movie is an emotional gut punch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What version of the Joker is this? I'm assuming you mean the Michael Keaton one but I don't remember that line at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut your commie mouth, SPR is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is playing at my theater on Wednesday. I'm so excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 08:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to hear this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 08:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

Goddamn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think story mode has a difficulty setting. And yeah I'm pretty sure they  raise the difficulty as you progress through classic, so each fight is a bit more difficult than the last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it was one match in the entire thing that I got hung up on and I've been playing Mortal Kombat for five years so you can fuck right off with that, dipshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is 21+ right? I can't find an age requirement but pretty much everything I've heard of happening at this venue is 21+. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually kind of did this lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, movies don't just get worse as time goes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play a lot of fighting games, and I don't really know why you're trying to be a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What it feels like to play against Aquaman: 
https://uproxx.files.wordpress.com/2012/09/tumblr_m9tzu9er5r1qb73tpo1_500.gif?w=650 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Oh they're taking off their clothes, are they? Let me be real sly about this and casually exit the room to avoid an awkward moment with my parents.*

"**I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM NOW AND IT SURE IS A REAL BUMMER THAT I'M GONNA MISS THE NEXT 5-10 MINUTES OF THIS MOVIE BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT I DON'T MIND TOO MUCH**"

*Nailed it.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus fucking Christ, Aquaman is about to make me uninstall this game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so goddamn pissed off right now. I'm playing story and I got to the part where you play as Supes and fight Aquaman. Up until now, I haven't died once in the story, and I can beat classic battles on hard. But now, I've been trying to beat this fucker for 2 hours and he is raping me so hard.

First, Superman isn't bad, but he isn't fast at all. On the other hand, Aquaman is crazy fast and has really good range. Aside from that, he keeps spamming that thing where he shanks you with the trident four thousand times and there's not a lot you can do about it.

I've tried literally everything I know how to do to beat him, but nothing is working. Spamming heat vision works on anyone else in the game (not that this is my main strategy or anything, I don't even play a lot of Superman, but every time I've tried it it works), but not him, apparently.

Did anyone else have this problem or am I just a colossal fucking idiot?

Edit: I'm just booted the game back up to start trying again. As soon as the match started he jumped over my punch and proceeded to do a 10 hit, 41% damage combo. Goddamn you to hell, Aquaman.

Edit 2: WHO FUCKED UR SHIT UP NOW U LIL BITCH Guys I just beat that son of a fish and it wasn't even that satisfying because that fishdick lovin bastard isn't even real goddamn it. So after about 2 and a half hours of fighting him I got to Doomsday and Superman and I beat both of them on the second try. Wtf Aquaman you weren't even preparing me for a bigger battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't know what that dude's deal is, I'm glad you liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like the beginning of a text I would have to forward to 10 people with 5 minutes to prevent a little girl's ghost from killing me in the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been suggesting Ash for so fucking long. He would be perfect, and I feel like Bruce Campbell would be down to do the VO work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only All-Star runs people seem to care about are the Superman one and this one, which just started like a month ago.

I think it has to do with the fact that in this series, its a look at Batman that almost seems like a "greatest hits" thing, even though its all new material. THen again I could totally be wrong about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? It wasn't in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is he playing the same character as other movie's he's been in? He's a borderline psychopath and also a very poorly written character, unlike any other role I've seen him in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kid is way more open about that than I was at that age. I would have denied that I even knew she exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Everything is backwards

Yeah! I mean it made sense to start out with a Superman movie, but for the next one to be BvS, which is kind of a subversion of what would be typical, then jump straight to Suicide Squad? It legitimately confuses me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No? All-Star comics have never been aimed at kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what do you have a link to a page for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing if the guy was that into comic collecting, they're probably in pretty damn good shape, for the most part.

I'd guess multiple millions of dollars, if not more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That second page makes me so sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool, didn't realize it was back up yet.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Mignola was Mike Magnolia, then Mignolia, then Minolia, then Mignola with the G pronounced, and now its "Minola", which I think is correct?

I guess I just never really looked much at his name and just kinda assumed what it would be.

I thought I put the accent in but it isn't working so yeah, minyola. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me its Darkseed but I'm pretty sure that's wrong. Pretty stupid fucking way of spelling it.

And I thought it was like Thaann-os? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait is this guy for real? I thought it was a joke until I read some of his other posts. What a douche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 09:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ, I'm sorry for your loss but I'm losing my shit reading this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 09:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's sad, horrifying, and hilarious all at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 09:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap you look amazing! We're proud of you, keep it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 09:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol why you so mad tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so fuck. My standard team comp with friends is Parnell, Abe, and Cabot + whatever medic is chosen (shut up it works well for us).

Aaaaaaaaaaaand they all got nerfed on their most important (to us) abilities.

I don't like this patch very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want a Dr. Doom movie where he is the protagonist.

It would chronicle his rise to power and potentially fall, like Goodfellas or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 08:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm imagining it like Birdman but rather than imagining a character he used to play, young Stan puts himself in the world of the comics, so we'll see Spider-man swinging around him and the X-Men doing stuff near him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a dipshit who thinks quoting a cringe video is good trolling meets another idiot, this is the outcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment chain is one of the most cancerous things I've seen in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 07:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what the fuck who thought that was a good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 02:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I don't know if I've ever been this sad that a movie isn't going to be made.

This sounds like it would be one of my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 11:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she cute tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 11:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm stealing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 11:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah?

Have you seen Fight Club? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 10:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you like comic but regardless, if that's what you want, read Squarriors.

Its basically just a super brutal version of Redwall but without the amazing characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 10:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hells yeah, even though there's no way it could live up to the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol clearly you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avengers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight Club </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
