<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4616</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 22:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I _loved_ the Mandarin twist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was Carter's show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well spotted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably close enough t'the mark, but *Thor* brought it's own memes t'the table, right? That .gif of him smashing the cup?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very possible, now that you mention it, although I'm not sure I see Thor doing the job... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Predictability ruins a movie, don't be so hard on yourself. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll be more the Peggy Carter/Howard Stark generation, though, which I think adds tremendous potential to his character. He still pioneered the whole Ultron gig, though, Tony just kickstarts it from dormancy, if I'm correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before and I'll say it again; I love you. :'-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent post. I can't link a screenie right now, but Vision's appearance at the end of *Age of Ultron's* third trailer did appear to show a yellow stone in his forehead. It's been speculated that this may be the Soul Gem, and the ultimate difference between Vision and Ultron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else surprised that he doesn't appear to have repulsors on the palms of his hands? It appears they're very definitely "humanizing" him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Far more "human," right?

I think it's all in the eyes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, thank you so much for doing this AMA!

I've a strong interest on oceanography, but my background in biochemistry/molecular biology has left me a little on the outside, so I have to ask: how useful have [those escaped rubber duckies]( http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Friendly_Floatees) really been? I can imagine them being useful to some extent, but also can't help but feel that they eventually became a bit of a joke in the field, no?

Also, what kind of molecular techniques have been applied to your work? Would you ever use DNA fingerprinting to identify a particular group you've been following, or is it still all down to the tags?

Thanks again for taking part in this AMA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 11:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hair, neck, pits, groin/ass, lower back, back-of-knees, feet, and all the way back, washing off the soap and scrubbing the peripheries along the way, like shins, thighs, arms, and the upper back.

After five minutes (or when your chosen shower song ends) you may exit the shower.

Edit: Give the back of your ears a wipe while you're at the hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 20:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard a story about one of my old Religion teachers; she was highly dedicated t'the job, and took the time to attend their various meetings as "research" for her classes on the thing. Eventually her husband stepped in, told her there'd be no more Scientology for her, and eventually they stopped contacting her.

She later came to realize just how deep she'd been with them. One thing's for certain - the lady did her research! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 11:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I understood that reference dot jiff.](http://i.imgur.com/XS5LK.jpg?fb) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either that or you were overestimating the capabilities of the GameBoy camera attachment... :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 00:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Vine, y'know, like one of those short videos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 20:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT WAS AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, you couldn't make a Vine on one of those things!

*goes back to iOS-based GameBoy emulator.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Panelling in Ireland - Advice and Experiences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much summed up in the title, TBH.

The warm weather today got me thinking about it, but I realize that it's not a straightforward as getting a few strips on your roof and watching the electricity bill fall through the floor...

What kind of experiences have y'all had with solar? What benefits have you reaped, exactly, and were there complications getting things off of the ground? Finally, I suppose I'd be open to suggestions of an installer, and relevant pricing estimates won't go amiss.

Huge thanks in advance, folks, here's hoping we see plenty of solar-suited weather this summer. B-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it was mentioned in the game at one point or another, by well done on making the connection. There's a certain sense of satisfaction t'think that a natural progression was made in the five years between *Sons of Liberty* and *Guns of the Patriots*, isn't there?

I felt similarly about the game's ubiquitous nanomachinery, I think that "commercial" at the beginning served to hammer the point home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your place or mine?

(   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 18:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing that came to mind was [this](https://i.imgur.com/s28PsRv.gif), but that's probably my romantic life leaking into things... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 17:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of that one *Smallville* episode, I think it was from the sixth season, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 13:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe me and you could get funding to test this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed a hundred times over.

Taking out a subscription the *Marvel Unlimited* might be a good way of going about this on the cheap, FYI... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A packet of tissues; if I don't need them, someone else might. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Will pay $$$ for kickflips." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nearly had this once, I had to actively concentrate on not referring to her as my girlfriend when talking with other people, which was tough because she came up all the time somehow.

It's the best thing ever, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why you're being downvoted, everything you've said is completely correct.

I know this whole "Friend Zone" idea is widely considered toxic, but so too is the idea that we're in complete and utter control of our feelings; we're not, nor should we be expected to be. It's our *actions* that we can and should control, certainly, but this whole idea that the worst that can happen is "you'll make a rad new friend" is highly disrespectful to both parties, and only serves to devalue our relationships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you're certainly *closer* than the fried rice guy was anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 01:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop being an ass!

Yes, OP, that's a fairly accurate translation, but I'd get a second opinion just to be sure of what you'd like to say in the translation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *hugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 00:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, welcome our new, naked mole rat overlords.

All joking aside I'd to study them as part of a college zoology course, they're fascinating creatures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wondered about that more than I did the fingers; her mouth looks like it came out of a *Sims* game... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 23:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We don't need to defend feminism; we need to keep the egalitarianism and throw the feminism away.

Soon, perhaps, but I can't agree that feminism was "always" about the supremacy of women above men. Fighting for the right to vote, equality opportunities, and legal protection where it was otherwise denied are all worthy battles, which were perhaps waged under an unfortunately-titled banner, one which has allowed the once-noble fight to devolve into demeaning wars against "stare rape," preferential employment over those best qualified in order to fix quotas, and the complete, utter, and unquestioned infantilisation of intelligent and fully capable women.

The language, as you see, is all very important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 16:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say I entirely disagree with him; the assumption that he's discussing *actual* feminism, rather than the Tumblr variety of Radical Feminazism, isn't that great a jump to make.

Aside from the ironic fact that he's making this post on Tumblr, of course... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 16:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They both carry the same maximum sentence.

In court, yes, but outside of it? The term "rape" may carry a certain sentence of its own that "assault" wouldn't necessarily... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 12:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did s/he say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 12:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did s/he say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 00:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How d'we know [Your Number One Fan](https://31.media.tumblr.com/96e94d3bbd0f30af8e1bfe9f423edd62/tumblr_n8fnuv5J1F1rj0o3to3_500.gif) didn't kill you and assume your identity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Paul, it looks like you still haven't learned your lesson...

Reddit Creeps, ASSEMBLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 15:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could also try NiteLine if you're a university student... Not that they'll know for sure... ;-)

The only reason I suggest them is because they also have an IMing service, you might be more comfortable typing about things rather than talking.

[Good luck, and I promise you, it will get better.]( http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/11114/111140925/4327762-6490987084-pc12n.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, put the kettle on and we'll continue this thread in yours so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cut out the Venom-lightening-flash bit from the trailer, yet left the hair part in...

I'll never understand what went on during the production of that film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loki set him off against his wishes, and "aimed" Hulk at the rest of the team.

Later on, Banner "aimed" Hulk at the Chitauri invaders, which left him aligned with the others on the team.

If you haven't seen the 2008 Hulk film (the MCU one), I'd strongly recommend it, you'll find the seeds of my explanation there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 16:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kids who triggered Tony's first panic attack were doing just that, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 08:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thumbnail makes this one, t'be fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too true.

Anyway, given the day that's in it, I thought it'd be polite of me to [include a source](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/health/11458825/Teenager-diagnosed-with-testicular-cancer-after-pregnancy-test.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. A guy posted his own positive test result here some years ago, and the comments advised him to get checked, they managed to detect early-stage testicular cancer in plenty of time to save him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 19:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true...

International Pregnancy Test Day, anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are much more comprehensive answers in this thread (I'd honestly *love* an AMA with a Continuity Editor, or whatever the job title is), but editors do take advantage of sliding timescales, and even RetCons when the need arises.

Great question, by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hickman's current *Avengers* run might be something to consider as *Secret Wars* approaches... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know our Earth is able to blow up their Earth. Rabum Alal "borrowed" those trillions of missing dollars from The Pentagon, HE FAVOURS OUR EARTH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long as you don't take a pregnancy test only for it to show up positive... Testicular cancer is no joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 12:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liquid Snake: he wanted to save the lives of his genome soldier brothers, expose the hypocrisy of the United States government, and finally resurrect Big Boss's dream of Outer Heaven, where all soldiers of all nations would be respected for their skills and dedication, never to be abused by the whims of weak politicians or their corporate masters again.

Even more so, Solidus Snake: he sought to destroy The Patriots and restore the U.S. to its former glory and ideals. Everything he did was toward that noble end. He would have established Big Boss's Outer Heaven in the heart of Manhattan, and lead his people against their clandestine rulers. He died staring up at a statue of George Washington, befitting of such a true patriot.

Colonel Volgin: he was just a bastard...

Liquid Ocelot: NANOMACHINES SON!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 12:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The public cheered Spidey on, though; I can imagine anybody getting upset at the thought that the whole city all around you wanted the local superhero t'beat the crap outta you for no apparent reason...

FYI, an earlier draft had him (Max) witness his mother, who he'd waited on his whole life, finally exercise some independence in collecting a cheque from OsCorp compensating her on the death of her son. Would've added a bit more power t'the story, y'ask me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'mean /u/NetworkNoel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 00:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say this is one of those ideas that sounded witty and sensible in his head... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheo Hodari Coker (Ray Donovan, Southland, Unbelievable) announced as executive producer/showrunner for 2016's Netflix exclusive, Luke Cage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 19:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it is a pretty ambitious update, such a serious project has likely been in development for a year or more... ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 14:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike never knows where to draw the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always loved that little exchange...

"Never let me forget the golden rule; The show must go on!"

:'-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 20:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An excellent suggestion, I don't think I'd've thought of it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted for the suggested name alone, well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 20:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   don't think she was fat shaming; rather, she understood the repercussions of obesity and didn't want you to be another statistic.

Additionally, as far as I'm aware Asian mothers can be very forthcoming with such comments - they don't necessarily see it as insulting to pass a remark about somebody's weight, for example, merely an observation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 23:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See if you can pick up the *Shadowland* and *Daredevil: Shadowland* trades; I'm not sure what the general consensus was, but I certainly enjoyed them both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You. You're the kind of poster Reddit needs. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I actually quite like apple devices, they're not for me, but I respect their utility to a certain market.

Native hardware access is a *huge* boon to iOS, it's gotta be said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number ten, though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible he asked to be made exempt from Google's search results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was unsure of what flair to use, I'm happy to have a mod correct it should the need arise. I hadn't quite wanted to call it an action opportunity, but hopefully the poster will make some headway with the results.

Without inciting a war of words, I'm curious as to why, exactly, the other comments in that sub are so opposed to this one in particular? What exactly is it that they're perceiving?

Finally, the OP in that thread started another one about half an hour earlier that day, but was advised that the title wouldn't be very helpful. [Here's a link to it](https://www.reddit.com/r/ireland/comments/30l9lb/looking_for_men_to_talk_to_me/), as there was some progressive advice given to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to my earlier post, I might also suggest heading over to /r/AskReddit and performing a search of topics associated with mental health, including bipolar disorder. Don't forget to check the box beneath the search bar to ensure you're performing a search of /r/AskReddit topics *only*. From there you can arrange the search results by popularity, size, age, etc. I'd suggest opening each one, hitting Ctrl+F to search within that page, and inputting your key terms; for example, you might search for "my wife had," or "my ex suffered from..." and so on.

If you do search within the page, be sure to load more results from the very bottom of the comments thread, as some of them can be quite large, and have been truncated to expedite the page's loading time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly did I miss here?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Master's thesis surveying the experiences of men living with partners who suffer from bipolar disorder. (x-post from /r/Ireland) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 16:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly haven't been... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 12:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Breda,

I can't comment myself, thankfully, but if Skyping non-Irish men is a possibility you should try asking over at /r/MensRights.

I'll crosspost it for you myself later on, if you don't get the chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 12:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be correct to say that the infant has no "agency" in terms circumcision? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Slott.

...

Cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why you're being downvoted, I'd **love** t'see that! Regardless of whether it was her or the person receiving the hug dressed as Pikachu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 22:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'mean Slott? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize that Egypt isn't exactly the bastion of freedom that this world looks to when its moral compass appears to falter, but this is outright discrimination regardless.

Though the case is quite controversial in Ireland, Mr Halawa is still a human being and citizen of this world, and if there exist any means possible to save his life then they should be taken.

The continued commitment and tenacity of his sisters to his case is commendable, and they deserve the admiration of MRAs and feminists, insofar as there's any *real* determinable difference, alike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of four Irish citizens arrested for "illegal" protesting in Egypt, three sisters have been released, while their brother awaits his possible execution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I've been saying; I don't think it *would* work in a movie. The best option, as far as I can see, would be to remove the mask. Not entirely, obviously, but I think proper characterization of Spidey on film would be a much more achievable goal if he spent more time without the mask than with it, y'know?

SpOck lenses are really only a second choice, if you know what I mean. Maybe something Tony Stark develops?

Heck, now that I think of it, maybe Stark could be influential in having him unmask t'the public, just like in the books; he's the trendsetter, after all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an amazing letter once explaining it, how they're such wonderful "windows to the soul," but it's quite difficult to explain in a post; focus on Spidey's eyes on the books, how they narrow t'show anger, or expand to show surprise.

The old animated series from the 90s might help in my expansion, look up a few clips on YouTube and see if you can see what I'm talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which could happen again, of course.

Also, maybe he'd have it off during team meetings and the like. I feel like strategically keeping the mask off of him would allow whatever actor secures the role to apply a greater range of emotional expressions to the character, rather than hoping that appropriate gesticulation was enough for Spidey to develop as a character and personality of his own.

D'you have any other suggestions as to how they could expand upon the character's emotional spectrum? What d'you think of the SpOck lenses idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a while, maybe? Toward the film's climax? It'd be a lot like Raimi's *Spider-Man 2*, or Webb's first flick with Garfield fighting The Lizard, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 22:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not beyond the realm of possibility t'think that he'll go without it; as far as I can see, the mask (specifically the lenses) have posed the greatest difficulty to presenting a comic-accurate Spidey on the big screen. We, the audience, have seen the mask often enough by now to know what it looks like as part of the whole costume, it wouldn't be that great a sacrifice if he appeared without it, for the most part, would it?

Oh, or maybe they could go with some implementation of SpOck's lenses?! What d'we think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ther may be shown as a literally strong person - but her character is weak, and her story is patronizing.

I'm currently reading through it, and I'm inclined to agree that the mystery surrounding her identity contributes to a certain lacking in terms of character development. D'you think it'd be fair to say that this story, thus far, has focused more on Odinson than Thor herself? It seems to present his grief (and possible depression?) quite well, as well as his dedication to Midgard and its protection.

I'm not sold on the whole Frost Giant/Malekith team-up; it's absolute **pandering** to otherwise unfamiliar cinema audiences, even though I doubt half of them would have remembered Malekith from his, what, five minutes of screen time in *The Dark World*?

Moving onwards and forwards through the series, so long as it lasts, I'd expect we'll see a wider variety of rogues who haven't yet made a cinematic appearance, and they'll certainly be interesting, but I think the true test of Thor's character development (or lack thereof) will come when her identity is revealed. Don't quote me, but I heard it's issue eight... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 21:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why thank you! I shall endeavor to find out where it was purchased from at the earliest available opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 20:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I'll be looking forward t'that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be a broadsheet?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Are you surprised by how little power you have?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sick, light-headed feeling when the bath I'm in is too full with hot water

It doesn't actually scare me enough t'keep me up at night, but it's the reason I never lock the door when I take a bath, and why said "baths" are actually just shallow showers I take in the tub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D'you even antler, bro? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much, it's gotta be said, but it was always the last one printed off the press for the day.

Was it this bad before we all had the Internet in our eyes, or has it steadily declined in desperation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mystery solved. I was hoping for something a little more dramatic...

Likewise. Another leg day shall go unskipped... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not (it's a parody account) but rest assured that the tweet itself is very real... and very retweetable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pah, as if.

We did get it at home once though, the City Final edition being the latest news publication of that day, but not so much anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sensitive reporting as always from this scholarly journal... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 15:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 10:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you consult with MCD over what posters are free to discuss first, obvs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 22:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like as if this advice applies to relationships as well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Multicoloured Boob Talbot Street" - Can anyone shed light on what exactly this... thing is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 16:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 15:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you manage to go two full days without beating up women and/or children?!

Are you *sure* you're a man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's contagious, you see... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oven mitts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't, but in that case it says a lot about *the adult's* artistic potential... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought I was the only one who noticed! The sheer attention to detail says so much about the kid's artistic potential. I'd bet s/he spent literally *hours* simply admiring a Buzz Lightyear action figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 15:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's much worse than that; wherever the mug is, the term "bitch" has become so widespread it hardly even refers exclusively to women anymore. Irritating men are often referred to as "bitches," just as inanimate machinery is, too. I could easily see the mug in question sitting comfortably in a systems administrator's desk, the "bitch" in question being whatever computer was giving him or her the most trouble that day.

The "Boys are Stupid" memorabilia, on the other hand, is a clear and distinct incitement of violence, against boys. No, not men, but *boys*. Children.

Is there really any ambiguity as to which of the two is worse?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 14:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D'you really believe we can get a completing interpretation of Joker in a full without Batman? I'm sure we'll see them together at some point, but I'll reserve judgment on Leto's take until then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The message delivered by Luthor also seems quite relevant in this day (and quite ironic coming from DC in light of recent "controversies").

Very interesting point, if I'm understanding you correctly. Would you be able to elaborate for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The epilogue, or Lex's letter? I liked the former, but the latter did nothing for me, I'm afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think part of the point is that they've changed it. Or "modernized" it, if you prefer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is dog, bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Weeds actor Mateus Ward auditioned for the role of Peter Parker in the MCU? (x-post from /r/Spiderman) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Mateus Ward auditioned for the role of Peter Parker in the MCU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would anyone be able to help [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/samsung/comments/302ahv/im_kinda_fucked_send_help/) poor soul from /r/Samsung out? Seems like a very unfortunate way to lose so much storage space... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 00:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help, but there's still time to seek the wisdom of /r/Android's [Moronic Monday thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/Android/comments/3000ji/moronic_monday_mar_23_2015_your_weekly_questions/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 02:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I particularly like the cardboard box variant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still did a great job, though, all things considered.

How'd it taste? Or could you bring yourself to eat our favourite hero? :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 21:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense, but the burn put me in mind of [this guy](http://img3.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20100216033402/marveldatabase/images/7/7c/Kaine-(\Earth-1610\).png).

Great job though, practise makes perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
