<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6842</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 18:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you try to improve that by linking a **photo**?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 17:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ctrl in German </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 19:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also doesn't seem like they are abandoning the Nook e-readers at all, which does make sense from a business perspective: 

We are taking big steps to reduce the losses in the NOOK segment, as we move to a partner-centric model in tablets and reduce overhead costs. We plan to continue to innovate in the single purpose black-and-white eReader category, and the underpinning of our strategy remains the same today as it has since we first entered the digital market, which is to offer customers any digital book, magazine or newspaper, on any device.

[source (ctrl-F "eReader")](http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20130625005839/en/Barnes-Noble-Reports-Fiscal-2013-Year-End-Financial)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 14:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/formula1/22672228 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 16:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AGGEymAXD7s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 16:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At that point he hadn't had a contract since the end of June, though, so in a sense you are both right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 14:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically true, although some historical perspective might be needed:

The statute of limitations for murder in Germany was 20 years since 1871 (Deutsches Kaiserreich). In 1965 - exactly 20 years after WWII had ended - the German parliament pushed the limit forward by 4 years for crimes commited in WWII, in 1969 they extended the statute to 30 years  for murder and dropped time limitations for acts of genocide. Only in 1979 did they get rid of the statute of limitations for murder entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 17:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The German commentator said it was 78% for City in the first 18 minutes.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.. that was easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 16:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen absinthe infused (or, rather, mixed) with cannabis as a sort of herb in Spain. [Spanish Wikipedia](http://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/Absenta#Variantes) even mentions it. I can't say much about concentrations, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 19:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dabei handelte es sich um eine dpa-Meldung - es ist also zweifelhaft ob man SpOn hier Vorsatz oder hnliches unterstellen kann.

Zudem: SpOn - wie auch die dpa - hat den Artikel schon vor einer Weile aktualisiert. Wer also hier ber Verifikation von Informationen schimpft, sollte vorher vielleicht versuchen den Artikel zu lesen.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 01:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, provided there exist other "collecting societies" the legal justification for the assumption would cease to exist. 
Take a look at [UrhWahrG 13c](http://www.gesetze-im-internet.de/urhwahrng/__13c.html) (emphasis mine):

 (1) Macht die Verwertungsgesellschaft einen Auskunftsanspruch geltend, **der nur durch eine Verwertungsgesellschaft geltend gemacht werden kann**, so wird vermutet, da sie die Rechte aller Berechtigten wahrnimmt.

 (2) Macht die Verwertungsgesellschaft einen Vergtungsanspruch nach  27, 54 Abs. 1,  54c Abs. 1,  77 Abs. 2,  85 Abs. 4,  94 Abs. 4 oder  137l Abs. 5 des Urheberrechtsgesetzes geltend, so wird vermutet, da sie die Rechte aller Berechtigten wahrnimmt. **Sind mehr als eine Verwertungsgesellschaft zur Geltendmachung des Anspruchs berechtigt, so gilt die Vermutung nur, wenn der Anspruch von allen berechtigten Verwertungsgesellschaften gemeinsam geltend gemacht wird.** Soweit die Verwertungsgesellschaft Zahlungen auch fr die Berechtigten erhlt, deren Rechte sie nicht wahrnimmt, hat sie den zur Zahlung Verpflichteten von den Vergtungsansprchen dieser Berechtigten freizustellen.

In short (and in English), the assumption the GEMA relies upon does not seem to have a legal basis when there are multiple agencies collecting fees with the support of a significant number of artists.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 00:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an alternative to the GEMA in the making - [C3S (cultural commons collecting society)](http://c3s.cc/). 

I think this is the one of most promising ideas to get rid of the *GEMA-Assumption*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 22:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link](http://www.newyorker.com/online/podcasts/fiction) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 17:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that was sort of my point. These phrases look like they were put together by a computer program or by someone without actual knowledge of the German language. 

The literal translation would be "lifelong destiny treasure". ("Schatz" could also be translated as something akin to "darling" or "sweetheart".)
 Both variants don't actually make sense and have probably never been used by an actual German.

Also, let's not even talk about the phrase he uses after that. There he's just trying to get through as many syllables as possible within half a second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 11:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. That was really bad German.

One of the phrases was "lebenslanger Schicksalschatz"? They simply put two nouns together, pronounced them horribly and called it German. I still haven't understood the second one (*something*- "Gegenstand"?) he explains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 16:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That date seems to refer to the by-elections for the German Reichstag in the Sudetenland region in 1938.

(The Annexation of the Sudetenland had happened in September and the elections for the rest of Germany had happened in April of 1938) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 13:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the reunification of West Germany and East German worked greatly in Germany's favor here. The base line for carbon dioxide emissions defined by the Kyoto protocol was 1990 and that coincides with the year the (very energy-hungry) East German industry started collapsing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 13:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I couldn't find the word "only" in my comment.  
Anyway, solar power (which is what I said) was less than a quarter of the **renewable** energy generated. So it's a quarter of a quarter "of a huge 1st world country's power production". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 12:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Can't find that in the article, quote please.

It's in the[ first graph](http://media.economist.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/290-width/images/print-edition/20120728_EUC696.png) on the page.
The data is obviously outdated now, though, with Germany at 25%..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 12:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than a quarter of those 67.8 billion kWh (14.4 billion kWh) was produced by photovoltaics. [[source (PDF!](http://www.bdew.de/internet.nsf/id/20120726-pi-erneuerbare-energien-liefern-mehr-als-ein-viertel-des-stroms-de/$file/Strom_Erneuerbaren_Energien_1_Halbjahr_2012.pdf)]

The rest can be produced without direct sunlight. Currently, Germany is still a net exporter of electricity, although that might change, of course. I don't think year-to-year data is as relevant here as it's made out to be - there are a few factors that might skew the data in all directions. We should look at long(er)-term trends, and those are rather encouraging, I think.

By the way - France has a problem relying on nuclear power generation as much as it does. One heat wave and they'll have to shut down many nuclear power plants. (The cooling water has to be below a certain temperature) Guess were their electricity will come from then?
Monoculture is never a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 23:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's only true for Southern Germany, I think. It *is* called "Eszett" (almost) everywhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 19:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the paper sprinktron linked to.

Criteria used [emphasis mine]:

 (1) one twin used marijuana **at least once weekly** for a minimum
of 1 year, while his co-twin never used marijuana more than ve times in his life; 

(2) the
marijuana-using twin reported not using marijuana for at least 1 month prior to the DIS-III-R telephone interview;

(3) neither sibling reported
regularly using, at least once weekly, any other
illicit drug; and 

(4) neither sibling reported ever
experiencing symptoms of alcohol withdrawal
(e.g.  shakes, diculty sleeping, feeling anxious
or depressed, sweating, rapid heart beat, delirium tremens, hallucinations, seizures)

Edit: I forgot to say, they then (using telephone interview data) calculated marijuana use days, depending on number of days per week used and total number of weeks of regular use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 16:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This study](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/15672455) is 8 years old. I wonder if there's new data out there. Also, where did this "news" come from all of a sudden?

Anyway, from the abstract of a [toxicological evaluation](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/11759152) of nitrosamines in condoms (from 2001) comes this conclusion:
 [...] humans are regularly exposed to nitrosamines from food and tobacco smoke at a dose which is 1,000 to 10,000 fold higher than expected from condom use. In summary, the risk for the induction of tumors from nitrosamines in condoms is very low.

Adding to this, only one condom tested in the 2004 study contained levels of nitrosamines high enough to exceed nitrosamine intake via food in their model calculation.

No reason to panic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 22:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all I was only answering the question relating to the second pass. There, Navas was behind the ball and therefore not offsides.

Secondly what you are quoting does NOT relate to the situation at hand. Navas was not actively interfering with the play when the pass to Iniesta happened and he was not offsides when Iniesta passed to him. That is all that counts. Iniesta receiving and controlling the ball is enough for this to be a new "game situation".

FIFA has a rather nice illustration of this (oblig. PDF warning).
[Look at page 26.](http://www.fifa.com/mm/document/afdeveloping/refereeing/law_11_offside_en_47383.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 22:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Navas was behind the ball for the second pass which means no offside there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 01:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Try this.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=5SuTIR5n6oc#t=34s) 

It's in German, though. In the beginning you can kind of see/hear the sheer power of this beast:  0-100 km/h (~62mph) in 2.3 seconds, 0-200 km/h in 5.4s. It's the 1200 horsepower version - without forced induction!

One other thing they mention is that the engine probably has a lot more horsepower but there's no dyno available in Germany to measure it.  Go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 21:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignoring the possibility and failing to voice opposition was rather helpful, though. That is exactly what the people of Dresden didn't want to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 20:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Sky seems to have wanted some exclusivity left for the CL.. On the bright side you don't have to listen to Marcel Reif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 19:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not many people were questioning the nazis freedom of opinion. It's just that they didn't want to offer the whole city as a platform for their hatred, thus limiting their reach to the main station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-03 21:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Dresden and it snowed for like 5 minutes in the city center an hour ago. I don't even see snow on the ground where I am now - about 2 kilometers away from the center.. That said, they did have quite a lot of snow in the Leipzig/Halle region last weekend so you have every right to call yourself lucky! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-09 20:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [...] or am I missing something?

You might be missing this: 

 *End-user price, includes all taxes.*

I can't personally speak for the UK (maybe someone else can) but about 50% of the price for electricity (in $/kW**h**, by the way) is made up of taxes or subsidies. ([German source](http://de.wikipedia.org/w/index.php?title=Datei:Strompreis_2D.png filetimestamp=20120107034500))

Short Explanation:

"KWK" and "EEG" signify two laws in place to incentivise cogenerating gas units and renewable energy respectively. The "dirty" green is the actual tax on electricity as well as a tax to reduce non-renewable energy sources, called kosteuer. The rest would be an additional VAT (dark blue). So, yeah, I'm really not sure if the end user prices depict this issue accurately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 12:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laut Printausgabe haben die beiden erfolgeichsten Sendungen (beide RTL) 2,2 bzw. 1,9 Millionen Zuschauer in der Altersgruppe 14-49. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.organspende-info.de) is the URL you are looking for. You can download the Organspendeausweis (organ donation card) on that page or order one (or more) for free.

I'd advise you to order more than, so you might be able to give some to your friends. Surprisingly few people have one even if they would be willing to donate. (Which is why the law has been changed) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-25 12:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Wikipedia, the German "newspaper" Bild has the biggest circulation in Europe. The numbers they cite don't seem to reflect the current situation, though. Bild's circulation has been declining constantly in the last few years and they are certainly selling fewer than 3 million - actually under 2.9 million in 2011. ([German source](http://daten.ivw.eu/index.php?menuid=1 u= p= 20113=ON 20112=ON detail=true titelnrliste=1090; alle=%5BDetails%5D))

Wikipedia puts the Sun at 2.9 million in 2009, so this might actually be right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-25 11:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using ones cell phone while pumping gas/petrol can cause an explosion.

BUSTED

A properly-working cell phone poses almost no danger of igniting gasoline, even when surrounded by gasoline vapor with the optimum fuel-air mix for ignition. The actual risk comes from an electrostatic discharge between a charged driver and the car, often a result of continually getting into and out of the vehicle. [source](http://mythbustersresults.com/episode2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-23 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI "Bund" ist what Germans sometimes say when referring to the German federal government. (There's also a rather big environmental organization called BUND.)

Anyway, "German bund" as a synonym for the bond is only used by English-speakers or (infrequently) in conversations among (German) traders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-30 19:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Apparently](http://www.fcbayern.telekom.de/de/fankurve/fanaktionen/16656.php) you can win a seat on that couch for home games by sending photos of yourself (+ friends) celebrating on your own couch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-24 15:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One presidential term is 6 years but he could be reelected once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-21 14:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did take a few votes away from the Greens (quick translation by me):

 The entry of the Pirate Party into the parliament was in part due to mobilizing former non-voters (+23k). Other gains include former voters of small parties (+22k), non-natives (+20k), former voters of the Green party (+17k), former SPD voters (+14k), former voters of Die Linke (leftist party) (+13k) and first-time voters (+14k). 
([source](http://www.rbb-online.de/themen/dossiers/berlin_wahl_2011/wahl/aktuell/deutliche_unterschiede.html))

So, the voters seem to have come from a rather big part of the political spectrum. It's not surprising that CDU and FDP weren't among them - the average CDU voter is probably too old, and FDP voters switched to the CDU mostly. (Although ~6000 went from the FDP to the Pirates)

As an aside: The biggest chunk of gains for the Green Party came from people who had relocated to Berlin recently.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 13:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [...] but i should have used the ' to be completly on the safe side.

No. This was an imperative ("Befehlsform"). You don't use an apostrophe with an imperative - even if the -e could be used at the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-10 21:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, Robben has an infection in the pubic bone.. let's call it pubic boneitis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-31 15:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that the original meaning isn't even relevant. Yes, "geil" has had sexual connotations since the 15th century, probably stemming (ha) from its botanical meaning, but there have also been other uses of the word before that.

Still, the word is certainly not necessarily a "cool" one, it's just *a* word and everyone understands its meaning in context. That's the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-30 12:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The German sports news agency (SID) has picked up on this as well. They are saying that Mertesacker is in London for his medical **today** and that he'll cost 9m.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 22:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only on Sky.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 22:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing your crest after reading your comment made me laugh. Thanks for the comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 15:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concur. 

Also, I'm kind of surprised that Bayern hasn't been mentioned more often around here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-28 17:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Germans do like darker beer, but most of them stay with "Pils" or "Weizen". This varies a lot by region, though. Schwarzbier (dark beer) has a market share of around 1.6% in all of Germany. [German source](http://www.sz-online.de/nachrichten/artikel.asp?id=2816249)

Keep in mind that there are other variants that are "darker" than normal Pils or Weibier, but their market share is similarly small. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-26 23:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I always wondered why they didn't release this car with a more practical power plant. 

Volkswagen offered a Golf V GTI with 200 hp and a Golf V R32 version with 250 hp. The Clio V-6 had 254 hp, so you could say they are pretty close, although I'd say that a Clio is even smaller than a Golf. 
(Maybe the VW Polo would be a match, but there the most powerful engine is rated at 180 hp.)

 BTW, to all the European Redditors, how well did the Clio V-6 sell in Europe? They made it for a few years, so I can't imagine they were too rare.

I don't know the numbers for all of Europe (I can imagine they actually sold most of these Clios in France), but I can tell you numbers for Germany: Renault sold 1611 of the first V6 version and 1303 of the second. [source](http://www.clio-v6.com/Clio_Phase_2.htm) 

In comparison the Golf V R32 was sold around 3000 times in Germany. Additionally, the Clio was pretty expensive: ~40000 ($58000!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-20 11:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. If you look at one of his [school certificates](http://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Datei:Albert_Einstein_Zeugnis_Kunst_am_Bau.jpg) you can see the problem.
From a German perspective this certainly looks like a total failure. 

This difference in grading systems still exists, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-10 20:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit

*edit*: btw.. The stadium is definitely pro USA by now.. I'm in Dresden (didn't get tickets, though) and the volume here (like 2km away) was comparable to a goal by Dynamo Dresden.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-10 19:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [fifa.com](http://www.fifa.com/live/competitions/womensworldcup/matchday=12/day=1/match=300144440/index.html) has stats: 

Spoiler: (119')

Total shots on goal: Brazil 14 - USA 12

On Target: 4 - 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-04 00:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prices for getting your license vary a lot depending on talent and driving school, but in general you are right. 

The speed limit depends a lot on the region you are driving around in. There a stretches where you have no limit for a hundred kilometers end to end, and some stretches where you are going at around 80 mph (130 km/h) for an eternity or two.

Another important thing you have to keep in mind in general is that every German car has to undergo inspection on a regular basis. If your car doesn't have that ("TV") it's not allowed on the streets. It is also not allowed to modify the car's engine or other safety-relevant features without registering (and testing) the modifcation at a government-endorsed testing facility. (This inspection happens every 2 years after the first inspection. The first one has to take place within 3 years after the initial registration) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-03 23:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A player, substitute or substituted player is sent off if he commits any of the following seven offences:

- [...] denying the opposing team **a goal or an obvious goalscoring opportunity** by deliberately handling the ball (this does not apply to a goalkeeper within his own penalty area)

 - denying an **obvious goalscoring opportunity** to an opponent moving towards the players goal by an offence punishable by a free kick or a penalty kick [Emphasis mine.] [...]

[source: [FIFA Laws of the Game, page 35 (PDF!)](http://www.fifa.com/mm/document/affederation/generic/81/42/36/lawsofthegame_2010_11_e.pdf)]

The question then becomes, if this was an obvious goalscoring opportunity. She would definitely have been able to shoot the ball away, with the next Australian player a few meters behind her, so I don't think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-03 13:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Anm. d. Red.: In einer frheren Version dieses Artikels erweckte die berschrift den Eindruck, Deutschland verkaufe Saudi-Arabien 200 Kampfpanzer. Das Geschft ist allerdings noch nicht besiegelt. Wir haben den Text entsprechend gendert und bitten, den Fehler zu entschuldigen.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-03 11:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about the first one but the "huge greenhouse" is the "Tropical Islands" ~50km south of Berlin. (Autobahn A13 toward Dresden) It should be possible to get there by train, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-02 23:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The advertisements after **every** fucking round suck, though. Or maybe they've learned by now? Let's see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-02 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rather big part of that is standing room normally, though. I guess the capacity is around  25000 when totally converted to seating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 02:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with negative numbers as opposed to complex numbers seems to be that for a very long time in Europe, negative numbers were regarded as essentially meaningless and therefore discarded or ignored by many. *"How can something be less than nothing?"*

The main way to visualize them in the end was via debt. (Euler did that, for example)

It looks like there was still some kind of debate regarding negative numbers in Europe - even in the 1700s. (Take a look at [this page](http://www.ma.utexas.edu/users/mks/326K/Negnos.html) for an overview) That doesn't mean the notion wasn't accepted by some notable characters, of course.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-01 02:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems that they are talking about the same thing from 2 perspectives in your quotes: In the first one their statistical analysis including these factors did not change the overall outcome. 

The second one, from the discussion section, is more of a cautionary note: Their data simply doesn't allow a clear enough statistical conclusion determining the associations of saturated fat with stroke or CHD in these subgroups. 
They didn't see an association, but that might be due to insufficient data.

Another quote:
 Furthermore, despite several indications in the published literature that sex and age may modify the association of saturated fat with CHD (5, 6, 8, 10), we did not observe effects of these variables on CHD risk. The lack of an association may have been related to **limited statistical power**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-29 12:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure. It might also depend on the country you are in. There is probably a dedicated agency for this problem in your country, too. They will have advice and measurements in place.

I do know that you can buy measuring devices for radon exposition in Germany for around 40. These do not have a display so you have to send them to a specific laboratory for examination. This gives you an average for a specified time frame. 
*Edited:* (There are devices that can show you measurements directly but these are only for professional purposes and very expensive)

It's also not clear if these measurements are actually relevant to you, as you probably don't live in a region with very high concentration and the dangers of Radon are of a statistical nature: 20000 people does sound like a lot, but the hazard for you personally might not be.

Additionally you can help yourself by intensive ventilation of your rooms and airtight closing of the basement (doors), for example. High concentration of Radon in general originates from the soil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-29 12:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a problem here as well. Look at this map of Germany for instance: http://www.bfs.de/de/ion/radon/radon_boden/radonkarte.gif (BfS: Bundesamt fr Strahlenschutz. [Federal Office for Radiation Protection])
The same office estimates that in Europe around 20000 deaths by lung cancer can be attributed to higher Radon concentrations. (1900 for Germany) [Source \(German\).](http://www.bfs.de/de/ion/radon/ion/wirkungen/radon_ges.html)

Note that the region in Saxony in the south and south west of Dresden has once been one of the major uranium mining regions in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-28 12:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zattoo ist jedoch nicht illegal. (Auerdem: Kommt da nicht nur eine ~15sec Werbung beim Start des Streams? Das halte ich fr vertretbar.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-27 13:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Empires of the Word - Nicholas Ostler

Flowers for Algernon - Daniel Keyes (beginning today)

Also, if that counts: I finished "Roadside Picnic" by the Strugatzky brothers (in German, though) only a few minutes ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-26 18:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all-caps type the ** is simply replaced by *ss*. That has been the rule for quite some time now and that's the rule they still teach in school, as far as I know. I don't see that changing. 
Additionally, the ** has gotten somewhat marginalized by the 'spelling reform' in '96. (There are fewer use cases now.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 18:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A girl in a club in Germany gave me her ICQ # instead of her phone number once.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't sound that far-fetched, does it? 

Off the top of my head:

* You only need one cell phone tower to serve a rather wide area and therefore many people, making it rather cheap for the phone company. (With GSM and unobstructed view you can get up to 35 km (22 miles). That figure is pretty unrealistic, of course.) 
* They've used latrines (or the ground or the river..) for generations. Some might think it's not worth the money to change that - after all it has worked for their grand parents, too. Cell phones don't have that problem. (For the record: I don't think this is a major obstacle)
*  Cell phones can be pretty cheap.
* There is profit to be made by telecommunications companies.
* Costs of 300 Dollars per toilet (from the UN report) is a lot, maybe too much. 
* A cell phone could be required for your job, a functioning toilet isn't. When you struggle to feed your family, you probably won't have the money for plumbing.
* Widespread toilet use requires certain infrastructure which probably doesn't exist, especially in slum-like areas.
* For cell phones, peer pressure might be an issue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 17:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First things first: I am German, so if you have any questions regarding specific parts of the article, just ask.

Now, the paper Die Welt isn't necessarily one I read (like.. ever) but let me just name some things to keep in mind:

1. This is an opinion piece, by a political* journalist nonetheless. Does that tell you much about Europe's perception of American sports? Possible, but not probable.
1. They judge a whole article by a Google translation of a few paragraphs? *Seriously*? 
1. One exemplary quote for the quality of translation:

 "Nowitzki is the man who would hesitate to the average American is not in his living room. He is reticent, has manners and is cultivated."

The original sentence says: "Nowitzki is the kind of person an average American would let into his living room without hesitating. He is reticent [or maybe tentative], well-mannered and civilized." 

They did get the gist of the article kind of right. Although: 

 Maybe ghetto basketball is just a poor term for selfish play?

I wouldn't say that's what the author meant. Maybe selfish play is a part of his definition of "ghetto basketball" but it seems to me that on the whole it's more about the *show* aspect of it. Dunking as opposed to throwing. Depending on the one (or two) star player(s). Things like that seem to - for him - lessen the impact of team play on basketball. He then supposes that, in light of the Mavs' recent success, that is changing.

*I don't really know that guy but judging from past articles he's writing all kinds of business and politics related articles. I wouldn't call him a sports expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 15:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, with the corona being at ~1-3 million kelvin and the core at more than 13 million kelvin, the centre is still considerably hotter. (sources [1](http://nssdc.gsfc.nasa.gov/planetary/factsheet/sunfact.html) and [2](http://imagine.gsfc.nasa.gov/docs/science/mysteries_l1/corona.html))
The corona is certainly hotter than the surface, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany elections. that's all i saying.

...regional elections in 2 states (Berlin, Mecklenburg-West Pomerania) and local elections in Lower Saxony in *September*. Do you really think that's an issue here?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-08 14:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that Germany has surplus in their trade with China.

Do you have a source for that? According to [destatis \[German\]](http://www.destatis.de/jetspeed/portal/cms/Sites/destatis/Internet/DE/Navigation/Publikationen/STATmagazin/2008/Aussenhandel2008__7,templateId=renderPrint.psml__nnn=true) (the German federal agency for statistics) Germany hasn't had a trade surplus with China since 1989.

Look at [this graphic.](http://www.destatis.de/jetspeed/portal/cms/Sites/destatis//Internet/DE/Grafiken/Publikationen/STATmagazin/Aussenhandel/AHChina,property=image.gif) "Einfuhr" means imports, "Ausfuhr" stands for exports, "Milliarden" is billions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-23 11:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After some googling it doesn't seem like CRS3 adoption is unsatisfactory: 

 Liu added that the total capacity of the CRS-3's now in deployment adds up to 7.5 petabits per second. That said, Liu was not able to disclose how many actual units Cisco has sold or shipped, but noted that the uptake of the CRS-3 has been four times faster than it was for the CRS-1. The company has also said that both AT T and Comcast are CRS-3 customers.
[\[source\]](http://www.enterprisenetworkingplanet.com/nethub/article.php/3930581/Cisco-Grows-CRS-3.htm)

Compatibilty with the predecessor CRS-1 might be helping here. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DIW muss Statistik korrigieren: Kinderarmut nur halb so hoch wie gedacht </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-06 13:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 20:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The club was founded in 1904. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-15 16:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The steam that turns the turbines is in its own closed loop and does not interact with the water that passes over the fuel.

To further clarify, that sentence is true for Pressurized Water Reactors (PWR) but not for Boiling Water Reactors (BWR). The latter type of reactor has only one water/steam loop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rethinking Germany: After not endorsing the Libya no-fly zone and its small Green party victory, developments in Germany should be praised. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-15 14:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visualization of deaths per TWh of different energy sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-16 19:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 22:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the ticker they said Robben had signalled some injury before. I didn't see that either, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 12:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fuel rods at No. 2 reactor of Fukushima No. 1 nuke plant fully exposed](http://english.kyodonews.jp/news/2011/03/77854.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
