<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2724</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The source for Donald Trump's inaccurate "crime statistics" tweet was an actual neo-Nazi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 05:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Democratic senator is pressing for an audit of the Pentagon after a task force spent $43 million to build a compressed natural gas station in Afghanistan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 17:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government to Chelsea Manning: Were Denying Your Treatment for Your Own Good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 23:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TPP trade pact spreads SOPA-like censorship worldwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 22:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TPP trade pact spreads SOPA-like censorship worldwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 22:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Tillman, the original skateboarding dog from the viral video, died about two weeks ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Everyone Thinks T-Mobile's 'Binge On' Video Streaming Is a Good Idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 23:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the piece? You totally missed the point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama Is Not My Ally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 22:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 22:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree -- and that's without even getting into how deeply his policies are failing poor folks and queer people of color </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This morning, I read that OUT Magazine named President Obama as its LGBT "Ally of the Year." Literally one minute later, Chelsea Manning called me from prison." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 22:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama Is Not My Ally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 21:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This morning, I read that OUT Magazine named President Obama as its LGBT "Ally of the Year." Literally one minute later, Chelsea Manning called me from prison." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 21:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama Is Not My Ally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire Water Park Founder Chains Himself to Water Slide to Save Business. The founder of New Hampshire's Liquid Planet Water Park has chained himself to a 30-foot slide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 21:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire Water Park Founder Chains Himself to Water Slide to Save Business. The founder of New Hampshire's Liquid Planet Water Park has chained himself to a 30-foot slide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire Water Park Founder Chains Himself to Water Slide to Save Business. The founder of New Hampshire's Liquid Planet Water Park has chained himself to a 30-foot slide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Blocks NSA Spying and Sets an Important Precedent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 22:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning's statement for Aaron Swartz Day 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 16:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clock is ticking on a time bomb that could blow up a free internet: the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clock is ticking on a time bomb that could blow up a free internet: the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell hath no fury like the Internet scorned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clock is ticking on a time bomb that could blow up a free internet: the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 17:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clock is ticking on a time bomb that could blow up a free internet: the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the TPP will affect digital rights and the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tldr: the TPP basically exports the DMCA to the rest of the signatories.

Yes, but it doesn't export the DMCA's counter-notice / fair use provisions. That's what makes it so dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clock is ticking on a time bomb that could blow up a free internet: the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are battles raging in each country, it's definitely not a done deal yet. Each country's parliament still needs to vote on this, including U.S. Congress. Handy dandy link to contact your congresscritters if you want, by the way: https://www.fightthetpp.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, for what its worth, I didn't write this headline, though I do think its a fair assessment of the situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clock is ticking on a time bomb that could blow up a free internet: the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 18:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 18:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, I think you'd be hard pressed to find any economist who would argue that the TPP is socialism. It's certainly not "free market capitalism" as proponents claim, but it's about as far as it can be from anything resembling marxism or related ideologies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full chapter by chapter analysis of the Trans-Pacific Partnership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 16:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TPP: Jailbreaking Your Phone Could Land You In Jail Under Treaty Rules, Critics Claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TPP: Jailbreaking Your Phone Could Land You In Jail Under Treaty Rules, Critics Claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 20:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 19:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a bunch:
Fight for the Future
Electronic Frontier Foundation
Open Media
Popular Resistance 
Flush the TPP
Public Citizen Global Trade Watch
Label GMOs
Communication Workers of America
Free Software Foundation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final text of the TPP has been released. Here's how the Intellectual Property chapter will affect the Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 18:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early this morning, the government of New Zealand released the [final negotiated text](http://www.mfat.govt.nz/Treaties-and-International-Law/01-Treaties-for-which-NZ-is-Depositary/0-Trans-Pacific-Partnership-Text.php) of the Trans-Pacific Partnership agreement (TPP.) 

Disclosure: I work for [Fight for the Future](https://www.fightforthefuture.org), a grassroots Internet freedom group that has been [opposing the TPP](https://www.fightthetpp.org) due to concerns over the lack of transparency and extremist copyright provisions that we feel could lead to Internet censorship and other threats to freedom of expression.

Since the TPP text was released this morning, we've been reading through it, starting with the Intellectual Property chapter. I'm pasting below my initial raw notes on what we've found so far. It would be awesome if others could read through it, see if they agree with our analysis, and add other sections of concern in the comments, so we can start to get a full picture of how this agreement will impact the Internet and related technology issues.

This list is also on a press release we put out this morning: http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/132605875893/final-tpp-text-confirms-worst-fears-shadowy

*Article 18.26: Term of Protection for Trademarks*
Increases the minimum protection for trademarks to 10 years, forcing countries to follow the U.S. model on this rather than make their own trademark policy based on the public interest. This will limit technological innovation and could curtail affordable access to medicines or other basic necessities.

*Article 18.37: Patentable Subject Matter*
Allows for the patenting of "new methods of using a known product," which essentially allows for unlimited patents from Pharmaceutical companies and will block affordable access to medicines and medical procedures and prevent innovation of better and more affordable healthcare procedures.

*Article 18:28: Domain Names*
This undermines anonymous online expression by requiring governments to keep a public database of real names and addresses associated with country code top level domain names, (such as .us, .au, .ca, etc). This is dangerous especially for the ability of opposition groups in repressive countries to voice their concerns online without fear of violent retribution.

*Article 18.63: Term of Protection for Copyright and related Rights*
This is one of the most egregious pieces of the deal. It forces the most draconian parts of the U.S.'s broken copyright system on the rest of the world without expanding protections for fair use and free speech. This section requires countries to enforce copyright until 70 years after the creators death. This will keep an enormous amount of information, art, and creativity out of the public domain for decades longer than necessary, and allow for governments to abuse copyright laws to censor online content at will, since so much of it will be copyrighted for so long.

*Article 18.68: Technological Protection Measures*
This section attempts to make it a crime to circumvent any "Digital Rights Management" (DRM) locks on a device, even if you own it. It could criminalize people who unlock their phones in order to use accessibility software, for example, or make it illegal to circumvent DRM on a computer in order to use Linux.

*Article 18.69: Rights Management Information* 
This section criminalizes basic activities that involve removing a Rights Management marker, even if its done in the process of creating something totally legal. For example, cropping a photo that has a watermark on it in order to use it as part of a fair use creation or as part of a political protest. And yes, that does include if you give credit elsewhere (like the description of a YouTube video).

*Article 18.78: Trade Secrets*
Criminalizes the "unauthorized and wilful disclosure of a trade secret including via a computer system." This is clearly intended to stifle whistleblowers and journalism covering the documents they expose -- it could criminalize, for example, The Guardian's reporting on the documents they received from Edward Snowden.

*Section J: Internet Service Providers*
This is one of the worst sections that impacts the openness of the Internet. This section requires Internet Service Providers to play "copyright cops" and assist in the enforcement of copyright takedown requests -- but it does not require countries to have a system for counter-notices, so a U.S company could order a website to be taken down in another country, and there would be no way for the person running that website to refute their claims if, say, it was a political criticism website using copyrighted content in a manner consistent with fair use.

Section J makes it so ISPs are not liable for any wrongdoing when they take down content -- incentivizing them to err on the side of copyright holders rather than on the side of free speech. 

Additionally, the Trans-Pacific Partnerships chapter on investments includes intellectual property as a matter that can be included in investor-state dispute settlements (ISDS). 

*Article 9: Investor-State Dispute Settlement*
No matter what else is in the Trans-Pacific Partnership, this section makes it bad for people everywhere. It allows companies to sue governments  but not the other way around. These legally-binding challenges are decided by arbitrators hired for that case only, and investors have every reason to stack the cases with as many standards violations as theyd like. Intellectual property is just one of the many things that investors can bring suits over, but we could soon see cases of investors suing governments because they think punishments and rewards for copyright or trademark violations arent enough to satisfy them. Decisions that impact the future of the Internet should never be made in secretive international tribunals  especially not ad hoc ones.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning publishes a 129-page surveillance reform bill from her cell in Leavenworth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imprisoned government leaker Chelsea Manning spent months behind bars writing draft legislation to overhaul the nations spying powers, she revealed on Tuesday. The sweeping legislation would abolish the shadowy court used to oversee American intelligence operations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning just wrote a 129 page bill to abolish the secret surveillance courts that authorize NSA bulk spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 17:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now Chelsea's entering into it? So... that's a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 17:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe "curtail" would be a better word?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 17:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a bunch of experts to read it and help summarize it, but the big #1 main thing that it does is abolish the secretive Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Courts (the so-called "secret courts" that are always referenced in stories about the NSA etc) and move that system over to District Court system, to provide for more transparency and oversight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 17:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the purpose here is to spark a discussion amongst all the various groups and experts that are working on this. Chelsea explains clearly why the USA Freedom Act totally failed -- if groups had read her analysis on that before getting behind it things might be different right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning just wrote a bill that could fix the U.S. government's mass surveillance programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning just wrote a 139 page bill to fix the U.S. government's mass surveillance programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> F.B.I. Tool to Identify Extremists Is Criticized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 18:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Parliament Urges Protection for Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU Parliament Votes To Drop Charges Against Snowden. They also encouraged members to block his extradition "in recognition of his status as a whistleblower and human rights defender." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 18:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 17:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a nonbinding resolution, but this is a really good sign. I hope Snowden gets a decent beer and an epic party thrown for him when he arrives in the EU country of his choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Parliament has called on EU member states to drop all criminal charges against Edward Snowden and protect him against extradition to the United States. MEPs voted 285 votes to 281 in favour of a resolution that the NSA whistleblower should be allowed to seek safe asylum in the EU. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 17:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Union Calls For Edward Snowden Criminal Charges To Be Dropped: Will Whistleblower Find Asylum in Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 16:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Union Calls For Edward Snowden Criminal Charges To Be Dropped: Will Whistleblower Find Asylum in Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 16:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposed cyberlaw gives feds too much access to our data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 16:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Parliament just dealt a major blow to net neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 17:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA: Facebook denies lobbying for controversial surveillance law but fails to reveal stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 13:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 19:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook has shown themselves time and again to have little regard for their users' privacy. It's not that surprising that they'd be quietly supporting this bill -- it would give them sweeping legal immunity for a wide range of abusive data practices. It's also not surprising that they're doing it in secret rather than publicly, and then lying about it to the press. CISA is supremely unpopular, and Facebook knows that supporting it publicly would be a PR nightmare. It seems they've decided to avoid taking a stance and instead are just casually supporting it in closed door conversations with the Hill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on what you mean by "this shit," i think it's definitely true that there will always be an ongoing battle between forces of authoritarianism and those who advocate for freedom, but to paraphrase MLK the arc of moral history bends toward justice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IRS possessed Stingray cellphone surveillance gear, documents reveal. Invoices reveal tax service, 13th federal agency to use secretive dragnet, upgraded device that pretends to be cellphone tower to gather metadata </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 15:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While Most Of The Rest Of The Internet Industry Is Fighting Against CISA, Facebook Accused Of Secretly Lobbying For It | Techdirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 15:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy group slams Facebook for quiet CISA support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 13:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well these people are making us all look like slacktivists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 11:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awesome design, important topic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 11:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 11:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the U.S. would be totally fine with a law like this in Russia or China that allowed them to jail U.S. citizens for crimes committed here, right? Oh wait no not at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cisa amendment would allow US to jail foreigners for crimes committed abroad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 11:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These are not slacktivists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 11:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Has Never Read CISA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 01:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz Has Never Read CISA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 01:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate debates cybersecurity bill as opposition grows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 09:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate debates cybersecurity bill as opposition grows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 09:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 09:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone can use this easy tool to email, tweet, and call their lawmakers against CISA: https://www.decidethefuture.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 09:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You betcha! At FaxBigBrother.com

But also read this: https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/3pjmb7/the_senate_lost_hundreds_of_thousands_of_faxes/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 09:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sadly really true. We at FFTF used to be able to raise a lot of awareness on reddit and now many of our staff are shadowbanned in major subreddits for posting totally relevant and important information </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech industry leaders oppose CISA as dangerous to privacy and security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 00:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy's last chance: CISA is on the Senate floor NOW and WE MUST KILL IT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 23:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA cyber spying bill is up for a vote in a matter of days. Internet users are planning a protest in Washington, DC tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 23:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA cyber spying bill is up for a vote in a matter of days. Internet users are planning a protest in Washington, DC tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 23:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 23:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would give companies like Facebook and Google legal immunity -- making it so no one can sue them in court -- when they share private data with the U.S. government, in the name of preventing cyber attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 23:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your'e confused. This bill doesn't have to do with regulating content, it's about allowing companies to share data with the government.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 18:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly helps to have the companies but it's not a silver bullet. We still need to rally and pester congress. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 18:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's often true when companies speak out like this, but in this case it's not. CISA would give these companies sweeping legal immunity, which would actually be really good for them. I think they're opposing this not so much out of economic self-interest but because they've realized it's really unpopular with their users and they want to maintain their image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 18:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are valid points. Companies should definitely do more, but getting them just to say ANYTHING, is the first step. Now we can pressure and call for them to do more and take action like they did with SOPA, but first we have to get them on the record as opposing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 18:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear! Keep the pressure on. Everyone can call and email easily using this page: https://www.decidethefuture.org

EFF also has a call tool here: https://act.eff.org/action/tell-the-senate-vote-no-on-the-cybersecurity-information-sharing-act </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good point -- we'll see if we can add some functionality where you can hover over the company's "star" and see some details for how they got it. I think we can do this soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 15:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's a good sign. Unfortunately Congress cares a lot more about what these companies think than what all of us think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple, Google and Twitter among 22 tech companies opposing CISA bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 15:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple, Google and Twitter among 22 tech companies opposing Cisa bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 12:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, definitely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple said Tuesday that it opposes a controversial cybersecurity bill that, according to critics, would give the government sweeping new powers to spy on Americans in the name of protecting them from hackers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 01:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy-invasive "cybersecurity" legislation is back from the dead. The Senate Intelligence Committee is pushing the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act (CISA). It's a privacy invasive surveillance bill that must be stopped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy-invasive "cybersecurity" legislation is back from the dead. The Senate Intelligence Committee is pushing the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act (CISA). It's a privacy invasive surveillance bill that must be stopped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple says its against a key cybersecurity bill, days before a crucial vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 01:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but T-Mobile trusted them with their customers data knowing that Experian had been hacked more than 100 times. Companies need to be held accountable when they make decisions like that
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter is the latest tech heavyweight to voice its opposition to CISA, a controversial cybersecurity bill that could hit the Senate floor as early as Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 18:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter is the latest tech heavyweight to voice its opposition to CISA, a controversial cybersecurity bill that could hit the Senate floor as early as Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile let millions of their customers get hacked. Now they're lobbying to get away with it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 16:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've Got Fail: high school students hack CIA director's AOL account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 02:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've Got Fail: high school students hack CIA director's AOL account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 02:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA cyber bill could hit the Senate floor Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 22:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sprint to throttle unlimited data after customers use 23GB per month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP Exclusive: Under Clinton, State's cybersecurity suffered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 15:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP Exclusive: Under Clinton, State's cybersecurity suffered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 15:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops are asking Ancestry.com and 23andMe for their customers DNA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 15:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 22:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, pretty much agree, but for those of us who have been fighting CISA, this is good news. Congress sadly cares more about what Google and Facebook think than hundreds of thousands of constituent calls and emails  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 22:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure I'll get a lot of criticism here, which I welcome, but I just want to say that if we can't criticize our favorite candidates and call them out when they take a bad position, we'll forever be in a position of voting for lesser evils instead of pushing for the best and most sweeping policy changes we can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really want to #FeelTheBern, but Bernie's response about Edward Snowden made me write this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 22:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery was also legal once. Do you think escaped slaves should have been punished? 

How about people who resisted Stalin? That was illegal for them too.

If we choose to care more about legality than morality, i fear for our future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech giants warn cybersecurity bill could undermine users' privacy. Facebook, Google and Yahoo argue Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act under Senate review could cause collateral damage to innocent third parties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech giants warn cybersecurity bill could undermine users' privacy. Facebook, Google and Yahoo argue Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act under Senate review could cause collateral damage to innocent third parties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders' Snowden Response Proves He Doesn't Want a "Revolution" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 18:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NSA and U.S. government also broke the law. Where are Bernie and Clinton on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowden might want to ask Chelsea Manning how she's doing before deciding he'll get a fair trial here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders' Snowden Response Proves He Doesn't Want a "Revolution" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 17:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber bill could let feds spy on library users, advocate warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber bill could let Feds spy on library users, advocate warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 15:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York woman sues 12-year-old nephew over hug that broke her wrist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 03:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 22:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish Ron Wyden had thought of this before he helped pave the way for the TPP, which would export the U.S.'s broken copyright system to the rest of the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Copyright law may have hindered VW emissions detection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 22:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About Bernie Sander's revolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders comes out against CISA, a controversial cybersecurity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 18:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet Providers Would Be Forced to Block Filesharing Sites Under TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 22:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Senators keep lying about what CISA would be used for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 21:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 21:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend and I are diving into the text now. Some big takeaways:

* TPP would increase most country's maximum copyright term limits by 10 years

* TPP would allow companies to patent "new ways of using" an existing invention, which could create a somewhat infinite patent loop

* TPP could force ISPs to block pirate sites or other sites hosting infringing content (like SOPA)

* TPP would introduce new criminal penalties for modifying or unlocking your own devices

There's a ton more in there. Hope others will read the text and share their thoughts: https://wikileaks.org/tpp-ip3/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks release of TPP deal text confirms 'freedom of expression' fears. Intellectual property rights chapter appears to give Trans-Pacific Partnership countries countries greater power to stop information from going public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 20:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks release of TPP deal text confirms 'freedom of expression' fears. Intellectual property rights chapter appears to give Trans-Pacific Partnership countries countries greater power to stop information from going public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks release of TPP deal text confirms 'freedom of expression' fears. Intellectual property rights chapter appears to give Trans-Pacific Partnership countries countries greater power to stop information from going public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 20:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother Jones was sued by a billionaire political donor. They won. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 01:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TPP trade deal ready for final approval as digital rights groups sound warning. After five years of marathon talks, the Trans-Pacific Partnership has finally been agreed to. But as trade leaders take the hard sell back home, civil liberties advocates say the deal is bad news for digital rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 20:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's trade minister is promising to release a provisional copy of the Trans-Pacific Partnership trade agreement in the next few days  but Ed Fast won't say whether it will include details of the all-important side deals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 20:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly don't disagree with you, but I think the significance of this is more about the rising public opposition to TPP that's forcing candidates like her to come out against it. It's good news for the Internet, so worth celebrating, even if we know they're only doing it because they have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't trust any politician, but this is good news for the movement that's been fighting TPP (and other bad, secretive trade deals, for years.) Keep pushing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton comes out against TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton says she doesn't support Trans-Pacific Partnership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top European Court Rules That NSA Spying Makes U.S. Unsafe For Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 23:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy groups hail 'freedom from surveillance' in European court's Facebook ruling. European court finds in favor of Max Schrems, student who asked EUs data protection commissioner to bar Facebook from transmitting his data to the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 20:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European court affirms citizens right to privacy from American tech companies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 19:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trans-Pacific Partnership will ban data localization laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 18:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The TPP deal protects old companies at the expense of the new </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 15:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critics say Experian CEO should resign after the latest data breach. Pending legislation would give companies immunity for data breaches if they agree to share data with the feds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 18:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
