<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject723</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amos 5:26 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A down vote never hurt anyone.  I get them all the time.  Truth has its own power, and you should never despair of telling it!  If you get downvoted for posting truth from scripture just take heart that God will honor that as persecution (very minor persecution, to be sure).  The cross is offensive to the natural mind and the old heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the correct thing to say is that your views no longer align with scripture.  That frames it correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narrow is the way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little snark to spice up your Sunday.  Seriously though-destroy that idol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing how old heresies always creep back up.  Google Annihilationism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Then choose and don't look back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know-maybe trust Jesus and be satisfied by obeying Him?  I know it's a crazy idea.  I'd hate for you to have to sacrifice your tantric orgasms when all Jesus did was save your soul from hell. 
Seriously, at this point sex is your god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't support Trump and I'm a Christian. I have to be very careful to think through the reasons why I am disagreeing with him and not just react negatively to anything he does.  It's a challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you're wrong.  You are injecting what you want to hear into the text.  Ex 22  16-17 and Deuteronomy 22: 13-21 both indicate that premarital sex was viewed as wrong in the OT.  Penalties ranged from financial to corporal to death-depending in the exact circumstances.  If it was totally fine then  why any penalty at all?
You're avoiding answering the single, simple, unifying question: what did Jesus mean in the Sermon on the Mount when He forbade lust?  I would assume you would consider His words as binding.  He is saying that lust is sinful.  I don't see how you get to premarital sex without lust-it is, in fact, the culmination of it.  
Finally, you saying porn is okay is also dead wrong, given Christ's forbidding that we lust.
You are essential embracing a libertarian view of sin-"as long as no one is hurt it's okay", while rejecting that God established absolutes and that when we reject those we are rebelling and offending Him-even if You and God are the only ones who know.

I hope you are not teaching your twisted, destructive view.  If you are I hope God forgives you, but I pray He makes an example of you to refute what you are teaching and protect the integrity of His Word.  Jesus said it would be better for you to have a millstone around your neck and be cast into the sea than for you to lead His young impressionable lambs astray-pretty strong words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested to hear your definition of lust, then.
In regards to two married people, there is clear direction in the epistles to have regular, frequent, unhindered sex within the confines of marriage.  So Jesus isn't talking about that.

Here's some more scripture since Jesus's clear directive isn't sufficient for you.

Do you not know that the wicked will not inherit the kingdom of God? Do not be deceived: Neither the sexually immoral (GREEK PORNEA) nor idolaters nor adulterers nor male prostitutes nor homosexual offenders nor thieves nor the greedy nor drunkards nor slanderers nor swindlers will inherit the kingdom of God.   1 Corinthians 6:9-10

Now concerning the matters about which you wrote: It is good for a man not to have sexual relations with a woman. But because of the temptation to sexual immorality (GREEK PORNEA), each man should have his own wife and each woman her own husband. The husband should give to his wife her conjugal rights, and likewise the wife to her husband. For the wife does not have authority over her own body, but the husband does. Likewise the husband does not have authority over his own body, but the wife does. Do not deprive one another, except perhaps by agreement for a limited time, that you may devote yourselves to prayer; but then come together again, so that Satan may not tempt you because of your lack of self-control. Now as a concession, not a command, I say this. I wish that all were as I myself am. But each has his own gift from God, one of one kind and one of another. To the unmarried and the widows I say that it is good for them to remain single as I am. But if they cannot exercise self-control, they should marry. For it is better to marry than to burn with passion.
1 Corinthians 7:1-9

The argument is very clear here.  The Greek word PORNEA does not just refer to sex in a pagan temple, but any sex outside of marriage.  Verse 9 further reinforces this reading-"if they cannot exercise self control they should marry".  

Your argument is heretical.  Stop telling young Christians it's okay to have premarital sex.  Their own consciences are offended and that ought to be a pretty good indication it's wrong even if they listen to your serpent's whispering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump will make it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ate parts of that guy too.  Canadian justice is fuc{ed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is Americas punishment for this.  God holds a grudge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to tie your shoes left-handed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bout time.  This world needs a tune up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah-totally into lisps too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping for #4! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested to hear your definition of "lust". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have heard that it was said, You shall not commit adultery. But I say to you that everyone who looks at a woman with lustful intent has already committed adultery with her in his heart. If your right eye causes you to sin, tear it out and throw it away. For it is better that you lose one of your members than that your whole body be thrown into hell. And if your right hand causes you to sin, cut it off and throw it away. For it is better that you lose one of your members than that your whole body go into hell.
Matthew 5:27-30 

1 Thes 4:3-5
1 Corinth 6:13

If you are saying that premarital sex is not immoral then you are a heretic.  Plain and simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow-your response is "go ahead, have sex outside of marriage-just get good birth control"?  Did you ever read the Sermon on the Mount?  You should not offer people advice.

Your advice has a familiar ring...

Now the serpent was more crafty than any other beast of the field that the Lord God had made. He said to the woman, Did God actually say, You shall not eat of any tree in the garden?

But the serpent said to the woman, You will not surely die. For God knows that when you eat of it your eyes will be opened, and you will be like God, knowing good and evil.
Genesis 3:1, 4-5 ESV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the couch color.  It's like old copper-it makes the room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you 100%.  I have a visceral negative reaction to this space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sterile-it has the opposite of character.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article!  I especially appreciate the discussion on what prophecy looks like in today's evangelical church.  Great shout-out to Moore.

I agree that Evangelical's reaction to Trump has been revelatory or apocalyptic to me as well.  It is a moment of crisis-an unmasking.  It's so interesting that this callow demagogue could unhinge this part of the church so easily! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irresistible grace is resistible until it isn't.  I'd say be very patient, compassionate, get ready to be hurt and be honest.  Remember-they're not dumb-they're blind.  Like you were.  You can't get mad at a blind man who doesn't believe in sunsets.  
The ones who really love you probably feel hurt and threatened.  The rest will fall away.  Cast your cares in Christ.  He is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where would the threshing floor David purchased from the Jebusite have been?  The City of David, which is called Zion.  There were 2 600ft walkways leading DOWN from Ft Antonia to the Temple compound, according to Josephus who actually was there.  There is no down if the Temple was on the " Temple Mount"-only if the Fort was and the Temple was in the City
 of David, over the Ophel.
I honestly don't care if I convince you at all- if I'm right it will come out in time.  If you're right you'll never get to rebuild your Temple.  It only interests me how such a historically pivotal place has been misplaced by about 1000 meters! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This also explains the Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter is for guys with huge hands, Reddit is for guys with little tiny hands who get captured. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got banned from r/Republican too.  Kinds hard to believe I was a card-carrying member this time last year... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally banned-took me about 10 minutes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these facts or alternative facts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one can read in Detroit anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SolidJoys-a daily devotional by John Piper.

Also, for teaching your kids the Word there's an app called FighterVerses.  We just started using it, so I can't give a whole lot of feedback on it yet, but my friends use it with their kids and my Pastor highly recommends it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may sound mean, but is not intended that way:  get off Reddit.  Get off Facebook, Instagram-any social media.  Declare a fast from it for 1 week.  Actually socialize with you church, your friends-go ice skating, register for a class doing something you've never done.  Cook something.  Go to the library and pick up a book and just sit down, read it until you don't feel like reading it any more, then put it back.
Social media life kind of feels like real life, but it isn't.  The longer you only are nourished by it, the closer a crisis of personality and depression comes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you "unearth" a cave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem.  I've actually found that the Sunday school answers are like seeds that yield fruit later in life.  I know what you are saying, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want me to actually respond to that or do you feel better having vented your spleen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imperfect mirrors still reflect-just imperfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  I'll have to try iBirdPro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we're recommending movies, I trust you've seen SPOLIGHT?  If not, please do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What apps have helped you with your Walk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to hear what apps you guys think are edifying and helpful.  The entire spectrum is welcome to comment.  Please contribute but don't criticize!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also-unlike The RCC, the police were told at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be a friend.  Don't marry her or get romantically involved.  You will be unequally yoked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the 11th plague in my opinion.  The first 10 were chosen by God too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw man, they outsmarted God! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is imperfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else just sick of his face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I am rapidly losing interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post!  Thanks for taking the time to correct some of that.  I hope you enjoy the link-it's kind of thick reading, but very interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-logic would suggest that the allegations are brought to the clergy in sort form or fashion.  If they are brought to the police first, then they aren't what we are talking about here.  
When the allegation is brought, I would assume some sort of internal investigation (more or less thorough, depending on a lot of factors) is undertaken within the parrish.  The matter is settled in a quiet way.  These occurances all have some sort of paper trail-letters, transcripts of interviews, legal council, records of settlement and monetary payout.  All of this stuff leaves a trail of some sort.  The Boston Parrish under C. Law had much more explicit and thorough documentation of hundreds of sexual predators STILL in the clergy, for example.
When an allegation is made within a Parrish-the legal authorities should be notified IMMEDIATELY and all internal records regarding the incident made available to them.  This is the very LEAST that would be done in any other setting-say like in a daycare or public school if the same thing were to occur.
Since you seem to be the main RC on this sub standing in the smoke and saying " no fire, nothing to see here", why don't you inform us of what the actual protocol is in these instances.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the organizations official ( to say nothing of knee-jerk) reaction is self-protective and self-serving:the opposite of Christian in other words.  Do you agree?
The priests that commit these atrocities don't lose their salvation, they don't lose their membership in the True Church, but they are deservedly hated and shunned.  The only way to minister to the predator priests is to force them to face the law first-then be cared for by the brothers.  The RC Church has that order exactly reversed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "what can we do about it?" attitude.  The RC Church has information on ALL the allegations made against any priest-that is the nature of such a rigid hierarchy.  They aren't all in the Pope's basement ( jokes about child-buggering are HILARIOUS, especially when it still rampant in your Church), but the organization has the information AND power to snuff this out.  Zero tolerance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would happen to a priest who robbed a bank, or committed a murder?  Would he be defrocked?  Would he be sent on a special " sabbatical" and moved to a Parrish where no one knew he was a murderer or bank robber?  Just hypotheticals......THAT ACTUALLY HAPPENED if you change the word "murder" with "child rape". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We appreciate you foul language.  Your attitude reinforces my comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is definitely a criminal law enforcement issue and NOT a church discipline issue as the Catholic Church seems to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Anything you think worth passionately pursuing in life, someone will think is dumb and then helpfully inform you of their opinion.
Atheism isn't a problem of processing power or IQ, it's a problem of pride and perception and self-awareness.
Read Psalms 1 and be confident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repent, then when you fall repent again!  The goal of the Christian life is dependence...on Christ.  
God still Ioves you, you are still the apple of His eye and His beloved child.
Our problem isn't that we want too much and should be satisfied with little.  Our problem is we want too timidly and are too easily satisfied with cheap imitations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still shocked by how blas the Roman Catholic laity is about this.  On these boards if you mention it you are likely as not to get some version of "oh, not that old trope again!".  
It is a MASSIVE issue.   Predator priests are destroying, consuming the most defenseless lambs in the flock.  Bishops are covering up-no definitive change looks to be forthcoming.  Where are the shepherds willing to lay down their lives for the sheep?  Shepherds had staffs for a reason-to kill the wolves.  Instead of a mark of moral courage the collar may as well be a millstone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay-I think it's pretty clear now.  Good discussion Atheists!  I appreciate everyone's input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My two year old opened the shower door, looked at me, said "quack", and walked out.  Weird kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess 120 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We love it!  I've got 3 kids under 6 and one on the way.  The childcare at Hoover YMCA is TOP NOTCH.  They know my kids names, they sing songs, they are staffed by people who really care.  Ms. Lissen ( pronounced leeson, I have no idea if I spelled it right) has known my boys since they could walk.  
 
We go to Shades Valley for their outdoor pool, but otherwise stick to Hoover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snark is the spice of life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps I should have said " Theologian" instead of Anglican?  I thought he was a member of the Anglican Church.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok-fair enough.  I just thought it'd be interesting to share these writings-make them accessible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I defer to your superior knowledge.  Should I alter the header, and if so, how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For all our Atheist friends-and anyone really...Sir Isaac Newton's Biblical Writings! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isaac Newton was a towering intellect and a passionate Anglican Christian-he wrote over 1.3 million words on the Bible.
Enjoy!

http://www.newtonproject.ox.ac.uk/texts/newtons-works/religious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you don't have faith in the reasoning of the scientist who you went to school to study?  You accept no axioms, adopt no pre-existing formulas, rely on no conversion tables, count all the electrons in the Li atom yourself to make sure they got it right?
Ridiculous. That's so false on its face that it doesn't even need to be said.
The problem here is not processing power (it never is).  It's pride and a lack of self-awareness.

Faith: complete trust or confidence in someone or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Enjoy yourself-do it to the glory of God!  Be vocal about it too.  God gave you a gift, He is sending people to you who wouldn't hear about Him any other way, and He wants you to be happy.
It's good that you ask these questions-it shows that your heart is tender and receptive to His word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's safe to say you haven't worked out the proof that momentum is the product of mass and velocity-you take it on the authority of scientists before you...you have faith in their reasoning, don't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 Corinthians 8-In regards to freedom and conscience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you remove my comment, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain then, that if momentum is the product of mass and velocity, but a photon has no mass, how it has momentum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't understand physics-you just have faith in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly wrong.  I am trusting the HOLY  SPIRIT to preserve the Word.  You trust those people.  You are acting like they wrote it out of whole cloth 400AD, but everything was there-they just collated and filtered with the guidance of...guess who..the Holy Spirit.
Feel free not to message me-you are very condescending and arrogant.  You should google Fruits of the Spirit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please remove-that guy is obviously dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thing is too big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great!  Then you should be encouraging the OP to trust Him rather than abandoning the faith if (when) the pope dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clarify.  Why would you presume such a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah-that was weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He reminded me that my attitude at work was sucking today (had to work a Sunday), and that everything I did I should try to do to glorify Him.  
Would you like an introduction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  I know Him personally.  I just needed an introduction:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust in a man-trust in Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like a crymax.  Get that kid outta there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine.  Have a nice day.

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2065254/Coins-Jerusalems-Western-Wall-hints-sacred-site-older-Herod.html

The eye cannot see what the mind cannot imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obey your mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WW5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird that such a question generating a response from a Christian on a sub called r/Christianity would generate that sort of condescending psychoanalysis.  
My answer is:
1.  What I think is true
2.  Also supported by a good bit of archaeology and contemporary writings
3.  Definitely NOT anti-Semitic:  if Herrod's temple stood in the City of David, then Israel could rebuild whenever it liked
4.  Not mean-spirited in the least.  I assume the OP wanted some warm, tingly answer expressing awe at the foundation stone's antiquity and the extreme level of devotion and sincerity expressed there by the Orthodox daily.  
Sincerity doesn't guarantee accuracy-otherwise we would all have to admit that Mohammed landed on the "Temple Mount" on a flying horse.   
I believed Jesus when He said "not one stone".    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you asked, didn't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really.  I actually think it is the lower layer of the Roman Fort and not the foundation of the Second Temple.  The Second Temple was built in the City of David on Mt Zion near ( or possibly over) the Gihon Spring.  This is located about 1000m south of the Temple Mount in the City of David.  Springs do not move.
Jesus said not a single stone would be left atop another of the Second Temple and Josephus places the Second Temple lower vertically than Fort Antonia-so the fort was on what has since been renamed the Temple Mount and the Wailing Wall is one of the foundation stones of that fort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a Christian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-he said he'd do it at the convention.  No one should be surprised.  On its face I think it's the correct thing-but I trust Trump not one bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No-it's pretty vile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, why won't people just shut up about this child-raping stuff?  It's SO awkward to talk about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The heart is deceitful above all things, and desperately sick; who can understand it?
Jeremiah 17:9 ESV

You need to ask for a new heart-your old one is sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kidding.  Marian devotion bring a stereotypically Catholic problem and the sign of the cross being a stereotypically Catholic gesture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
