<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5756</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booping noses is kind of like saying hello in the bunny world.  My bonded buns used to do it whenever they would pass each other, but now that they've been together over a year not so much anymore.  She should calm down once she gets spayed, the humping could also be an act of dominance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDM isn't real music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 17:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be like him when I grow up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 02:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's scary.  What type of advice did he give you so I know what to avoid and watch out for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 02:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes!  I have no idea what the protocol is because I've never tried to contact a therapist.  All of my medical is through Kaiser, and my general doctor likes to just prescribe me medicine instead of really trying to figure out what's going on - so I doubt she would refer me.  =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Cake Day!

Thank you for the very specific feedback and strategies.  I will try my best to incorporate them into my life as well (rabbits may become my thing now).  I'm starting to think that I cry when I feel frustrated, especially when I'm trying to get a point across and I can't or I feel completely helpless in any given situation.  In terms of conversations, I have no way of knowing if people feel like I don't care when they tell me problems - because most of the time they talk to me once and that's it.  The only person in my life who is brutally honest about my social shortcomings is my husband - learning about them at 29 is a bit late in the game.

Thanks for helping me feel a little more hopeful about what a therapist could do for me, even one with very little ASD experience.  =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome!  I'm thinking being diagnosed will be a relief too if I decide to see someone about it.

The exact same thing is happening in my life.  All I want is to help, and I'm slowly figuring out how to do that without sounding arrogant and like a know-it-all.  I'm not sure if I'd rather have influence over situations or people, because in my workplace the actions and decisions of the people highly inform the systems.  I guess the main thing I want to do is turn our campus into a well-oiled machine - I often feel like we waste time on unimportant busy work when we should be problem solving and moving forward.  Efficiency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 02:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will definitely do that. At first I was concerned that people would judge me for joining and not being diagnosed, but it feels like there are a lot of understanding people here who will help whether you're an Aspie or just wondering if you are one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 07:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I'm not worried about labeling, in fact my fear is to go and not be labeled as ASD. I've spent all of my life feeling like an outcast who can't get it (social interaction) right no matter how hard I try. It would be nice to feel like I belong somewhere.

My concern in the workplace is better understanding my faults and how to improve myself so that I can make a difference and have a greater impact possibly in a leadership or support role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can getting diagnosed and seeing a psychologist or therapist help a fairly high functioning adult with Asperger Syndrome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, I just have to say that "Aspergers" being squiggly red underlined is really killing me.  I even changed it to "Asperger Syndrome" but it was still squiggled.  UGH.  I think this is a group of like-minded souls, so hopefully some of you will understand and appreciate my sentiment.

As a 29 year old female who always just considered myself socially awkward, I have begun to realize that I may have Aspergers due to other personality traits of mine. As a teacher, I try to be the most positive and professional version of myself at all times (while at work), yet I am always unintentionally angering students, parents, and coworkers or am under the impression that they just don't like me .  The only grade level I feel comfortable working with is Kindergarten - I get them and they get me (it's very difficult to offend a Kindergartner because they just say what they mean just like me)!  I have a real passion for education reform and have great ideas for improving our school and creating a more effective and efficient workplace - which I try to share with everyone a lot more than I probably should.

However, sharing the first thing that pops into my mind and accidentally offending people is not the best way to effect change or become a leader.  I have learned how to control my verbal outbursts in most social settings, but it is damn near impossible when I am so passionate about the subject!  

TL;DR: I am considering getting an official diagnosis and doing therapy in order to improve my professionalism in the workplace, but is it worth it?  Have any of you been through therapy as an adult diagnosed with Aspergers and had it improve your social standing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fit Check] First bras that (kinda) fit! What do you think of the fit...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 19:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to wear a 34B, but my husband convinced me to come here and determine my true bra size. He helped me record measurements and everything, so I've measured myself to a 30F/FF by U.K. sizes. I live in the U.S. so there weren't really any places to shop nearby and I had to purchase online. To make matters worse, I also realize that I measured myself in the middle of my cycle which is supposed to be when breasts swell up.

Some of you lovely ladies recommended bra styles for narrow, even, and projected breasts.  After trying these on, I'm not sure if I'm as even as I thought I was (or maybe the size is just too large).

These are pictures of me in the Panache Jasmine:
[30FF Front](http://i.imgur.com/AdOkyOx)
and [30FF Side](http://i.imgur.com/cBPdqod)

and the Cleo Lily, which fits better but still seems a little loose at the top even after the scoop and swoop. The underwire is also somewhat digging into my sternum, leaving marks:
[30F Front](http://i.imgur.com/Rw0NJH6)
and [30F Side](http://i.imgur.com/vJkp5LX)

So what are my next steps?  Are there any other sizes/brands/styles you would recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 15:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others said, having a routine and sticking to it faithfully is crucial. Your first few weeks should be focused on getting those routines and procedures in order with fewer academics. Also, get to know your kids and let them get to know you. You should also provide time for "brain breaks," which are short spurts of time the kids can just relax so they can focus better on learning throughout the day. Check GoNoodle.com for some cool ones you can do with the kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 22:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what I was hoping to see done with the picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 20:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the Downtown Fullerton area! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
