<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried water marbling on my mom. I'm semi-pleased with the results, although I think it would be easier to do it on myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 03:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried to do a gradient design last night. It turned out pretty good, though the colors are too similar that you can barely see it. I also added a little extra flair. I love them!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 16:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've tried gradient/ombre nails a few times, but I can't for the life of me get it right. Any tips?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 18:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 18:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it!! I'm going to try it myself. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 19:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 here. I've been battling depression more than half of my life. The past few years have been the worst, but I'm doing much better. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 00:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 00:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I just picked out the colors I wanted. There are still several colors I didn't buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 06:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, each color was $1.99 at Walgreens, except for the base coat which was $3.99 and the white was $0.99. Not too shabby, if you ask me. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 05:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, apparently I was... Oh well, a better opportunity is to be had elsewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a verbal offer and went through all the pre-screening requirements for them to tell me that they require an Associate's Degree. WTF?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in June, I was contacted by a staffing agency about a position with a large healthcare company. Long story short, it didn't work out but I wasn't too upset because it was a 100 mile commute. 

Right after, another position opened very close to home and they asked if I would be interested. I said I was, and they proceeded to set up a phone interview which went great. At the end of the call, the supervisor said I had passed the phone screen and they would call me for a face-to-face interview. I didn't hear anything for a week or two until the staffing agency called to tell me that although their client is very interested in me, they are on a hiring freeze which they expected to be over the beginning of August. Okay, that's fine...

Finally, the week before last I get a call saying that unfortunately they are still on the freeze, however the client would like to extend a verbal offer because they expect the freeze to be over the following week. Great news! I'm excited because I really want this job and it's kinda cool because I didn't even have to go in for an interview.

Fast forward to this week. The original agent I was working with transitioned to a new role and another took over. Over the course of this week, I filled out all of the paperwork, took the drug test, background check, online training courses, etc. This morning I received a call from the agency telling me that the client decided that the position requires an Associate's Degree!!!

Why on earth did they make me go through all that crap knowing from the beginning that I didn't have an AA? I know they have every right to change their mind; it just REALLY pisses me off!!!

Question: I'm thinking about contacting the original agent about the whole situation and seeing if she can find out what happened. I have also thought about calling the person I interviewed with over the phone to see if he can do/tell me anything. I have a hard time believing they just changed their education requirement at the last minute. Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a bad day so I decided to do a little retail therapy. :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 03:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 19:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too!! I thought I was the only one who felt like this. Calling people by their names just feels weird to me. I will do it to get their attention in a situation where there is no way they would know I was talking to them otherwise, but other than that I pretty much can't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever my mom eats, she stabs at her food which makes a loud tapping/clinking sound on the plate. Ugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 12:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great!! I have a long list of books I'd like to read, but my concentration is terrible. Kudos to you for this huge accomplishment.

P.S. I'm so jealous! Just sayin'. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's my congressman, too! I emailed him regarding SOPA and this was his response:

"While I believe that those who violate copyright laws should be held accountable for their actions, I am concerned that this legislation also violates the free speech and due process rights of content producers and Internet consumers.  As it is currently written, SOPA enables law enforcement to target all sites that contain some infringing content (no matter how small), and those who "facilitate" infringing content.  This is comparable to taking down all of Facebook because someone posts a copyright-protected video to his or her profile.  Furthermore, a copyright holder could issue an order to have a website seized without seeking court approval. 

Until actions are taken by SOPA's authors to ensure that this bill does not infringe upon basic civil liberties, I cannot support it."

Love this guy!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
