<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4276</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know of any interesting information where they believe that  animals may be trying to communicate with us  somehow regarding the change in environment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article explaining how society and life may be shaped   in the near future by new technologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 14:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou for the input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 19:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article highlighting the issue regarding an ageing population amongst European countries and the affects this will have on the economy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello I'm just wondering why precisely has this been removed ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 14:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insightful article detailing a privileged participant in a trade which  has resulted in  the horrendous bloodshed and estimated more than 100,000 deaths in Mexico over the past decades drug wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 11:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame you couldn't clink on the link in the article.Never mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 23:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating article showing 100s of scientists concerns for the environment,  and the issues which need to be addressed by their own government.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its interesting you have no replies.Thanks for the input.Do you know why this is the case..what changed ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article regarding how technology and isolation could go hand in hand, leading to a possible more lonely life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad article regarding how disabled people are treated in society, the article touches on what individuals have to go through, and a disabled  foreigners point of view on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ecy.1558/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LL cool J would thunk it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the title of the article.So i can make my own ones up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fascinating piece where the author talked about his terminal illness and how he planned to live the rest of his life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree that it is a subject no one can ignore and should be  thrust into the limelight. However as with any topic you will get opposing views. Whichever views which oppose climate change should not be crushed. In my opinion by all means have a debate and show proof and evidence which may back up a belief. Win people over through evidence and facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this article in particular interesting as it shows people with two opposing views about climate change. This topic is relevant to us all if we like it or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article on how a woman has come to terms with her past and the stigma attached to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why has it been removed? The article you linked has less than 100 up votes.As stated in the subs own rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A interesting article regarding how one person who had a terminal illness chose how to die amongst her family and friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link Study http://www.spsp.org/press-release/healthiest-eaters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cityam.com/246931/permanent-jobs-fall-fastest-rate-since-financial-crisis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 12:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bosses of Britains largest public companies earned an average of 5.5m last year, and have enjoyed a 10% pay rise while wages in the rest of the economy lag far behind.

Rapid inflation for the countrys best paid executives is being driven by a small, all-male group at the top of the corporate tree, according to the High Pay Centre, which published its annual survey on earnings at FTSE 100 companies on Monday.

There is apparently no end yet in sight for the rise and rise of chief executive pay packages, said the centres director, Stefan Stern. In spite of the occasional flurry from more active shareholders, boards continue to award ever larger amounts of pay to their most senior executives.

Leading company bosses now typically earn 129 times more  including pensions and bonuses  than their employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a protest. Its to make people aware ( in their eyes )  and talk about it. Which it is doing, hence this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is full of anti Islam comments who make up shit to fit their agenda. How long have you been around for ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a  good point. Most articles which have an  anti Muslim story have thousands more upvotes. If the idiots who think all Muslims are the same offend you just downvote them. If they are really offensive and are racist  and trolling just report them. Consider it open season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The face, nose and hair looked so much like Trumps that I had to share it with you, explains well-known Martian researcher Scott C Waring on his UFO Sightings Daily blog.
This bizarre sighting now has some alien hunters questioning Trumps real place of birth, as some believe he could be linked to or is a creature not of this world.
Is this a symbol of an alien in the Mars culture that had power and prestige one that cause the people of this planet to feel empowered, enough to make his face permanently in the scenery?


Is this a sign that Trump is an alien, or decided from the aliens on Mars?
Waring explains that the Republicans face is visible with great detail, however some looking at the image may see a jagged rock cloaked in a black shadow.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is referring to   global emissions countries have created over the years. If you look at who ( what countries ) has contributed to the emissions over the years he has a very good point.


Greenhouse Gas Emissions by Country. In 2011, the top carbon dioxide (CO2) emitters were China, the United States, the European Union, India, the Russian Federation, Japan, and Canada. These data include CO2 emissions from fossil fuel combustion, as well as cement manufacturing and gas flaring.

http://www.wri.org/blog/2014/11/6-graphs-explain-world%E2%80%99s-top-10-emitters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article 

These horrors of climate change are the fault of big nations, such as China and India, and rich ones such as the United States.

President Rodrigo Duterte is now issuing an ultimatum to nations that have been destroying the climate.

You can pay poor countries (like the Philippines) to forego cheap, dirty fossil fuels. Or, he says, our politicians will chuck your United Nations-brokered climate change treaty in the trash.

China, America, Europe, they continued to emit their poisonous fumes in the name of prosperity, Duterte said, according to the Philippine Star. There really is climate change. But who caused it? Not us.




Greenhouse Gas Emissions by Country. In 2011, the top carbon dioxide (CO2) emitters were China, the United States, the European Union, India, the Russian Federation, Japan, and Canada. These data include CO2 emissions from fossil fuel combustion, as well as cement manufacturing and gas flaring.

http://www.wri.org/blog/2014/11/6-graphs-explain-world%E2%80%99s-top-10-emitters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>    Hmmm in 1916 how many people were displaced and died from war in Syria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope your wrong

At its core, the civil war in Syria is not a religious conflict. The dividing line is ones loyalty to the Assads government. However, some religious communities tend to be more supportive of the regime than the others, fuelling mutual suspicion and religious intolerance in many parts of the country.

http://middleeast.about.com/od/syria/a/Religion-And-Conflict-In-Syria.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You totally skipped the question i asked. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world is such an abstract context. Now in Syria  ( the content of the article ) would you say that its safer than 100 years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article regarding trauma and personality traits and how we cope with events individually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no evidence or proof  including sources which show this was a set up then ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all the thousands of  wild accusations of a inside  conspiracy  about the coup ( by the government)  been passed around on this sub so quickly was a little strange. Did anyone prove with sources that indeed it was set up by Erdogan and  it was a fake coup attempt?

Its strange that so may commented  so quickly that it was staged without no proof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 13:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have the link please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 12:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your thinking way to much into this, regarding the purpose of the article, and a propaganda piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2015 State of the Climate report examined 50 different aspects of climate , including dramatic melting of Arctic sea ice and glaciers worldwide. A dozen different nations set hottest year records, including Russia and China. South Africa had the hottest temperature ever recorded in the month of October: 48.4 C (119.1 F). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear of your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot 1400 altogether but the 12 regarding the article are not mentioned .Not sure why. Here is an interesting read.

ICIJs review of Mossack Fonsecas internal records shows that the Panama-based law firm is a major provider of secrecy to companies involved in extractive industries. The firms internal files include more than 1,400 companies whose names refer to mining, minerals, oil, petrol or gas. Other less explicitly named companies  including the 12 companies allegedly used by Bedjaoui in the Algerian energy deal  also played roles in the extractive sector, the files show.

https://panamapapers.icij.org/20160725-natural-resource-africa-offshore.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not to sure why you are getting downvoted? You have gave as much information than any other comment.Thanks for the comment and all the best with your grandfather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are repeatedly having to say, in very strong terms, that what he has said is unacceptable, why are you still endorsing him? Obama asked during a White House news conference. What does this say about your party that this is your standard-bearer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Trump the almighty speaks again.What i find interesting is how come so many want a guy to be their president. Even though at times he comes out with as much fantasy as a Harry Potter novel. Why WHY why are republican officials and his fans  ignoring this lunacy? The republicans have tried to convince people in this country that they are the sober, family oriented, business friendly and love thy neighbour christians. Yet the establishment republicans continue to back this disaster of a human being and, apparently, think they can somehow contain his lips and direct his actions as president? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their research, published Sunday, focuses on a case in Algeria, where Farid Bedjaoui, nephew of a former Algerian foreign minister, arranged US$275 million in bribes through offshore companies to award US$10 billion oil contracts.

Twelve of the 17 companies he used were created by Mossack Fonseca in a crossroads of illicit financial flows, according to Italian investigators. Algeria lost an estimated US$1.5 billion annually to tax dodging, bribery, corruption and criminality between 2004 and 2013, according to Global Financial Integrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks i will take a look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very interesting. I have looked at a few articles but wanted to know other view points. I understand perfectionism isnt necessarily a bad thing.I am interested in the aspect of setting high standards  which are realistic , which dont result in negative aspects after certain goals/ expectations are  achieved.I particularly find it interesting how employers set high bench marks and standards for their workers, and the affects this has when results are not achieved. Kind of like striving for perfection, always improving, no matter what the consequences on its workforce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any sources  or information which you would recommend which shows any links which shows a link between perfectionism and anxiety ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study link 

http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736%2816%2930175-1/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Wednesday, at a news conference in Florida, Trump said he has never met Russian President Vladimir Putin. "I never met Putin, I don't know who Putin is," he said.

 Last November, he claimed that he "got to know [Putin] very well because we were both on '60 Minutes.'" That made no sense; while the two men were featured the same evening on the CBS newsmagazine show, they were interviewed in different cities and would have had no interaction. But there's more: In 2014, speaking at the National Press Club, Trump said, "I was in Moscow recently and I spoke, indirectly and directly, with President Putin, who could not have been nicer, and we had a tremendous success."

So was he lying last week, when he was trying to deflect criticism of his admiring words for the Russian strongman? Or was he lying two years ago, when he was trying to convince everyone what a big shot he was?

 Also within the week, Trump lied in complaining about the presidential debate schedule and its conflicts with professional football. He told ABC News' George Stephanopoulos, "I got a letter from the NFL saying, 'This is ridiculous. Why are the debates against -- ' because the NFL doesn't want to go against the debates."

 The National Football League responded: "We did not send a letter."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting insight into patients  who had serious illnesses regarding their fears and their views on death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have sources which show these personal tax deals with multinationals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brigaded perhaps. How would they do this ?  and more to the point can the mods or Reddit do anything about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are most posts regarding Trump automatically downvoted to around 60-65 points . Can someone explain this ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can people support this guy Trump? Donald Trump represents the worst of America - the bigotry, hatred, and festering bitterness and resentment that exists in some circles. He is very appealing to white supremacists. As an individual, he has shown himself to be a braggart, a liar, and worse. He has never served his nation in the military or as a community leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really couldn't say anything constructive when faced with Khan's pointed observations, and targeted a grief-struck mother instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 14:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tut tut tut.Oh dear makes a change. Strange how most posts regarding anything about  Trump get downvoted to around 60 per cent.I would put a wager that r/politics has been brigaded in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, cool. Sorry if any mix up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice but quote where you got the info from 

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4vjg5b/jeb_trump_so_incredibly_disrespectful_of_khan/d5yxqg6?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think everyone should care that a guy 

who believes that climate change is a hoax

http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2016/jun/03/hillary-clinton/yes-donald-trump-did-call-climate-change-chinese-h/

is a threat to every nation on earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump quotes

Ive got black accountants at Trump Castle and Trump Plaza. Black guys counting my money! I hate it. The only kind of people I want counting my money are short guys that wear yarmulkes every day . I think the guy is lazy. And its probably not his fault because laziness is a trait in blacks. It really is, I believe that. Its not anything they can control.

They should be forced to suffer and, when they kill, they should be executed for their crimes. I want to hate these murderers and I always will.

The government contended that Trump Management had refused to rent or negotiate rentals because of race and color, The Times reported. It also charged that the company had required different rental terms and conditions because of race and that it had misrepresented to blacks that apartments were not available.


http://www.snopes.com/donald-trump-racist-meme/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can anyone vote for this guy Trump ? Donald  lacks empathy and basic humanity. He's also a narcissist with sociopathic tendences. A presidential candidate who dodged the draft for Vietnam, but who now mocks veterans, and publicly squabbles with the mourning family of a fallen soldier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 10:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.facebook.com/deanfluence/videos/vb.751201178224406/1122807587730428/?type=2 theater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 13:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original study article

http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160223/ncomms10698/full/ncomms10698.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey im rushed for time.Im not American and are not an expert in law in the states.this article may be of some use to you 

https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/jul/27/worlds-largest-carbon-producers-face-landmark-human-rights-case?

If you have not seen in already.And also this 

http://www.ourchildrenstrust.org/us/federal-lawsuit/

Look into it.. if i get more info and time i will write back.Take care  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have more information please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 13:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the comment.Do you have have any info regarding the dry up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 23:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump supporters are racists cheering on the juggernaut of authoritarian fascism while thinking it'll make them more "free". A Trump presidency is a little like investing in a Trump casino. Looks good on paper, then he builds it, the sucker costs more than he said, and he runs it into the ground. Everyone loses, except one person: Trump. That's because he got his fees out before the bankruptcy proceedings.Make America Broke Again.

How to solve the USA presidency problem. Go out in the streets and pick randomly , lets say 200 US citizens, interview them and guaranteed you will find much better candidates than the two CLOWNS you got now!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback. I have a feeling your going to live forever ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Africa has been bad to the weather god !!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Trumps mind, he thinks that the winner of a debate and run up to the election is the one who delivers the most and crudest insults. Maybe that worked with his "poorly-educated" Republican base, but the general election is a very different game.Its a shame when pro Trump brigades on this sub try and alter reality and stifle every article which isnt pro Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, im just wondering how would the mind ( if free from natural degeneration of ageing ) cope with a body which unable to carry out its wants and desires? Would this not cause extreme frustration and stress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to ask about fascism and the difference then you havent been following what Trump. . He has proven he's a racist by calling Mexicans murderers and rapist and using derogatory comments to refer to other races. He doesnt believe in the first ammendment of our constitution; he's already banned reporters, that don't agree with him, from his press conferences. His knowledge of geography is that of a 2yr old, he actually said that Belgium is a beautiful city </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie is determined to prevent a fascist takeover of the country come November. Some of his supporters on the other hand are prepared to aid and abet such takeover! Anything but Trump!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gibberish. Yes your perception is challenged hence the emotion of your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i read it , having children strapped up to chairs with hoods over their heads is taking things to far. How can this kid see even for starters ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone yet have any solid evidence it was a hoax backed up with sources? Because i haven't seen any, all iv seen is people annoyed that the majority of Turks still wants Erdogan in power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is that question supposed to deflect the fact that Qatar, a slave using, cult run mysoginist anti western shithole trys to influence world new

You tried to deflect the news story yourself and was given facts from several other news sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a shame when the retards saying this cannot distinguish between a 2 nd generation  Indian ( born in England )  and a refugee from Syria.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound upset. Do you not like your perception challenged ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Population at large 

http://www.thefreedictionary.com/at+large

As a whole; in general ( population ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would an article like this get downvoted ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is making promises he can't keep to poor and desperate people

Americans cannot pay their mortgages because the rich are taking all the wealth out of the US - its nothing to do with immigration, just as that is a lie in the UK too.

There is now $30 TRILLION in off shore tax havens. Most of it is US, UK and EU money. There was not $30 Trillion in tax havens 35 years ago.

You can blame immigrants and globalisation as much as you like, but the reality is that untaxed profits of corporations and the rich taking monies off shore is 3 larger an issue than the banker bankruptcies / Credit Crunch in 2008 (world wide QE since is now $10 Trillion.

There is no way on earth that immigrants and globalisation in the US is taking these sorts of monies out of the economy.

The sad fact is that Trump is blaming immigration and globalisation for the cause of the slump in the US economy - as Brexiteers do in the UK - but it's cack, lies, fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 10:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right so you touched on the refugee crises and the west trying to solve the worlds problems leading to the mess. So do you think enough has been done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 22:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think they need to admit his heritage was a factor. There is evidence it did factor in. Something about he was teased for being an immigrant and he responded with "I'll kill you"

Do you have a source for this about the claims about killing?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isnt the first time gun laws have been in the news though. Whoever he got it from and i havent seen any link to organised crime.People getting guns and passing it on ( or even keeping them )  in whatever way should not have access to them in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the root causes are what  exactly then ? Obviously this guy was given a gun by an irresponsible gun owner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The root cause? Like in America ? People having access to guns when they shouldnt have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 18:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no clue about American history.What country are you from? Please dont say America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 15:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do Muslims feel about groups like ISIS?

Recent surveys show that most people in several countries with significant Muslim populations have an unfavorable view of ISIS, including virtually all respondents in Lebanon and 94% in Jordan. Relatively small shares say they see ISIS favorably. In some countries, considerable portions of the population do not offer an opinion about ISIS, including a majority (62%) of Pakistanis.

Favorable views of ISIS are somewhat higher in Nigeria (14%) than most other nations. Among Nigerian Muslims, 20% say they see ISIS favorably (compared with 7% of Nigerian Christians). The Nigerian militant group Boko Haram, which has been conducting a terrorist campaign in the country for years, has sworn allegiance to ISIS.

More generally, Muslims mostly say that suicide bombings and other forms of violence against civilians in the name of Islam are rarely or never justified, including 92% in Indonesia and 91% in Iraq. In the United States, a 2011 survey found that 86% of Muslims say that such tactics are rarely or never justified. An additional 7% say suicide bombings are sometimes justified and 1% say they are often justified in these circumstances.

In a few countries, a quarter or more of Muslims say that these acts of violence are at least sometimes justified, including 40% in the Palestinian territories, 39% in Afghanistan, 29% in Egypt and 26% in Bangladesh.

In many cases, people in countries with large Muslim populations are as concerned as Western nations about the threat of Islamic extremism, and have become increasingly concerned in recent years. About two-thirds of people in Nigeria (68%) and Lebanon (67%) said earlier this year they are very concerned about Islamic extremism in their country, both up significantly since 2013.

http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2016/07/22/muslims-and-islam-key-findings-in-the-u-s-and-around-the-world/? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes a truck would drive by its own accord and has the ability to kill many people.Certain makes of trucks do indeed has a predisposition to kill and this is implanted on the production line through hypnosis . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They blamed the Nice attack on a truck in their headlines,

Lol. What nonsense ! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes bating you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? he didnt even say about groups been dis-positioned to mental illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 13:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed desperate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 13:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course.Indeed history has shown that the most evil killers have a nack of pre meditation and an ability to manipulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 12:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange, people down voting .Do they not want to hear that this guy had a mental illness? Why do they see this as a negative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is correct that preliminary FBI data show a significant increase in big-city homicides in 2015. But he is extremely incorrect in asserting that decades of progress in reducing the incidence of violent crime have been reversed by the Obama Administration's (unspecified and unsubstantiated) "rollback of criminal enforcement." In fact, violent crime has fallen dramatically since the current president took office.

http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2016/07/manafort-fbi-crime-statistics-cant-be-trusted.html# </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [W]hen CNNs Jake Tapper confronted Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort with the inconvenient facts about how historically safe most Americans are, Manafort chose to attack the messenger. Which is to say, to attack the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
 
Empirically, according to FBI statistics, crime rates have been going down for decades, Tapper said. How can Republicans make the argument that, somehow, its more dangerous today, when the facts dont back that up?
 
People dont feel safe in their neighborhoods. I dont know what statistics youre talking about, Manafort replied. The FBI is suspect these days, after what they just did with Hillary Clinton.

http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2016/07/manafort-fbi-crime-statistics-cant-be-trusted.html# </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Williamson, chief economist at Markit, said: July saw a dramatic deterioration in the economy, with business activity slumping at the fastest rate since the height of the global financial crisis in early-2009.
The downturn, whether manifesting itself in order book cancellations, a lack of new orders or the postponement or halting of projects, was most commonly attributed in one way or another to Brexit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S and NATO were together in the Afghan war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanger and Haberman also pressed Trump for his reaction to last week's failed coup in Turkey. A mutinous faction of the country's military launched a deadly Friday night putsch that was ultimately repelled by forces loyal to Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan. In the days since, authorities have embarked on an astonishing purge of the state's institutions, leading to the arrest, detention or suspensions of tens of thousands of soldiers, judges, academics, civil servants and others caught in the dragnet of the government's roundup.
"I dont think so," Trump said, responding to a question from the journalists about whether the attempted coup against Erdogan could have been staged, "but I do give great credit to him for turning it around."

https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2016/07/21/donald-trump-says-u-s-shouldnt-criticize-turkeys-erdogan-over-post-coup-purge/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have been watching to much V for Vendetta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's run through the global warming deniers' points, then.

There's no such thing as the greenhouse effect.

Even if there is, we're not adding to it.

Even if we are, there's nothing we can do about it.

Even if there is, why bother... we'll never get as hot as Venus.

CO2 is good for plants

It's only a small change

We can easily adapt.

Nothing can be done because China.

We are fucked anyway. Build that wall ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the hell would anyone think he was going to endorse someone who called him Lyin' Ted and accused his father of killing JFK?

What a freak show this is turning into. Between the plagiarism incidents and now this from Cruz, this has to be one of the worst run conventions I can ever recall, lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is an American platform and he is the Republican nominee up for presidency.Now if he didnt talk about Erdogan and it was made up, fine. But he did and this article is about suppression of liberties which Trump mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I thought most countries have human rights records  and breaks human rights easily ? Trump thinks that we shouldn't lecture


US Republican Party presidential nominee Donald Trump has praised Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan for his handling of last week's failed coup.

"I give great credit to him for being able to turn that around,"

Asked if Erdogan was exploiting the coup attempt to get rid of his enemies, Trump said "I don't think we have a right to lecture".

http://www.news.com.au/world/breaking-news/trump-praises-erdogan-for-coup-crackdown/news-story/52a1786d7b1a69a108a3f9a082351c4e </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id say that Trump being so popular on Reddit and not denouncing Erdogan and the suppression of civil liberties is relevant though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame , no surprise . However Trump joins this lot  at the UN.

Trump also warned that, if elected, he would not pressure Turkey or other authoritarian allies to end crackdowns on political opponents or the suppression of civil liberties.

https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/jul/21/donald-trump-america-automatically-nato-allies-under-attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he started saying he would  not crack down on people like Erdogan and leaders who abuse human rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump doesnt support the crackdown on Human rights from Turkey 

Trump also warned that, if elected, " he would not pressure Turkey or other authoritarian allies to end crackdowns on political opponents or the suppression of civil liberties."

https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/jul/21/donald-trump-america-automatically-nato-allies-under-attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does Donald Trump support not support the crackdown in Turkey i wonder ?

Trump also warned that, if elected, " he would not pressure Turkey or other authoritarian allies to end crackdowns on political opponents or the suppression of civil liberties."

https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/jul/21/donald-trump-america-automatically-nato-allies-under-attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 14:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck trying to persuade bible-loving literallists who think the world is 6,000 years old and Noahs Ark is a true story to believe scientific papers.The only climate change deniers left are profiteers and idiots... so unless you're making a ton of money... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 11:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Donald Trump doesnt support messing with Turkeys affairs i wonder why?

Trump also warned that, if elected, " he would not pressure Turkey or other authoritarian allies to end crackdowns on political opponents or the suppression of civil liberties."

https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/jul/21/donald-trump-america-automatically-nato-allies-under-attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 11:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt trust a president who has been bankrupt four times.I wouldnt want him to make deals with peace on the line with his past his  history of deals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 10:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote Trump, lets make Erdogan great again !!...Trump also warned that, if elected, he would not pressure Turkey or other authoritarian allies to end crackdowns on political opponents or the suppression of civil liberties."

Please USA just don't your own civil  liberties have been eroded enough

A bit about Trump

Said about women, You have to treat em like shit

Said a U.S.-born judge couldn't be impartial because of his Mexican heritage

Advocated waterboarding as punishment even if it doesnt help gain information, because they deserve it anyway

Proposed to create a database system to track Muslims in the U.S.

Urged supporters to beat up protesters at his rallies

Made fun of a reporters physical disability

Suggested the U.S. should reduce its debts by partially defaulting on them

Advocated shutting down mosques

Said women should be punished for having abortions

Described global warming as a hoax perpetrated by the Chinese for competitive reasons

Fraternizes with avowed white supremacists on Twitter

Called Mexican immigrants rapists

Disparaged Sen. John McCain's military service because he was captured by the North Vietnamese

Described Fox debate moderator Megyn Kelly as having blood coming out of her wherever

Said, I could stand in the middle of Fifth Avenue and shoot somebody, and I wouldn't lose voters

Refused to rule out using nuclear weapons against ISIS

Kept a collection of Adolf Hitlers collected speeches in a cabinet by his bed

Said, If Ivanka werent my daughter, perhaps Id be dating her


http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/cover_story/2016/07/donald_trump_is_unfit_to_be_president_here_are_141_reasons_why.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The following are Christian terrorists movements


Lords Resistance Army

Active: 1980s-Present, about 30 years


 
Who are they? The Lords Resistance Army (LRA) is a Christian Fundamentalist terrorist group originally from Uganda, but now active in the Sudan, the Central African Republic, and other places. Uganda, you may remember, is a hotbed of Christian Fundamentalism, so it makes sense that a group who calls themselves Christianist would come from the country. The LRA surfaced in the popular conscious sometime ago when Joesph Kony suddenly became a meme on the internet; up to that point, their main claim to fame is child sex slaves and children soldiers. Indeed, the LRA is known to orchestrate kidnappings, railroading young boys into fighting while forcing young girls into sexual slavery. Those who refused to fight were hacked to pieces. The young girls are forced to be brides for the soldiers, and thus helping to spread HIV. Theyre especially brutal towards civilians, as well, wiping out entire villages and attacking refugee camps.

The goal of the LRA is pretty straight froward: they want a Bible-based state that uses the Ten Commandments as guide posts. Thats something any right-wing politician or Christianist can sympathize with, right?

 Ku Klux Klan

Active: 1860s-Present, 149 years

Who are they? These guys dont need any introduction; every American knows who the Invisible Empire is. The Klan name probably comes from the Ancient Greek  (kuklos), which means circle. Theres a frightening overlap between White Supremacist ideology and Christian terrorism in the Western World, and the Klan is the tip of that iceberg. Thereve actually been three Klans; the first one was formed in 1865, in Pulaski, and drew on former members of the Confederacy Army. They were a vigilante group, and they wore the sheets as a reminder of their fellow Confederates who died (think the classic sheet ghost and youre not far off). Everything about the Klan is geared towards terrorism and psychological war, from the uniform to the cross burning. And while its true the Klan got their start as an arm of the Democratic Party, it was back when the Republicans were Theodore Roosevelt and not Sarah Palin, so I dare you to tell a modern Klansman they voted for Barack Obama.

While the Klan started out hunting down and terrorizing freemen and women, that wasnt their sole target. The Klan is a far right-wing Protestant organization, and being a Protestant organization, they hate Catholics. As a result, Klan has targeted both Catholics and Jews in the (not-so-distant) past. The KKKs history is so violent, in fact, that many draw a comparison between the KKK and Al Qaeda, although I think thats an unfair comparison, as Ill explain below.

National Liberation Front of Tripura

Active: 1989 to present, about 30 years

Who are they? Youve probably heard of the Lords Resistance Army and the KKK, but this is a group that Im pretty sure you havent, unless youre from India. Its easy for us to forget, as Americans, just how big India is; its far more diverse than Europe is, culturally speaking, and its roughly the same size. Its called the worlds largest democracy for a reason, but as the United States shows, no democracy is without its secessionists. And these folks are just some of the many secessionist organizations in India.

According to their manifesto, the NLFT wants  to expand the kingdom of God and Christ in Tripura, and often does so at the point of a gun. They threatened anyone celebrating the Hindu Festival of Durga Puja with death, and are backed by a Baptist Church thats selling them arms. Theyve orchestrated at least two massacres, and used rape as a tool of intimidation. While the Nayanbasi faction has been shut down, the Biswamohan faction has promised to fight on. So here we have a Christian terrorist group spreading their faith in India by sword, metaphorically, and at the point of a gun more prosaically  small wonder we havent heard anything about them in the West, huh?

Antibalaka

Active: 1990s to present, about 25 years

Who are they? Ive cited the Central African Genocide in at least two articles now; these are the militia behind that genocide. Their name means anti-machete in the Sango and Mandja languages, and they first formed to defend Christians and Animists who were on the receiving end of politically motivated violence carried out by Muslims. As these things often do, the tables turned, and now the Antibalaka is doing what right-wingers only wish they could do: ethnically cleanse their country of all Muslims. This includes children, who theyve targeted and murdered in the past. Now, the Antibalaka now stand accused of crimes far worse than anything that Slka, the Muslim rebel group, are guilty of.

Catholic Reaction Force/Protestant Action Force

Active: 1983 till 1994; at least 2002 for other groups using the CRF name; 1970s till 1990s for PAF

Who are they? Really, anytime some claims that Christians arent violent, all you have to do is direct them to Ireland. I could do a whole entry on what happened in North Ireland, beginning in the 1970s. Americans like to pretend that Eire is Guinness, the Blarney Stone, and leprechauns, but during the 1970s, religious violence a la the Thirty Years War was painting the Emerald Isle ruby red. The Irish call this time period The Troubles, and thats an understatement if there ever was one.

The Provisional IRA is perhaps the best known terrorist agency from the period and would definitely earn their spot on this list, if I werent aiming for more obscure groups, but the Catholic Reaction Force and Protestant Action Force were also active and, in the case of the latter, also responsible for a large number of murders. For those who are unfamiliar with the Troubles, it occurred in North Ireland and, as so many European conflicts do, pitted Protestants against Catholics in unmitigated bloodshed. The CRF was behind the Darkley killings, in addition to several mailed bombings in the early 2000s. The PAF, which was far more effective in their killings, has a rap sheet a mile long. You can find it on the Wikipedia page, here.

The Orange Volunteers

Active: Early 1970s to Present, about 40 years

Who are they: Were staying in Ireland for this next group. Fans of science fiction probably remember the Orange Catholic Bible from Frank Herberts Dune, but may never have understood why that name was so subversive, or why it was similar to Herberts other Coca-Pepsi religious hybrids like Zensunni. Orange is the color of Protestantism in Ireland, and green is the color of Catholicism; when you wear green on St. Pattys Day, youre proclaiming your Catholic heritage. The Orange Volunteers, then, are a Protestant terrorist organization.

The OV are Protestant Fundamentalist, and responsible for a number of violent attacks in North Ireland. While the police have been cracking down on the group, the group is still considered to be active and is still terrorizing Catholic citizens and hitting soft targets.

 The Aryan Nations

Active: Unknown, to the Present

Who are they?  The Aryan Nations is an umbrella agency that nets a large number of White and Christian Supremacist agencies ranging from certain breeds of Neo-Nazi to the KKK itself. Its heyday was in the 1980s and the 1990s, when various White Nationalist groups would convene at the groups Idaho compound for their annual congress.

The Aryan Nations got their start in the Christian Identity movement, but has since fractured into no fewer than three factions, with one faction even looking to buddy-buddy with Al-Qaeda in 2005. The Phineas Priesthood is another branch, and theyve made headlines here on AATTP before. The last faction is the Aryan Nation Revival, which holds to their Christian Identity heritage like small-town Conservatives cling to their guns and Bibles.

 The Christian Identity Movement

Active: 1920/1930s to Present, about 95 years

Who are they? When youre dealing with White Nationalism and White Supremacy in the United States, its turtles all the way down, but you can almost certainly find God at the top of the heap. Thats what the Christian Identity Movement is; its not necessarily an organization so much as it is a loose affiliation of organizations like the Aryan Nations.

The Christian Identity Movement is a very weird movement; they actually have hostile relations with Evangelicals and other charismatic Protestants  not because theyre racist bigots, no; its because the CIM is Post-Millennial, where the vast majority of Evangelicals are Pre-Millennial. This distinction is lost on anyone who hasnt studied the Scofield-Derby Heresies, but the basic idea is that the Tribulation has already occurred and the goal is to build up the world to the second coming. Their theology is just as skewed, though; for instance, members of the CIM believe that non-Caucasians dont have souls, and therefore, cant be saved.

http://aattp.org/here-are-8-christian-terrorist-organizations-that-equal-isis/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right !! good job you were banned !! Nice to see you again !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I remember this user! About 6 months ago he was in a raging battle with me that the refugees in Europe would never commit attacks. And all the migrants coming in was a good thing and good people. ISIS could never sneak any weapons or any terrorist in!
 Oh boy. good seeing you again. Seems like you were really the one who was right. Continue on /u/wagamaga , you have not changed.

Lol ok ! Im happy you remember me, im glad i made an impact take care. By the way your account is 1 month old.I hope your doing ok with your memory.There is lots of help you can get with that  on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it when people look me in the eye and, with a straight face, try to convince me that pumping billions upon billions of metric tons of heat trapping gases into our atmosphere has no effect on our climate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wow a whole 0.9c!?? The WATERD ALREADY AT MY NECK

Hmmm have you slipped and fell over your keyboard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mohamed Lahouaiej Bouhlel is not a muslim. People who were slaughtered are muslim. It is known the victims never ate porc, drank alcohol, practised sodomy, prayed enough, were not gay etc, shiite. Is one going on their background?

Hes dead , and going back to the question the article says where the information came from .Do some research and you will see.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to read the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey not Muslim here but your right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol ok go hug Allah.. be together as one :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm ok cool , but i thought we were talking 2016 , but whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dont get scared by people fuelling propaganda and fear :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have hope in humanity, try not to be scared by terror and people peddling fear.You will be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 13:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes your right most Muslims are happy and peaceful,  out of billions worldwide , a few like  group of people  spoil it.Glad you said it. its great that your pointing out this and  helping get rid of stereotypes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 13:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what ? This shows how many Muslims are in France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 13:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 13:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know these victims believe in the same philosophy which killed them ? Do you have facts which prove these victims wanted to die by a terrorist attack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4.7 million Muslims in France (7.5%).

http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2016/07/19/5-facts-about-the-muslim-population-in-europe/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But that is seldomly the point of these kinds of articles.
 People write this to be able to say that they can do whatever the hell they want.
 How old are you, 6?

Your getting angry now, maybe you should take some deep breaths or go walk a dog or something? Articles can be written however they like.Something obviously you dont agree with.Oh well nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah the West is allied with some messed up countries, like Saudi Arabia. Does that mean the West should then refrain from commenting when other perfectly good countries start to regress and slide into autocracy? Nope, it doesn't.

Likewise should people refrain from commenting on hypocritical countries? No they should not. Just because you dont like the article and its content, this wont make it go away.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Yes the coup that was set up.. despite no evidence, facts or sources to prove it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama spoke with Erdogan by phone Tuesday and pledged any needed assistance to the Turkish government in the wake of last weeks attempted coup, White House spokesman Josh Earnest told reporters in Washington. Even so, Obama made clear the U.S. expects that any inquiry should be conducted consistent with the democratic values of the Turkish constitution, he said while declining to answer whether the U.S. is concerned that the response wont respect those democratic values.
Those are the values that the Turkish people were defending in repelling the coup, Earnest said. One good piece of evidence of that is you promptly saw all parties of the Turkish parliament condemning the attempted coup -- even parties who have vigorous political disagreements with the Turkish government.
Keep up with the race of a lifetime.
Get our politics newsletter daily.


The coup attempt led by a faction of Turkeys military the night of July 15 has tested relations between the U.S. and Turkey, which is a NATO ally and important partner in the fight against Islamic State extremists in Syria and Iraq. Erdogan has demanded that the U.S. extradite or deport a reclusive Turkish cleric, Fethullah Gulen, who lives in Pennsylvania and whom he blames for inciting the rebellion. Erdogan and Gulen are onetime allies who are now political opponents.

Extradition Steps

During their call, Obama and Erdogan discussed Gulens status, Earnest said. Separately, he said, the Turkish government on Tuesday submitted information related to the cleric that the U.S. government is reviewing. He said it was too early to say whether the documents represent a formal extradition request.
Earnest said any decision on Gulen would be made according to steps established by U.S. law and not by Obama. If a formal request is received, the U.S. would consider it on its merits and make a decision based on whether it thinks it relates to crimes covered by the extradition treaty between the U.S. and Turkey and on whether theres evidence that crimes were committed.

http://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2016-07-19/obama-presses-turkey-s-erdogan-to-respect-rights-after-rebellion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read the actual article that may help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you any evidence /sources for this ? so many people trust you , your the top comment so you must be reliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boris Johnson was embarrassingly forced onto the back foot during his first London press conference as foreign secretary on Tuesday as he was repeatedly pressed to explain his past outright lies and insults about world leaders, including describing the president of the United States as part Kenyan and hypocritical.

Standing alongside John Kerry, the US secretary of state, Johnson claimed his remarks had been misconstrued, that his past journalism had been taken out of context, and world leaders he had met since his appointment fully understood his past remarks.

Johnson was holding a press conference designed to showcase the continuing closeness of the UK-US special relationship in the wake of Brexit, as well as the joint commitment to finding a solution to the crisis in Syria.

Johnson twice referred to the crisis in Egypt, but was believed to be referring to Turkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey sorry to hear about your friend but i was looking for real facts/sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch that wasnt very nice.Good luck with finding the sources.Have confidence you can do it. Smile be happy now :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No problem. Its a pleasure :) keep on smiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dont worry its fine.This is on the front page of the sub.Have a great day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal insults. Im wondering why you think  this.You must not have lots of confidence in yourself to take things personally maybe.Im not sure.Happy hunting on the sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good im glad your convinced about false flags, deeper into the rabbit hole you go.Have a great day.Enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Plenty from the following countries

Britain The foreign secretary, Boris Johnson, said he had spoken to his Turkish counterpart, Mevlut Cavusoglu, to underline support for Turkeys democratic elected government and institutions in the wake of the overnight coup attempt.

The Foreign Office is advising Britons in Turkey to stay indoors, avoid public places  especially demonstrations  and remain vigilant.

It says: The situation now appears quieter in Istanbul, and the bridges across the Bosphorus are reopening. But there are reports of tank fire and small arms fire in Ankara.

British Airways says it is canceling all flights to and from Turkey on Saturday, but easyJet says it plans to runs its scheduled flights, largely to Turkish resort towns. The budget airline says the schedule will be kept under continuous review.
Natos chief says all alliance personnel and military units in Turkey are safe and secure following the attempted coup.
Nato secretary general, Jens Stoltenberg, said in a Twitter post that he had spoken to Natos supreme commander, US Army Gen Curtis M Scapparrotti, who confirms that all Nato personnel and units in Turkey are safe and secure.

The alliance chief also tweeted that he welcomed the strong support shown by the people and all political parties to democracy and to the democratically elected government of Turkey.
Spains acting foreign minister, Jose Manuel Garcia Margallo, condemned the attempted coup, telling Spanish national television that his government completely supports the Turkish government headed by President Erdogan.

He said: Without a doubt we support respecting the constitution and democratically elected institutions, and we condemn all coups without reservation.
Garcia Margallo spoke by telephone from Mongolia, where he is attending the ASEM Asia-Europe Meeting.
Syrian opposition The exiled Syrian opposition congratulated the Turkish people for halting the attempted military coup.
The Turkey-based Syrian National Coalition said Turkey has protected its democratic institutions in the face of dark and desperate attempts that sought to take control of the popular will.
It says the Turkish people value democracy and will not let a group of putschists take it away in a desperate attempt to restore military rule.

Turkey has been one of the main backers of the uprising against the Syrian president, Bashar al-Assad, and is hosting 2.7 million Syrian refugees.
In the early hours of the attempted coup, celebratory gunfire broke out across Damascus. The government and its supporters view the rebels as terrorists and consider Turkey to be one of their chief sponsors.

Hamas The Islamic militant group Hamas has congratulated Erdogan for quashing a vicious plot to overthrow him.
The Turkish leader has been a staunch supporter of Hamas and a fierce critic of Israel. Hamas says it remembers Turkeys wise leadership in supporting the Palestinian people and their cause and working to lift the blockade on Gaza, the coastal territory ruled by the group.

Hamas supporters took to the streets in several places across the Gaza Strip to celebrate the failure of the coup, raising Turkish flags and posters bearing Erdogans image.
Turkey recently restored ties with Israel after a six-year lull following a deadly Israeli naval raid to stop an activist flotilla aiming to breach the Gaza blockade.

Qatar The Gulf nation of Qatar, which has close ties to Erdogans government, was quick to condemn the military coup attempt.
It called the attempted coup a violation of the constitutional legitimacy in Turkey and said it supports all legal measures the government takes to maintain security and stability.

The official Qatar News Agency said the ruling emir, Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani, has spoken with Erdogan by phone to express Qatars support.

Qatar and Turkey have grown increasingly close in recent years, and share similar stances on their support for Syrian rebel groups and the Muslim Brotherhood. The two countries agreed last year to establish a Turkish military base in Qatar.
Iran said the attempted military coup in Turkey was doomed to fail.

The foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, was quoted by the official IRNA news agency as praising the brave defence by the people of Turkey of their democracy and elected government.
He said the events in neighbouring Turkey prove that coup dtat has no place and is doomed to fail in our region.

Pakistan An aide to prime minister Nawaz Sharif condemned the attempted coup in a statement and said Pakistan hopes that peace and normalcy will be restored in Turkey.
Tariq Fatimi also said he had contacted Turkeys foreign minister to express solidarity with Turkeys government and democratic institutions.

Pakistans main political parties have also praised the people of Turkey for foiling the coup.
Sharif was himself overthrown in a 1999 coup led by Gen. Pervez Musharraf, who ruled Pakistan until 2008.
Afghanistan President Ashraf Ghani expressed support for Turkeys elected government, saying in a statement that democratic elections are the most effective means for peaceful transfer of power.

Militaristic options will only undermine democratic institutions, stability and development in the country, the statement from Ghanis office said.
Azerbaijan The president of Turkeys neighbor Azerbaijan condemned the attempted coup.

President Ilham Aliev was concerned about developments in Turkey and welcomed measures taken to prevent the attempt at a coup and to stabilise the situation, spokesman Ali Hasanov said.

Azerbaijan is a Turkic nation and its late president Geidar Aliev once described their relations as one nation, two states  a phrase later echoed by TErdogan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm lots of speculation but no evidence .You should stick to the conspiracy's.Generals and judges been arrested as well hundreds of others who were supposedly in on a massive conspiracy to some people, but not one says before or even after whats going on. HINT there wasnt a cover  up of a coup. Hence why judges havent said anything ! As mentioned multiple intelligence agencies from around the world didnt pick up on anything neither.You should try r/conspiracy, your idea would sound better there.Not common sense im afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right so all of the generals and Judges who were in on the coup which are now facing the death penalty haven't even come forward to say it was staged. As well as multiple countries with intelligence around Turkey.Interesting, common sense works wonder , you should try it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The former UK Independence Party leader was hosting a live phone-in show on LBC radio on Sunday when a caller named Richard phoned in, appearing to agree with Mr Farage's views on integration, especially that foreigners in Britain were not learning English.

Richard coaxed Mr Farage by saying: "I don't see how you can integrate if you don't speak the language of the country, you know?"

Mr Farage wholeheartedly agreed with Richard, saying learning the language was "absolutely fundamental".

Richard then interjected with the crux of his question.

"I was wondering why you've spent more than 20 years living in Belgium and yet you don't speak a word of Flemish, German or French?"

"How do you know that?" Mr Farage asked.

Richard continued to question him on his linguistic capabilities.

"I'll have you know Richard I am very good with a French wine list ... I know my way around a menu," Mr Farage said.

After failing to confirm that he could speak any of Belgium's official languages of Dutch, French and German, he conceded defeat.

"I'm not a brilliant linguist, I'll admit to it," Mr Farage said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your amusing, but you are trolling lots with the personal insults.If you cannot take what you read without getting stressed and calling people names you shouldnt be on here.You may be a sensitive person who knows. Anyway have a great day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound very upset and you are not making sense, i hope your not to upset.Have a great day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said then go shit on a sub ? all im pointing out that articles are biased by downvotes and upvotes. Do you not think this is the case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats half of Turkeys population? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he is the main beneficiary, that doesnt mean he planned and did this .Thanks for the source but a German mp isnt exactly  a world leader .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello you.You sound like a very sensitive human, i will try to be nice. The views expressed in this sub especially by me, you  may not want to hear. If you think having a debate and disagreeing with viewpoints is attacking people,  maybe you need not visit this sub or even reddit. I hope you dont take this personally like you have before. Try not to see anyone who doesnt agree with you as having an agenda. I know conspiracy theories of late are popular  on r/worldnews but try not to think to much. Erdogan suppresses free speech.Dont be that guy.Have a great day /u/The_Voice_of_Dog  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right so where are the individuals in Turkeys military facing the death penalty ( generals ) etc  who have admitted that its staged ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool show me all the condemnation from world leaders where they said it was planned. The ones which have swathes of intelligence which shows this.If your friends have as much intelligence surely you could show it to us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool  hundreds of those generals and judges are in on the conspiracy as well , although facing death they want to keep it secret, and  not confess that it was staged. Sounds right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right,  have any facts/sources  from the past few days on this to back up your claim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprised in the slightest. When neo-liberal ideologues stop pretending to know more than the vast majority of climate scientists and start offering solutions in line with their politics, the better,for everyone (including themselves and their unfortunate offspring). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and all those soldiers arrested and top officials in the army who are facing death are keeping quiet to save and uphold a conspiracy.Do you know how ridiculous this sounds ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right so hundreds of soldiers and officials who have been arrested and may die  are still playing along with the conspiracy to save Erdogan. Makes perfect sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm but show me  a  major news site where an article an article is allowed to get buried from bias of its readers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah of course every article you read is built of evidence and facts

To quote you from an early comment you made.

 "The world absolutely has events and information "up voted and down voted" just not in the reddit sense. National beliefs, journalist bias, propaganda, censorship of self or by stste, etc."

Slight contradiction there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok right so all the intelligence agencies in the West knew about this coup but wanted to keep the conspiracy secret . Right got you, sounds like fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  what you said also has nothing to do with what i said. simply put, the coup failed and right away erdogan consolidated his power, like, the very second the coup failed, he consolidated his power. such rapidity should set off alarm bells for anyone with half a brain, because it suggests he planned it.

Right so anyone who thinks differently is ignorant and has half a brain .Slight bias detected.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Every heard of 911 conspiracy theories, dipshit?

Yeah 9/11 happened in Europe.Very intelligent comment .Troll somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Articles , yeah but no evidence or facts . Conspiracy theories are just that . Conspiracy's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok right so a coup failed .World leaders condemn the coup with swathes of intelligence more than redditors. r/worldnews complains and calls it a conspiracy because a coup failed .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, so why would a coup not fail ? it has failed so this sub gets upset . Yeah he has made the most of it . Even though Turks themselves didnt want it . So people outside Turkey complain what Turkish people want . Where is the logic in that ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool i will trust r/worldnews for facts and unbiased news sources . Why would loads of world leaders condemn this ? are these world leaders from swathes of nations across the globe in on it ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope only if you search for it, and you get it lots on r/worldnews. Where are all these world leaders declaring that it was a false flag. Hey and please dont say they were all in on it !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get away from this sub and read and browse the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/worldnews doesnt represent reality. Reality doesnt get upvoted in favour of bias, or downvoted in favour of bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right so hundreds of news sources  from across say completely different from r/worldnews where you upvote articles and comments and downvote ones you dislike . Please think before commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv visited this sub many times and whenever there is a terrorist attack   say in Europe no one mentions conspiracys. But when it comes to Turkey . Surprise !! conspiracies galore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political crimes.You mean shooting up of  innocent civilians ? do some research . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone points to him having planned it ! Rubbish . Only on r/worldnews ( which isnt reality, where you downvote articles and comments ) Yes and DO NOT  listen to the media . Listen to r/worldnews they know the facts :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of right so civilians defending their political belief from an armed coup they didnt want was a bad thing. Strange .And the death penalty , well countries in the Western world still have the death penalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 265 innocent people were killed from this coup from the coup plotters the vast  majority which were civilians . I wonder if there was 265 people killed in any other Western nation from terrorists there would be conspiracy theories galore. Hundreds of soliders and generals who are facing death are in on this conspiracy too .You know to risk their lives to keep it secret. Makes perfect sense !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 08:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey its all good.When people dont read articles but troll instead thats up to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says in the article, if you read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reread the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes what President wouldnt fight an armed coup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought the election. Hmmm that is no different to lobbying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realise that the president got elected by a majority. Love him or hate him the people voted for him and want him in power.Turkish democracy is different to that of the west maybe. Looking back at history shows that spreading democracy is a big mistake Iraq/Syria/Libya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannot find it at the moment

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv included the paper ( as asked ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The poll, taken jointly by Latino television channel Univision, the Dallas Morning News and Arizona State University's student-staffed Cronkite News, found that 86 percent of those living on the Mexican side are against the project, compared with 72 percent living in U.S. border cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research paper 

http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2783800 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abnormal is the new normal, David Carlson, the director of the World Climate Research Program at NASA's Goddard Institute for Space Studies, said in a statement on Wednesday. 
NOAA and NASA are particularly concerned about the warming of Earths polar regions. The climate of these areas, scientists argue, affects climates thousands of miles away.
Sea ice in the Arctic Sea and the Greenland ice sheet have melted unusually early this year.
The state of the climate so far this year gives us much cause for alarm, Carlson warned. 
 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id rather trust several news sources from multiple perspectives than people on r/worldnews thats for sure.As here you get biased opinions where the truth can be upvoted or downvoted according to ones belief and how much they want to get Karma. Would you not ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to this sub only.Not in the outside world who accept a coup didnt happen and isnt spoilt by circlejerks and karma whoring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about the stories that havent made the front page ?

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/search?q=turkey sort=relevance restrict_sr=on t=day count=51 before=t3_4teqyp

r/worldnews upvotes articles according to bias. Always has always will. Like comments with the upvote /downvote button, the truth can quickly get buried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated article 

There are conflicting reports about whether a former Turkish air force commander has confessed to planning Friday's attempted military coup.
At least 232 people died and 1,400 were wounded in the ensuing violence, and there have been mass arrests.
The state-run Anadolu news agency quoted Gen Akin Ozturk as telling interrogators he had "acted with intention to stage a coup".
But two private broadcasters said the general had denied playing a role.

NTV quoted him as saying: "I am not someone who has planned or directed the coup attempt... I don't know who did."
Anadolu said he was one of 112 generals and admirals who had been detained. Fifty had been remanded in custody pending trial, it added.

http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-36829574 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know this ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
