<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2574</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Warlords to Puzzle Quest: The journey of a video game pioneer -- TIL the guy responsible for the game Warlords also made the game Puzzle Quest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Sterling is now Reviews Editor at The Escapist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 16:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News homepage was hacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 20:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was one documented case of a publication interfering with its reviews (Gamespot, Gerstmann, etc, etc), but that was it.  IIRC, there have been lots of unsubstantiated rumors (many times from people simply don't like the score of a particular review), but no other actual cases backed by evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of the picture: why the world's best photo startup is going out of business. Everpix was great. This is how it died. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 19:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 19:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dale North's message.  Not clear from the wording if it was a firing or a mutual consent resignation

http://www.twitlonger.com/show/n_1rqsrc6

 Dear Destructoid readers and friends,

 Destructoid and Jim Sterling part ways today. Jim has been an important part of Destructoid since our earliest days, so I'm sad to see him go. Really sad. Totally bummed. 

 Change is the only constant in our strange little internet world, as you know. It turned out that where Destructoid and Jim were moving toward didn't line up anymore. So Jim and I have come to a mutual agreement this week: for us to continue on our paths, we'll have to do so separately. 

 I like to imagine that we are friends that have fought in the same trenches in wars these past five or so years. But now Jim is moving to a fight on a new front in the war. Though we're no longer in the same company, we can both continue pushing forward, knowing that the other is out there fighting the good fight. 

 And just like any good soldier, I will always have Jim's back. 

 And you never know where the war will take us -- I'm sure we'll be fighting alongside each other someday. 

 Jim, thanks so much for everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Sterling leaves Destructoid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airline passengers will be able to use electronics such as readers and games from throughout flights, the Federal Aviation Administration announced Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 15:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 19:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated:

 "The team at Victory Games will be disbanded," an Electronic Arts spokesperson confirmed to Polygon. "Wherever possible, we are working to help these talented people find other opportunities within EA." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EA cancels free-to-play Command   Conquer, reportedly closes development studio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 19:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virgin Gaming opens subscription-based paid eSports leagues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 01:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what actual news and press orgs do at all.  If the rights of the image are in doubt, or if they weren't able to obtain permission or find a copyright notice giving them permission (CC-attribution commercial license, etc), they don't use the image.   It's that simple.

I'm not saying we should hold Lewis or Cadred to the same standards as legitimate press outlets, but we *should* be aware of what the industry standard is with regard to photo and image licensing and usage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 00:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It is actually, that's why if you place your pictures somewhere publicly you always include a copyright notice.

 If you post a picture or some artistic work you made some-where without any notification of the author or copyright notice, it's effectively public domain.

This hasn't been true since 1989, when the U.S joined the Berne Convention, and no longer required copyright notices for photos to be considered under copyright. http://photosecrets.com/copyright-notice

The UK, which is where Richard Lewis lives and where the publication originates is also a member and adherent of the convention.

All photos *anyone* takes, unless explicitly put into the public domain or similar, is considered to be copyrighted for at least 25 years from the date the photo was taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaving the office, a wild Joe Biden appears! Apparently he was shopping at the Brooks Brothers store downstairs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 02:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTA V cutscenes involving Trevor are now 100x more hilarious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 06:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "did valve fire their hardware people before or after that controller showed up? because either would explain a lot of things" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How LucasArts Fell Apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 16:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> brb, buying the IP for one of the best RTS titles I've ever played with my credit card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 00:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SEC accuses Left Behind dev of 'revenue inflation', Left Behind CEO says SEC 'conspired' against studio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 23:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grand Theft Auto V Worldwide Sales Surpass $1 Billion In First Three Days -- new world record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 18:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The B1G Roadtrip: A journey through football's heartland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 18:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what it's like showing an unfinished game at PAX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 05:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're from Washington DC, USA!  We were in the Cusco/Sacred Valley/Machu Picchu region for three days.  

We're actually going to be heading out to Lima tomorrow to spend several days there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone was a little out of breath after the climb, but it was worth it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 03:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TMNT: Out of the Shadows Review -- "Out of the Shadows is a barely playable letdown." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 02:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MOBA developers need to stop chasing leaders of the genre -- "Chasing League of Legends doesn't work. We're not in this industry to re-skin games." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 21:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret passages, vampire hunting kits and Sputnik: A tour of Richard Garriott's New York home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 18:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: this game is getting mostly terrible to middling reviews across the board, not just from Polygon.

http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/killer-is-dead

http://www.metacritic.com/game/playstation-3/killer-is-dead/critic-reviews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 17:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is getting terrible to middling reviews across the board, not just from Polygon.

http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/killer-is-dead

http://www.metacritic.com/game/playstation-3/killer-is-dead/critic-reviews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 03:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is your theatre appreciation's son? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And this is why people use Adblock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And this is why people use adblock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 18:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 16:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clicks haven't been the primary metric that ads use for a long time now.  Most of the ads you see -- video prerools, Google ad words, ads on NY Times, etc etc are all based around impressions.

So yes, blocking views of the ad directly impacts the metrics they use to sell more ads to advertisers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 03:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go to IKEA instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AOL boss Tim Armstrong says on this morning's conference call that 40% of Patch will be laid off today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 17:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 16:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note that Polygon has updated their original report with more clarifying quotes from Hepler.  (The original report did not say one way or the other why she left Bioware):

 When asked if the harassment led to her depature, Hepler told Polygon "No, leaving Bioware was for family reasons. I am going to be working on a text book on narrative design among other game-related freelance projects." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 16:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polygon's article has been updated:

 When asked if the harassment led to her depature, Hepler told Polygon "No, leaving Bioware was for family reasons. I am going to be working on a text book on narrative design among other game-related freelance projects." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In direct contradiction to Metro's article on Hepler quitting Bioware due to threats, the original Polygon report that Metro sourced: "No, leaving Bioware was for family reasons. I am going to be working on a text book on narrative design among other game-related freelance projects." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 16:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard gives employees who have been with the company for 5 years a sword. Each year, the sword design changes. Here is a gallery of the various sword designs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 08:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked E-mails Suggest Bethesda Misled Gamers About Prey 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you feel the same if your real identity was leaked on Reddit or other sites?  Or if someone posted pictures of your kids and/or loved ones online?

Such things have happened in the past to Reddit moderators, to devs, to many other people.

The vast majority of online threats are nothing more than an angry person on the other end venting. But then every so often, you get someone who posts or collects information that could very well impact your offline life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gone Home Review: "Gone Home is a master class in how to tell a personal, affecting story in a video game." (10/10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 10:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> strange, i'm the opposite: graces really grated on me, and i had to push myself to finish.  the cities weren't interesting, the characters for the most part were boring and/or fairly standard for the genre.  

i did like the new fighting gameplay though.

i'm about 6 hours into Xillia, and so far it's been miles ahead of Graces for me.  You don't have the *really* sluggish childhood arc in Graces to go through, the characters are immediately fascinating, and Maxwell dealing with being a normal human is a more interesting conceit to me than Sophie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korean casters at The International 3 Grand Finals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 19:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A history of (muted) violence: The present and future of Adults Only games -- 'A look at how the game industry struggles with "AO" content.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 19:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 17:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MLG's office*

AFAIK, they actually save  money  holding it in NYC beacuse they don't have to rent a venue, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Dead Redemption voice actor Rob Wiethoff, best known for his role as the voice of John Marston, is joining the cast of a new iOS interactive radio drama called Codename Cygnus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not according to the latest round of  updates from press </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW INFO: Carmack is still with id

http://www.polygon.com/2013/8/7/4597780/john-carmack-becomes-oculus-cto

 Carmack will also remain at id, a spokesman confirmed to Polygon.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't trust that Eurogamer article one bit.  AFAIK, every outlet has sourced from the same press release, with some reading more into the "working from Dallas office" more than others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been able to find anything concrete about whether if he's leaving.  This could be something like his Armadillo work, where it's in conjunction with his id work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Carmack Joins Oculus as CTO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Carmack Joins Oculus as CTO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 16:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 02:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Top tier journalism" and TechCrunch have never been in the same sentence. I mean many in the tech industry (their primary audience) see them as something akin to a startup tabloid rag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 02:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The site linked is TechCrunch, hardly regarded anywhere as a shining beacon of journalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 23:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Let's say Dragon's Crown was marketed as a porn game for men. Do you think there's something inherently wrong with porn?

I think if Dragon's Crown was explicitly marketed as a porn game for men, it would have put to rest a lot of complaints.  But then, it would also have been a porn game for men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 23:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that same Pilot vanishing point! (assuming I ID'd it correctly)  Have had it for nearly six years now, still going strong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard's new vision for Titan: 'unlikely' a subscription-based MMO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cryptozoic to rescue Kickstarted board game failure, fulfill orders: "The Doom that Came to Atlantic City, the board game that pulled in almost $123,000 on Kickstarter and was canceled last week, will see the light of day thanks to Cryptozoic Entertainment, the company announced today." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 23:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man's best friend (fixed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 20:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Tencent? -- Chinese company that made investments into Activision Blizzard, has a majority stake in Riot (League of Legends), and a minority stake (nearly 40%) in Epic Games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 11:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Collapse of the Animal Crossing Economy and the Rise of Villager Trading: "It's the seedy underbelly of Animal Crossing -- swapping, discarding, and dealing in villagers to get an ideal town composition." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 22:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Collapse of the Animal Crossing Economy and the Rise of Villager Trading: "It's the seedy underbelly of Animal Crossing -- swapping, discarding, and dealing in villagers to get an ideal town composition." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 22:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Precursor Games confronts controversy, relaunches Shadow of the Eternals Kickstarter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 17:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chroma Squad, a super-sentai power rangers tactical turn based game where you run a super-sentai production studio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 00:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ouya Review -- "The Ouya's potential is matched by its rough edges." (5.0/10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 01:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese MMO Age of Wushu adds castration as a game mechanic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 22:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The benefits of developing for PS3, not PS4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 22:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traveling the World, Playing Fighting Games: How 27-year-old Nicolas Gonzalez left his home country of Chile, traversed foreign lands and found himself through fighting games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 18:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traveling the World, Playing Fighting Games: How 27-year-old Nicolas Gonzalez left his home country of Chile, traversed foreign lands and found himself through fighting games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 18:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 19:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that was a naming mistake (gets confusing when people reference old and new coaches both as "Coach Park").  I let them know and they're fixing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 19:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *cough* fixed 

http://assets.sbnation.com/assets/2925931/ceofront.jpg

:p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The time a StarCraft supergroup took on Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 19:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evo 2013 in Photos. First time there, it was amazing, will definitely be going back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 16:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was at Evo for the first time this past weekend, and some photos I took finally went up. It was a total blast, definitely going back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 16:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evo 2013 in Photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 16:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 00:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly certain there will be more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 06:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were females there, but yeah, probably a small minority.  I don't think it reflects that negatively though.  I personally didn't see any females treated any differently than other spectactors.

Well, unless the female in question was dressed in a revealing cosplay costume, in which case she received a lot of requests for photos by various spectators.  So who knows how that went, it's always awkward listening in on those conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 01:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was -- but there were many people who preferred watching the players play, versus watching an (admittedly much more visible) larger projected screen on the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 23:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One more photo of the absolutely insane Smash crowd (this wasn't even finals on the main stage):

http://i.imgur.com/Pg8T9Ez.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was Smash at EVO. Why would you want to stop this, Nintendo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 22:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows 0:32 is the best moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 17:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xHa1N4flrnQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The story of Crytek: From X-Isle through Redemption -- How a talented programmer practically bluffed his way into the games industry, and why Crytek has not yet fulfilled its potential. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, let's see.

Tomato soup with or without milk?

The intellectual integrity of this debate is counting on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 08:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping in mind that Dreamhack Summer 1st place for SC2 is around $10k (IIRC), this is actually fairly huge for an inaugural tournament from a relative unknown.  (Though obviously, the overall pool from DH is larger) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 10:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told you so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 06:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol k. I'm too tired to stage shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLG aftermath: things left behind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 05:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 04:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt kisses his trophy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 03:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 03:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol it was funny at the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 03:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a picture on the floor stage with my phone of the back of my DSLR since Polk was still holding and kissing the trophy :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt wins! Thumbs up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 03:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt: "Aw yeah, gonna win" Hyun: "Polt, you're going to what?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 01:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt's satisfaction face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 00:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Totalbiscuit's face after Naniwa's jab at Polt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 22:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not bad, Naniwa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 21:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 09:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EG curse incoming  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 08:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, three others came: Dez Bryant, Ty Lawson, DeJuan Blair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 07:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's another:

http://i.imgur.com/lysE1g2.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt is ecstatic in his booth! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 07:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBA's Dwight Howard was at MLG to play Call of Duty, and stopped by the StarCraft 2 booths. He could barely fit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 07:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hyun celebrates after his match against Hero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 07:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 22:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MLG photos are here: http://www.majorleaguegaming.com/competitions/57/photos

Photos from prior MLGs and some other events are here: http://www.flickr.com/photos/nodnod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 22:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I took that one too. It was at Blizzcon in 2011.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 22:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SeleCT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 21:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLG Anaheim Day 2 Black Op stage when filled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 20:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 19:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see all the other photos from Day 1 here:

http://www.majorleaguegaming.com/competitions/57/photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 19:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 18:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hilarious, hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 11:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shoot for MLG, so all my photos are on their site  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeMusliM sure knows how to work his sponsors after a match! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 07:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 05:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's already been done with another pic I took :)

http://i.imgur.com/utJsV.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The SC2 crowd is still quite large </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 04:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 04:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here are photos of all the games:

http://www.majorleaguegaming.com/competitions/57/photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 04:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that kid :| :| :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DJWheat collects himself, part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 04:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> StarCraft: Team Pillow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 04:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prior to taking the stage, DJ Wheat collects himself in the back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 03:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLG Anaheim Black Ops 2 stage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 01:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a better shot of the SC2 stage -- there's actually a bunch of seats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 01:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome back to MLG, Tyler! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 23:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLG StarCraft II stage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 23:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Apple Obstacle for Serious Games: "Making a serious game for iOS devices is not as easy as you'd think" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 20:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google's SVP of People Operations (HR): "On the hiring side, we found that brainteasers are a complete waste of time." "GPAs are worthless as a criteria for hiring, and test scores are worthless" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 08:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft to backtrack on Xbox One games DRM and "always online": "Microsoft is set to announce it will remove DRM restrictions on Xbox One games and the need for you to have the new Xbox 'always online'." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 21:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding John Marston? -- "Rob Weithoff played John Marston in the hit game Red Dead Redemption. Then he walked away from the industry for good." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding John Marston? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Bomb, Polygon, and Vlambeer all have expensive electronic or A/V equipment stolen from E3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 18:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only first-party PS4 games to be DRM free. "PlayStation 4 third-party publishers can dictate their own DRM terms, Tretton says" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 19:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft confirms: Xbox One to perform online checks every 24 hours, every hour if playing on separate console </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 00:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interplay purchases Freespace IP from THQ and Volition for $7,500 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 00:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Defiance's combat carries the game despite the scope of its many faults. However, when its rough edges start to get in the way of the game's only strength, no amount of forgiveness or patience can remedy the experience." -- Defiance Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 06:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Shadowrun Returns will release in June." -- latest Kickstarter Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 23:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ouya isn't a viable gaming platform, or a good console, or even a nice TV interface." -- The Verge review of the Ouya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 18:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reviewers Roundtable: Ben Kuchera, Adam Sessler, Arthur Gies discuss BioShock Infinite (spoilers, obv) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 20:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
