<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6782</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maximo Park - Our Velocity (Imported Base + My Lyrics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 17:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well let's hope it goes somewhere, the place is already seeing more visits within a day than it ever has so far!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 03:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, wouldn't be here without the sequencer! Feel free to make any changes you want to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the Online Sequencer Subreddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This place has been here for a long time but hasn't seen any traction until now, so welcome to all. I'm currently testing flairs for links and users, you should be able to use your own flairs on everything and I've made some pre-made ones as well. If anyone has any suggestions or comments about this place please post them in this thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeder - Comfort in Sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Bloody Valentine - What You Want (Sequence) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Croll - From Nowhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neutral Milk Hotel - Naomi (Sequence) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arcade Fire - The Suburbs (Sequence) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ride - Vapour Trail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sufjan Stevens - Casimir Pulaski Day (base) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beachwood Sparks - By Your Side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ride - In a Different Place (Intro) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 17:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polyphony Digital </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 16:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, I'm glad to see you and PD starting to go a little more public and open up to the community. 

As a long term, avid player of the GT series, I have noticed that there have been reiterative new additions of features to each of the games such as B-Spec mode, course creators and photomode. Are you currently looking into more innovative content such as this to add to GT6/7? (eg. a drag racing mode)

Do you ever think car customisation will become more prevalent in future GT games? I felt that GT has been going somewhat backwards in terms of cars themselves but forward in terms of driving. I personally loved the racing modifications on GT2 and loved turning family sedans into race cars. On top of visual modifications, performance modifications also seem to have been more packaged together unlike in older GT games. I feel as if this has taken away some of the immersion of the older games where you started poor and built up your cars using cheap parts along the career mode. Is there a possibility in future GT games that this will return? Or is the playerbase generally looking for a quicker way to modify their cars? 

GT appears to be heading towards actual racing with race-prepped cars and moving away from more 'normal' road cars. Is the game heading towards an emphasis of actual racing cars and less towards road cars? 

Are there any plans on bringing back shuffle racing (such as in GT5) to GT6/7? I know for a fact that this is something the community misses. 

Do you and/or PD actively listen to communities and fanbases such as GTPlanet for inspiration or do 

you have a-set-in-stone vision for future updates and general advancement of the series? 

And one personally, what is your favourite car and track combo on GT6? 

Finally, thank you for creating GT. It really helped ignite my love of cars and is collectively my most played game series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 09:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeps most people away... more space left for us. Not complaining haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 05:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, will probably need a headlight restoration soon thanks to not having a garage. That area is great for photos, I find usually find it nice and quiet during odd times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 03:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks like some amazing work done on a now spectacular car, I now wish I could afford a detail from you guys! Are those pictures taken in Clayton? Seems very familiar to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 02:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's here: http://snapmap.wikigta.org/index.php?map=V_Z title= set=181,1057 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 01:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The car's in Australia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 08:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [2004 Subaru Liberty 2.5i Safety Pack](http://i.imgur.com/6xTvzPO.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 03:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's because you have.](http://www.reddit.com/r/subaru/comments/162o70/damn_xpost_from_rcarporn/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 03:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to try out the Optimum Spray Wax, but it's relatively difficult to come by here in Aus and I've never come across any retail stores that stock it (at least in my state). Costs well over double to get it here compared to the U.S.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 12:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 11:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks more like the standard AUDM rims that came on the Gen 4 facelift Spec.B, painted with a darker shade of silver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 08:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the facelift tails you have there, looks great on the pre-facelift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Selling] Brand new HTC 8S Unlocked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 03:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listing on Gumtree: http://www.gumtree.com.au/s-ad/carnegie/mobile-phones/brand-new-htc-8s-windows-phone-unlocked/1026345032

Mention reddit in a text and I'll either personally deliver it to you (as long as it isn't ridiculously far off), or I can negotiate more with the price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 06:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 2004 Subaru Liberty 2.5i Safety Pack   2008 Subaru Liberty 2.5i in background.

http://i.imgur.com/FytXGtz.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 10:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subaru has never offered anything with a 6-cylinder and a manual.

In the US, anyway. The Legacy (Liberty) sold well here in Australia with the H6 and manual. No idea why it wasn't sold there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 04:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 159,600km or 99,170miles. About average mileage for this model/year of car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 04:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a few here before, but not many Aus users overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 16:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Af2rvOlj9UU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detailed my car, I think it looks much better now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 05:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 08:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I guess I should give it a try some time. Only like $15 for the whole setup anyway, including app. I'm not expecting an instant readout, but a reasonable estimate should be fine, just for fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 04:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking at getting one of these myself, but I've heard they have a bit of time lag (a few seconds), when using the bluetooth to phone. Is this true? Or is the time lag really not that bad?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 04:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lovely, I like the look of the Gen 2s with the yellow lamps and Legacy badges, looks so clean. What rims are they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 11:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4.4k is ridiculous money to spend on a 2.5 N/A Gen 3 IMHO. Back when I was searching for a Gen 3, I could've picked one up in reasonable condition for about 5k (manual) with around 200ks on the clock. At that kind of cost, I would probably just find a new engine with less usage on it and drop that in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 11:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally don't find rev-matching impossible with the 2.5i, infact I do it very frequently and it makes driving a lot smoother in general, whether or not I'm driving quickly. Heel-toeing isn't any more difficult but of course, I don't do this very often compared to simple rev-matching. I haven't driven an older car quickly before but since I'm used to driving "newer" cars, I absolutely don't find it that difficult at all. That said, DBW sucks and it makes the car feel sluggish and makes you have less confidence when driving, but I've heard a good tune can solve that. 

Speaking of which, I recently drove a 2011 WRX and for once, I really felt glad getting back into my much slower car, since it felt a lot nicer to drive in my opinion. The WRX felt 'too big' to me, but I guess that's just because again, I'm used to an older car that like you have stated, feels much more "fun" to drive. No doubt the WRX isn't quick though, brilliant car for what its meant to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 23:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called [Hanlon's Razor](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hanlon's_razor).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 21:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the scale shows "only" a 30NM drop, but the power curve's gap between about 4000-4600, I would think is where the significance is. What I'm saying is, it's not really the power lost, but the "large" gap in time between the sequential turbos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 11:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard about the "valley of death" but didn't think it was that bad... wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 08:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the best thing I've seen on the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 03:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On top of this, if the instructor says to do something that is inherently unsafe, don't do it. On my test, the instructor, at the last moment on a busy 2 lane divided road, told me to turn left at the next lights while I was in the right lane and about 100m away from the lights. Didn't help that there was already a truck right next to me at the time. I simply said that I thought it was unsafe to do so, and didn't lose any marks at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 2.5i Liberty Safety Pack after some Subaruing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 07:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 06:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah had a 9-2x (basically a WRX) and Toby had an Impreza too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-01 05:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subaru as well, though mainly towards S8-ish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 03:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that an OEM colour? Either way, looks *really* nice on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
