<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he deserves [this] (http://i.imgur.com/5miiw.gif) x 1000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looks like they got him: Suspect in custody after active shooting at the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Stewart adopts emaciated pony abandoned in Pennsylvania and hit by 125 paintball shots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [relevant] (http://holyjoe.org/poetry/adams.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Montreal Airplane Passengers Were Screaming As Tarantulas Crawled On Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Study scientists note that over the last decade, large groups of Nile crocodiles have been imported from South Africa and Madagascar for display at places like Disney's Animal Kingdom **and to supply Florida's flourishing pet trade, *with the latter being the most likely introduction* pathway,** according to the study."

Florida Man releases pet Nile Crocodile into the wild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Guy Clark] (https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/obituaries/guy-clark-grammy-winning-country-singer-songwriter-dies-at-74/2016/05/17/ce609f18-1c47-11e6-8c7b-6931e66333e7_story.html), RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Denver pot company wants to buy naming rights for Mile High Stadium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a cautionary tale: Exploding vaporizer rips hole in man's tongue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Rockland's in Alexandria sells a bunch, so maybe the others do, too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Comic-Con 2016 Will Be Stan Lees Final Appearance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly Killed In 1998 Fire, Woman Reunites at College Graduation With Cop Who Saved Her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Border Collie fights off bear, saves owner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 14:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the owners of the two ABA teams that didn't merge into the NBA have made over $300 million from TV royalties, because the NBA failed to include a termination clause in their buyout contract </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 23:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remains of sailor killed at Pearl Harbor finally make their way home - mother had saved gravesite next to hers, in case his body was ever found and delivered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAN DIEGO  Zippers are the most frequent cause of penile trauma among adults in the United States, with an estimated 2000 cases each year, according to a presentation here at the American Urological Association 2016 Annual Meeting.

For children, toilet seats are the leading cause, but zippers are "a close second," Lawrence Wyner, MD, a urologist at Joan C. Edwards School of Medicine at Marshall University in Huntington, West Virginia, reports in his meeting abstract.

The phenomenon even has its own acronym  ZIRPI, for zipper-related penile injury  and was first described in JAMA in 1936 (1936;107:809).

"Many urologists have seen at least one ZIRPI during their careers," Dr Wyner writes.




Risk factors for ZIRPI include being younger than 18 years and having an uncircumcised or insufficiently circumcised penis. "The contribution of 'going commando' (i.e., sans underwear) remains controversial," he writes.

Dr Wyner's presentation  entitled A Century of Urological Mayhem From Zippers  was part of the History of Urology session.

His efforts did not go unnoticed. "New favorite medical acronym, ZIRPI. See I learned something at #AUA16," tweeted Benjamin Davies, MD, a urologist from the University of Pittsburgh in Pennsylvania (@daviesbj).

The legal world views a penis caught in a zipper as being the fault of the male. "Consumer complaints involving zippers are almost exclusively related to either choking or asphyxiation hazards, and potential litigation involving ZIRPI is generally regarded as frivolous," says Dr Wyner.

A "Separable Fastener" 

Although zippers are commonplace today, their uptake was slow.

Nearly 100 years ago, SwedishAmerican engineer Gideon Sundback obtained a patent in the United States for his improvements to the clasp locker, which was known as an unreliable boot-lacing mechanism. The invention went unnoticed until the B.F. Goodrich company placed the new device, which was called a "separable fastener," on rubber galoshes in 1923. The device was given the "catchy onomatopoetic name" of zipper at that time, says Dr Wyner.




For the next decade, zippers were reserved for footwear and tobacco pouches. Aldous Huxley, in his famed 1923 novel Brave New World, even satirized zippers.

Things dramatically changed in the mid-1930s, when British royalty began wearing zippered trousers and the fashion took hold.

Dr Wyner reports that Sundback and his zipper company, eventually known as the Hookless Fastener Company, had "some reservations about possible genital mishaps from its creation."


But the device has been time- and market-tested. As Dr Wyner points out, even Velcro, introduced in the 1950s, has not derailed the zipper.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats latest Supreme Court tactic: No recess till confirmation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massachusetts Trooper Shares Meal With Panhandling Homeless Mom of Four Instead of Citing Her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United Had Men-Only Flights Until 1970, Advertising a Slew of "Manly" Services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saltwater Brewery Creates Edible Six-Pack Rings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 17:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 17:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try the Tower Club in Tysons -- it's high up, so amazing views, but indoors with tons of windows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit mailman saves two lives when pet pit bull mix attacks family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NY lawmakers want cat declawing outlawed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington DC Canoe Club boathouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 23:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it means that 70% of the previous times the weather pattern has looked like it does now, it's rained </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man drives truck onto National Mall, claims he has 'dangerous substance' in truck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [relevant] (http://www.convert-me.com/en/convert/history_length/bibcubit.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6-Year-Old With Autism Reads to Shelter Dogs So They Won't Feel Lonely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Canoe Club boathouse: then and now(ish) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man with $65K to buy marijuana didn't commit crime, judge says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the anniversary of Brown v. Board, new evidence that U.S. schools are resegregating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 19:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that this report comes from w-JAC-tv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [according to the crawl under this news report, he's "dong well"] (http://i.imgur.com/TeoL7Vb.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Land of Oz theme park in NC opening for limited time next month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to church could help you live longer, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> W. Va. woman dies getting a "Brazilian Butt Lift" in Miami </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olympians to get 'Zika-proof' condoms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone finds and returns Paralympics athlete's missing prosthetic legs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 15:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is this, an Olympics for ants? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [verified] (http://www.biography.com/people/groups/famous-named-kitty) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [good one, Shecky] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9CdVTCDdEwI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [confirmed] (http://thumbsnap.com/i/KFI61AN4.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that at the 1936 Olympic games in Nazi Germany, the USA replaced two Jewish runners on its 4x100 relay team the day before the race and replaced them with two African American sprinters (Jesse Owens and Ralph Metcalfe, the team's two fastest sprinters). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wouldn't that be cheet-ing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ "Wild Side" was a story song with a cast of characters that all came from the Andy Warhol Factory scene. "Little Joe" refers to Joe Dallesandro, who was in several films by Warhol. "Sugar Plum Fairy" is the nickname of actor Joe Campbell, while "Holly," "Candy," and "Jackie" are based on Holly Woodlawn, Candy Darling, and Jackie Curtis, all real-life drag queens who appeared in Warhol's 1972 movie Women in Revolt.] (http://www.neatorama.com/2012/09/17/The-Story-Behind-Lou-Reeds-Walk-on-the-Wild-Side/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Shepherd takes rattlesnake bite to protect a 7-year-old girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The long history and slow death of a word once used to describe everyone and everything from Egypt to China as well as rugs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "rescued from a dog meat farm in Wonju, South Korea"

I know we're supposed to be sensitive to other cultures, but...

seriously... wtf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs destined to be dinner get 2nd chance at N.J. shelter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 15:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UCR Professor Discovers the Science Behind Superheroes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 15:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 15:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [seriously?] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n7zfnbdyAW8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keep headphone wires from getting tangled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 21:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know what they say...

if it's not baroque, don't fix it

seriously, though, thanks -- sounds like a blast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Know who doesnt like the Crying Jordan meme? Michael Jordan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 20:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 20:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 20:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tammy John surgery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
