<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9619</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A cultural and artisan event" FBI files on Burning Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 18:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carbon dating suggests early Quran is older than Muhammad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What good/great songs from popular artists do you never hear on the radio, but wish you did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 17:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trauma   Emergency Bandage, Combat, Israeli Battle Dressing - Good to watch and a good item to keep in your hunting kit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 18:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twenty percent of deputies walk off job after Oregon sheriff allegedly beats handcuffed suspect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 16:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope that if I have daughters that I die when they're young enough to still adore me, that way no man they ever meet will compare to the idea of me and they'll marry someone that's worth a damn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U/throwaway-4-R4R-use answers an r/AskReddit question that is amazingly heartfelt, context included since the yellow linked part was a little burried. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 19:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U/throwaway-4-R4R-use answers an r/AskReddit question that is amazingly heartfelt, context included since the yellow linked part was a little burried. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 19:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Disney company is responsible for our current "millennials" slacker attitude and need of constant gadgets to entertain. The Lion Kings' most famous song is Hakuna Matata. It means no worries for the rest of your days, as in "you no longer give a shit you apathetic fuck". Toy Story showed them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how much cooler the new Buzz Lighter toy was than the old boring Woody. Bo Peep thought the new toy was cool   sexy. Disney created the millennias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How companies make millions off lead-poisoned, poor blacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 23:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a universal flu vaccine on the horizon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweet Home Alabama is a pretty meta song, it's a song called Sweet Home Alabama about people being instructed to sing a song called Sweet Home Alabama that they already know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 17:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LGBTQIA is a silly abbreviation. Queers are gay, lesbians are gay, this redundancy is literally gay! (/s a little bit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 23:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millennials' Lack of Faith in Stocks Will Cost Them in Long Run: Experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 18:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor u/mikemaca spreads some knowledge about how many mammoth skeletons there are in the world and that's why we should encourage mammoth ivory use over elephant ivory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 16:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Dies After Being Run Over By WWII-Era Tank in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 16:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I bet Hillary Clinton's private email address was HDawg@aol.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 12:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] I'm trying to apply for an HQL in Maryland and the website doesn't work for the Prerequisite section </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 01:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title shows, I'm trying to apply for my handgun license in Maryland (such a pain in the ass) and the website is not working correctly.  On the prerequisite section it shows up with nothing in the area where there should be something to fill out.  Googling the issue has only shown that you need IE 11 and maybe to add it to the compatibility view list.  I did both of these and it still doesn't work.  No one is in the office until Monday to help me through the Maryland State Police, so anyone here that might have some advice would be awesome.  
  
I have tried Chrome, Safari, Safari on iPad, IE on WindowsPhone, Firefox and  none of them seem to work.  On the website they state they only take applications through the website.

Edit: thanks to u/Catriany I called up the MSPD and talked to a lady there, she had to log onto my account but she verified my other info was input correctly and finished the Prerequisite part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone done an HQL application? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 01:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get the prerequisite section to load on any computer or any internet browser I use and it is really frustrating.  Anyone with any help would be much appreciated.  
  
Edit: thanks to u/Catriany I called up the MSPD and talked to a lady there, she had to log onto my account but she verified my other info was input correctly and finished the Prerequisite part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cortana helping out after the party  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 20:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your most favorite band that you're so embarrassed about that you won't tell any of your friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 22:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ahh, the 90s - Collective Soul - Listen (Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 21:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ahh, the 90s - Collective Soul - Listen (Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, no, no. I was asking Maya Angelou! - Lenny (And one of my favorite Simpsons Scenes) Bonus Lisa gets put her in place by Amy Tan! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your worst reoccurring dream/nightmare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 16:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless I am very ill/sick I don't remember my dreams and I haven't for years (probably due to sleep apnea), share yours with me :) or :( if it's a nightmare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swimming pool 'bridge' to link London towers - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 12:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder if prostitutes working on weekend nights is similar to bartending, you're always working on everyone else's fun night, and then you have to clean up after them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 23:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone doing anything mildly entertaining tomorrow night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your peers should be people within the same age group, education level, in the US religion (cause being a different faith could hurt you), and probably body shape to avoid bias. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 12:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically this is the only way to get people that think similarly enough to the defendant to judge if you committed a crime in their society. If criminal cases were really just about the law then we'd have panels of judges that decided all cases. In the US a jury can decide that a law is a bad law and vote not guilty. But a lot of states try to make it seem like it's a crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I snooze my Wi-Fi or turn it off, it will not reconnect to my home Wi-Fi without a reboot. Lumia 1520 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 01:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Border war: Iowa finds way to issue red light camera tickets despite South Dakotas DMV firewall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 22:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 10 Upgrade? Try A MacBook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 22:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia Wants War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 20:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best drink you invented? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter if it turned out to already exist, in your mind it was completely original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best part about buying shots for girls is that as a man I too can drink a tasty shot and not be ridiculed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite drink to buy when you're buying for a small to medium group of people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 12:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HONDO "Swimming Lesson" 1953 Warner Brothers John Wayne Geraldine Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 21:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your greatest moment of making someones day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unauthorized 'amiiqo' device stores amiibo data, impersonates them on Wii U </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 19:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mapping the invisible scourge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 18:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Can Tell You That You Can't Fly; We Can't Tell You Why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 18:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unauthorized 'amiiqo' device stores amiibo data, impersonates them on Wii U </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 17:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which TV or Movie family do you think yours resembles the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 17:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone that hates their siblings, what's the beef? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends didn't appreciate my humor (xpost /all) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 15:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man trying to prevent suicide falls to his death from University of Hawaii dorm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 13:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man trying to prevent suicide falls to his death from University of Hawaii dorm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 11:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I ever save the world I want my name not to just be on some highschool, it's got to be on carriers, planes, government buildings, etc. And since I'm American in counties like North Korea too, like they need to acknowledge how important it was. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 04:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My roommates cat takes sitting in a box very seriously </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 02:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm pretty sure there are many girls out there that wouldn't mind a guy going down on them after a long hard day at the office if the guy had no reciprocation expected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 20:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleaning out my life and I found this cork board from when I was a kid. I think there's a button for everyone to enjoy on here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 19:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought you'd enjoy these Simpsons CDs I own </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 17:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thanks to /u/docious I have seen the great bard escape!] One guy vs two cops. - YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 15:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What, that's an odd name. I'd have called them chazwazzers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 00:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need a word for a girl that is attractive with giant sunglasses on, but isn't really that pretty without them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 00:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some English/American words that have no equivalent in some language? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 23:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is what happens when a homeless child begged for money in the freezing streets on new york city </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 22:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Cuba become the Las Vegas of the Caribbean once again or something else entirely? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 19:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have AC Black Flag for both the 360 and the One, does my season pass work with both or just the 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 18:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gavin Seim follows a cop, citizens (CIs) eventually come to defend the cop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 18:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else have issues loading games sometimes? Like I'll pop in AC3 and it will get to the "downloading content" or whatever it says when checking all of my previous downloads for the game and it won't progress past this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I exit the game, restart it, etc. it's the same issue.  If I go play an arcade game for a bit then come back it will work sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tianjin Port Explosion -- Extremely Close Dashcam Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 16:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Tricks to Double Your Chipotle Burrito Size (for free!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 16:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone on here use any apps for their motorcycle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On my iPhone they're was a good one that I could set the parameters and it would let me know if I could ride to work that day or not. Plus there are a few they were good for finding planned rides or making them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans override Nixon, enact new welfare standards - The Missouri Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 01:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone always draws the sun smiling, you never see it sad, maybe it gets sad when the moon blocks it's view of earth, it it gets more pumped to see it's bald friend! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 00:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you finish this sentence: "I can't get no, ___________"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 03:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin Police officer saves woman choking on biscuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 18:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the police killing of this unarmed white man hasn't led to national outcry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend just sent me this and he can't stop laughing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 16:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chopper Flying Just Above The Road [Ukraine probably] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 19:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a simple photo editing app, like that I can add a line to hide a license plate or name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 00:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweet Home Alabama is a meta song: it's a song about singing the song Sweet Home Alabama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have yet to see a comic online where some is literally beating the "living shit" out of someone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 23:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are almost guaranteed to see a Walter Cronkite news cast if you watch anything about US or world changing history between 1950 and 1980. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 20:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That man was phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your second favorite Disney "Classic" movie and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 15:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't asset forfeiture the same thing as cops stealing your freedom of speech? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 17:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, since money equals speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taliban leader Mullah Omar died over 2 years ago: Afghan official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 17:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Deal with it yourself': Dispatcher hung up on woman giving first aid to shooting victim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 17:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone asks, "do you mind..." We answer in the negative like, "sure" or "yea," but it's understood in the positive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 14:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] I'm watching Penn and Teller fool us and I can't find a clip from the Simpsons where Teller says, "He'll do it, I'm not the first Teller" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 04:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If it wasn't for ESPN, sports sites and blogs, most of my coworkers wouldn't know what to think about the game they watched last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 00:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I could use your help with a wedding sermon :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 17:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing the wedding sermon for my friends, the groom is really into Star Wars and I'm hoping you all could help me sneak some stuff into the sermon.  The bride and groom are both ok with this, but I need help making it sound as legitimate as possible.  
  
So far I do plan on trying to get the groomsmen to bust out some fake medals like the end of episode IV.  But we'll see.  
  
Also I'm going to other subreddits looking for Harry Potter (which I don't know as much about) and LotR if you see a similar post from me else where.  
  
Thanks for all your help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides the dead guy in the back, driving a hearse must be pretty sweet since they're usually Cadillacs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 15:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix Xbox achievements make me feel pathetic - you've watched 10 weeks of Netflix everyday in a row. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whitney Houston daughter Bobbi Kristina Brown dies aged 22 - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 03:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm giving the sermon at a wedding, would give me as many slip ins as you can for Star Wars, Lord of the Ring and Harry Potter as you can? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MacGyver is STEM the tv show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 19:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I turn the knob on the left to the left the water gets hotter, when I turn the right knob to the left the water also gets hotter, what kind of person installs knobs like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 20:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If politicians put as much time, effort and money into mental health access as they do with gun control we wouldn't need gun control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 19:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Down votes on reddit are more emotionally based than logically based </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 02:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most of the people I know in relationships are in "lust" rather than "love" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 02:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else notice that Cortana's voice recognition has gotten really bad over the last few months or so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 23:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ford Social  Helping drivers see people, animals and junctions at night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the most quoted scenes from the Simpsons in my house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BEEP BEEP I'm a truck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All these updates have messed up my Band </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've contacted MS on twitter, phone, etc. They replaced my band hoping that was the issue since I hard reset it twice and uninstalled and reinstalled the MS Health app.  But unfortunately the bands keyboard still doesn't function like it used to (it's basically unusable).  Then with these latest updates the bands battery takes a real beating.  I don't know what's going on, but I hope there's some sort of fix soon.  (Side note: I was also worried that 3rd party apps were causing the issue so I didn't install them after another hard reset of the new band, [but no dice](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h55HYoV0HH4).) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No double moon in 2015, or ever | Astronomy Essentials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hydraulic Fracturing Linked to Increases in Hospitalization Rates in the Marcellus Shale Region, According to Penn Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Using Your Bank For Targeted Ads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Using Your Bank For Targeted Ads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 17:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin Should Be Exempted from VAT Says European Court of Justice Official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They're No. 1: U.S. Wins Math Olympiad For First Time In 21 Years : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slingbox Class Action Lawsuit Filed Over Unwanted Ads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Make Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Run Much Faster On AMD Catalyst For Linux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some zombies would be double scary to some people like: clown zombies, little people zombies, dentist zombies, dr. Zombies, cop zombies, skin head nazis, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there were a sudden zombie outbreak there would some zombies on rollerblades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor from Canada explains how dropping a few of the deadliest cities from America's gun homicide rate takes the US towards the bottom and goes on to explain how burdensome Canada's gun laws are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wildfire sweeps across California freeway, burns vehicles | Local News - WCVB Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trainwreck is R-rated riot by Apatow, Schumer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 22:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsters Inc: Rules of Comedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsters Inc: Rules of Comedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 19:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Wrong With Monsters Inc. In 14 Minutes Or Less </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dumber you are the more you like "Shut Up and Dance" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 16:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arielle Kebbel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 01:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Travel mugs are adult sippy cups. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/ means realm... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Star Trek copyright laws have been extended so far they can only use books over 300 years old for holodeck programs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 21:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ian McKellen On Why Superman Is A Joke   James Bond Is a British Twit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Playing army': Military reservists with DEA jobs say agency bosses ridiculed their service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keyboard issue update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 04:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I called MS since my keyboard would function ultra slowly. I told them I reset the band twice with the same issue. They told me to take it into the store and they'd replace it for no charge. I took it in and switched it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is having some better than having none, in a world where you had it all, but can never have it again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Accountant of Auschwitz,' 94, sentenced to 4 years in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 01:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If speeding tickets weren't so lucrative we wouldn't have a high patrol anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops should change the motto: "To protect property and serve warrants violently" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laura Poitras Sues US Government To Find Out Why She Was Detained Every Time She Flew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 22:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Military Once Tested Biological Warfare On The Whole Of San Francisco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All music if just variations of pop music, country is pop with twang, alternative is pop with a guitar solo,   rock is pop with a better drummer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What things do you do regularly to prepare for a sudden evacuation from your home/area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 18:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chasing Outbreaks: How Safe Is Our Food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How America became the world's leader in incarceration, in 28 maps and charts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 17:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man arrested after charging iPhone on London Overground train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti Piracy warning - IT Crowd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 14:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It keeps failing to load posts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few times this was due to reddit being down, but it keeps happening, any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you read a conspiracy theory, but said theory would fuck over rich people, it probably isn't true. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 21:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend needs a public defender in West Virginia, question about the form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my buddy is filing some paperwork to request a public defender, his contract ended at work and he'll have another job soonish, but on the paper work it asks for employer and income, should he put zero down or an average or what would be recommended? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Rees, a Tony Winner as Nickleby, Is Dead at 71 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 02:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coquitlam teenager sentenced to 16 months in jail for 'swatting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father says bomb scare was teens chemistry set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa's DOT Chief Expects the State's Road Network to Shrink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adblock Plus Saves University 40 Percent Network Bandwidth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best images of Pluto and Charon yet - album in comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adblock Plus Saves University 40 Percent Network Bandwidth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lumia 1520 AT T, weird bluetooth issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 15:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a MS Band (love it, haters!) but my bluetooth keeps disconnecting.  I have recently reset the band and went through all the steps, it seems to be fine, but my phones bluetooth keeps disconnecting.  I recently power cycled it normally, not the hold volume down and power reset, it linked up after that, but for some reason it seems to disconnect but I can't figure out why.  It will reconnect by itself after I've waken the phone up and stay connected for a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sia - Chandelier (Official Video) - Her expressions are pretty creepy sometimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sia - Chandelier (Official Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Military personnel, can you tell the difference between your own ordnance and the enemies by sound? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking more about large explosives versus small arms fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In_The_News comments on Bakers who refused to make lesbian wedding cake told to pay $135K by Monday -- or else </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has update 2 come to AT T 1520 phones yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Ghostbusters' new Ecto-1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crash victims may have lain injured for three days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sherlock Victorian special image revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I find myself using this gif more and more IRL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I find myself using this gif more and more often </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 20:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All trading on New York Stock Exchange halted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 18:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What things/phrases/words/themes were commonplace in your youth but are now taboo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 15:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What morals do you personally have that others see as contradictory, but you see no problem with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 23:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the weirdest/craziest/most messed up thing that happened to you at a church or the immediate area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After eight years of paid leave, Paterson cop may get money for unused vacation days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This lady doesn't like pranks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most funny stereotype you've heard of that you've seen to be true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When looking back at your younger self, what event could you have easily died from if one variable changed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposed regulation could keep 3D-printed gun blueprints offline for good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 17:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keyboard for texting is all messed up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Windows phone 8.1, but in the last couple of days, right before the update and now after it, the keyboard takes forever to recognize words I've typed out skips some. I could type "cool" swipe to the screen right of the keyboard input and it takes several seconds to show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 82 shot- 15 fatally- in Chicago over holiday weekend | abc7chicago.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 14:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't click on the title bar to bring the main part back up to swipe to new posts unless I scroll all the way back up the comments to the top. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will you be doing for the 4th of July? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We live out on a farm with a couple of neighbors, we've got a 100ft tarp set up on a hill as a slip 'n slide. At the bottom we're using hay bales to hold the tarp into a "pool" for a splash zone.  We've got tons of fireworks and I'm smoking pork shoulder (butt).  Any fun plans out there, especially for military overseas (I was a military dependent and the Germans were cool enough to shoot fireworks all over town on the 4th). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fabled CD-playing, SNES-compatible Play Station prototype found in a box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung, Oppo facing landmark lawsuits over pre-installed apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's gold in them thar bills! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Killings Inspire Copycats, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airlines Under Justice Dept. Investigation Over Possible Collusion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accuweather is pissing me off!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need a million push notifications for the same fucking information.  I get it, there's a severe thunderstorm warning.  I have litterally gotten 20 in the last 10-15 min.  I get when it changes from an alert to a warnning etc, but these are all exactly the same.  I like weather alerts in general, but this is fucking with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What actor is really popular and stars in a lot of movies but you think makes the movie worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Evil I Live With </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Level 9 Fire Flying I can only get 78% any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 00:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the only stage I don't have good on, I need a tip. I've adjusted my upgrades on the one style plane in that level, the medium one, in every configuration possible. I usually send one plane to the bottom and one to the top. Dump the water right on the fire and refill. After that the fire goes crazy in the middle and I can't get it in two total runs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Escaped NY prisoner Richard Matt shot, killed - New York Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 22:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to the Maryland State Constitution I never have to serve jury duty or be called on as a witness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art. 36. That as it is the duty of every man to worship God in such manner as he thinks most acceptable to Him, all persons are equally entitled to protection in their religious liberty; wherefore, no person ought by any law to be molested in his person or estate, on account of his religious persuasion, or profession, or for his religious practice, unless, under the color of religion, he shall disturb the good order, peace or safety of the State, or shall infringe the laws of morality, or injure others in their natural, civil or religious rights; nor ought any person to be compelled to frequent, or maintain, or contribute, unless on contract, to maintain, any place of worship, or any ministry; nor shall any person, otherwise competent, be deemed incompetent as a witness, or juror, on account of his religious belief; provided, he believes in the existence of God, and that under His dispensation such person will be held morally accountable for his acts, and be rewarded or punished therefor either in this world or in the world to come.  
  
http://msa.maryland.gov/msa/mdmanual/43const/html/00dec.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Park Service to stop selling Confederate flags </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 19:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Robertss full-throated gay marriage dissent: Constitution had nothing to do with it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 17:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your coolest "ninja/Jedi" momment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like catching a jar as it fell out of the fridge without thinking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your coolest "ninja/jedi" momment? (Like catching a jar as it fell out of the fridge without thinking about it.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non Sequitur was spot on today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurdish successes against ISIL pose risks to Obama strategy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Wars hoverbikes' may be coming to the US military </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 22:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie do you mention or reference that you're surprised to find out that people have no idea what you're referencing? (Mine's Dr. Strangelove) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 21:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was posted over here, and has made it's way to r/amibeingdetained, the comments are the most disgusting part </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 20:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog lovers and dog eaters clash in China - CNN.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube Algorithm Can Decide Your Channel URL Now Belongs To Someone Else - Gave Away Mr. Lush's URL to Lush Cosmetics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors of Australia, what clever things have you come up to get around your expensive/non-existent tech and media imports? (Sorry to hear "Copyright Amendment (Online Infringement) Bill 2015" passed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Pushes Critical Update to Fix Random Reboot to AT T Lumia 830, 1020 and 1520 - Softpedia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 15:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E-Detective: Spying tool used by over 100 law enforcement agencies has major security holes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Driver in California Will Be Considered Employee, Not Contractor (Updated) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 16:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VICE News correspondent Simon Ostrovsky follows the digital and literal footprints of one Russian soldier, tracking him from eastern Ukraine to Siberia, to prove that Russian soldiers are fighting in Ukraine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Turnabout, Disney Cancels Tech Worker Layoffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyway to listen to a voicemail and jot down some notes while it plays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Stuns E3 With Drool Worthy Customizable Xbox Elite Wireless Controller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to change the default reminder time for calendar events to an hour? Sometimes I forget to change it from 15 minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 14:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got an email that my Amazon app is out of date and being discontinued, instructed me to update the app, no updates available. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 13:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: http://imgur.com/Vu0zd3o here's a screen shot of the email. When I click the link in the upper right corner it launches an iTunes website that then loads to our WP store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
