<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 19:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said the ending I wanted, not the ending I expected. That's probably why I was okay with it. Up until you're actually presented with it, I didn't expect the final choice to be choosing between Bay and Bae. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 17:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I don't have any glaring problems that I want Dontnod to go back and fix. But if they could just make the lip syncing a little better in a couple scenes, that'd be great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any qualms with the ending(s) of LiS, but I'll admit that I have been let down by some other games this year. As much as I absolutely adore Until Dawn, I was disappointed with how its "butterfly effect" actually worked, and that there's really just one ending (though it's the only logical ending to a story like that, but still). Arkham Knight was a game that had my hype levels through the roof and, while I did enjoy playing the game, I was burned badly by both the story and the content (screw those AR challenges, they done effed it up). So I totally understand the feeling of being let down by something that had you so pumped up. But when it comes to Life is Strange, the story mostly went where I wanted it to and I got the ending that I've wanted since the beginning.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 14:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever gotten so attached to fictional characters, or been so in love with a fictional world before. As a result, when shit starts to go down in the final two episodes I was so invested in them. I've never cared about a character as much as I have about Chloe. She may as well be a real person in my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 14:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That man's going to talking mad shit til the day he dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 14:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem dude. I say just smile and move forward. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 14:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, in terms of scope The Witcher 3 is unbelievable. But to me it still *feels* like an average-good RPG, if that makes any sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 01:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What inspires me? Jeez, I didn't think I'd have to be thinking so deep tonight! I feel like a self-motivated and self-made person most of the time, though I've started to learn that this concept doesn't exist. I am who I am and do what I do because of the people around me. My environment is responsible for who I am, even though I feel like I'm always fighting my fight alone (and I'm content with that). When I think of the people who inspire me, I can only think of people on the other side of the screen. There's my childhood best friend who I haven't seen in person for years, who inspires me every day because he's still my best friend (love is a powerful thing). Then I have my role models who inspire me. They're not people who I want to be just like as much as they're people who I respect and have learned from. They range from Markiplier to Conor McGregor to our very own Max Caulfield. I'm inspired by the adversity these people have overcome and what they stand for. They all inspire me to be a better person, to work harder, to love, and to be myself. When I think of my friends, I think of my best friend and Markiplier and Greg Miller and Chloe Price. They're always there for me in my mind. 

But most of all I find inspiration and motivation in the horizon. I believe every single one of us has unlimited potential. I'm always looking beyond, dreaming of doing awesome things and *knowing* that one day I will make my dreams into reality. The prospect of the future inspires me. 

Anyways, that's a look inside my mind. Hopefully that's enough good feels for ya OP :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your insanity had to be made known :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called respect, you ape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of world does this? Who does this? 

*(I don't mean to be taking this lightly, I just feel like Chloe said it best.)*

Hopefully this nightmare will be over soon. To affected or in the affected areas, stay safe, stay strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. Just please be respectful, if not to the Parisians who are going through hell right now, at least to everyone here who is concerned about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ready for the mosh pit, shaka brah."

Sums up the ridiculousness of this game and why I love it so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the day, I guess we just have to come back to what Max told us a long time ago: who ever said we only have one fate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the top contenders for Game of the Year are Life is Strange, Until Dawn, and MGS5. But I still understand that almost all of the praise will be directed to the *huge* AAA big budget titles (MGS is among them). I'm not saying games like The Witcher, Arkham Knight, and Fallout 4 are bad by any stretch. I just don't really see them as being game-changers (pun intended). LiS, Until Dawn, and MGS are the three games I've seen this year that try to boldly go where no game has gone before. I think they deserve recognition for that, and I don't think "Games for Change" really stresses that enough. But that's just my two cents. :)

For reals though, why wasn't LiS nominated for Art Direction and/or Soundtrack? The art of LiS is beautiful and gives Arcadia Bay a very distinct feel (one that we don't get a lot of in games); and the soundtrack isn't just amazing, it's really well implemented. I can't think of another game off the top of my head that makes use of music so well for setting tone and conveying feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 23:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EP 1: This game is pretty sweet. Lovely art style, incredibly atmospheric, cute dialogue, very quirky. Got a nice soundtrack too. It makes me feel all fuzzy inside, and also pretty nostalgic. Kinda zen too. I like it.  

EP 5: I'LL NEVER LEAVE YOU CHLOE I'LL DO ANYTHING FOR YOU *YOU ARE ALL THAT MATTERS TO ME* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm arguing for it, but I hate it too. I didn't pick the Bay ending, and I never will, so I don't actually accept this as a valid theory. It's just my only way of making sense of the Bay ending, because there are a lot of variables and inconsistencies that don't make logical sense. How does letting Chloe die in the bathroom stop the storm? How does rewinding to change the past solve a problem that was created *by rewinding to change the past*? How does Jefferson still get arrested? There are too many things in the Bay ending that don't add up; the only way I can accept that ending as a possible outcome is if the week has all been a dream.

But thankfully I don't need to accept the Bay ending. Bae over Bay, all day every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 00:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And electrocutes you if you lick both terminals at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably gooo...

1. Life is Strange (duh)

2. Tales from the Borderlands (so style much funny very wow)

3. The Wolf Among Us (NEEEEEOOOOOONNNNNN)

4. TWD Season 1 (I cried like a baby. But that doesn't necessarily mean it's the best ever.)

5. TWD Season 2 (I enjoyed it, but I have no real love for it. Clem has a cool hat though.)

Life is Strange and TFtB take the top spots for me. Here's (a general reason that applies to both) why: they're both fairly lighthearted. I know Life is Strange often deals with very serious themes, and it takes a dark turn in Episodes 4 and 5, but more often than not it's a very chill, fun, and dreamy game. At least 80% of the time in the first four episodes I had a goofy smile plastered on my face. Life is Strange has actually left me with fond, nostalgic memories. The we have TFtB. TFtB is a goofy, ridiculous, cartoonish game that doesn't take itself too seriously. I have no attachment to TFtB, but I can really appreciate a game like that just tries to be *fun* and get a smile out of you, especially these days. 

But LiS takes my number one spot because of a) its immersive and dreamlike world and b) its incredible duo. I don't need to say much more than that; I already spend all of my time in this sub gushing over how much I love LiS and Max and Chloe. :P

Quickfire: I love The Wolf Among Us for its gorgeous graphic style, genuinely engrossing plot, and character progression. The Walking Dead Season 1 is a very emotional experience that made me question my morality a few times, but I can't say it actually had a lasting impact on me (which is surprising to me; those tears were flowing like Niagra Falls). Season 2 was fun too, but I think I may have been better off without it. Quick aside, I think TFtB is the only Telltale Game that actually benefits from the Telltale formula. The other stories end up suffering as a result of a lack of consequences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, that is the best Twitter account in the history of ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah, my eyes are totally watering because I got punched right in the eyeball. It's totally not anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, a LiS rap is never something I thought could work.

Thank you for proving me wrong. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who doesn't love them some Pricefield? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On your second point: I was actually thinking as well that, if you take the Bay ending as canon, the events of the week could very likely be all a dream. It sounds like a cop out, but by leaving it ambiguous it really isn't. Also I feel like this *is* a context where the "it was all a dream ending" could work. Max left behind Chloe five years ago and never attempted to contact her. We can infer that Max also didn't make any really good friends in Seattle. After having not seen Chloe for five years, Max happens to stumble across her getting murdered in a school bathroom. Apart from plain old shock (she saw someone get murdered for Pete's sake), Max gets hit with a tsunami of guilt. If only she had made some attempt to contact Chloe. I think we can assume that Max wanted to see Chloe again, but she was just too scared to try and call her. Guilt, grief, and, most of all, regret. If only she had done something. What if..? For the whole week, Max is on autopilot. She can't come to terms with what's happened. So in her mind, she imagines what could have been. She saves Chloe. The two immediately become best friends again. They go on an often-nonsensical adventure around the *dreamlike* Arcadia Bay (I think that's the best way to describe Arcadia Bay, and the entire game itself: dreamlike). It's the happiest week of both of their lives. But deep down, Max knows the truth. She knows that none of this is real. The (main) embodiment of the rapidly approaching reality is the storm. The storm can't be stopped. It gets worse and worse the more Max tries to withdraw from reality and live in her perfect dream world. In the end, sacrificing Chloe is the only way for Max to accept the loss of her best friend. Chloe Price is dead and she'll die alone, not having the memories of her last moments with Max Caulfield to comfort her as she disappears into the void. Max mourns Chloe, but finds comfort in the fact that the memories of the week (which she manufactured) will always be real to her, and she will always love *her* Chloe.

...I got really into that. Shit.

**tl;dr:** Max goes into shock following Chloe's death and feels regret for not having tried to contact her best friend. To cope, she dreams a whole week where she and Chloe get to be best friends again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually started to tear up a little listening to your cover of Obstacles, and not because I thought it was "dreadful" (it wasn't dreadful at all). It was super touching. No matter what obstacles appear in front of you, you can always overcome them with perseverance and a little help from some friends. It's absolutely insane to see the impact this game has had on people.

I wish you all the best in the future buddy! See you around!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y-1CUBEEuIA index=86 list=FLhRaU1uoqa0pb0hoqj6YEEw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 20:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you brought attention to the beautiful fact that *Life is Strange could not be made in any other medium*. Being able to rewind and change your choices is as much of a story element as the relationship between Max and Chloe. The story is about discovering yourself and deciding what kind of person you want to be; rewinding is the mechanism through which we can do this. It's not something that could work in a linear medium AT ALL. If Life is Strange had to be made into a movie/book/graphic novel, I actually think they'd have to either remove or completely rework Max's powers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 20:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VR couldn't work for Life is Strange *Season One* in any way. At least without the game being completely reworked. AR on the other hand...that sounds hella cool. I'd love being able to see the little while icons and outlines; I think the hand drawn style of the UI is really neat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 20:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Frank? *What about Beans?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 20:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this came up in another thread, but it's possible that Dontnod could bring Max and Chloe back for Season 2 by making the Bae ending canon. And before you start jumping down my throat, let me explain. [EP5 SPOILERTAGTOBESAFE](#s "There are enough posts around here that talk about why the Bay ending is "impossible", or at least why it wouldn't stop the storm, so I don't need to go into detail there. Taking that into account, Max might end up taking the butterfly photo -let's assume she keeps it, they can do a tiny bit of rewriting- and undoing the Bay ending, ultimately ending up in the aftermath of the Bae ending. This could let Dontnod bring back Max and Chloe AND start the second season from the same point, though if you chose Bay you might get an extra 10 or 15 minutes. That said, the people who chose the Bay ending would feel cheated, and I don't know if there's a real story to be told there that's anything more than Pricefield fluff, which I'd love but probably couldn't carry the game in the long run. I wouldn't rule it out though. It would be the easiest way to bring them back and pick up where they left off.") 

Or they could just give us Max and Chloe in an alternate reality. Each season of Life is Strange could be us reliving the same week in drastically different alternate realities, where the one constant is the friendship/love of Max and Chloe. I actually really like that idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 19:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They ran out of money. With the Bay ending, there was more that they had to show. You can infer everything you need to know from the Bae ending from the little they show you. The Bay ending *had* to be longer, so they dedicated more resources towards it. It's really as simple as that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 19:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, playing the game over the course of the year only enhanced that feeling. It felt like a freaking journey. LiS really became a part of my life; when I wasn't playing a new episode, I was constantly thinking about what would happen next and farting around in this subreddit. Having so much time to reflect really made me connect with the story and characters so much more. If I had played the game in one short burst, I wouldn't have been as invested in the story. Max, Chloe, Kate, and Warren started to become real people in my mind, friends who I couldn't wait to see again. And in the case of Chloe, she became someone that I cared about more than anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 19:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Who ever said we only have one fate?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 19:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't look so sad. I'm never leaving you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 19:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected this thing to be at least 70 bucks. But 35 Euros? Damn Square, thank you! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 08:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a beautiful painting! So warm and atmospheric. Captures that dreamlike quality which I love the game for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Chloe, why do you have to keep dying?"

"What, you don't like how the blue looks Max?"

(because her friends keep *dyeing* eheh eheh eheheheh)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *You are all that matters to me.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding? *Don't you forget about me.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Having difficulty concentrating" might be the story of everyone in the subreddit right now :P. It's so strange thinking about Life is Strange being over. Done. Capiche! For most of 2015, Life is Strange has been a huge part of my life. I was always thinking about it, daydreaming about it (specifically Pricefield), listening to the soundtrack. Arcadia Bay started to feel like home. And now...it's just gone. While it's left an everlasting imprint on me, it's just so *strange* that there isn't another episode to look forward to, more of Chloe and Max to eagerly await. It's left a gap in my life really. 

Despite it being over, I'm so glad that I've been left with these incredible memories of my last week in Arcadia Bay (*sniff*). I'm also finding comfort in the fact that, no matter what happens in my life next, Max and Chloe will always be forever alive through me and through all of us. They aren't going anywhere anytime soon, or ever.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 22:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, the praise is well deserved. :) 

Also your username is perfect. Sums up all of us here :P  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 18:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood the second the choice came up what the more emotional, superior, and "true" ending would be. For a second I kind of regretted not choosing to sacrifice her, thinking "I'd probably get more of an emotional response from that one." But that's not really how this works for me. I don't agree with sacrificing Chloe, and I certainly wasn't going to make the moral choice for morality's sake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 16:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently played the finale, and I went back to school for the first time since then today. I couldn't really focus on anything. 

^then ^again ^it's ^not ^like ^we're ^doing ^anything ^important ^or ^remotely ^interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 16:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really really adorable.

Edit: Sorry. That's *hella* adorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 16:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great drawing! Love the design, love the style, and Max looks great! Don't undersell yourself. Also I have to admit, this is the best Chloe I've seen. It captures her general look as well as her character really nicely. I can see both her attitude and her softer side in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 01:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat shit and die  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 23:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine, you don't have to apologize to me or anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 23:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this drawing on my mind for a very long time. The chill scenes are my favorite scenes from the game. Happier times! Thanks for the kind comments. I thought the best way to capture the "chillness" was to avoid any kind of hard outlines and just roll with soft shades of color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 22:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading this makes me think that a very possible setup for Season 2, if it happens, is Max letting the storm wreck Arcadia Bay. The new Season would either pick up right after the Bae ending, or begin with Bay Max reconsidering her decision and rewinding back through the photo to save Chloe. I think it would be a bit of a cop out, but I think Dontnod knows how much we love these characters and would throw our money at them the second it gets announced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 22:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it just sucks to see the inevitability of reddit in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 22:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Chloe would like that drawing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 22:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pre ordering as soon as they confirm that this is a real thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 21:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is /r/lifeisstrange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 21:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we all *please* stop arguing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 20:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of adding her room but making it blurry, keeping Max as the focus. I might just do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is crazy how almost every day someone finds something new in this game and post it here. Really shows how developed Dontnod made the world of Arcadia Bay. 

 I think Chloe breaks character by not going haywire about the fact that Max didn't save william.

I thought she would do that as well, but I think we were underestimating her. She probably couldn't stop thinking about that later, but I think she understood that what Max went through was terrible, as well as the fact that Max was trying to make things better for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This picture is filtered. Here are a few more filters on the image, as well as the original pencil drawing. 

[Link](http://imgur.com/a/iOhwq)

I'm also considering adding a minimalistic background. Do you think that would work?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FANART] Max with guitar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best things about Life is Strange is how it balances light and dark. At its worst, the game is brutal and it breaks you. At its best, it has you grinning ear to ear and feeling like the happiest person in the world. For every tear that was shed, there was a smile to be had. It's kind of like real life in that respect; ups and downs. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Don't rush yourself though, we're used to longer waits around here :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was pretty heartbreaking as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, it would kind of diminish the effect of the ending if everyone important made it out okay. The choice was ultimately meant to be a sacrifice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their chemistry is amazing, but I don't think Hannah Telle would really fit in with the version of Ashly from HAWP. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that was a neat read. That bit towards the end of Chapter 3 was heavy on the feels. Any more chapters incoming, if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 18:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't replayed or rewatched that scene, so I didn't realize that it actually made a difference. I told her that Jefferson hurt Max to be clear, and how concerned she got was actually really sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 18:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, these are amazing! Thanks for posting these, I think I might have a new wallpaper :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 18:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Max is not the only butterfly emerging from chrysalis to me.

Huh. I never actually thought about it like that. I like it. Two butterflies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was really touching to see just how much Chloe trusts Max in this scene. She's willing to drop revenge (and we know just how hell bent she was on killing Nathan then) and believe her best friend, who just came outta nowhere with all the things she says. And like you said, the scene has Chloe finally realizing what hell Max has gone through to be with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all still clinging onto Life is Strange and begging for dlc and epilogues, so it's understandable that people are seeing "Season 2 Confirmed" and losing their minds. You're right though; we are being really dumb. Just understandably so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was brief, yeah, but there was a sense of urgency throughout. At the beginning when Max snaps at Chloe (the first time I think that's ever happened), you get a sense that time is running out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The worst, for me, is Max who has to wait Nathan to kill Chloe and hearing him tell to Chloe that nobody will care about her death... and Chloe dying with that in mind :'(

That is so painful to think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pleasepleasepleasepleasepleasepleasepleasepleasepleaseplz be real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EP5 SPOILERS] I haven't really seen anyone talking about this scene... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene in question being when you first see Chloe in Episode 5 after jumping through Warren's photo. I don't know about the rest of you, but Max telling Chloe about the alt-timeline, William, and how Chloe asked her to euthanize her (obviously you could choose not to tell her, but fuck that) was the most emotional scene in the whole game for me. It was bad enough back in July when I was given the choice, but having to say it aloud to Chloe just brought it all back, and that's on top of all the other shit that had happened. I also feel like this scene had some of the best acting in the entire game; I think this was definitely Hannah Telle at her absolute best. I'm a little surprised that this scene is being kind of overlooked. Or was it just not that hard hitting for most of you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 16:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The void in my soul is slowly being filled by these post-ending comics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 12:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having trouble thinking about what power they could use in season 2. What's something that we all wish we could do, that also speaks to the themes of coming of age and finding yourself? I don't think Dontnod will just pick a new power because it'll make for great gameplay; it has to be relevant to the arc of our new protagonist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 12:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This already looks awesome! Looking forward to seeing the completed piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 12:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as my emotions have been running wild, I don't regret saving Chloe over the town. I think for me that always was and will be the right choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 12:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, links would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writing is "on fleek".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 02:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's gotta say it...

***I WAS EATING THOSE BEANS!*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great way to put it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a tough one to answer. All I know is that I was only invested in finding Rachel because of how much she meant to Chloe. I've verbalized too often that Chloe was my only priority, and I didn't want to see her in any more pain. I thought the scene where we found the body was incredibly sad solely because of how much it broke Chloe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was listening to Spanish Sahara earlier, thinking about my own best friend. Ending up crying. Thought I'd listen to something other than LiS soundtrack. Listened to "Hello" by Adele....bad choice. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean. I might make me sound like a sad, lonely human being, but Chloe Price *is* my friend (not so much Max, because I really feel like I am Max). After going on this wild ride with her, how could she not be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A well deserved "go fuck your selfie". I personally would've gone for "**eat shit and die**". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't think you understand what you've started, letting Max and Chloe loose on this world. They're dangerous."

"They surely are. The whole world knows it. Every world knows it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need me, I'll be in my bunker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be quite honest with you, I never considered Sacrificing Chloe as a possibility. Right now, I still don't. I've known that me and Chloe would leave Arcadia Bay together for a long time. 

*Someday we will forsee obstacles*

*through the blizzard, through the blizzard*

*today we will sell our uniform*

*live together, live together*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it. Returning to the original timeline is one of my favorite scenes in the entire game. such happy very tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Frank seeking vengeance for his beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  once while driving, I told an old woman to "go fuck your selfie".

Just because, or did she deserve it? Are you a serial heckler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nailed it. It's all about how it affects you as a person. Maybe other people won't remember anything, but if it's real to you, *it's fucking real*. 

I would still never in a million years choose to sacrifice Chloe. *Together* they can move past the terrible shit they experienced that week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first heard Wildest Dreams back in late July or early August, and it instantly made me think of Life is Strange. Made me tear up a little back then. Now this...this is just...yeah. Thank you for making this, shaka brah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Max, I'll always be with you." 

*"Forever."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Episode 3 Chloe tells Max that she's never leaving her side a handful of times. In Episode 4 we see Chloe willing to kill Frank to save Max. Max is Chloe's everything; she would not let Max die to save the town. Not even Joyce and her step-*father* mean as much to her as her best friend/soulmate/partner in time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't break down the outcomes like this to make my decision, but I still didn't see any way in which sacrificing Chloe was a good thing. If Max's powers were really fucking everything up though, the best move at that point would've been to hug Chloe really tight and look away from the town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHYYYYYYYYYYYYYY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful. Minor discrepancies in the faces, but who gives a fuck. This is incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great Scott! We've got to go back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even fathom what it's been like to go through what you have, but just know that you always have a home here on this sub. I'm so sorry about Ryan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really hoping that Samuel would show up with a platoon of squirrels to save the day....oh well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit out there, but I enjoyed reading it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Chloe. She's got a good heart. She's willing to do anything for Max, as she proves by (determinant) shooting Frank without hesitation to save her. Chloe has a lot of hurt bottled up inside her from everything that's happened to her and, while I can't really relate to the tragic loss of her father, I know a little something about bottling up everything and becoming incredible volatile. Chloe is confident and brash, but that's her armor. She feels like the whole world is against her, which is why she needs her armor. I understand this completely. I also understand what it's like to want your best friend back. 

Also her hair is sooooooooo pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
