<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7478</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 04:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relatively certain its a raspberry pi powered emulation box with some short barrel buttons. Beautiful, but not overly difficult to recreate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, it was all sort of done in my head. I can tell you that the entire thing was built out of a 4 x 8 x 3/4 piece of maple cabinet-grade plywood, with a sheet of 2x8x5/8 shelving MDF. I started by cutting two panels from the ply. The sides are 24 wide, and the ends are 19. This left enough for the sides of the control panels.

After that, I measured out my controls and found out that I wanted to go about 20" including the sides for the long control panel.

Once the sides were cut, I did the routering around the edges to create the slots for the t-molding. Then I stained everything. I screwed through the sides into the control panel sides, and added metal corner brackets on the inside for safe measure.

The trickiest part was the trackball. I didn't realize when I ordered it that it was going to be flush mount. For it, I cut a hole in the mdf the size of the body of the trackball. I then flush mounted it with the top, and put a piece of plexiglas over top of it.

The assembly is powered by an AMD Dual-Core 2.6ghz with 2gb of ram and onboard Radeon VC. Its running Hyperspin and I added all the video and marquee files so that the games she adds will automatically have the logos and such.

If you have any more questions, I'd be glad to answer them. The other thing is that, while it seems to have 4 sets of controls, its actually two duplicated. She wanted to be able to play games from both orientations, so I split off each of the connections so I could wire two controls to each of them. It worked well, and made configuration very simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cocktail cabinet I built on request... What do you guys think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 13:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 16:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would reddit gold make me feel like a man? Whats all the hub bub about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just realized randomly its my cakeday... Bowser was impressed when I told him! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 14:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 13:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be nuts to pass that up. Or at least legumes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RCMP search for armed and dangerous man after at least </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 04:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 20:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obiously the Jesus Christ Riotz.

Or James Cameron Riotz.

In the future, all movies are avatar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family catches dog theft on video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 00:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 18:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is also James Cameron. Can i get an apology for all the lame jokes i have to endure every time you release a movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 02:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a fan of 1943, you might appreciate this 1943 arcade cabinet that I built a few weeks back

http://www.reddit.com/r/MAME/comments/1wt9cl/1943_custom_bartop/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This image is also from 1942. The quality is amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 01:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 05:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not quite perfect yet. If i can't make it perfect, I will try something else for the front end. Since it has spent most of its time playing 1943 so far, it hasn't been too much of an issue. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mounted the motherboard onto the bottom of the cabinet, and placed a shelf above it for the power supply and the hard drive. The machine is an old XP2500 plus running xp with hyperspin. 1gb ram, 80gb hard drive, and a bfg 5500 graphics card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1943 Custom Bartop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 17:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 07:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is the same as a famous director. Every time he puts out a new movie, people ask me if I realize this. Or tell me they love my movies. Even when it's bed years since his last movie, I still get it. 

It got so bad at one point that I had a guy who works for Rogers in Canada start cracking jokes when I had called in to complain about an incorrect charge on my bill. Soon as he saw my name on the account. Said something about I should be able to pay for extra charges since I made millions off my movie. I just about lost it on him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 12:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 16 I tripped carrying a computer up a flight of stairs at the repair shop I was working at. I caught the computer in the face on the way down and broke my nose flat. The amount and speed at which it bled was downright frightening for someone who has never needed so much as stitches before. 

The most interesting thing is, my mom insisted we go to the doctor, even though I had set my nose back and the bleeding was stopped. My shirt and pants were severely covered in blood. After waiting for hours for the doctor, he looked at me for a few seconds in my blood stained clothing and asked if there was any bleeding. Then he grabbed the bridge of my nose, twisted lightly until he heard the crunch, and said "Your nose is broken. Seems like it's set right. Nothing to do here."  I know they don't do anything for broken noses, but his observational skills left me feeling less than in the best of hands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 19:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Dante's Inferno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remembering Mario Thoret: Cyclist feared for safety on busy Ottawa commute | </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 16:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 12:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.google.ca/url?q=http://m.youtube.com/watch%3Fv%3DVt7hIk_jZww%26desktop_uri%3D%252Fwatch%253Fv%253DVt7hIk_jZww sa=U ei=UbxCUt_CGsSH2gXDuYDoBA ved=0CA4QtwIwAA usg=AFQjCNGiGAKVKaC2v-mgjrNmEbGLHto7Gw

relephant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's a real Doctor, from... Canada??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 12:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read the signs, and there is only one way... His way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 12:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having never attempted to consume fecal matter, I have no grounds for comparison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 12:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0.68 seconds. For an android, that is nearly an eternity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 12:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using Bing as a search engine. Shame on you, Spider-Man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 09:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Picasso, the fifth ninja turtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 17:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried match sticks for a stripped hole in wall. House burned down. You owe me one house, good sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 14:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw my grandfather died and my mother dug up...

Ended better than expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 12:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up-chuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 12:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got married at 25, and had our first date at 16... Never regretted it for a moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 12:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KHANNNNNNNNNNN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 13:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five guys, one cup. Powerful picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 03:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sonic.exe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 22:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TV show ReBoot. Can watch that show all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 22:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reboot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 13:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does God need with a starship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beaker's enjoying his Canadian vacation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 22:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 12:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's where all the high ping counter strike global offensive players come from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 12:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they creeped up on my porch, i dont think i could bear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 04:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead before dawn... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever I am late... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 13:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 12:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That escalated quickly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My ThinkGeek order came with a free Space Invader model! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 01:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 11:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moreover, it is clearly not the Enterprise. They imply it is by showing the big E in an orbital decay, but if you examine the ship that hits the Earth, you will find that its nacells are squared instead of round. Its secondary hull also seems to be set higher in. Based on the impact, I feel it is likely this scene ties in to the original attack on London, which takes place towards the beginning of the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 11:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be awful aggressive in your posts. Or you don't realize that there is a difference between shift and caps lock. Either way, I never said I didn't like him because of his music. He is rude, he thinks he is above the law, and lacks general intelligence. And he is nearing burn out, if his most recent outbursts are any indication.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 14:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know where I am moving next. Said I would never leaving Canada. Never say never.

...

Damnit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 14:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the top voted comment is not Justin Bieber, there is something very wrong with this world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its my first time, so be nice... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 13:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 12:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't for anything food related, but still kind of relates to rediculousness.

When I was working as an acting supervisor for a cable company in new York, I had an escalated call come in from an irate customer. Guy says "Yeah... We just ordered this UFC fight on pay per vue. Its not being offered in HD in our area. I think we should be getting a discount, and toss in HBO and a few movie channels for free for a few months for our inconvenience."

So I politely explained that the event was only in SD (this was years back) and that we had no control over what the provider gave us as a feed. I also told him that, if he was unhappy, I could cancel his order and he could choose not to order it. He persisted, saying that this phone call is a huge inconvenience and that a few months of premium channels is the least we could do (the UTC event was 49.99, and he was asking for approximately 90 dollars in free service over the three months). 

Finally he blurts out "My friend spends a lot of money with you every month, you really should be more accommodating". Turns out he isn't even the account holder. He had lied to my rep when he called in because the account holder was too drunk to talk but thought his hilarious negotiations skills were too good to miss.

The best part? I am still on the phone with him when the right starts (standard no hang up on customers policy... although I can't garauntee he was a customer of ours anyway) and he suddenly blurts out "Well fuck you. Fight is starting. But I promise this isn't over" then puts the phone down off the hook. Hear him say "Let him eat air for a bit. Two hours to of hold time should straighten him out" luckily at that point, I was able to wait two minutes, inform our QA group the customer has become unresponsive, and disconnect.

Also, I had  guy call in wanting me to discount his porn and give him phone sex because his TV cut out during his porn, and his boyfriend was asleep and he didn't want to wake him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to buy her an eye mask... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 06:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 00:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earthworm Jim? He's such a groovie guy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
