<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't inherently saying bring them in, I was showing an example of where it is not just a time saving thing. I guess if my intent was that a better example would be if I go on long drives to unwind (I know people who do), I have one friend who likes to end stressful days by driving down this forested road by the ocean (example). I must apologize for that coming off wrong and hope I expressed myself a bit better.

On the other hand what you just said wasn't the implication I got from your post that led to this particular discussion. I thought you meant "if you aren't willing to learn to build a PC you shouldn't be allowed to play games" - "no time to learn, no time to play" would be a fallacy, a strawman (correct me if I'm wrong) to be exact. Implying if you don't have time ( which time is relative, people value their free time differently and semantically speaking could mean if they say 'I don't have time to learn to build a PC' could mean 'I have 0 interest in learning and console provides an experience I'm okay with and rather spend my free time playing a game than building the PC') to learn you don't deserve to play.

I admitted a few times in this thread I was wrong about the price issue, but that still doesn't really relate to this exact discussion we're having now. Also I know PC  console in overall performance and graphics, on the higher end side and even now on the sub 300-400$ side. That still doesn't mean that people who don't want to learn to build a PC by default should be completely excluded from gaming, this is in large part why consoles still exist. 

Edited to clarify a bit better and to fix some spelling and grammatical errors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an example, not meant to be a literal translation word per word but to show a comparison. And I think car enthusiasts may greatly disagree with cars being their just to save time.

And it still doesn't change the fact what you said is still a fallacy, if one does not want to/does not have time to (some people value their free time differently and playing games may be  learning to build a PC) it =/= one should not be able to play games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 12:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Last Of Us 2 is announced if you liked that for the ps3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 12:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tip my hat to you.

This sub has surprised me, I'm new to reddit tbh but have seen people say many times in my short time here stay away from pcmasterrace sub cuz it's all elitists. I now feel I know better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well don't have time VS don't want to. I personally think knowing how about PC hardware (bare minimum) should be mandatory but not everyone shares, or should have to share, this view.

Saying don't have "time to learn you don't have time to play" is also a bit of a fallacy. I don't (want to) learn how to fix my my car, many people would probably love to learn but don't have time, but it doesn't mean I don't have time to drive 300 miles for a vacation. 

Example not meant to literally transfer word per word in meaning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who tries to defend this (and I sadly see people in this thread doing it) need to get a better understanding of how the internet and it's infrastructure work. There's a reason wired (Sat. and Cell providers don't count here) internet companies have been charging for BANDWIDTH SPEED and not total DATA USED since the beginning of broadband (in the US at least). It doesn't cost an ISP anymore to deliver 10 GB or 5 TB of data, what will cost them is how much bandwidth is needed in total per neighborhood. My DSL I had to have living in Wyoming a few years ago had a 250 GB cap though, I always went over it (seriously every month I used 1 TB+ data between downloading games, streaming, etc) and they never bothered to even send me a letter and I had them a year +.

If you have cable your neighborhood has a a max amount of bandwidth allocated that it can use at any given time, a "pool" of bandwidth. Whether your neighborhood as a whole uses 100 GB in a month or 30 TB it's going to be the same to the ISP. What will cost them is upgrading the neighborhood so the "pool" can support 10 GB bandwidth at any given moment VS say 3 GB.

It's why ISPs label their speeds as UP TO xx/x , during peak times if a lot of people in your area are using their net a lot you will see yourself getting less than your promised 100/10 line can normally, but it's why you pay for more bandwidth in the first place, or at least part of why.

Note: this is basic and doesn't get into node backhauls and etc.

So in short, data caps from cable companies are complete and utter bullshit. Bandwidth caps are not, if anyone tells you otherwise laugh at them and feel sorry for the world as they help ISPs rape us.

Edit: a mistake in phrasing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I have nothing against people that just love Apple's OS and are willing to pay more for hardware with it. Even the people who just want it because it's Apple, its their life and their choices. But (and don't get me wrong I've seen Android users do this too, though most of the ones I see do it are Galaxy S users) I hate it when they get online and push it on everyone; "PC sucks, Android sucks, enjoy your viruses".

My friends girlfriend falls in between. She admitted she liked Windows fine and even knows it's a bit more practical overall but just loves Apple. On the phones she likes the superior finger print detection /lock (I personally dunno how it holds up VS high end Androids) and just likes Macbooks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know, I will look more into it still but I hope this puts FF back onto the map, so to speak. I have loved the series since I was a kid but it has hit some rough waters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides frame issues how are you liking FF15? I know off topic but I have my eye on the game but am wary after FF12/13/13-2 all of which I didn't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I stand corrected someone else pointed out this error on my part too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason to buy Apple (outside of people who want to brag they have an i whatever) is for the OS, I have a friend who's girlfriend is an Apple person. I did some work on her Macbook Air for her (setup Bootcamp mainly) and I thought the OS was decent and pretty for my short time on it, not worth the markup for it being Apple though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can, but I just have preferences. I enjoy my consoles and my PC and the experiences they provide, though I know I can hook an X1 controller to my PC if I wanted; it just doesnt2 "feel" the same to me. I'm sure it's all mental but hey. Also no The Last Of Us on PC, only my ps4. Though this is a small factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never liked exclusives BUT I understand why MS and Sony do them, MS won't really have exclusives anymore (so to speak, if you own a Windows PC) but I know Quantum Break fiasco doesn't have many confident, and a lot of people see UWP as GFWL 2.0 and are wary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I acknowledged in another comment I was wrong about that. But another respectable opinion. I agree the subs are BS, I only started really subbing for the free games. I can grab a year for 30$ with some luck and by the end of that year I always get more than I paid back in games I enjoy. Xbox's old (and thankfully removed) BS of no Netflix and etc without a sub was really some BS though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This I totally agree with for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another opinion I can respect, though I haven't run into any issues with my console game it doesn't mean they aren't out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do stand corrected on that, I haven't put a PC together from scratch in a long time now (relatively). My current rig has seen ram (4 GB - 8 GB, GPU 770 - 1060, HDD - added an SSD).

Most users won't want to put that together though (or learn how in most cases) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can respect this stance. I'm by no means an expert, I've been tinkering with PCs since I was 12 and building and or replacing parts since I was 15 or so. I've always enjoyed both platforms for gaming, and PCs for general web use (though my phone is replacing that quickly I hate to say). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play CS on my PC, which I lnow isn't the inherently the height of FPS. I also play Overwatch (also probably objectivly a meh casual game) on PC.

On my X1 I play Halo 5 since it doesn't really have a true PC version, and my roommate (technically) owns Doom for m the X1 (he uses mine) and I play that there since we already have it for console.

Edit

Also I acknowledged you can use your TV, just not many people would suggest it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Live and let live"
Pretty much my philosophy on life. I don't like Apple, their products are over priced for what you get, but I don't hate them or people who use their products. If you want to spend 800$ on a 300$ phone for the OS and brand then go ahead. (example of course) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add, I went through almost the entire 360 gen without any Xbox Live sub as I rarely game online back then (edit: on console to clarify). I finally got it for the free games you get with both consoles and have even gamed online a bit since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see this as a con, but not to HATE console gaming. I get my Xbox Gold, for example, on sales for 30$ or so a year. Definitely more expensive than 0 and I'm NOT using that to justify Xbox Live and PS+ fees. But I see it as a con VS omg consoles need to DIE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you hate consoles, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was wondering if I could find out why PC only gamers hate consoles so much.

As a PC (MMOs, RTS's, FPS's) and console (everything else) gamer I never understood. Now I know the common arguments like 

Consoles hold PCs back

Console communities are cancerous (from my experience PC is just as bad, but don't get me wrong they both are really bad with some exceptions)

But some PC gamers hate consoles with such a ferocity it makes me think their PS2 did bad things to them as kids (a joke, no one get too upset).

I hope the discussion (if anyone bothers to reply) can stay civil, I just really want to understand why some people in the "PCmasterrace" (not just this sub but a vocal part of the community as a whole) hate it so much. And I do know not every PC gamer hates consoles so much, or at all.

I guess to add from a console(and on a smaller scale PC gamer) side why I like consoles:
Cheaper, I got my semi recent PS4 for 200$ used, had it for a year now 0 problems (I also own an X1). I put together my current PC 4690k, 8 gb ram, GTX 1060 (upgraded from my GTX 770 I got new back when it was new tech) and I don't see how one, even buying used since I bought my PS4 used, can put together a PC to meet PS4 graphics for 200$.

To expand even if someone new was getting into gaming a PS4 slim is 300$ new, most people already have a TV, so besides games you're good to go. For PC it would be very hard to buy new and get PS4 graphics for 300$ when including MOBO, RAM, case, cpu, GPU, HDD etc. They could technically use their TV as a monitor but very few PC gamers would recommend that.

Console has no driver issues, it's UPNP pretty much. On my PC I have to do DDU every so often and will still get a game with weird issues that I, or Google, can't fix.

Edit for clarification and grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
