<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who could 5/10 Odin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 01:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel 616 Odin. 

Round 1: Odin is in-character. 

Round 2: Odin is bloodlusted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest character Omnicredible could defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omnicredible is a superhero who has all of the powers of the Incredibles, incuding:

- Super Strength/Durability

- Elasticity

- Super Speed

- Invisibility

- Force Field Generation

- Laser Eyes

- Can turn into fire

- Intangibility

- Can turn into metal

- Teleportation

- Devil mode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Azula is dropped in Westeros. How long does it take her to sit on the Iron Throne. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 02:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/3789vc/i_am_voice_actress_grey_delislegriffin_you_might/crkhf1u) comment from the Grey Delisle-Griffin AMA.

Azula, Mai, and Ty Lee appear in King's Landing disguised as members of the City Watch at the beginning of the series. Azula thinks that if she takes over Westeros then the Fire Nation will win the 100 Years War. How long does it take her?

Show only, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got another fight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanos with the Heart of the Universe vs. The Beyonders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 00:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Marvel] I want to be a superhero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 15:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the other day I was walking past the nuclear power plant and I was struck by lightning. Now I have super strength and I can fly. My town has had a lot of crime recently, and I've heard about this guy Spider-Man in New York and War Machine out west, and I want to do what they do. But how do I do that? Can I just go out and fight crime whenever I want? Do I need a costume? Is there a superhero union that I can join? Do I get paid, or is it like volunteer work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can any live-action movie superhero defeat 'Man of Steel' Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 02:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas the Tank Engine vs. The Little Engine that Could </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 01:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: They ram into each other at full speed. Who is less damaged?

Round 2: They each have one box car carrying the One Ring and must travel on an indestructible rail line from The Shire to Mount Doom. Who makes it further? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the Rugrats survive the landing on Omaha Beach? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larfleeze vs. Silver Surfer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 00:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

The battle takes place in deep space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shazam (Billy Batson) vs. Kazaam (Shaq) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shazam is N52 and Kazaam is EoM

Round 1: Rapping

Round 2: Fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many Mike Tysons would it take to beat Batman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mike Tysons are bloodlusted and have brass knuckles.

Batman (N52) is naked.

They fight in an inescapable boxing ring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultron (AoU) vs. A Sentinel (DoFP) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 21:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultron Prime and Future Sentinel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'haha' vs. 'lol' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/OldWorldGlory vs. /u/WhoWouldWinBot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman vs. Ash Ketchum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 22:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Respect Ash](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2uf0y6/respect_ash_ketchum_pokemon_anime/)

[Respect Batman](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/286fle/respect_batman_bruce_wayne/)

Round 1: Both unarmed.

Round 2: Batman has his suit. Ash has his hat backwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mojo Jojo (The Powerpuff Girls) vs. Caesar (Planet of the Apes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Hand-to-hand fight.

Round 2: Both get a spear.

Round 3: Both have 1 week of prep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver Surfer vs. Superman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman from *Man of Steel* and Silver Surfer from *Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer*.

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speed Racer in a Podracer vs. Anakin Skywalker in the Mach 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 03:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speed Racer from the original show and Anakin Skywalker from *The Phantom Menace*.

The race is the Tour de France 100 times in a row.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Kingpin vs. Hammerhead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 04:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 616 for each. Fight takes place in an abandoned warehouse. Pure hand-to-hand.

EDIT: Pre-powered endoskeleton Hammerhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Respect Toph Beifong, The Blind Bandit (Avatar: The Last Airbender) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Toph Beifong](http://vignette2.wikia.nocookie.net/avatar/images/4/46/Toph_Beifong.png/revision/latest?cb=20131230122047) is the only daughter of Earth Kingdom nobles, Lao and Poppy Beifong. Intending for her to become a respected noblewoman, Toph's blindness caused her parents to try to keep her locked up. But Toph's blindness became her strength, and led her to become the greatest earthbender in the world.

###Early Biography

Toph was born to Lao and Poppy Beifong. After discovering that she was blind, they tried to keep her locked up in their estate to protect her. Toph, not satisfied with this life, ran away when she was young. She met badgermoles (the first earthbenders), who were also blind, and they taught her their techniques and how to see with earthbending (seismic sense). As she grew older, Toph became one of the most powerful earthbenders in the world, and was a champion fighter at 'Earth Rumble IV' under the guise of 'The Blind Bandit' when she was only 12 years old. After an encounter with Aang, Katara, and Sokka, she agreed to travel with them to teach Aang earthbending and help end the 100 Year War.

###Earthbending, Metalbending, and Sandbending Skill

Toph has been described as the 'greatest earthbender in the world'. She invented the art of metalbending and mastered 4 of the 5 known earthbending sub-skills (earth, metal, seismic sense, and sand).

**Attacks**:

- [Accurately launches flaming boulders over 100 feet](https://youtu.be/tWJzENvAsZw?t=54).

- [Flips slabs of stone over to trap guards](https://youtu.be/6HLlJFyocGU?t=171).

-  [Knocks guards back with a wall of earth](https://youtu.be/ZGSuHKi38PA?t=118).

- [Pins guards to the ceiling with pillars raised from the ground](https://youtu.be/6HLlJFyocGU?t=249).

- [Alters ground where opponents are stepping](https://youtu.be/RBq87PoxIj0?t=340).

- [Sends trail of rocks at Combustion Man](https://youtu.be/iMqJmygsZlA?t=32).

- [Opens up the ground beneath several people](https://youtu.be/4XKZY7SJx64?t=138).

- [Launches a barrage of rocks at a wasp](https://youtu.be/6vTNjd5K2ms?t=478).

**Durability/Strength (Through Bending)**:

- [Shatters a boulder using only her head](https://youtu.be/5GmcYEJ4Q1o?t=118).

- [Launches herself and kicks through a stone wall](https://youtu.be/qdcdhgn0zHM?t=87).

- [Bends the rudder of an airship](https://youtu.be/e6NYW67Sbj8?t=369).

- Punches through a tank. [1](http://i.imgur.com/lV378pm.jpg) [2](http://i.imgur.com/SQQ2pl9.jpg)

- [Breaks through a metal door](https://youtu.be/Oh8BlJ4ezUU?t=199).

- [Destroys a prison door](https://youtu.be/zkladQpz5as?t=980).

- [Holds up Wan Shi Tong's Library](https://youtu.be/3RKNw--UbBg?t=299).

**Immobilization**:

- [Traps a Dai Li agent](https://youtu.be/qdcdhgn0zHM?t=168).

- [Completely encases Azula in stone](https://youtu.be/qdcdhgn0zHM?t=54).

- [Pins Azula's arm to a wall](https://youtu.be/qdcdhgn0zHM?t=225).


**Defense**:

- [Creates rock armor for herself in 1 second an launches herself forward with it](https://youtu.be/5GmcYEJ4Q1o?t=181). 

- [Blocks a bomb with a earth](https://youtu.be/4-c0it3J0b4).

- [Blocks 2 attacks from the Dai Li](https://youtu.be/qdcdhgn0zHM?t=91). 

- [Creates metal armor and defeats several comet-enhanced firebenders, while taking several blasts in the process](https://youtu.be/e6NYW67Sbj8?t=86). For comparison, Ozai's blast [tore through a stone wall from a much further distance](https://youtu.be/j3dT8oK7y80?t=193).

- [Erects a giant wall to stop Azula and her friends](https://youtu.be/4l--QfwZjuk?t=403).


**General Bending Skills**:

- [Easily raises 2 stone walls several meters high](https://youtu.be/5GmcYEJ4Q1o?t=178).

- [Creates a dust cloud and destroys a fighting ring](https://youtu.be/ukr5c07gaUI?t=95).

- [Effortlessly defeats several professional earthbenders at once](https://youtu.be/ukr5c07gaUI?t=106).

- [Repeatedly raises a giant slab of rock](https://youtu.be/OIsQ9H_MyDY?t=341).

- [Puts out a giant fire with rocks](https://youtu.be/QYvOnwitIYs?t=82).

- [Flattens a staircase several hundred feet tall and raises herself, Katara, Sokka, and Appa to the top (with Aang's help)](https://youtu.be/6HLlJFyocGU?t=216).

- [Creates and controls several life-sized replicas of soldiers from over 100 feet away to 'attack' Sokka and Suki](https://youtu.be/tWJzENvAsZw?t=46).

- [Traps 2 master earthbenders and launches herself at them](https://youtu.be/Tk8P1nPgJio?t=75).

- ['Earth-surfs' to travel at high speeds](https://youtu.be/Tk8P1nPgJio).

- Toph can sense earth even if it's not connected to the ground. [Launched rocks across an expanse of water onto another boat to destroy a catapult and intercepts flaming rocks in the air](https://youtu.be/iJ3iJynjPXI?t=139).

- [Topples a group of mechs and Earth Empire soldiers](https://youtu.be/N-wIieqpNIM?t=113).

- Creates an underground tunnel to sneak into the center of a Fire Nation army. [1](http://i.imgur.com/qXCphKh.jpg) [2](http://i.imgur.com/lV378pm.jpg)

- [Along with her students, removes the armor of an ancient spirit](http://static.comicvine.com/uploads/original/5/52828/4374401-aang+and+old+iron.jpg).

- [Bends a scale model of Ba Sing Se](https://youtu.be/N2SYDrQw3YY?t=85).

-  [Defeats Korra](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zouRX2Tw6Ew). States that she is much weaker than she was in her prime. 


**Precision**:

- [Senses a hedgehog from a few hundred feet away and launches it into her hand](https://youtu.be/w_Ko7VusR04?t=203).

-  [Launches herself, Sokka, and Suki onto an airship](https://youtu.be/e6NYW67Sbj8?t=35).

- [Knocks the screws out of the wheels of several tanks](http://i.imgur.com/Ma5NgFj.jpg).


###Seismic Sense

Despite her being blind, Toph is able to 'see' with earthbending by sensing the vibrations in the ground, which provides her with incredible situational awareness and a mild precognition from being able to sense where her opponent will move.

**Seismic Sense (Reaction Times)**:

- [Able to sense where **THE BOULDER** will step and alter the ground at that location](https://youtu.be/9Q4Qweam-D8?t=183).

- Senses and dodges an earth attack and sends another attack back. Occurs several times in that scene [1](https://youtu.be/ukr5c07gaUI?t=138) [2](https://youtu.be/ukr5c07gaUI?t=149) [3](https://youtu.be/ukr5c07gaUI?t=175) [4](https://youtu.be/ukr5c07gaUI?t=213).

- [Catches a boulder with one hand and launches it back](https://youtu.be/Sslcahr_Yn0?t=29).

- [Blocks repeated attacks from Earth Kingdom Palace guards](https://youtu.be/6HLlJFyocGU?t=151).

- [Blocks spring-loaded darts from Mai and launches the wall at her](https://youtu.be/4l--QfwZjuk?t=414). 



**Seismic Sense (Situational Awareness)**:

- [Can use her seismic sense as a lie detector test by sensing the minute physical changes in a person's breathing and heartbeat that occur when they lie](https://youtu.be/Kr4NwVFrUo4?t=416).

- [Able to sense Combustion Man from over one hundred meters away while she is asleep with her seismic sense](https://youtu.be/iMqJmygsZlA).

- [Senses Azula take out a knife to stab Sokka and traps her](https://youtu.be/qdcdhgn0zHM?t=225).

- [Explains how she sees, and is able to sense ants walking a few meters away](https://youtu.be/309H1DT7F4M?t=134). 

- [Sensed and remembered every detail of Ba Sing Se enough to create an exact replica](https://youtu.be/N2SYDrQw3YY?t=85).

- [Senses metal that had been circulating in Korra's body for 3 years](https://youtu.be/1v8v3dN9npE?t=240). For comparison, Korra and Suyin (both masters) were completely unaware that she still had metal inside of her.

- [By old age, her seismic sense had grown to a range of miles with the aid of the spirit vines, being able to sense prisoners being moved to a prison](https://youtu.be/---AydjgqYI?t=72).

###Physicals

**Endurance**

- [Holds up Wan Shi Tong's Library for an extended period of time](https://youtu.be/3RKNw--UbBg?t=299). [Drawing of library for scale](http://img3.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20131220144507/avatar/es/images/f/f4/Ilustraci%C3%B3n_con_el_nombre_de_la_bilbioteca.png).

- [Holds up a cave-in around herself and others for several hours](http://i.imgur.com/AHQljnQ.jpg).

**Durability**

- [Gets blown across an earth arena and falls 10 meters and is only mildly annoyed](https://youtu.be/7s0ti3eV4F4?t=55).


###Other Information:

- Toph started a metalbending academy after the 100 Year War. This later grew into the Republic City Police Force, of which she was it's first chief.

- Toph is the only known earthbender to practice Southern Praying Mantis style earthbending.

- Toph is the one of only two known characters to invent an entirely new bending art (metalbending).

- Toph has trained 2 Avatars in earthbending (Aang and Korra).

(Other information will be edited in if I forgot anything).

*This is my first 'real' RT, so please excuse me if it is a little rough.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elektra vs. Black Cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 20:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight takes place on a rooftop in NYC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My desire to keep watching Daredevil vs. My need for sleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I (finally) started Daredevil tonight, and it's damn good. On episode 2 and I want to keep watching, but it is almost 1 AM and my bed is really comfortable. Which will win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Star Wars hype vs. My Age of Ultron Hype </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you who still don't know, [the new Star Wars trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ngElkyQ6Rhs) came out today. Can the hype it generates surpass Age of Ultron's?

Round 1: Which movie will be better received critically?

Round 2: Which will make more money?

Round 3: Which are you looking forward to more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mojo Jojo vs. Mandark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 02:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Standard fight. They each have 1 week of prep.

Round 2: The PPGs and Dexter must fight Mojo and Mandark. Each have 1 month of prep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [How the Hell] could the Powerpuff Girls beat Goku? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing [this thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/32k1i0/how_the_hell_could_the_powerpuff_girls_defeat/) by /u/selfproclaimed, it got me thinking about whether the PPGs could take Goku.

Round 1: Saiyan Saga Goku

Round 2: Frieza Saga Goku (Goku can go SSJ)

Round 3: Cell Saga Goku (Goku can go SSJ)

Round 4: Buu Saga Goku (Goku can go SSJ3)

Round 5: Post-BoG Goku (Goku can go SSJ1). The PPGs have a month of prep.

Goku is in-character, but the PPGs are willing to kill. They can get help from anyone in their universe for the prep, but everyone besides the PPGs are in-character. Goku and the PPGs are unaware of the fights until they happen (besides Round 5 where the PPGs have prep). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danny Phantom vs. Aquaman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EoS Danny and N52 Aquaman

Round 1: Both are in-character. They fight at SeaWorld.

Round 2: Both are bloodlusted. They fight in a city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many Evel Knievels would it take to beat Daredevil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real-life peak Evel and 616 Daredevil. All are unarmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Flair vs. Your Flair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They fight in an open field. Both are in-character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any, literally ANY scenario where Batman defeats Spider-Man in a random encounter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 02:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC Batman and 616 Peter

Rules:

1. Both have standard equipment.

2. Both do not start the fight harmed/tired/anything that could give them a disadvantage physically.

3. Both have no idea who each other are or what they're capable of.

BONUS: Batman has Dick, Barbara, Jason, Tim and Damien with him. All vs. Spidey in a random encounter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman is encased up to his neck in a block of adamantium and thrown into the sun. How long will he need to stay in there to break out, if it's even possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: He cannot vibrate through it. He needs to break it apart with his physical strength. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danny Phantom vs. Magneto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 01:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current Magneto and EoS Danny

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

BONUS: Peak Magneto vs. [Dan Phantom](http://dannyphantom.wikia.com/wiki/Dan_Phantom)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman, Captain America, and Master Chief vs. The Furious Five </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Fight takes place on a bridge crossing a large canyon. They start on opposite sides. Bats, Cap, and Chief have their armor but no gadgets, weapons, or shields.

Round 2: Fight in an open field. Bats, Cap, and Chief are wearing nothing but T-shirts and shorts.

Round 3: Open field. Po joins the FF. Bats, Cap, and Chief have standard gear.

Round 4: Po vs. Batman, Cap, and Chief. Same gear as Round 2. They fight on a city street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apocalypse vs. Krillin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 03:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my [last Apocalypse thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/31jnhc/aquaman_vs_apocalypse/) was a bit of a mismatch. How would he do against Krillin?

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

EoS and 616. If EoS is a stomp for Krillin, use the point that it would be the most even.

Bonus: Who is the strongest DBZ character Apocalypse could defeat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krillin vs. Frieza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Krillin is at his peak strength. Frieza is from the Namek Saga.

Round 1: First Form Frieza.

Round 2: Second Form Frieza.

Round 3: Third Form Frieza.

Round 4: Final Form Frieza 5% Power.

Krillin and Frieza remember who each other are and remember their last fight. Krillin is pissed off at being impaled/blown up and Frieza is pissed off about his tail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman vs. Firelord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 00:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The battle takes place in deep space.

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

Bonus: Batman vs. Firelord and Spider-Man vs. Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE Hacker vs. Ultron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Respect Ultron](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2xvj89/respect_ultron/)

[*The* Hacker's Wiki Page](http://cyberchase.wikia.com/wiki/Hacker)

Fight to the death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aquaman vs. Apocalypse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 21:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Respect Aquaman](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/29b5wf/respect_aquaman/)

[Respect Apocalypse](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2b6z1s/respect_en_sabah_nur_apocalypse/)

616/N52

Round 1: In-character. They fight on a beach.

Round 2: In-character. They fight in Death Valley.

Round 3: In-character. They fight in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean.

Round 4: Bloodlusted. They start in Shamu Stadium of Sea World Orlando. Apocalypse starts in the stands and Aquaman starts in the water. The fight can spread throughout all of Sea World, but they cannot leave the park. There are no animals present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Iron Giant vs. Oozaru Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIG is in his battle mode.

Round 1: TIG vs. Goku (Oozaru that killed Gohan).

Round 2: TIG vs. Goku (Oozaru at Pilaf's castle). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flash vs. Spaceball One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 00:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a 10 Quadrillion mile long race. 

Flash is PC Wally West running as fast as he can. 

Spaceball One is going Ludicrous Speed and has infinite fuel. 

No speed stealing or tractor beams or any of that. No affecting their opponent in any way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the weakest character who could tank Butterball? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman does a Fastball Special with Butterball as hard as he can. No phasing or dodging or blocking or any of that. They just need to take a Superman-thrown Butterball hitting them right in the chest. Who is the weakest who could do it? And since Butterball is being thrown, he is preoccupied, and is unable to be the one to tank the hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goten and Kid Trunks vs. The Powerpuff Girls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Powerpuff Girls are from their original series. Goten and Trunks are from BoG.

Round 1: Standard in-character fight.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

Round 3: Goten and Trunks can fuse and the PPGs get 1 year of prep. The Professor and all of their villains can help with the prep.

Bonus: Bulma vs. The Professor. They both have 1 week to create weapons for their fight to the death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gohan vs. Hal Jordan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC and Buu Saga.

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jar Jar Binks, Jar Jar Binks, Jar Jar Binks, and Jar Jar Binks play a game of Risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 02:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whosa would win? Howsa would it be goin down? What kinds of tacticsa would be usa?

If yousa be wanten, yousa can be changen da game to Diplomacy, or any other game yousa would feel to bein appropriatesa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jar Jar whosa be usen da Brass Knuckles vs. Jar Jar whosa be usen da Nunchaku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De Tradey Federation's Bombad Mechanik Army vs. The New Layout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 06:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can the 'Tradey Federation' restore the old layout before it's too late? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piccolo vs. Elsa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...at making clothes.

Who can make the best outfit?

Use direct feats only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gohan vs. Thor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mystic Gohan (Buu Saga)

Worthy Thor (616)

Round 1: In-character. 

Round 2: Bloodlusted. 

Fight takes place on an empty and indestructible DC Earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Base Goku vs. Frieza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 00:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In light of the new movie coming out, GOKU VS. FRIEZA!

Goku is as strong as he is at the end of the Buu Saga. He cannot use Super Saiyan or Kaio-ken.

Frieza is at his final form.

The fight takes place on an indestructible and empty Namek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanos vs. Mr. Crocker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanos has the IG.

Mr. Crocker has the Magic Muffin.

The fight takes place in deep space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest person Bruce Nolan (Bruce Almighty) can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as how he has a new [respect thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/30k3z0/respect_bruce_nolan_bruce_almighty/), who could Bruce defeat with all the powers of God?

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Respect Bruce Nolan (Bruce Almighty) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mild-mannered reporter Bruce Nolan had what he thought was an awful life. He had just been passed over for a promotion, had gotten fired from his job, and was mad at the world in general. But, after blaming God for all his problems, the Big Guy gave him a challenge: do the job better. And so, Bruce became Bruce Almighty, bestowed with all of the powers of God.

Bruce has complete control over God's powers, and can use them in any way he chooses, with 2 rules: He cannot tell anyone that he is God, and he cannot mess with free will. Bruce's new divine powers gave him a wide array of abilities, including...

**High-tier matter manipulation**:

1. [Erase clouds from existence with a wave of his hand](https://youtu.be/3c6pDzrk2lA?t=74).

2. [Create and destroy stars instantly with only his fingers](https://youtu.be/3c6pDzrk2lA?t=114).

3. [Turn off lights with his breath](https://youtu.be/3c6pDzrk2lA?t=159).

4. [Destroy fire hydrants](https://youtu.be/3uX0wjl9PzM?t=10).

5. [Creates a spoon from inside his body](https://youtu.be/A23bzMN3vSg?t=87).

6. [Alters the text on a teleprompter](https://youtu.be/j1o9ZWqCnKk?t=47).

7. [Changes his crappy car into a new one](https://youtu.be/nhTupXSJkYQ?t=38).

8. [Changes water into wine](https://youtu.be/NRDK5GQlGss?t=3152).

**High-level telepathy**

1. [Can hear the prayers and desires of every person on Earth](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E_lPHU2QpeA).

**Teleportation**:

1. [Teleport his clothes and the clothes of a mannequin instantly](https://youtu.be/3uX0wjl9PzM?t=31).

2. [Teleports to his girlfriend's window](https://youtu.be/NRDK5GQlGss?t=4246).

3. [Teleports the dead body of a missing person into the ground](https://youtu.be/nhTupXSJkYQ?t=124).

4. [Makes a meteor crash into Earth](https://youtu.be/qxVSvdqGmow?t=144).

5. [Places 220lb of weed inside of a van](https://youtu.be/qxVSvdqGmow?t=36).

**Pyrokinesis**:

1. [Generate fire](https://youtu.be/3c6pDzrk2lA?t=154).

**Aerokinesis**:

1. [Generate gusts of wind](https://youtu.be/3uX0wjl9PzM?t=17).

**High-level telekinesis**:

1. [Moves cream and sugar into his hand](https://youtu.be/A23bzMN3vSg?t=62).

2. [Parts the tomato soup and causes a restaurant to shake](https://youtu.be/A23bzMN3vSg?t=126).

3. [Pulls in the moon](https://youtu.be/3c6pDzrk2lA?t=87).

4. [Moves every car to the side of the road during rush hour](https://youtu.be/nhTupXSJkYQ?t=66).

**Create life**:

1. [Creates a monkey inside of someone's rectum](https://youtu.be/3uX0wjl9PzM?t=94).

2. [Breathes a swarm of flies through his mouth](https://youtu.be/3uX0wjl9PzM?t=141).

3. [Creates a Colombian man and donkey to give him coffee](https://youtu.be/n0cG11lTS1E?t=97).

**Body manipulation**:

1. [Alter's his rival's voice during the news](https://youtu.be/j1o9ZWqCnKk?t=21).

2. [Gives his rival uncontrollable gas](https://youtu.be/j1o9ZWqCnKk?t=91).

3. [Makes him speak gibberish](https://youtu.be/j1o9ZWqCnKk?t=97).

4. [Gives his girlfriend an orgasm through sheer willpower](https://youtu.be/3c6pDzrk2lA?t=165).

5. [Change the number of fingers on someone's hand](https://youtu.be/bjAM2J_D4UY?t=136). (Note: Not demonstrated by Bruce, but falls under 'All of God's Powers).

6. [Makes his girlfriend's boobs grow](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aYM0SAcDZ0c).

**Reality warping**:

1. [Able to change the prayers of the entire world into physical objects](https://youtu.be/n0cG11lTS1E?t=12).

2. [Makes it so every prayer is answered 'Yes'](https://youtu.be/n0cG11lTS1E?t=171).

**Super-speed**:

1. [Types incredibly fast](https://youtu.be/n0cG11lTS1E?t=130).

**Walk on water**:

1. [Walks on water](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O5AVORrDRvY).

**Command over machinery**:

1. [His car starts at his command](https://youtu.be/uIVH8_JDP2I?t=22).

**Personality alteration**:

1. [Makes himself think that he is Clint Eastwood](https://youtu.be/uIVH8_JDP2I?t=38).

**Control over animals**:

1. [Commands the Butt-Monkey to 'return home'](https://youtu.be/pZ7QMrR81yc?t=129).

2. [Toilet trains his dog](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FR7Ma8BVzKM).

3. [Forces birds to send a message to his girlfriend](https://youtu.be/NRDK5GQlGss?t=3501).

**High-speed flight**:

1. [Flies from Buffalo to NYC and stands at the top of the Empire State Building](https://youtu.be/pZ7QMrR81yc?t=146).

**Weather manipulation**:

1. [Creates a thunderstorm](https://youtu.be/pZ7QMrR81yc?t=146).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galactimus, Eater of Planets vs. Galactus, Devourer of Worlds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 22:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Galactimus](http://fairlyoddparents.wikia.com/wiki/Galactimus)

They fight on an indestructible and empty Earth.

Bonus: [Mighty Mom and Dyno Dad](http://fairlyoddparents.wikia.com/wiki/Mighty_Mom_and_Dyno_Dad_(heroes\)) vs. Silver Surfer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speed Force vs. The Force vs. Power Cosmic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: You get to use 1 for the rest of your life. Which do you choose?

Round 2: The 3 gain human forms and fight. All bloodlusted. Who wins?

Round 3: Same as 3, but all of them fuse and fight against Toon Force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cosmo Cosma vs. Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Respect Cosmo](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2khxpk/respect_cosmo_cosma_fairly_odd_parents/)

[Respect Goku](http://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2dywir/respect_dbz_part_4_buu_arkbotg_final/)

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

Fight takes place on an empty and indestructible Marvel Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a Batman villain that Spider-Man couldn't defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC and 616.

Round 1: Random encounter.

Round 2: Villain gets 1 day of prep.

Round 3: Peter gets 1 day of prep.

Round 4: Both get 1 day of prep.

ANSWERS SO FAR: 

1. Clayface

2. Hugo Strange (with prep)

3. Poison Ivy (with prep)

4. Mr. Freeze

5. Ra's al Ghul (with prep)

6. Deathstroke

7. Solomon Grundy

8. Bane (with prep)

9. Superman

10. The Joker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Punisher with 1 week of prep vs. Batman with 1 hour of prep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is too one-sided either way, what is the most even amount of prep for both sides?

Round 1: In Gotham.

Round 2: In NYC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Spy Kids vs. Sharkboy and Lavagirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carmen and Juni Cortez face off against Sharkboy and Lavagirl.

Round 1: Random encounter on Floop's island.

Round 2: Random encounter in OSS HQ.

Round 3: The Spy Kids have 1 week of prep to fight SB and LG on Planet Drool.

Bonus: [Uncle Machete](http://gotchamovies.com/ul/photos/movie/o/725dc59d07dd7fa0cf3c421b16782ecf-sc.jpg) vs. [Robot George Lopez](http://hollywoodmomblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Screen-Shot-2013-09-11-at-2.57.34-PM.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venom Goku vs. Carnage Vegeta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh off of their defeat of Kid Buu, 2 symbiotes latch onto Goku and Vegeta! Who would win in a fight to the death? Fight takes place on an indestructible Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EoS Krillin vs. Frieza Saga Vegeta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 23:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

They fight on an empty and indestructible planet Namek.

EDIT: End of DBZ. No GT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai Jack vs. Batman, Captain America, and Master Chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 23:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all carry their standard equipment. The fight is in a forest and they are all in-character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avatar Wan vs. the New Team Avatar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 16:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Wan vs Asami.

Round 2: Wan vs. Opal.

Round 3: Wan vs. Mako.

Round 4: Wan vs. Bolin.

All of Team Avatar are EoS. Wan is from right after he defeated Vaatu. He is fused with Raava but cannot enter the Avatar State. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Cypher vs. Freddy Krueger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 16:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fight takes place in a 15 year old's mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dipper and Mabel vs. Phineas and Ferb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 22:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are each told that their universes will be destroyed if they do not win in a battle against 2 other children their age. Phineas and Ferb have one day to build something for the fight. Dipper and Mabel have access to all 3 journals and 1 day to gather any items or allies that the journals talk about. Any creatures or demons (gnomes, Bill Cypher, etc.) will cooperate with them for the battle. WHO WOULD WIN?

BONUS: Waddles vs. Perry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Disney air 2 episodes? [No Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 03:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Love God" aired in November. I originally thought that would be the midseason break, but now, after "Not What He Seems", the next episode won't air until Summer, and I've heard that described as the midseason break. What was the point of waiting a few months to air only 2 episodes before taking another several-month-long break? It would have made more sense (to me, at least) to just air these last 2 back in November/December and *then* take the break. Is it just Disney's weird airing schedule, or is there an actual reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avada Kedavra vs. Deadpool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would the killing curse be able to kill him for good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Marvel (Carol Danvers) vs. Iron Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know anything about Carol. Could she beat Iron Man? 616 for both.

Round 1: In-character. Current versions of each.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. Carol is at her strongest and Tony has his strongest suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloodlusted Flash vs. Odin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 00:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could Odin hit Flash? Does Flash have a way to put down Odin?

EDIT: I give it to Odin. He has time manipulation, which is basically Flash's kryptonite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making friends with walkers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 04:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daredevil vs. The Punisher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 03:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Random encounter.

Round 2: Each have 1 day of prep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flame Alchemist has gained mastery of the four elements. Who is the strongest person Colonel Roy MustAang can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 16:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manga Goku vs. Anime Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 06:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Katara vs. Zuko </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Book 1 Katara vs. Book 1 Zuko.

Round 2: Book 2 Katara vs. Book 2 Zuko.

Round 3: Book 3 Katara vs. Book 3 Zuko.

Round 4: Legend of Korra Katara vs. Legend of Korra Zuko.

BONUS: Bloodlusted fight. There is a full Moon and Sozin's Comet is there.

All fights take place in the Fire Nation Royal Courtyard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flash vs. The Z-Fighters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can the Flash (PC Wally West) defeat all of the EoS Z-Fighters?

Round 1: In-character. He fights each one one at a time.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. Flash fights every Z-Fighter at once.

Wally **does not have ki**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the weakest character who could solo the Harry Potter Wizarding World? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Azula (A:TLA) vs. Edward Elric (FMA:Brotherhood) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 00:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: In-character fight in the Colosseum. Azula is not crazy.

Round 2: Bloodlusted fight in an open field. Azula has the comet and Ed has a Philosopher's Stone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who could win against a bloodlusted version of themselves while fighting in-character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if that title sounds a little weird. What I'm basically asking is if someone could win in a fight against a bloodlusted version of themselves, but they remain fighting in-character the entire time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegeta vs. Hal Jordan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: SSJ2 Vegeta vs. PC Hal. In-character

Round 1.5: Same but bloodlusted.

Round 2: SSJ1 Vegeta vs. New 52 Hal. In-character.

Round 2.5: Same but bloodlusted.

All fights take place on an empty Marvel Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phineas and Ferb vs. Jimmy Neutron vs. Dexter, Boy Genius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 23:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are each told that their universes will be destroyed if they do not win a fight against 2 other teams of children who are as smart as they are. They have 1 week of prep to prepare for the fight and build their gear. They are all in-character but are willing to kill.

Dexter and Jimmy may ask ONE friend for aid from their own universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Azathoth vs. The Living Tribunal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I know next to nothing about Azathoth besides the fact that it's apparently some dark god ruler of the universe. Could it beat the LT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man vs. Various Street Levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 22:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spider-Man is **the** top of street level. He pretty much stomps any other street level hero. But, could this team beat him in a fight? 

1. Batman
2. The Punisher
3. Daredevil
4. Captain America
5. ~~Luke Cage~~
6. Nightwing
7. ~~Deathstroke~~
8. ~~Iron Fist~~
9. Wolverine
10. Deadpool

PC and 616 for all.

Round 1: Random encounter in NYC. In-character.

Round 2: Team Street Level gets 1 day of prep. At NYC and in-character.

Round 3: Random encounter. Bloodlusted. No prep in NYC.

If it's still a stomp for Spidey, add some other street levels. It it's a stomp for them, take some out.

EDIT: Remove Iron Fist, Luke Cage, and Deathstroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Powerpuff Girls vs. Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 14:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EoS for both. The fights take place on an indestructible Earth.

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanos vs. Doomsday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 19:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Random encounter.

Round 2: Thanos has 1 hour of prep.

Edit: Hunter/Prey Doomsday and 616 Thanos (no IG or HotU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gohan vs. Superman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 22:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This'll be fun.

ROUND 1: In-character.

ROUND 2: Bloodlusted.

They fight on an indestructible Earth.

Mystic Gohan and PC Superman. Superman **does not have Ki**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dexter and Jimmy Neutron have 10 years to prepare for the arrival of the Imperial Fleet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 02:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy and Dexter have just learned that the Imperial Navy (Star Wars) is heading towards Earth and intends to take it over! Can their combined brainpower create a defense strong enough to defeat them?

Round 1: 10 Star Destroyers.

Round 2: The Fleet from the Battle of Yavin (no Death Star). 

Round 3: The First Death Star.

Round 4: The Fleet from the Battle of Yavin (with Death Star).

Round 5: The Fleet at its height with both Death Stars.

A win for Jimmy and Dexter is either destroying the Fleet or forcing them to turn back. A win for the Empire is successfully invading and taking over the planet or destroying all defenses. The Death Stars *cannot* destroy the planet, but it can target any enemy ships. Jimmy and Dexter are not limited to space defenses (they can put extra defenses on the ground incase ships enter the atmosphere). Dexter and Jimmy have all of the resources and manpower they need (they will have people to fly any ships they make, etc.). Canon Star Wars only. Vader and the Emperor are not present.

EDIT: Jimmy cannot travel to Timmy Turner'a dimension to make wishes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2 thieves that broke into /u/Dat_Bass1's house vs. George Clooney and Brad Pitt from Ocean's 11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 12:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aang vs. Kratos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 02:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: No Avatar State. They start 100 yards apart in a field.

Round 2: Avatar State. They start 50 yards apart in the place where Aang fought Ozai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peak Yamcha vs. Frieza Saga Vegeta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 22:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegeta as he was when he was fighting 4th Form Frieza.

Yamcha as he was at the height of his power (Cell Saga?).

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest opponent Obi Wan could beat if he had infinite high ground? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 03:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Strange vs. Jorgen von Strangle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modern Strange.

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted.

Jorgen is not bound by Da Rules in either round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegeta vs. Superboy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 12:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, guys. Help me settle an argument I'm having with a friend. I say that Superboy (*NOT* Prime) could beat Vegeta. My reasoning is:

SSJ3 Goku  Superman

SSJ2 Vegeta = 1/4 of SSJ3 Goku

Superboy = 1/2 Superman

Superboy  2 SSJ2 Vegetas

He says that Vegeta's superior fighting skills would more than make up for the difference in power, but I'm not so sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Experiments (Lilo and Stitch) vs. The Z-Fighters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 02:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jumba has gone crazy(er), and has decided to unleash [all 628 experiments](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_experiments_from_Lilo_%26_Stitch) on DBZ Earth right after the Buu Saga, and they're destroying everything! Earth's only hope is the Z-Fighters.

The Z-Fighters include:

Goku, Gohan, Vegeta, Krillin, Majin Buu (Good), Piccolo, Yamcha, Tien, Chiaotzu, Videl, Kid Trunks, Goten, Android 18, Earth's Hero Mr. Satan.

Some examples of Experiments:

1. # 167: Frizzy. Can stop time.
2. #210: Retro. Renders technology useless with his tongue.
3. #300: Spooky. Shapeshifts into your worst fear.
4. #303: Amnesio. Erases people's memory.
5. #316: Morpholomew. Can transform organisms into any other organism.Only needs to see a picture of the target to transform them.
6. #321: Lighfoot. Can tapdance.
7. #502: Yang. Shoots lava from his back.
8. #604: Houdini. Can make himself and anything else disappear.
9. #606: Holio. Can create black holes.
10. #607: Launch. Can warp the fabric of space and time.
11. #610: Witch. Can possess other organisms and place them under her control.
12. #626: Stitch. Virtually indestructible (fireproof, bulletproof). Can think faster than a supercomputer. Able to lift objects 3000 times his own weight.

All experiments have 1 goal: Destroy the human race. Can the Z-Fighters stop them in time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MCU Captain America vs. 2 Smart Car Transformers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 01:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Games] Now that Spider-Man is in the MCU, it gives me hope that we can one day see this scene put to film. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 12:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America vs. Batmen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 03:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cap from the MCU is going up against the various live-action Batmen all at once, including:

Michael Keaton

Val Kilmer

George Clooney

Christian Bale

Round 1: The Batmen ambush Cap in a warehouse at night. They have 1 day of prep.

Round 2: The Batmen and Cap have a random encounter on the streets of Gotham at noon.

BONUS: Add Robin (Chris O'Donnel), Batgirl (Alicia Silverstone), and Robin (Joseph Gordon-Levitt) to any round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Xenomorph (Alien) vs. a Mimic (Edge of Tomorrow) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 04:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Standard Xenomorph vs. standard Mimic.

Round 2: Which species could conquer Earth faster?

Round 3: Queen Xenomorph vs. Alpha Mimic (no resets).

Round 4: How many resets would it take for a Mimic army to conquer and destroy the Xenomorph nest on LV-426? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire Lord Zuko vs. Pyro (616) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 02:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pyro has his flamethrowers.

Round 1: Agni Kai in the Fire Nation Royal Courtyard

Round 2: Bloodlusted fight to the death in an open field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suki and 5 Kyoshi Wariors vs. Batman with no armor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 02:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feats for Suki:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MuUbksGYPFI#t=45

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NqLW7D2P1HE#t=52

Feats for Kyoshi Warriors:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajweq2VWnhg

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sSM8HYQ1oh4

Use the Batman that you think would be the most even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avatar Aang vs. Roy Mustang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 01:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Random encounter. Aang can enter the Avatar State but does not start the fight in it.

Round 2: Both begin the fight knowing what the other can do. No prep and Aang can enter the Avatar State.

Round 3: Random encounter. Aang starts in the Avatar State and Mustang is pissed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Bloodmatch] Superman vs. Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freddy Krueger vs. Neo in a dream he's having while asleep in the Matrix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 23:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neo decides to take a quick nap inside the Matrix after a long day of freeing humans and beating up agents. Unfortunately for him, Freddy Krueger is in the Matrix, and has named Neo his next victim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A united modern-day Earth vs. Raditz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 02:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we knew as a species that Raditz would arrive in a spaceship one month before he arrived, would we be able to defeat him before he killed every human? Assume all world leaders will work together and each have a copy of the DBZ anime and manga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman 10 Billion vs. SSJ3 Goku^4294967296 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 23:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Superman 10 Billion](http://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/2getf6/superman_has_been_in_the_sun_for_10_billion_years/ckiiu7z)

[SSJ3 Goku^4294967296](http://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/29er5n/which_battle_would_change_the_most_if_we_switched/cik8o86)

The fight takes place in our universe. If this universe gets destroyed by the fight, both combatants are instantly transported to another universe identical to ours. It is a fight to the death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superboy-Prime vs. Odin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kuvira and Baatar Jr. vs. The Elric Brothers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 18:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kuvira learns that the Elric brothers have become a threat to her empire and decides to try and take them out.

Round 1: Kuvira vs. Edward. In-character fight in a junkyard. There is plenty of earth and metal around.

Round 1.5: Same but Al instead of Edward.

Round 2: Kuvira and Baatar Jr. in a mech suit vs. Edward and Al. Same location.

Round 3: Baatar Jr. in a mech vs Al. Fight takes place in a forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans vs. Mutants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally fed up with each other, the humans and mutants of Marvel 616 Earth decide to simultaneously declare all out war on each other in a war of extermination. Omega-Level Mutants (ie Franklin Richards) are not included, and heroes and villains will work together, and the world governments have all united against the mutant menace.

Round 1: Humans vs. Mutants. All other superheroes on Earth who are not mutants (Spider-Man, Fantastic Four, Iron Man etc.) are neutral.

Round 2: Humans vs. Mutants. All other superheroes on Earth side with humanity.

Round 3: Humans vs. Mutants. All other superheroes on Earth side with the mutants.

Rounds 4-6: Same as 1-3 but *with* Omega-Levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if the Speaker of the House does not invite the President to speak for the State of the Union Address? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 23:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the President is not allowed in the House unless he is invited, so every year the Speaker sends him formal letter to invite him to speak so he can give the SotUA. But what if one year he didn't invite the President? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Krillin vs. Iceman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fight takes place on an abandoned Earth. 616 Iceman and end of DBZ Krillin.

Round 1: In-character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DBZ] Why is King Kai so weak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King Kai is supposed to pretty much be the *god* of an entire section of the universe. Why then, is he so weak? Even Nappa was more powerful than him. How can he be expected to do his job if he's weaker than some of the weakest beings in the universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superboy-Prime vs. Vegeto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 21:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Vegeto can only stay in base form.

Round 2: Vegeto starts in base but can go SSJ.

Round 3: Bloodlusted. Vegeto starts in SSJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegeta vs. Chiaotzu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 18:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...at blowing themselves up.

Round 1: Whose self-destruct was more emotional for the viewers?

Round 2: Whose self-destruct was more emotional for the characters?

Round 3: Whose self-destruct actually did something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ginyu Force vs. DCAU Justice League </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 01:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DCAU Justice League consists of:

Batman

Flash (Wally West)

Green Lantern (John Stewart)

Wonder Woman

Superman

Martian Manhunter

The Ginyu Force consists of:

Captain Ginyu

Recoome

Jeice

Burter

Guldo

Round 1: In-character battle on an abandoned Earth.

Round 2: Bloodlusted battle on Namek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hulk vs. Raditz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 22:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Make it MCU Hulk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goku vs. 2 Vegetas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 04:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The battle takes place on an indestructible and uninhabited version of DBZ Earth. The Vegetas will work together but CANNOT fuse in any way. Goku and the Vegetas are from the end of the Buu Saga.

Round 1: Base Goku vs. Base Vegetas.

Round 2: SSJ Goku vs. SSJ Vegetas.

Round 3:  SSJ2 Goku vs. SSJ2 Vegetas.

Round 4: SSJ3 Goku vs. SSJ2 Vegetas.

Bonus: Same as round 4 but Goku accidentally kills Bulma in front of the Vegetas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toph (A:TLA) vs. Terra (Teen Titans Animated Series) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 01:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: First appearance Terra vs. First appearance Toph. Battle takes place in an open field.

Round 2: Terra pre-suit vs. Toph pre-metalbending. Battle takes place in Jump City.

Round 3: Terra with the suit vs. Toph with metalbending. Battle takes place in Republic City.

Round 4: Bloodlusted Terra with suit vs. bloodlusted Toph with metalbending. Battle takes place where Aang fought Ozai in the Avatar finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanos vs. Buuhan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanos does NOT have access to the Infinity Gauntlet or any Infinity Gems.

Round 1: Buuhan wants to fight Thanos to become even more powerful. Thanos learns he is coming and has the entire DBZ anime series to learn from and has 1 week of prep before Buuhan arrives. Buuhan *will* attempt to absorb Thanos during the fight if he is losing.

Round 1a: Same but Buuhan will not attempt to absorb Thanos.

Round 2: Random encounter. Buuhan will not attempt to absorb Thanos.

Round 2a: Random encounter Buuhan *will* attempt to absorb Thanos if he is losing.

Round 3: Thanos learns of the threat Buuhan poses and decides to take action and destroy him. He has access to the entire DBZ anime and has 1 week of prep. Buuhan does not know he is coming but will attempt to absorb him.

BONUS: Thanos with 3 days of prep vs. SSJ Vegeto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King Kamehameha launches a Kamehameha while standing on the back of a turtle in a tsunami. Who is the strongest character he can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 18:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [King Kamehameha](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kamehameha_I) launches the turtle destruction wave on a turtle on a destruction wave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Satan (Hercule) receives 1 week of training from each of the Z-Fighters. Who is the strongest person he can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 20:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gets 1 week of training from every character in this order, and gets 1 day of rest in between.

Videl

Kid Pan

Master Roshi

Korin

Chiaotzu

Dende

Yajirobe

Mr. Popo

King Kai

Yamcha

Tien

Krillin

Android 18

Goten

Kid Trunks

Piccolo

Majin Buu

Uub

Future Trunks

Gohan

Vegeta

Goku

Who is the strongest character he can defeat after training with these masters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultron vs Android 18 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Standard Ultron (if there is one?) vs first-appearance Android 18.

Round 2: Most powerful version of Ultron vs strongest Android 18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sulley vs. Chewbacca </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 02:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: In-character fight.

Round 2: Chewbacca accidentally steps on Boo's head and kills her so Sulley is bloodlusted.

Round 3: Sulley defeats Chewbacca in getting the Scare Record so Chewbacca is bloodlusted.

Bonus 1: Sulley gets Mike's help and Chewbacca gets C-3PO tied to his back for help.

Bonus 2: Who could fill the most scare canisters in 15 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aang vs Harry Potter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 23:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry is right after he defeated Voldemort and Aang is right after he defeated the Fire Lord.

Round 1: In-character in the Hogwarts Courtyard. No Avatar State.

Round 2: In-character in Wulong Forest. No Avatar State.

Round 3: In-character on a beach. Avatar State is allowed.

BONUS:

1. Adult Harry vs Adult Aang. Both are bloodlusted and it takes place at the Pyramids of Giza.

2. Team Avatar (Aang, Katara, Sokka, Toph, Zuko, Suki) vs Dumbledore's Army (Harry, Ron, Hermione, Luna, Neville, Ginny). In-character in the Department of Mysteries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ATLA] Just found this awesome Toph vs Azula GIF. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 20:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Yakko, Wakko and Dot annoy Galactus so much that he abandons Earth without devouring it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 21:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Irwin vs Killer Croc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 00:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Irwin has heard reports of a giant talking crocodile running around Australia, and decides to take action.

Round 1: Irwin must incap Killer Croc for at least 3 minutes to film him up-close for *The Crocodile Hunter*.

Round 2: Iriwn must hand-feed Killer Croc 2 steaks in the [Crocoseum](http://static.squarespace.com/static/516269ece4b0f29c92669e6e/517df6b5e4b02921d70dfe42/517df6b6e4b077614f16024a/1367209662913/australia-zoo-crocoseum-sunshine-coast1.jpg) in front of a live audience.

Round 2.5: Same as Round 2 but he has a [baby in one hand](http://bigredfury.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/Steve-Irwin-Baby.jpg).

Round 3: Irwin must track down and capture Killer Croc to put him in a new exhibit at the Australia Zoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest team that the students of Sky High could beat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the Disney movie. The team consists of:

**Will Stronghold**: Super strength and flight.

**Layla**: Control over plant life.

**Warren Peace**: Pyrokinesis.

**Ethan**: Can "melt" and turn his body into a fluid.

**Majenta**: Can shapeshift into a guinea pig.

**Zach**: Can glow in the dark.

BONUS: The entire school and staff (named characters only) team up. Who can they beat? These include:

**The Commander**: Super strength and invulnerability.

**Jetstream**: Flight.

**Royal Pain**: Technopathy.

**Bruce Campbell**: Can release sonic waves from his mouth. 

**Lash**: Elasticity.

**Speed**: Super speed.

**Penny**: Can duplicate herself.

**Principal Powers**: Can turn into a ball of energy to travel at high speeds.

**Nurse Spex**: X-ray vision.

**Professor Medulla**: Genius-level intellect.

**Larry**: Can transform into a giant rock monster.

**Ron Wilson: Bus Driver**: Can grow to massive sizes.

**Stitches/All-American Boy**: No known powers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] When I see my sister studying for SATs when I've already been accepted to college. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 04:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [LoK B4] When Mike and Bryan say they want to work on other projects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 00:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gamora vs. Captain America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 00:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both MCU

Round 1: Hand-to-hand.

Round 2: Gamora gets her knife and Cap gets his shield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kuvira (LoK) vs Magneto (X-Men First Class) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 21:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> End of series Kuvira vs X-Men First Class movie Magneto. They start 100 yards away each round.

Round 1: [The Fire Nation Royal courtyard](http://media.carddit.com/a/tl0FKN39M.jpg).

Round 2: [Detroit](http://images.fineartamerica.com/images-medium-large/detroit-abandoned-buildings-joe-gee.jpg).

BONUS: Kuvira gets her Colossus. They start 1000 yards away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gypsy Danger (Pacific Rim) vs Kuvira's Colossus (LoK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 04:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> POSSIBLE KORRA FINALE SPOILERS BELOW

The Colossus is fully manned and the Gypsy Danger is in prime condition.

They start in an open field 1000 yards away from each other, and metalbending soldiers (besides Kuvira) may exit the Colossus to fight on the ground at any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [B4E13] Makorra shippers be like... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai Jack vs Deathstroke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 04:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deathstroke has been hired by Aku to assassinate Jack.

Round 1: Jack has no warning.

Round 2: Jack knows that Aku has hired Deathstroke, but he has no idea when or where he will attack.

Round 3: Jack knows Deathstroke's plan exactly and tries to take him out before he can strike.

Use EoS Jack and New 52 Deathstroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Spoilers] Now that it's over, what are some of your favorite (or least favorite) theories that didn't come true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 03:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yajirobe (DBZ) vs Samurai Jack (Samurai Jack) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 23:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Who is the better swordsman?

Round 2: In-character fight.

Round 3: Bloodlusted fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Grinch gets a power ring powered by hatred of Christmas. Who's the strongest character he can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 21:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toph (End of A:TLA) vs Daredevil (616) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 06:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: In-character random encounter. Takes place in Ba Sing Se.

Round 2: In-character random encounter. Takes place in New York City.

Round 3: Bloodlusted random encounter. Takes place in an open field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alexander the Great, Julius Caesar, Genghis Khan, and Napoleon all play a game of Jumanji. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 23:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All standard rules apply. A death of one of the players counts as a loss for the remaining ones. They begin playing in modern-day suburban America. They are each equipped with the standard combat equipment of each of their respective armies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if all of the Papal States were annexed during the unification of Italy, and the current Vatican City was not allowed to exist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lion vs. Tuna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 02:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Fight takes place near a river or some sort of fresh water source.

Round 2: Fight takes place off the coast of South Africa. There are 20-foot waves and the tuna has his 20-30 friends.

Round 3. Tuna and friends construct a breathing apparatus with kelp. They stalk the lion's pride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Marvel] Why doesn't Galactus just eat stars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 23:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he needs energy to create the next universe, why doesn't he just eat stars? They have a lot more energy than planets, there are more of them, and most of them don't have civilizations that he has to destroy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danny Phantom vs Martian Manhunter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 22:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> End of series Danny vs DCAU Manhunter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman Beyond [DCAU] vs Iron Man [MCU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 05:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Episode 1 Terry vs *Iron Man* Tony.

Round 2: End of series Terry vs *Avengers* Tony.

Round 3: Adult Terry vs *Iron Man 3* Tony.

BONUS: Future Bruce Wayne in the Beyond suit vs Tony in the Mark 1 suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crash Bandicoot [PS1] vs Spyro the Dragon [PS1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Book 4] Does anybody else sometimes remember that Junior is Toph's grandson and then die a little inside? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 01:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walter White at cooking a 3 course meal vs. Gordon Ramsay at cooking blue meth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 21:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team Avatar vs. the Teen Titans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 23:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Team Avatar from the end of their series vs the Teen Titans from the end of their series. The teams consist of Aang, Katara, Sokka, Toph, and Zuko vs. Robin, Beast Boy, Cyborg, Starfire, and Raven.

**Round 1**: In character. They have no prior knowledge of each other. No Avatar State or Demon Raven.

**Round 1.5**: Same as Round 1 but with Avatar State and Demon Raven.

**Round 2**: Team Avatar plans to fight the Titans. The Titans don't know they are coming.

**Round 3**: The Titans plan to fight Team Avatar. Team Avatar doesn't know they are coming.

**Round 4**: Both teams plan to fight each other.

**Round 5**: Both teams are bloodlusted. It is a full moon and they have no prior knowledge of each other. Full access to Avatar State and Demon Raven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aang [A:TLA] vs. Raven [Teen Titans cartoon] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 13:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both as strong as they are at the end of their respective series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DC] What are Batman's contingency plans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 06:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that Batman has a plan for every current and former member of the Justice League, just in case they go rogue. What exactly are the plans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loki [Son of the Mask] vs Loki [MCU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 22:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my little sister asks for help with her chemistry homework after I took the class 2 years ago. [GIF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 04:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] Me whenever we do experiments in Physics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 21:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your teacher bumps your grade up 0.05% to give you an A for the quarter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 02:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aang vs Kratos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 21:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Normal fight. Both are in character and there is no Avatar State for Aang.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. Both at their strongest. Aang has the Avatar State. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
