<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6412</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 08:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trey Parker has a team of writers even though he is solely credited (not that there's anything wrong with that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has any one person ever both written AND directed a single episode of an animated series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 09:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If J.J. wants to get it right, this is the thirty-six seconds he should focus on re-creating... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 06:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 19:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I bought the Xbox 1 at GameStop (then EB), salesman told me I absolutely needed a memory card -_- And though I was going to get it anyway, he secured the sale by telling me Microsoft was in the process of creating a disc that would make the Xbox backwards compatible with Dreamcast games (I had mentioned I owned a DC). As far as I know, EB didn't pay their employees any form of commission, so it's possible that when it comes to the memory card, he was just an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 07:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I would come out in just five years... also that the freeing feeling of a 22 year weight on your shoulders being lifted would only last a week or two... life would still suck :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been quite some time since I've seen a "Hitler reacts" vid that hit so close to home... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 08:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Horrendous Space KABLOOIE! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 09:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 10:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still feel like crying anytime I watch the Where The Wild Things Are trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 10:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The path to heaven runs through miles of clouded hell..."
-Imagine Dragons... heard this song for the first time coming back from Florida after my dad died this summer... still chokes me up when I hear it and I'm alone (especially their acoustic version). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 20:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awful. Especially at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
