<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too weird to live, and too rare to die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 17:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized this Hunter S. Thompson quote perfectly describes SWG for me. Maybe this is unrealistic or overly romanticized, but I can't help but feel like we'll never see a game like this again. 

I am actually hoping you all will tell me I'm wrong about that, and why. 

"There he goes. One of God's own prototypes. A high-powered mutant of some kind never even considered for mass production. Too weird to live, and too rare to die."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 18:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 06:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those questions where if you have to ask it, it shows that there is a deeper problem at hand and therefore a more important question you should be asking. 

In my opinion, your question seems to show a lack of respect and value for yourself, your space, and your safety. 

 As others have said, if someone is willing to assault you, they are certainly willing to do a lot worse. Predators test boundaries to see how far they can go. In the moment, what you should do is probably run.

That being said, you also need a longer term solution for your deeper problem of self respect. I suggest you find a gym and start training Brazilian jujitsu. Not just for self defense, but for the culture of respect, comfort in your space, etc.  It's hard to describe and others have done so more elegantly, but I hope you'll try it for yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 21:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope to get to the truly advanced stages of the disease in which my delicate palate can only support free-range kopi luwak, artisanally brewed by the very civets that excreted the beans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 21:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super interesting - I had no idea. Thanks! The rest of my diet is usually organic and paleo anyway, so might as well make this switch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 21:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also thought it was psychosomatic. Now that I think about it, I think one of the big factors is freshness. 

When I buy good coffee, it's from respected local roasters and generally is less than a week from the roast. I always drink it within two weeks. 

When I buy bad coffee, who knows how old that stuff is. The strength of the "stale" smell seems to correlate with how sick I feel afterward. Dunkin Donuts is pretty bad. But then I drank a metric shit-ton of Tim Hortons coffee on my last trip to Canada and felt fine. So maybe they have faster turnover. 

EDIT: I think the smell/flavor I'm thinking of is Rio/Rioy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lower-end coffee makes me sick, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 19:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I figured you would be the experts on this. I was hoping you could explain why lower-end coffee makes me feel sick to my stomach and headachy. 

At first I thought it was the caffeine content, but after lots of trial and error I've found that low-quality coffee makes me feel ill even if it's decaf. 

Then I thought it might be the preparation method, so I tried some controlled experiments only varying the type of coffee (even down to the same grind, etc.), and the cheap stuff consistently makes me feel sick. More than that, I can almost smell the staleness of the coffee in my sweat after drinking it. 

I've seen the bulletproof coffee conspiracy theories about mycotoxins or whatever and find them highly suspect... in my case it's probably something more mundane. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 18:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha this video never gets old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 18:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh thank you for this! Totally makes sense. I assume you mean too low on his lapel, which would give too much slack for me to finish the choke, allowing him just enough wiggle room to turn "against" the choke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 14:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry this is not going to be a very interesting answer.  Basically, I fucked up a long time ago in each of these cases and lost my pant grip on his near leg. That allowed him to get to his knees and come toward me, despite my having the cross collar grip which theoretically should be choking him more as he tried to stack (going the "wrong way" instead of unwinding the choke). 

My other mistake was not being able to stomp my foot in the crook of his far arm to trap it and use it as a lever to sit myself up away from the stack, which I'm normally able to do. 

Having lost the pant grip and far arm trap, I transitioned (correctly I think) to controlling his near arm instead, but I should have realized that if I wasn't finishing the choke from here, controlling the near arm wouldnt help because he wasn't trying to spin "the right way" away correctly anyway. It was always against very large dudes with strong necks that my arm alone is not going to finish. 

So from here, he is out of the bow and arrow, so when I am getting rolled up and stacked, I will either transition to an armbar or take my top knee and kick him in the back with it, which spins me from the perpendicular bow and arrow threat back to a more traditional parallel back mount, where I can start again. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 00:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed - your default should be to try to plant your outside foot and shrimp back to face him, if at all possible. If that fails, go for what I suggested above with deep half. 

Your top arm is key to defending this position. If you can get it inside his legs, you can use it to pull and scoot yourself into deep half. But be careful not to use this as a crutch rather than developing good hip movement - try to move your hips and face him first. If that fails, try deep half. 

The other reason your top arm is key: When I am on top in this position, I'll grab the sleeve of his top arm and pin it to the mat with my arm locked out (all my weight in it). Then I'll reach around his neck and get a cross-collar grip, and then I can easily roll to his back with one free hook already in (the leg that was in his half guard). 

This is because, as Kintanon said, he's basically on your back at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explanation really clicked with me, thanks. I have relatively short legs, so not letting my thighs break the perpendicular plane is key for me with the triangle as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move like a bag of water. Or better, mercury. 

When I pass the guard or maintain top position, I basically "ooze" through the available space (while maintaining good spinal posture, of course). So I am mobile and heavy at the same time. 

If there's a small space I need to get to, I make myself small and position myself so that my weight will pull me into that space. If I have to move, I make him carry my weight while I move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted - good question. This is a very bad position indeed. 

For me it depends whether my top arm is safe or isolated. If your top arm is buried and safe, you can transition to deep half from here to salvage the situation. Hard to explain, but look up deep half videos and youll find a relevant entry. 

If your top arm is isolated or your neck is caught, you're in bad shape for sure. I'm interested in seeing other people's ideas on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defending the stack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, let me start with a bit of a circlejerk by saying you've been a great resource for answering deeper questions about technique and principles. Sometimes your answers are better than those I get from world-class BB instructors. Thanks for taking the time to share your insight. 

My question is about getting stacked when going for submissions. How do you guys deal with it? For example, due to the stack I have lately had issues finishing the straight armbar from guard, the triangle, and sometimes even the bow and arrow. 

I give those examples because they all require me to cut an angle in the same way, which is supposed to prevent the stack, but lately has not been working for me on more skilled opponents. 

Here's what I know I should be doing:

-Shoulder and head walking back to extend my spine

-Popping my hips into extension to make my legs heavy and prevent the crunch

-Framing with my hands to keep his weight off

-Cutting an angle to one side or another to disrupt his base

Context-specific examples: 

-For the bow and arrow and belly-up straight armbar I always control the near leg to theoretically prevent him from getting back to his knees, but doesnt always work for me

-For the triangle, I underhook his free arm or near leg to cut an angle which theoretically should prevent the stack, but doesnt always work for me

TL;DR: What do you do to prevent the stack? How do you recover if you get stacked? Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 21:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a lot nicer than what I was going to say, but the spirit is the same. Listen to this man (or lady). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 21:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Also - it's not just the stacking motion. It looks like he's going for the technique where you grab their belt and flip them to turtle. I've always felt that technique is just unnecessarily dangerous and wondered why it's legal at all levels when things like leg locks aren't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 22:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I can see how the transition to bow and arrow will be very natural going that way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 22:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when I was a white belt I had a world champ as a professor. I couldn't train very consistently at the time, he was often off giving seminars elsewhere, and it was a pretty big gym. So I figured he didn't even know my name, much less anything about my particular strengths and weaknesses. 

One day I'm training with a senior blue belt and the guy is trying something on me, like a basic cross choke, and I just keep posturing out. My professor goes "are you kidding? he's way too sharp and his posture is too good. you'll never catch him with that."

An even better compliment: as a white belt, the browns and purples at my gym would specifically seek me out as a training partner in their week before competing because they knew I would provide a decent challenge without spazzing out and injuring them before the tournament.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 22:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhh I get it now. Thanks for taking the time to draw that! I will definitely be trying this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 21:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice. any chance you can post a picture or video? it sounds like your top hook is then "behind" his knee in this case?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 21:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't sweat it - it's only instinct. 

Over time, you'll be able to overcome your instincts as you develop the body awareness that enables you to recognize when you're really in danger vs. not. 

For example: maybe I'm really uncomfortable in a position, but I know that I'm not in "real" danger because I'm not yet getting the tunnel vision that is the precursor to going out. This allows me to avoid panicking so I can concentrate on waiting for him to give me an opening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this example and the mental/physical dichotomy. The mental aspect of cooking someone is very under-appreciated. I have that philosophy about grip breaks - if I am more patient and persistent with gripfighting (instead of trying to advance against his grips) I will eventually get him to give up and fight from a less advantageous situation. Insisting on the small advantages inch-by-inch maximizes my chance of improving my position vs. losing ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. I actually find it even more demoralizing when they move and flow with me like a wet blanket vs. when they just settle down in one place and smother me (because in the latter case I can usually make at least a little space)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 20:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree that it feels like bullying when it's being done to you. On the other hand (I'm just arguing semantics here) from the "chef's" point of view  it feels like the least bullying form of jujitsu, since I'm using my weight and skeletal structure to make things happen instead of yanking on their limbs. 

I think the big jerking movements that come from muscling things are part of the reason why I am a lot less concerned about getting injured by a more senior person. But you have to be prepared for both types of pressure, of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Hall vs. Maged Hammo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 20:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cooking" your opponent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 17:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard about this concept a lot lately and realized that it is something that really improved my top game when I incorporated it a while back. 

Have you guys heard of this? I'm going to do a pretty poor job explaining it. If I understand correctly, it means making slight modifications to your top pressure to suck the life out of your opponent while expending minimal effort of your own. It isn't just stalling because to me it tends to open up submissions better than trying to manhandle things. 

One example is when I am going for a crossface from side control. If he blocks my bicep, I will simply drag his blocking arm across his body, pinning his elbow to his chest, and dropping a lot of pressure on it. It gives people the impression of getting smothered even though their airway is still open. Part of it might be claustrophobia, or reducing your effective lung capacity... I don't know. 

I find that wrestlers are extremely good at this. Rather than just lock down on top of side control, they might walk clockwise from side to north/south to the other side, which seems to increase the pressure versus staying on one side and sinking down. Some judokas also have crazy pinning pressure in kesa gatame. 

TL;DR: What does it mean to "cook" your opponent? Do you guys have any tips on how to "cook" your opponent from different positions?

EDIT: Thanks for the awesome responses. Great stuff. 

Follow-up question: It seems to me like very good guys I train with (senior brown belts up to black) are able to subtly "cook" me even from the bottom. In other words, they never make big motions to escape or sweep. Instead, they just slowly adjust their position to make me feel less stable and comfortable on top until, all of a sudden, they've swept me or escaped. It's not exactly the same, but analogous. Any of you guys have examples of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd normally talk about principles but Kintanon and truthjusticeUSAway covered that beautifully. So I'll ask about your technique instead.

What kind of side control are you using? What kind of mount are you using? While the principles are the same regardless of the position, the execution varies a lot. Saulo makes this point on one of his DVDs from the opposite perspective of learning to escape - if the guy on top keeps changing his side control, the correct escape changes as well, so it's hard to learn any single escape if he keeps moving. 

So are you crossfacing or no? Are you using a kesa or reverse kesa style? Are you getting the underhook or losing it? Are you blocking his hip from the near side or far side? All makes a difference, and that's just from side control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, I know this deviates a bit from others' advice below, and I don't want to scare you or anything, but I've heard about this happening before. Turns out, all of the guys I know that backslid or plateaued in their first two years had the same rare neurodegenerative disease that slowly but irrevocably destroyed their muscular tonicity, coordination, proprioception, and procedural memory at the same time. I'm not saying you have the same thing, but if you don't start to improve again soon after consistent mat time, you should see a doctor to get that checked out. 

...JK. Same thing happens to me. Every time I come back from a layoff following an injury, might as well be my first class all over again. It's just a consequence of the sharp learning curve. Don't sweat it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 21:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great point. The same advice goes if you are that higher belt. 

When I was a white belt, the first time I submitted a purple belt it was with a technique that was relatively uncommon at the time (north/south choke, marcelo style). I didn't think this was anything special and immediately squared up to start again, but he actually stopped the roll to vent for 5 minutes about how he hadn't trained in a while, and how it's an illegitimate submission that nobody good or in shape would get caught with, etc. etc. 

His desire to explain it away just made him look bad, and our instructor was pissed at him for wasting all that training time to QQ about nothing.

The reality is, your belt doesn't give you magical powers. If you get caught in a compromising position, sometimes it doesn't matter how good you are or bad he is - you'll tap whether you're a new white belt off the street or you're roger gracie. It's not an existential threat and no explanation is needed. If he was really that threatened by tapping once, I don't even understand how he lasted long enough in the sport to get a purple belt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 19:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely love my Ring. Agreed on the nerdiness - the tengwar script in the trim and the quote inside are so baller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from the heel hook, I don't think I agree with most of these. 

I have seen #5 (breaking the twig) and a lot of silly stuff like it. It's still just a pain compliance move. Personally I think it's garbage, as it's super easy to bump most people off when they isometrically commit both hands in that position. 

Watch Calasans do his wristlock. THAT is scary.  

And what about neck cranks like the canopener? Face-bars? Jaw cranks?

How about slicers of all kinds? 

Another "scary" category is really obscure stuff that people don't know they should tap to, like hip locks (not banana split, think going in the opposite direction) and some of the weird shooto stuff like Erik Paulsen shows. 

If the criterion is commonality of injuries, what about the straight ankle lock? I've heard of more people getting injured from the straight ankle lock than anything else, because they think it's a pain move and dont realize that it's no different than a toe hold if done correctly. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 19:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! It was Rafa and Bill Cooper. Here's the link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2L0oXIHiPDg

6:40 onward is what you're looking for. 

I have actually done this from guard a couple times myself, as I tend to fish for that sprawl + cross-collar + sleeve grip that I learned from Ryan Hall as a nice setup to spin to the back. Rafa tries it here, but Bill defends. 

The idea, though, is that by holding his sleeve, and putting all your weight into it through the sprawl, you open up the space he would normally have defended by keeping his elbow jammed in his hip crease or flush to his side. So, through the sleeve grip, the force of your sprawl contributes to prying open his turtle guard, which then allows you to throw a hook or knee into that space more easily to take the back, clock choke (EDIT: and also, of course, your favorite crucifix to reverse omoplata), etc. When I do it right, feels super smooth and effortless. But then again, I'm not attempting it against Bill Cooper. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 17:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt -great timing on this video. I've been having issues controlling posture from bottom closed guard and looking for alternatives to just pushing and pulling. Then just this week watched a video of Rafa Mendes just opening guard, keeping his grips, standing up and sprawling on the guy - exactly like 3:33 in your video. Loved that part and the rest as well. 

Thanks; keep them coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, there are some techniques that people are just better defending against because they are very common (like the triangle and hip bump sweep).

What I see as "garbage" are the techniques that no skilled competitor will fall for, even if they've never seen it in action, because they are easily shut down if you use basic fundamentals. 

I personally love the gogoplata just for the fun of using it when people give it to me, but I know that my gogo is absolutely not a threat to anybody with decent posture and pressure - just due to the mechanics of the technique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great points. I actually think of the kimura as a position in itself - like a base of operations. It offers fantastic control that you can use to make some beautiful transitions. 

Just one example: I'm turtled and he's about to get my back. I overwrap his elbow and figure-4 and now I've got him in a kimura despite him being almost on my back. I escape my legs and now I'm top side control with a kimura. I sit on his head to make it a north/south kimura. Still can't get it, so I step over his head for a spinning straight armlock (keeping the kimura grip). Still can't get it and he stacks - I knee him in the back and get my hooks in - now I'm on his back with a kimura grip. 

mrpopenfresh: next time you can't finish it, think to yourself: instead of cranking this for a submission, can I use it to improve my position? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 18:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. 

HE'S RUNNING OUT OF AIR...AND TIME.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 18:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad to see you getting downvoted for truth. This is completely accurate. If you have to squeeze, it's inefficient by definition. The only time you really should squeeze is to give it the extra boost in competition, e.g. if time is running out. 

If you're squeezing all the time in class, you're learning it wrong. Just take the time to learn how to properly set it up and the squeeze will always be an option if you really need it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 17:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it was frames and distance control. I.e., if I can get an obstruction between me and my opponent to control distance without using strength, I will force him to deal with it (go around or try to smash through) which will give me openings to attack. 

If I don't effectively control distance, I'll constantly be defending and trying to recover from being smashed. 

But if I get overzealous with "pushing" to achieve distance control, I'll use a lot of strength and open myself up to attack (usually straight armbars). 

Finding that balance made a huge difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 17:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think about techniques. Think about reverse-engineering what they want and doing the opposite. 

1. They want to control your posture, so try posturing up. 
2. They want to avoid getting stacked (hips deep under you instead of square with your neck) so try pulling their hips under and stacking them. 
3. They want to control rotation and get at an angle by underhooking your free arm, so try rotating the opposite way. 
4. They want to get their thigh and your shoulder to form a triangle over your carotid arteries, so try going DEEPER into the choke to rotate the triangle around you, so that your carotids are open. 

Someone with a good triangle will stuff any obvious escape you try. But no matter how good they are, there are elements they need to meet to choke you. If you deny those elements, you wont get choked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FACT: BJJ is worthless against cephalopod mollucs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 14:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting aside on this: I haven't been on the scene all that long but I think this hasn't always been the case. Back in 2007 or 2008 I remember an instructor saying (with some surprise) that certain pro guys are starting to exclusively use a standing guard break - implying that, at that time, most guys broke the guard on the knees or used a mix of the two. 

I like neekz0r's explanation below for why it fell out of favor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 02:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much this. 

I would add that the quality of "MMA" classes can sometimes be suspect, depending on where you are. Most people I have talked to say that they had much better results training specific disciplines, e.g., BJJ plus pure wrestling, or BJJ plus pure kickboxing. 

"MMA Class" can sometimes be a mishmash of mediocre techniques by someone who knows one discipline well and only kind-of knows the other disciplines. But it can be good for learning very MMA-specialized techniques like how to do precise technical ground-n-pound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longer-cut rashguards that won't ride up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 02:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all - I am looking for a rashguard brand that has a slightly longer cut to the torso so it doesn't ride up as much from the bottom. 

I have a longish torso but shortish arms, so just getting a larger size wouldn't do it for me. E.g., I have a RVCA rashguard that is perfect in the arms but rides up a lot from the bottom. Ideally I'd like one that has enough material to tuck in a bit. 

Any ideas?

EDIT: Thanks for all the advice folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read the linked article yet, but I'm going to go out on a limb and say that Hemingway had more than 5 unusual habits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 16:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm with you. I actually don't care at all about budo. I'm turning the joke around to make fun of these guys. What I love to see is people who have this POV getting shamed by e.g., the sambo vet or MMA fighter with a BJJ white belt. 

I love the spectacular fails that take people down a peg and demonstrate that belts mean nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 16:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. If you're good and know you're good, what's the point? 

Only people who are not that good and have something to prove get excited about stomping people who suck. Or they're weird sadists who get off on dominating people. Hence Hannibal Lecter I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 14:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said in this post: http://www.reddit.com/r/bjj/comments/1jhizi/blue_belts/

"Your blue belts must not be very good if they get excited about tooling someone who doesn't even train yet. But maybe I'm misinterpreting your joke."

EDIT: People downvoting this, please feel free to share some tournament results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 14:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your blue belts must not be very good if they get excited about tooling someone who doesn't even train yet. But maybe I'm misinterpreting your joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
