<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1236</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 14:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 495 shows for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gangplank health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 13:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasnt it like 700 in lvl 1? or lolwiki is lying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It cancels katarina ultimate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 17:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It cancels katarina ultimate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wukong Ultimate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 16:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm.. how come that fiddle silence and fear doesnt cancel it? It litereally lost my game completly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thresh, Morde, Yorick are all bright, not too bright but not as dark as Vilemaws cave and still bend into the dark thingies. I just think Riot overkills with the blue things. Also, they ruin skins. Void Fizz is now Purple Boiled Fizz, Groovy Zilean is now Smoggy Zilean etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone with me? The new colors of new champions and icons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are so blue, neonish and modern. Like in my opinion Kalista is a bitch with led lamps and they are all different kinds of blue. Maokai is a tree. Trees are green and brownish, sometimes white and if really old and wet its grey. Well the new maokai he is colored like shit, new ability icons are again some blue-grey shit. This is a change that i would never like them to implement. Like seriosuly, why does everything need to be so dark and grey blue shit? Anyone feelin' then same? Like I hate this even more than the new dragon and smite changes. Let them implement the jungle and dragon but please add some colors to the game! PS: Karthus rework turned him to a blue folk aswell

**TL;DR**
Every new piece of art should not be grey-blue dark shit

EDIT: Title isn't properly spelled, should be just The colors of new champions and icons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 22:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completed 200 chat restrict games, guess what? 80 again and i hvae to play 75 games in 6 days to get the rewards.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to zen   chinese flute music. Helps me somehow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 20:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Void Fizz was completly removed and now its a 750 rp skin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 20:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the backgrounds are too simple, like dunno but like plain white blue oragne is kinda lame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AKALI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Draven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 21:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost 20 LP by dodgin yesterday since client was so laggy that i coudnt select a champion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 15:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riot isnt it the time to change flash icon? Riot isnt it the time to make the X look different on the window? Riot isnt the time  to change Sions face? Riot isnt it the time to blue buff icon? Riot isnt it the time to change the green button on the friends list? The cursor can be old but its sexy no need to change it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 12:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear it every day: report jungler didnt give me blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First before teamfights you gotta make your best to hit those spears, try to hit theese on squishy so you can force him/her back and get a 5v4 fight. Basically poke. in Teamfights pretty much you gotta like W E Q stuff and eventually flash out if you think you need to spear the bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 22:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately i have seen awesome trkFanboys actually! In Silver, litereally some of them know the game and can turn around every game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wierd glitch in Champion Select EUW (Not about the lagg) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 18:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, i had 40 seconds to pick. I hovered over udyr jarvan 4 and ezreal, then when i had 25 left i clicked j4 and didnt click lock-in button. Suddenly ezreal got locked in and i was forced to play ezreal jungle. Anybody experienced this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The slow was blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 20:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fizzerino and Yasuo since in enemy team they always good but my team is awfulerino </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Riot, can we keep some original splashes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 18:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want irelia's and leona's splash to stay as they are right now. we dont need those new ones that im not a fan of personally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got somebody, coulnt remove the guy from the list had to ignore him. The account was lvl 1000 and Challenger 2. THey litereally modificate the game aswell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 00:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 21:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is expansion tournament the challenger series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 00:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most unbalanced champion in the game and riot hasnt done any DAMAGE changes to her for ages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can make it so in a silver game i wouldnt have bronzers when enemy has golds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EUW]-[VERY Serious]-[Someone who smurfs in Silver] - Need some helperino carryrino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matchmaking made me not pay Rito a penny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im on EUW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than koreans, @Mister_Oink. I play until  a loss in a day aka 1 game. Im not kidding with this answer

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To gold: you cant ;to bronze: give your best in game, try and shine and you will lose more :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Chosen One, 25% WinRate forever Silver player, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost to my dream, 10%. Forever silver and bronze, i am in love with this division! Ask me anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 01:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 game losin streak. I hate fizz: most horrible laning phase in the game. SO hard to CS with the motherfucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not a smurf. Im looking for a smurfing duo partner who can help a little bit, carrying with 2 people is easier than 1 aka myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 01:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiddle game winning ultimates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 01:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just won a game as fiddle was 19/10 and carried my team with my ults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the thing is when i try to main a champ i kinda dont win with her :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fav champs are jayce and fiddle which can carry easily too but the thing is i get tired of champs easily, 5 games max straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why you think i make this shit  up? thats why I need help cause these scenarios happened too much for me since riot dislikes me for the 150 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I litereally need a smurfer duo partner to win or an elo boost to gold 5 then from there i will play it out myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im first pick liek 10% of the times LEL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell me: im 16-5 as Jayce. I got 300 CS at 35 minutes. We got 5/18 twitch, 120 farm at 35 minutes as well as shaco jungle with 60 CS and 5/9 and top laner riven as 8/19. They teamfight. When i clearly ping them to back off. Enemies has bot and top laner so fed. Still they fight. I cant win like that. That was the sitatation about 15 games in a row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its quite easy to lasthit as ahri and xerath aswell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean like lets say its 10 minutes and im 5-0 in my lane, at this time 90% of the times my other lanes including jungle are feeding. its the curse. + in silver jinx ahri are played alot. these champs in my team are autoloss. I haev never won a game with ahri in my team, Never.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean CSing with both akali and katarina is horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every game beginning: i calm down, i think what i need to do in order to win, i ward the shit out of my lane, win my lane, when i die i think why i died. suddenly you see enemy 20/0 bot lane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well if i get fed it means teammates will be de-fed and are destroyed in lane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you tihnk so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kat: too horrible laning phase as well as akali. dislike zed dont have talon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are diamond im silver dude and i cant win 1v5. i cant win 1v5 cant you understand, 5 champs do more dmg than 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i see how my decision making and CSing i 100x better than my teammates. I see how i make 100x less mistakes than my teammates. I know I dont deserve that elo. Anyway just got demoted agian, omw from Silver 2 to bronze I in 2 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant 1v5, enemies still do more DMG than 1 champion + CC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im the unlucky one. i hate to cry about it but its true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go top pick trynd let bot be 0/30* Last 5 games i playde trynd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need serious help, a diamond smurfer in EUW silver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need to win. Im at 22 game losin straek. I win my lane 90% of the time. But all of the other lanes are always horriblty feedingl I win about 25% of my games. I want to climb but riot is against it. Need somebody to help me. I can get them few kills but i cant leave CS. cant carry 1v5 either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EUW]-[Smurf in Silver]-[S]-[Very Serious]-[Every Role]-[Duo Q] Someone who smurfs in EUW and is kind enouhg to help me! (Matchmaking hates me!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 22:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 00:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anivia cause Q E combo 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 22:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's the more RP you buy the worst teams you will get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EUW]-[Smurf in Silver]-[S]-[Very Serious]-[Every Role]-[Duo Q] Someone who smurfs in EUW and is kind enouhg to help me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 22:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 22:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EUW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 21:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was at bronze 1. a friend made me silver 5 and from there i have climbed to silver 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 21:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im Silver 3 whos jumpin g between Silver 2 and silver 3. Would love to get to gold and the end Season but alone its impossbile for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need serious help, a Duo Partner who smurfs or something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 21:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0/12 botlane 5 games in a  row, last 5 times zed in my team-lose. Even if im 5/0 lane i cant roam 24/7. I need to CS and get objcetvies. Since matchmaking hates me and doesnt want me to climb i need some help from a smurfer duo partner. TeamRedditTeams doesnt give a shit. never geta good duo partner from there. EUW silver 3-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 22:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blitzcrank is my favorite, worst is zed: the sound and the animation is kinda  awful :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 21:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 21:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come their system is completly different than ours? Like how does it work? When I select China servers how should i be able to select Ionia, Zuan etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nop,  i dont have that problem. everytihng runs smoothlky for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one AA and i saw how my health bar was down for about 1200 health </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was at lvl 8-9-10 something there. not lvl 18^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not death recap, i saw how 1 auto attack and about 1200 from my health was down, im so fucking confused. like it must be some kind of modifictation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had Averice blade, 120-130 AD. I hadnt bought armor, i buidl triforce first. But still it isnt possbile to autoattack 3/4 of my health. I had giant belt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fiora hacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lvl 8-9 Fiora crit me with 1200 dmg, NO IM NOT CRYING OR MAKING THIS UP. How is that possible? No crit dmg runes, no crit chance runes e ven. This thing ruined my whole lane. He had averice blade when he critted 4/5 AA and one of them was 1200 to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear speed with E max is quite nice indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all my trying-to-mains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets focus on the words NA, AGAIN. Then lets remeber EUW, every week twice the serverinos were brokerino :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 23:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hire him eloboost to Bronze 1/2 where he can play against better players, have a bit of a hard time and learn there. Bronze 5 is impossible to get out of  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 17:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Place Where I play Zed ;:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 17:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 17:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played him a lot already too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actaully in silver he is free-elo since imo, he counters akali katarina vayne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I tell it once a game after 3 deaths straight in same spot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I can get enough IP fast. Missing 5 k :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played Sion already liek 20 games. First 5 ults i missed, other i've hit so i got good accuray but the first ult of mine was hilarious. Went for a mid lane gank and I ended up at enemy nexus turret dying :D:D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is seeing hallucinations like literally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell me a champion I should play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will play it like 50 games straight, jsut random i know right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 00:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He mechanics are quite bad at the moment and his voice is wierd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I wrecked a teeto in top, bot and mid were kinda winning in objectives too when they decided to throw, told them to stop getting caught and farm under turret and lets get a fight that we can snowball of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When 5 man is needed I wont go alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I carry a team literally 1v5? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 23:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Lucian player name, who had like 250+ lucian games was simply ,,Bikes'' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 22:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R.I.P Original lovely splashes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 23:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt really like AP soin since your W had long CD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 23:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You build: Shiv, PD, AS boots, Bork, Infity Edge and i woudl build BT. Then you go into teamfights with about 1000x extra health from E if you know how to farm well and just stun, toggle E, 3 hit an enemy. with utlimate you got like 128 something lifesteal, you crit as shit and you are kinda tanky, and heal as fuck too. In my opinion that was very op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 23:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 23:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> osu! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 22:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old sion with AD could 1v5 and 1 lifesteal item  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 22:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remove 2014, iv and win. even i can do these icons in photoshop lol. I mean tune the coloring, remove 2014 and replace it with IV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Xj9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 17:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 12:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 12:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in ranked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have played 28 games of my 30 last games on pruple side. 2 on blue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 12:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this Pando Media Booster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havent understood yet :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got a warning because i told a enemy varus that i report him for flaming teammates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 16:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, right now i got 80 chat restrict games, at 62, the game which i won my silver 2 prmos with, after that in lobby enemy team has a 0/8 Varus who flamed the shit out of this team and i say that dude stop flaming, the the guy flamed more i siad that reported np and suddenly a warning appears on my screen that i have been toxic. 100% sure only varus reported since i dont use my 15 messages in game for flaming. If i now get more chat restrict then im quite angry :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 23:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 22:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dislike thsoe new splashes, the Shaco Rape Face is good, i mean the portraits are good but the whole splash i dont enjoy. Akali one is great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played in PBE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S2 September i stared playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the global gold removes dragon for my point of view </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 3 was by far my favorite season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I have played PBE in these changes and i dislike them. Ok, the smite damage shower is interesting cool :D Also the S4 Icons are terrible. Like litereally, 5v5 Challenger looks maybe good but others are just made by some guy who was high and litereally just took a shit and they fell out of it. Season 3 Icons are very beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who completely HATES the Season 5 might-be-added things? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 14:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smite CD is 60 sec. 4 Machetes. Way too complicated. New jungle Camp bullshit. Dragon is useless, pointless atleast for me. I think Season 4 was completly fine, if the new SR comes I will mod myself back to the old one cause i cant change from that anymore. But the game is toooo complicated and if all of these chages will be in the game, I will not play in Season 5. I would be a osu! player instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 23:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why cant I play Teemo seriously? Like I litereally win lane everytime. Well something more: I have never won a game with jinx in my team. 50+ games. But at the same times I lose to half of the enemy jinxes. Today 2 of them got a pentakill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is the worst day of League in my life which leaded me to uninstall the game. Im making myself, or trying atleast not playing for 1 month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 23:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Endless glitches and bugs, Teemo Blind not applying to an enemy and he just crits me.  
2) 8 game losing streak, unlucky teamfights where, for real, 5 games the last teamfight every enemy was below 100 HP.  
3) Toxicity  
4) LP Gain and Loss  
5) Matchmaking  
I know it's useless to talk here since  you get downvoted to oblivion, but I think this was the worst day of League of me, and also the worst day of this year problably. In Real Life had some shit things too. 
And also, this ruined a bit too -  the new splashes are horrible, too detailed for a simplistic game. Jarvan 4, Rengar, Orianna, Akali had much better older splashes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I have a ward limit of 3,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I have a ward limit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok 30 can be enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets say i facecheck a random bush in jungle which is unused most of the times. I get caught. Im the carry and suddenly all the team follows and gtes aced. I called that braindeads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 22:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am happy if i have atleast 3 people who know when to do what and do not flame if someone dies. But </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no need for a 40game winstreak, you might couple of games too, after a 5+ winstreak usually my account starts getting you know which kind of player - toxic and llitereally player who should not be playing ranked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get replies in french, usually it is reporting me. Told a Syndra that your farm is horrible, go farm we are beihnd and got 4x reports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why am I the only one who realises that you should nto fight when 15+ kills behind? Why am i the onlyone that wont contest baron 3v5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for eloboost from Silver 3 - Gold 5, about 15 maximum. LP Gain: +15 max, -20 every time. Matchmaking hates me, you have to carry every single 40 etc. games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 21:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaco rework fuck off dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help modding a bit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi people! I would like to know if it's possible to change splash arts to the old ones, change health bars to season 3 ones, summoner icons. I really hate myself that I start to play every awesome game so late, like cs at 2009, LoL at preseason 4 so I'm kinda feeling i have been missing a lot out of league for some reason. no google answers ty, have been searching there for quite a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i lost about 25 to Silver IV from Silver 5. It was pure cancer, my MMR is shit so i lose about 20+ LP and earn 15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lookng for a cheap eloboost! Silver IV, You have to carry every game since matchmaking hates me, 13-18lp per game, 15 max to Gold 5 or Silver 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 21:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 18:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yyou can winwall poke with yasuo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farming with Katarina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Katarina is one of my favorite champions but im giving up on her since its impossible to lasthit in lane. You get poked down to 20% health everytime. How do you farm with her? Like winning lane with her is impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with replacing splashes with old ones! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 20:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello people! Since I absolutely hate the new caitlyn splash art and I prefer the old riven splash art and the icons and staff I would liek to know if it is possible to change the new riven splash and icons to the old ones and same with caitlyn. I would love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with replacing new splashes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 19:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello people!
Since I absolutely hate the new caitlyn splash art and I prefer the old riven splash art and the icons and staff I would liek to know if it is possible to change the new riven splash and icons to the old ones and same with caitlyn. I would love it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 16:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well then looking for a ,,friend'' who will duo with me who is a diamond smurf or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a cheap eloboost! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 15:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 02:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it doesnt work when the passive is not on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xin ult bug for so long. Sometimes it doesnt knockback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 19:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it doesnt knockback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 23:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> suht terane vend oled :D russia is cancer and should be nuked :D aga jah sesmttes et tsi ta on et nad seal jamavad pris korralikult ja nendega tuleks seal midagi teha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 14:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AP tristana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucian: Tons of Damage / Statik Shiv? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 23:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see pro players and high-elo player have moved away from triforce lucian and build statik shiv? Why is that? I personally build triforce cause sheen proc on lucian is simply amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 23:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pingtest.net/ speedtest.net? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 23:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 27 bo3 to silver 4, like literally i just felt that i want to uninstall that shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 01:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I find my main champion? Ive tried so much but i fail i fail and i get tired of that champ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
