<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9525</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 08:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give mana to whoever you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lion Aghs upgrade idea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 08:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep the aoe on the finger w/o aghs (maybe reduce the area), rescale the damage and cooldown. And give him the ability to drain his own mana to give allies mana like the pugna ult except with mana. It would increase his synergy with many spamming cores like enchantress who tend to run low on mana as the team fights go ahead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some day you will find that try hard enemy team that will run a tiny support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they can turn the ancient black dragons blue with the winter terrain, they can do this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely rtz.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 06:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dazzle: Think he's just a harmless support who just heals his allies for a little hp? 
Well, here comes the heal bomb 
Don't forget the mind numbingly frustrating shallow grave. Think you just got the jump on the carry? Think again. 
Ticks to -42 armour on his ult. Negative fucking 42 
Do you know what 42 is? 
THE ANSWER TO LIFE. 
Dazzle is life, not to mention love. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 06:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't the nothl realm in dazzle's lore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 05:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it retractable like how custom game instructions can be retracted to the side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singsing too busy trolling not-yet-6k players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Add an option to follow pro players so that we can watch their replays without having to search for them for hours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching pro players' pub replays goes a long way in improving our own game play. Volvo plisa give this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 06:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jake, you're a flower. GGWP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 04:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, IDK. I've already finished the manga. I don't really care. I feel bad for all the people who are waiting for canon episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last canon episode of the Naruto Shippuden anime was released in August 2015. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 07:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The experience of one of the best animes ever is being ruined by the studio's wish to keep the anime going for absolutely no reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tweeted to Noob from UA to make a video about this, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't sell items on the clone. 
You could do that in dota 1.
Not anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 15:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lina cosmetic 420blazeit confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dragon Lance should build into something like Mek builds into Guardian Greaves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 15:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't give good stats + wastes a slot. It would be much more viable if it built into something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 15:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. But you can't always be near a shop when your ult is off cd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 10:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could do that in dota1
Use ult, sell items for half price, repeat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 05:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wards, refresher orb and smoke don't work with the double. I checked after I posted this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arc warden support would be the most economical support ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 09:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would get 50% off on all consumables.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 05:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Yes, The International is the biggest tournament in Dota 2. Valve recently introduced the Majors system. Now, including TI, there will be 4 major tournaments organised by valve throughout the year. You can check those out. Teams qualify that through open qualifier matches for the Americas, Europe, SEA and China. Some teams are directly invited to participate in these tournaments based on their previous performances or standings in the world of pro dota2. 
2. There's no one best player or team in the pro Dota scene. You make up your own opinions as is the case with all other sports (as you well know, Dota is now a sport in itself). 
3. You'll get to see and understand all the strategies and playstyles of teams and individual players only by watching them play. Some rat, some play head on. Some slow the game down and outfarm their enemies. But the current meta favors huge team fights and taking advantages past those team fights. 
4. There are tons of analytical articles on gosugamers or joindota. You can check those out. Also, check out a channel called simply Dota. Roro gives us good analysis of the individual game play and helps us see where we can improve ourselves. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 04:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think of stacking neutrals when I see x:52 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice play though. Someone from that game might have submitted it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're in a NoobFromUA video, mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nerf shadow fiend. Take away the jungle advantage on radiant side and make the camps uphill like on dire side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 14:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we give the planet a temporary kick?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
