<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject130</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was attempted in Bollywood and I hated every minute of the fucking unoriginality (i was in minority though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vs, the best, top 5...throwing up (golum golum) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War poetry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lAXzqh9hLDA, covers a lot of cliches in terms of characters and who better than Steve Buscemi as the host ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pulp fiction is like that papa ketchup joke Mia tells, it's not funny, not subtle, it's not anything just the style and charm. I could rant about it hey but like people have already said, give it some time and watch it again. The main cast was great but the cameos from Harvey Keitel, Christopher Walken, Tim Roth kill me every time, great dialogues, great acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Payback, after which Mel wasn't the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey if number of movies delivered per year is the criterion I would say Daniel Day Lewis, but yeah I prefer his way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe similar to the big turnaround when Jamie's POV was introduced ? Do you think this POV manipulation will be the basis of climax, and some unanticipated twist ? I'd love to read that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 17:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a point, but since the rumor was wide spread so it is the same, I think it happened because they mutilated the dead in some way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah perfection my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I tried reading them together, I see the difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers Everything) Why overlapping chapters ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys so the first Samwell and Jon chapters in AFFC and ADWD respectively have a lot of common text/dialogues right ? Was that done just to give an idea of timeline or is there something more to it ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No ofcourse not, just that I agree in this context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 13:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that is very interesting, but now since he has decided to quit his recklessness and be honourable and all, I think he will fight/kill Tyrion irrespective of whether he hates him or not. I think how Tyrion feels about Jamie is equally interesting, what do you guys think ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The common people pray for rain, healthy children, and a summer that never ends. It is no matter to them if the high lords play their game of thrones, so long as they are left in peace. They never are. - Jorah Mormont to Daenerys Targaryen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ !! I'm actually shivering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How Coen Brothers always certainly put a certain southern character/narrator, its charming. How Tarantino always has one of the characters tell a really bizarre story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, wallpaper for Jorah the Andal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love his interviews, he is so passionate and makes you understand his POV so clearly, you know because he is never confused about what he wants to say and that same clarity appears in his movies, it's like solving a physics/maths problem when you understand every step you know...blah sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wild one, The fugitive kind for young Brando (Big thumbs up for streetcar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many times while watching I feel I'll get an epiphany that will change me, Most times just for fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remove the threat of violence and we are back to square one, don't you think that's how it went in the real world too, most dictatorships didn't last, something always comes back to bite them in the ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh ok smart girls making me feel stupid, what else is new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess, Dany and her dragons will bring the reckoning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey ! explain the joke, is it about stupid things posted on this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I haven't anything except asoiaf, but could you briefly say how Aegon's war was legitimate ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post, I think a lot of hatred for Frey's also stems from how they tied Grey Wind's head on Robb, and threw Catelyn Stark naked into the river. That kind of thing begs for vengeance not peace, maybe kill them and send their bones via silent sisters and folks will say ok it was war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 15:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That goes for violence in general, be it any of the five kings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 13:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the beauty I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 13:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 12:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sin City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw Qyburn and those kids, I remembered season 4 Wire, seeing those kids so fucked up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A redditor mentioned it a few days earlier,  the third eye (Bran, blood raven etc.) refers to butt hole usually, for me that's as real as it gets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see, I found this : http://awoiaf.westeros.org/index.php/Marillion#Game_of_Thrones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that movie, Juliette Lewis and Johnny Depp were great in that film. Everytime, I remember that "my knight in shimmering armor" line, I miss my own parents. Though, I don't understand why an actor when he plays someone with a disability (Daniel Day Lewis, Eddie Redmayne), he gets really a lot of attention and praise, I think it has also something to do with sympathy for the character played along with the acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool hand Luke when Luke's mother comes to visit him in prison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I only live for today. I'll show you just how fucked up that can be", I love that movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Min-sik Choi, Chan-wook Park...\m/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I didn't think of it this way, makes me miss a Stannis POV chapter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I get it, it's just really funny how he puts it in the post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the ultimate form of revenge, I do not know if It can get any uglier/beautiful than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the rest of the trilogy is good too and though there is a common theme of revenge they are different in many ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes without spoiling anything that's the best way to put it, maybe i can add that the painting will bring many twists along the way, and the final conclusion though I didn't fully understand it has a lot to do with the painting. Tell us what you think when you finish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want that chunk of meat dead too ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope they manage to salvage the wreck they made out of having Euron seem like a trailer trash uncle out for revenge because his niece/nephew stole a six pack of beer.

Lol Just so my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Euron is the greatest villain she and westeros will ever fight (I hope you read the forsaken, TWOW), and it has been discussed that Cersie might form an alliance with him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mountain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I can't help you but , from what you wrote your English seems very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is most guys would love to sleep with supermodels, and I agree all of them (including me) are big Hypocrites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for pointing this out, very interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simon Silvertongue was the one who knew about Shae and Tyrion, and tried to blackmail Tyrion, so he ordered Bronn to kill him. Sorry, I do not know who is Symon Notongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big lol, the whole modelling/fashion/porn industry will go to dust dude, i'm glad those guys know we are hypocrites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we can judge whether a person is a hypocrite or not only if we have a POV chapter, being a Hypocrite is about lying to yourself right ? I mean if Robb's inner thinking goes like, "I did the honorable thing by married Jeyne" he is a hypocrite, but if it goes like, "Man, she was hot, I let my dick do my thinking, I fucked up", then he is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he says he is an hypocrite because Stannis fits the standard definition. See when he does something bad/unjust what does he tell himself ? He goes "Whatever I do, I do for the realm", when someone acts like they do good/bad for someone other than themselves they are hypocrites (Remember Walter White). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, I always thought that Catelyn agreed that whatever Robb did, it was exactly what Ned would have done too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its the latter, and yeah Cersie's motto is "what I do, I do for the children", she definitely is one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High Sparrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ofcourse ! Wonder why this came so late in the thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really! well he had me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 09:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need the darkness, someone please cut the lights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its always, "Funny How", Goodfellas, and I don't want to change my opinion ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Clockwork Orange, disturbing and I never understood it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bad luck to name a baby unless its two seasons old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah when he laughs and says "I love this guy", It was like he just met his only friend and goes on to shoot him !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe he is dropping a hint that he is the singer of the song of ice and fire, and like all these singers he won't live to sing his complete song heh ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see wonder why George wants all of em dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey i dont get the joke what is it ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brienne chapters are the best for me in the whole series. I love the struggles of common folk and all the characters she meets - Nimble Dick, Septon Meribald, Creighton Longbough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough, I have the same opinion for LOTR, i read it completely but won't read it again, but the movies I could watch n times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers Everything) The song and the fate of its singers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, maybe this has been discussed before, but so far most of the singers in the asoiaf world are dead or supposed to be dead: Marillon (Eyrie), Blue Bard (KL), Darrion (Bravos), Symon Silvertongue (KL). I think only Tom O Sevens is living and that too very dangerously. Is there a common theme, I failed to pickup  or just coincidence ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, GRRM would be proud of this story man, good for you ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I have this dream of a lame gravedigger, he is filling this grave silently with a dog named dog by his side, when he finishes it, he places this burned toy knight on the grave ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw the first season a few months after it was aired, and wanted to find what happens next, so finished all the books before the second season was out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no I meant nice to meet a Coen brother's fan with your " I am a serious man, Larry" line :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't say you are the first, I have friends like you and your logic is reasonable. Just that the books can also grow on you, give them a chance when all is said and done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had reasons ofcourse but what was her objective ? Capturing him had to ensure a conflict with Lannisters, with Ned and her daughters in KL how could she ever hope to get a upper hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/AblemanSy, mine goes like : "Yeah, well, you know, that's just, like, your opinion, man", sorry for being off the point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 12:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who wants to see Ser Robert Strong and the gravedigger ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it can't have one conclusion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah she didn;t realize that not making a move at that point was as good as making a move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Tyrion was never that fun after he got separated from Bronn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, so if I conclude correctly you can't have both great political power and be a good human being at the same time. Or power acquired by absolute ruthlessness is only temporary and Tyrion should have patiently played the long game ?
(which gave the Lannisters the upper hand for the time being)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think cruelty is a necessity for achieving what Tyrion wants (positions of power) ? If not, him being a little man is the only thing that stops him (I agree with that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far that is what I conclude too, that he couldn't have "done" anything to change the outcome, it would always be like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he wanted a prominent castle (he demanded casterly rock) or to continue as the hand of the king. He felt slighted because the likes of Littlefinger got Harrenhall and Vale, Emmon Frey got riverrun etc. I see that what you say is that he was overly ambitious and had a too high perception of his own worth. But let us say he is that, then could he have done things differently to achieve that ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Catelyn with her capturing Tyrion, never understood her logic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers EVERYTHING) Could Tyrion have done better ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the time leading upto blackwater bay, Bronn once gets angry at Tyrion and says "you never go far enough", not saying that Bronn has a great understanding of westeros politics or human behaviour, I still felt he was trying to say something I felt all along . Even though Tyrion plays the game very close to Tywin's style, people do not rever hm as they did Tywin. Is it just his luck or could he have done something differently to avoid the way he was treated after Blackwater ? So guys can someone substantiate why I feel so or just grasping at straws ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No i cant agree when u say its our POV which changed he does have an arc, remember he would have killed Arya had he found her, just because Cersie wanted him to, Jaime is my favourite charachter in the books, but i think he really started to rethink his life once his hand was cut, before that he never tried recovering from the way Ned branded him kingslayer, and towards the end of books, being an oathkeeper is all that drives him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't pick up Tom O Seven's role at riverrun at all in the first read, while it is one of the more clearly stated things in the books. Simlarly, I had no idea about Lyanna Stark's charachter as I just breezed through that story Jojen tells Bran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 07:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to think the same and then came across that  summary of original version of asoiaf. This led me to think that conclusion is just a matter of GRRM's whim, its more about the writing and the journey of the characters. Ofcourse I don't say that the climax is not an important part of a series, but yeah we have already read the 5/7 th of the series, so if I were to die tomorrow i'd say what the hell, it was a damn fine book ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By what right (pause)
does the wolf (pause) 
judge the lion
BY WHAT RIGHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not a half wit like Hodor
..not sure of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just that since she is alive after the places she has been through, I consider her more resourceful that's all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but I can name a number of Starks who didn't have the wits to stay alive to that point, so how is she a disappointment as compared to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thinks the best part of asoiaf is already there in the existing books and even if the future books are never published the present series would remain as the most marvelous works in literature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Ayn Rand when I just graduated, and I was really I influenced by objectivity and superlavitism. Seven years hence, I still feel it is very motivating what she said, but also realize that people cannot be that one dimensional and when life deals you really rotten cards, all the objectivity in the world change it, it just is what it is. GRRM's charachters on the contrast are I think are more realistic, because they are good and bad at the same time and face more real life dilemmas and confusions. In Rand's world there is no room for mediocrity and when one grows old and realizes that he didn't go into space or isn't the CEO of facebook, her books can't give him much solace ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beric Dondarrion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sansa had a big contribution to Jon's victory and I think she knows how to play the game of thrones best amongst all Starks living or dead, having graduated from Cersie's school of scheming, Tyrion's school of administation and Littlefinger college of powerplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
