<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 04:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jayisgames. It essentially closed down at the end of April inasmuch that it will no longer be updated with games to play. #RIP13Years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 03:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hank: "Was she in there?"

Scott: "Hank, after going through that..."

Hank: "CAN'T YOU GIVE ME A STRAIGHT ANSWER ANYMORE? WAS SHE IN THERE?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 PokDollars says... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 07:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 12:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but can we just take note that Trott got no faults on that first track but didn't get the maximum points for no faults? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 14:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the true 70's Star Wars experience, go to an old theater and watch A New Hope while sitting in the absolute front row after taking a moderate amount of drugs.

I still get a laugh out of that story when Mum tells it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Dangerous Scene In Fallout 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 11:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL INSTITUTE, RAILROAD AND BROTHERHOOD AFFILIATES, VIEW AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU HAVE BEEN WARNED.

[A synth of unknown design fiddling with the controls in the heart of the flagship of the Brotherhood of Steel in clear view of a high-ranking officer.](http://imgur.com/CZbE4AM)

A truly horrifying image, indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 12:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy PII-HIIIILLLSSSS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 06:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Flynn reintegrating with C.L.U at the end of TRON: Legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 06:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This should help you out.](http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/MusicalEpisode) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 06:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHADDAYA MEAN THERE'S STILL JUICE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 05:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And also a sword!](http://baldursgate.wikia.com/wiki/The_Equalizer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 05:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Obligatory.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sdVFLTbQuHE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 04:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. This saga feels like when a TV show does a musical episode; we didn't ask for it, but the creator thought it was needed anyway, and it usually turns out shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 04:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4:26 "To fuck up, or not to fuck up?"

There's some Shakespeare parody (ShakeSmith? SmithSpeare?) to be had there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 04:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, don't forget the bonus tracks "Favorite Snap", "Too Much Too Short", "Disk-stealer" and "Demonstrator". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 01:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ICE BOIIIIIIII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 12:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fully-powered beacon pyramid can be made with a combination of gold blocks, diamond blocks AND iron blocks, FYI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 09:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the accidental ingredient? A damn fine singing voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 02:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex "Tommy Wiseau's shitty repetitive laugh in 'The Room', which is absolute shit but that isn't stopping James Franco from making a movie about it" Smith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 01:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Greyfriars Bobby was a Skye Terrier who became known in 19th-century Edinburgh for supposedly spending 14 years guarding the grave of his owner until he died himself on 14 January 1872."

(If you have the facilities to post to Reddit, what's stopping you from doing a quick Google search?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 07:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Thanks to the anti-torpedo bulge system utilised on warships between the First and Second World Wars, several ships were documented to have survived torpedo and equivalent assaults, such as the HMS Erebus that survived a direct hit from a remote-controlled boat filled with explosives and its sister ship, the HMS Terror, survived no less than 3 torpedo assaults during her service, both thanks to the bulge system." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One torpedo does not a sunken ship make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nuka-Cola Variant Ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend and I are avid Fallout fans, and we like all the different variants of Nuka-Cola that have cropped up throughout the games (yep, even THAT one), so we decided to come up with a few ourselves. Why not treat yourself to a cold...


**NUKA-COLA SUNSET**

Sunset Sarsaparilla and Nuka-Cola have held an amiable truce with each other since the earliest days of our company. Therefore, both companies have considered now to be the appropriate time to collaborate on a new variant: Nuka-Cola SUNSET!*

This yellow-labelled mixture combines the classic taste of Nuka-Cola with the vanilla-liquorice-tinted fizziness of Sunset Sarsaparilla to create a taste and feel that one can only describe as unifying!

Nuka-Cola Sunset: United We Brew, Divided We Drink!**

(*Nuka-Cola Sunset is labelled in the Western States as Sunset Cola.)

(**Limited Edition.)



**NUKA-COLA DYNAMITE**

That massive caffeine hit just not doing it for you? Straight from Mexico, it's Nuka-Cola DYNAMITE! The great taste you know and love with a new addition: extreme chili! That's right; one swig of this luminescent red brew will give you enough energy to build a house, paint the fence, fix the car, mow the lawn and go for a 20 mile run...all in one day! 

Nuka-Cola Dynamite: When Too Much Is Never Enough!*

(*Excessive consumption of this product may cause rashes, swelling, itching, temporary psychosis and heart palpitations. Consult a doctor before use.)



**NUKA-COLA PATRIOT**

Its not a proper party until theres Nuka-Cola! But, even then, Nuka-Cola can only provide so much fun, which is why we are proud to announce the new Nuka-Cola PATRIOT to our range of variants!

The new Patriot is an adult-only alcoholic Nuka-Cola that comes in a variety of different mixes, including, but not limited to Scotch, Vodka, Whiskey, Tequila and Moonshine just to name a few!

Nuka-Cola Patriot: A Soft Drink For A Hard Party!*

(*Excessive consumption will lead to alcohol poisoning. Nuka-Cola does not condone the excessive consumption alcohol and has released this product in the hopes that it will be enjoyed responsibly.)



**NUKA-COLA FREEDOM**

Our soldiers are out there, citizens; it's a harsh fight, and our American troops in Power Armor need all the help they can get. Support the war effort directly today with Nuka Cola FREEDOM! No need to convince anyone you're rooting for the War effort; show your bottle of Nuka Cola Freedom and everyone will see you for the patriot you are. Fight the Reds from your very home!

Nuka-Cola Freedom: For The Liberator In You!*

(*Nuka-Cola would like to remind consumers that, while supporting the Army is a worthy cause, it does not condone or encourage the public to resort to violence to do so, hence the creation of this promotion.)



**NUKA-COLA CUPID**

We at Nuka-Cola encourage companionship in times of crisis. So, in time for Valentines Day, we have decided to bring out Nuka-Cola CUPID!

Give one of these glowing pink brews (with custom naming, no less) to your significant other or lifelong crush to show them that youre thinking of them. What could be more romantic than sharing a bottle of Nuka-Cola with the love of your life while watching the sun go down?

Nuka-Cola Cupid: Loneliness Is Not Forever!*

(*Limited Edition. Nuka-Cola would also like to iterate that Nuka-Cola Cupid is not to be considered a love potion, nor is Nuka-Cola responsible for restraining orders and marital problems that may arise through the sale and distribution of Nuka-Cola Cupid.)



**NUKA-COLA PLASMA**

Need a little pizazz in your soft drink? Love the trademark taste of an ice cold Nuka Cola, but want a little more zing?

Have a blast with Nuka-Cola PLASMA! With the announcement RobCo's new joint project in Plasma Weaponry, we at Nuka-Cola wanted to bring you all the Zip, Pop and Whoosh of these extraordinary tools in your favourite drink! To achieve this, weve added a small, safely-consumable amount of the newly-patented Plasma liquid ammunition to our classic Nuka-Cola and shaken it up a bit! For those of us that just need some extra get up and go, get critical with Nuka-Cola Plasma!

Nuka-Cola Plasma: Straight From The Future!*

(*Limited edition. Nuka-Cola holds no responsibility for liquefied oesophaguses or stomachs, or total disintegration brought on by excessive consumption. Consult a doctor before use.)



**NUKA-COLA TROPICAL**

Tired of your office cubicle? House life got you feeling like you're in jail? Do you need a quick and easy escape? Enjoy your life...by not being there at all!

Our southern offices have been working around the clock so that YOU can try the NEW Nuka-Cola TROPICALl! One green sip of our patented Melon Burst recipe and you'll be whisked away to a golden beach in Hawaii or a cruise ship in the Caribbean!

Let your mind float away from your body as you envision yourself far, far away from where you'd rather not be, with a smile on your face and the refreshing exotic taste of melon on your lips!

Nuka-Cola Tropical: Paradise Is Just A Drink Away!*

(*Excessive consumption may result in a temporary fugue state, accompanied by incoherent mumbling and moderate drooling.) 



**NUKA-COLA BAYCHIMO**

It's a story that's delighted hunters for over 130 years, and now we're taking a leaf out of its history. A special promotion to YOU, from us at Nuka-Cola, we have come up with Nuka-Cola BAYCHIMO!

As a parallel to the sparse, rare sightings of the Ghost Ship of the Arctic, Nuka-Cola is releasing 5 (count them) bottles of Nuka-Cola Baychimo* among our seemingly-infinite supplies of Nuka-Cola in order to give 5 lucky consumers an executive VIP tour of the Nuka-Cola factory, culminating in a brainstorm session to determine what flavour and theme Nuka-Cola will be releasing next!

Nuka-Cola Baychimo: Every Story Has An End!**

(*Limited Edition. Bottles of Nuka-Cola Baychimo appear as a standard bottle of Nuka-Cola, but with the subtitle 'Baychimo' underneath written in smaller text under the title.)

(**Promotion ends August 31, 2077. Executive tour to take place October 23, 2077. This promotion will not be repeated.)



**NUKA-COLA PHANTASM**

Heads up, Nuka-Cola drinkers! Halloween is just around the corner and have we got the beverage for you!

Excited to gaily roam the streets on October 31 but don't have a costume prepared? With the new and extremely limited Nuka-Cola PHANTASM, you don't need a costume to fright and delight!
Our scientists have slaved over a hot Petri dish to synthesize a consumption-safe variant of the GFP gene found in jellyfish to put in America's favourite cola drink!

"What does all that mean?" I hear you ask! Simple! Upon consuming the bright yellow Phantasm concoction, your skin will glow varying shades of white, yellow and green for up to four whole hours! Plenty of time to get your trick-or-treating in!

With your skin glowing, all you need is a ghoul-like moan and voila! From no costume to a ghost version of yourself in no time! Happy Halloween!

Nuka-Cola Phantasm: Unleash The Freak!*

(*Limited edition. Excessive consumption may cause irreparable genome damage, including permanently glowing skin, and renal failure. Limit of one per customer per purchase.)



**WHAT VARIANTS CAN YOU COME UP WITH?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 13:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collecting pool balls when I come across them. I...don't actually know why, now that I think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traditionally, Ice Gyms have been seventh in their regions, and Dragon Gyms have been seventh or eighth in their regions. An early Ice or Dragon Gym makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said "Some semblance of order". I never claimed that this was the order I wanted the gyms in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see if I can save this...

I want to dress a gorilla in rags and call him Penurious George. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upon the announcement of Pokemon Sun and Moon, I found myself thinking about which types and what genders the Gyms, Elite Four and Champion might have. So, I compiled a table of the most commonly used types, what each specialist was and the genders of those specialists. Then, I went through and compiled a wishlist of the most under-represented of each type, specialist and gender, which you shall see below, along with my reasoning. So, in some semblance of order:

**GYM LEADERS**

1) Poison-type Male (part of a 4-way tie of the second-most under-represented types and there have been more female than male Poison specialists)

2) Ground-type Female (part of a 4-way tie of the second-most under-represented types and there have been more male than female Ground specialists)

3) Dragon-type Male (while part of a 3-way tie in second-most represented type and equal amounts of gender use, there have been half the amount of Dragon Gym Leaders than there have been Elite Four and Champions combined. Plus, I thought Drayden was awesome.)

4) Ghost-type Male (less Gym Leaders than Elite Four members and a 3:1 ratio of females to males #TeamMorty)

5) Dark-type Female (this type hasn't had a Gym yet and there have been more male Dark specialists than female)

6) Steel-type Female (part of a 5-way tie of the third-most under-represented types with an equal position split but with 3 male Steel specialists to 1 female specialist)

7) Flying-type Male (part of a 4-way tie of the second-most under-represented type, I know that all Flying specialists have been Gym Leaders but I wanted to give certain types a chance in the Elite Four, and there has only been 1 male specialist while the other 2 have been female)

8) Fire-type Female (a pretty average represented type with more Gyms than Elite Four, but with 3 male specialists compared to 2 female specialists)

**ELITE FOUR**

1) Rock-type Female (part of a 5-way tie of the third-most under-represented types where all specialists have been Gym Leaders and a ratio of 3 male to 1 female)

2) Electric-type Female (a pretty average represented type where all specialists have been Gym Leaders and a ratio of 4 male to 1 female)

3) Grass-type Male (part of a 5-way tie of the third-most under-represented types where all specialists have been Gym Leaders with an equal gender split)

4) Normal-type Male (Often seen as the worst type due to it not being super-effective against anything I thought I'd give it a chance in the EF as part of a 4-way tie of the second-most under-represented type with 4 Gym Leaders and an equal gender split)

**CHAMPION**

1) Fairy-type Male (Sexuality arguments aside, the Fairy type has had one Gym Leader which has been Female and needs a little more love in the specialist line-up) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 05:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Pokmon moves as Dark Side Of The Moon track titles**

Chatter  Speak To Me

Gust  Breathe

Agility  On The Run

Roar Of Time  Time

Relic Song  The Great Gig In The Sky

Pay Day  Money

Transform  Us And Them

Sketch  Any Colour You Like

Headbutt  Brain Damage

Moonblast - Eclipse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Look at that fine weapon. You can't convince me that the LeMat Carbine wouldn't be an awesome weapon in the upcoming game.*

(*I really hope this game has a good title. Red Dead Redemption 2 sounds like a cop-out.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gib LeMat Carbine plox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with the Civil War theory. The Southern States before the time of John Marston? Definitely Civil War...which means we'll be able to use the LeMat Revolver again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnily enough, my sister lives in Sydney, while I languish down in Tasmania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obtuse, Right, Acute, Straight, Reflex or Full Rotation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 07:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denzel Curry references the Senzu beans in "Ultimate" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 06:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 points to Sachyriel. Yes, I'm Australian...in an area of Australia no-one gives a crap about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, hot damn; shove 'em into a cannon and shoot them over a Texan country community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whiteboard marker or a texta would make the most sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't want ANY weapons in the hands of children. This isn't the 9th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual sword? There goes my umbrella theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 04:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, they're CANDLES! I always thought they were nails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 14:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ross in Trott's chair and Trott is Ross's chair? Have I missed something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 08:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...in a different dimension! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, a fellow Whovian. Greetings, good sir or madam, depending on your current incarnation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spacey wacey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How odd. It's not removed on my end. In any case, I'll repeat it here.

"I've been crunching a few numbers about this game to find a condensed way to wrap my head around how massive NMS is.

Here's what I've got (text wall incoming):

**ONE**

Grab your average 30cm ruler. Now, in your minds eye, picture a cube that's 29cm X 29cm X 29cm. Pretty easy, right?

But, wait; there's more. In your mind, segment the cube into 1cm blocks, so it looks like those big wooden blocks you used in school for counting.

Now imagine each one of those individual blocks is Planet Earth. That's right; imagine a cube of over 24,000 Planet Earths.

The population of Earth at the moment clocks in at about 7.4 billion. A lot of people, right? That's not the end, though; the average number of hairs on the human head is around 100,000. So, imagine all the people on all the Earths in your cube had 100,000 hairs on all of their heads.

Now for the math.

100,000 hairs X 7.4 billion people = 740 trillion (740 followed by 12 zeroes) hairs on one Planet. 740 trillion hairs X 24,389 Planet Earths (the number of planets in your cube) = 18,047,860,000,000,000,000 (18 quintillion, 47 quadrillion, 860 trillion) hairs on the heads of the combined people in your cube of Earths.

And that's STILL not enough to equal the amount of planets in NMS!

**TWO**

The estimated age of Planet Earth is 4.543 billion years old.

If Day One of Earth was Day One of No Man's Sky, and one planet was discovered every second in NMS, right now roughly 0.77% of the planets in NMS would have been discovered.

**THREE**

There's roughly 18.5 quintillion planets in No Man's Sky.

Hello Games believe that, over the course of the game, 99.9% of these planets will go undiscovered, which equals to about 18.5 quadrillion planets feasibly being discovered during the game's life-span.

**FOUR**

Remember those wood or plastic 1 centimetre cubes you used in primary school for maths?

Well, if one of those cubes was one planet in NMS, and you wanted a cubic representation of how many planets there are in NMS using them, the finished product would be a cube with sides almost 26.5 kilometres long.

**FIVE**

One spreadsheet in Microsoft Excel 2016 has 17,179,869,184 total cells. If you were to use Microsoft Excel 2016 to compile a database of the names of every planet in No Man's Sky with one name per cell, you would need exactly 1,073,741,824 complete spreadsheets to list them all." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleted it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that seems plausible enough. All fear SkullMaster.

Also, if an elephant sits on your fence, it's time you wondered how you warped into a episode of Viva La Bam and consequently look for a way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I talked about something similar the other day.](https://www.reddit.com/r/NoMansSkyTheGame/comments/4ejwpk/the_sheer_size_of_this_game/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...aside from the fact that I walked right into that one, where or who would a 14 year old turn to in order to extract and concentrate the ricin found in said castor beans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given where she frequents, I reckon that umbrella shoots caffeine pellets instead of ricin. Where would a 14 year old get ricin, anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 07:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: that's actually a sword-shaped umbrella on Sam's back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reindeer's Been Naughty (Traitor Remix) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sheer size of this game... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 11:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [DUNE REFERENCES FOREVER!](http://www.questionablecontent.net/view.php?comic=2400) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 13:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #SmithConfirmedAsKeanuReevesOfHatFilms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Banging?](http://i.imgur.com/FyedfTL.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 12:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good ole' Smiff, reppin' Command And Conquer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 11:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Number 2231, which was posted almost exactly a year later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 08:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will happen first. Hannelore's 5 year plan seems to happen in 2018. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 06:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing him, he's probably got a jar of stale farts fermenting somewhere. It'd go great with that farting noise app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It approaches... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 06:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember SMBC's guest comic  [here](http://www.questionablecontent.net/view.php?comic=1975)  ?

It was published Friday, July 26th, 2011. Pintsize said there was six years left before the poison gas was released, making that Doomsday fall on Wednesday, July 26th, 2017. Today's date is Tuesday, March 29th, 2016.

1 YEAR
3 MONTHS
27 DAYS

SLEEP IN FEAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 07:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you're about to see is a VERY rough proof of concept. 20 minutes in MS Paint doesn't exactly make this the Mona Lisa, but it does get my idea across nicely.

Presenting to you, the  [SHATT Films logo!](http://imgur.com/BMgmYcX)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 10:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realise that this bit of trivia is absolutely worthless (not even sure why I'm posting this) but in the Ocean dub of DBZ, when Raditz dodges Piccolo's Makankosappo, Piccolo exclaims that Raditz can move FTL to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 01:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm...no, no, Ross is right; Hat Films are my favourite people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 10:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a special place in Hell for people like you...and seeing as how I might be in the same place one day, I say "Go for it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 02:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but 1: he can now slice, dice and chicken fried rice with the best of them and 2: That's what Whitechapel Charlie's for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 00:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ACKCHUALLY When a Pokemon card has a shiny background in the Pokemon image (like the Vivillion Trott pulled), the card is called a 'holo' and when a Pokemon card is shiny on the rest of the card (like the Xerneas Trott pulled), the card is called a 'reverse holo'. Clearly, they don't watch Martyn's pack openings. Nnnnnnnthank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 05:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt kinda sorry for the poor guy, leaving him for 210 years, seeing him briefly for a few hours and then leaving again for three months.

So I did him a favour. Behold! [Mega Codsworth!](http://imgur.com/2ElwBsV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, that was unexpected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 06:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And NOT the way Geoff looked at Gavin in their drinking Mario Kart video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 06:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're the Beastie Boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 06:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, good; I've been running low on Crazy Pills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
