<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in the same boat, im still in shock at what i just witnessed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hes declined several offers from them, called them out a few days ago to. He won't be going anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greatest match i have ever seen, i had to stand up for the last 10 mins, my legs started to shake, fcking insane! i can't even rate this, it's not allowed, 5/5 doesn't do any justice to how impeccable this match was. I can't wait to watch more NJPW! thank you to everyone that has suggested i should watch this, nearly 5 hours of pure wrestling non stop! I LOVE IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOP THE MATCH, IT's IMPOSSIBLE TO GIVE 6* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh really? thats fair, this is my first NJPW event so i was just puzzled, seems cool though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone clue me in on Kenny Omegas entrance? why the terminator theme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm loving this strong style thing, sooo stiff, gives wrestling a whole new dimension... fcking love it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> missed about 5 mins of this match mid way, fs. looking forward to the final 3 showdown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious match! commentators are cracking me up xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first ever WK... how does this show compare so far to previous WK's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a black coffee for me, im intermittent fasting so not eating until 1pm gmt (8:00 am now) which sucks but hey, gotta get on the perfect body hypppppee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Streamer gets smacked in jaw whilst jammin' out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anderson needs this win! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SORT IT OUT SKY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want a legit braun push
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frustrated but im not angry, we should have won but sometimes shit happens and you just move on, hoping for spurs to beat Chelsea now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is his DJ career going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  born in after 2003

and if i was born after 2003... how would i have remember a goal from my birth year?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> born in 97... didn't start watching football until about 2006/07 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think i've ever witnessed a scorpian kick in my time, now i've seen two in a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i always do it, i love pre-season. playing with youngsters/fringe players, finding out how i want to play the upcoming season, using the new signings see how they fit in what position, style of play etc... it's still imo the best new feature EA have added to career mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in what way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the directors other movies, Dogtooth and Alps are also both very creative and bizarre n a very fascinating way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mignolet
clyne lovren klavan milner
can
lallana gini
mane studge origi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will take this every day of the f'kin week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Van Dijk, Redmond, Bertrand could all be possibilities in the future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wouldn't be watching WWE now if it wasn't for the brand split.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mane Mane Mane
Must be funny
In a Red mans world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're away, Everton are pressing us really well, so we've pretty much played on the counter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uhmm. yes all the time for the past 2 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Tag Champs at this stage was a bad thing (match was great), Charlotte winning was garbage, te main event was meh at best, Jericho vs Rollins was good, the Cruiserweight match was the best thing about the ppv as Neville turned heel... Poor PPV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jericho for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was a good match... nothing spectacular  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not right for me... Should have made New Day more convincing, dropping the belts asap after breaking the record feels so fake and garbage to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? They lose the belts their next match after breaking the record? unconvincing for me, New Day haven't had an impressive win in months and they drop the belts asap after the record... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most likely, unless Banks vs Charlotte doesn't get stale, but i think the fans are a bit meh about the feud so they really need to pull it out the bag if they're aree going to entertain everyone for 30min </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more twists and turns than a cheap garden hoes...  i wish Ray Hudson commentated my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 19:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A tribute to a player injured? Man City walking out with Gundogan shirts was pure cringe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure, but im sure as part of the sponsor deal you have to wear the away kit a minimum amount  of time on TV or something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sterling you spoon, should have buried that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they never do against City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scored quicker than Gundogan's passing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 16:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prediction 2-1 (Man City)

Sanchez

Dr Bruyne, Silva </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 16:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gundogan shirts? WTF? did he die? is he in intensive care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you guys could stop winning, that would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> romance? what romance? if they would have kissed at the end then i would have grabbed a noose, but it was two people who became connected towards the end literally moments away from facing death, it wasn't "romance" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gunfight by The Mighty Underdogs ft. MF DOOM. The Mighty Underdogs are Lateef, Gift of Gab... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that belt looks sexy as fuck i have to admit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firmino for me should be up front, Origi is best when he cuts in from the left, firmino is seriously being wasted playing on the wing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spurs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> box to box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> collymore closing in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or up front, you know. His best position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rivaldo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does anyone expect out defense to be solid when our midfield is all over the place? we have zero defensive cover in our midfield and is something that has been an issue for us for a loooooooong time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats been wrong with out defense?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Miz? not a chance, hes one of the big stars of Smackdown... i think it could be Ziggler/Kalisto/Corbin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's my point, we haven't had any good defensive midfielders in almost 10 years... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know, but we haven't had a defensive midfielder since Mascherano (Lucas being injured a lot never helped us, but looked great in his prime for us) 13/14 we had Gerrard as our deepest midfielder, now we have Hendo... two good midfielders who were/are great at moving the ball forward, but aren't defensively equipped to cover our back four, then are defensive gets exposed and it's their fault... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our focus in 13/14 was top four, we achieved that but everyone was pissed because we didn't win the league. Our focus at the start of this season was Top 4, now everyone is pissed that the league is out of reach... I'm still thrilled with how this season is going, and i'd be delighted with Top 4 come end of the season (if we get it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're shit? bad run of form? huuuuge difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think it's down to our midfield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes a forward, just like Muller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It worries me that people actually care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young M.A - Through The Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i understand that Chelsea are in a much better position than us, but theres more than half of the games left to be played, anything can happen. Chelsea looked poor vs City and scraped through as City scuffed there several opportunities. Chelsea will drop points as will other teams, it happens, we shouldn't overreact. Today was shit, but hopefully next week we can forget this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying we shouldn't have played Milner? someone who has probably been our stand out player playing at LB? he's been superb this season, and hopefully will continue playing that LB role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how is that fickle thinking we would be title contenders going so long unbeaten? we ARE title contenders and losing against Bournemouth doesn't mean we're not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> before the game? from kick off? when? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a kick in the dick and an uppercut to the balls. but hey, shit happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should be our 3rd choice now, Lucas has looked ok but Klavan should be given a go now when Matip/Lovren is out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it really isn't our defence as much as it is our midfield, Matip/Lovren have been very solid for us, even Lucas at the back has looked good, but we got overran in midfield due to our lack of defensive minded players and got very complacent. I'm still very optimistic about our defence, i just think Klavan should be played when Matip is out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times has Lucas started at the back for us this season? 4/5 in all comps, he's looked very solid, even in the first half he was solid for us, the whoel team collapsed 2nd half, lack of midfield cover mean't we were going to get overran and that's what happend, blaming the performance on individuals (apart from Karius) isn't really fair) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chelsea might look solid but they were picked apart by City and were lucky to get the win, Chelsea WILL drop points, that's for certain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *our only two defeats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bringing on Lallana was a bad choice? why? fresh pair of legs, more energy, it made sense. who should we have brought on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me save this comment and get back to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chelsea have two? you saying they are not in the title race?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading half the comments saying stuff like "Title Challenge gone" is making me chuckle, our 2nd defeat of the season, sitting in 3rd place and apparently we're shit... it was a bad 2nd half and our fans fickle enough to think everything is gone, pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Lucas has been fantastic at the back... ahh the power of hindsight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do our fans think we wont challenge for the title now? because we lost our first game since matchday 2? pathetic fickle fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we will? only the 2nd defeat of the season and its all over? you're pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah man i just made it for fun, all the vinyls are bootlegged, glad you enjoy it though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My final SADEVILLAIN mix... and a thank you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys

First and foremost i want to thank everyone that has supported my SADEVILLAIN tape, it has definitively been a highlight of my young life. I initially released the tape for fun not knowing it would blow up like it did, so as a thank you i wanted to make one last SADEVILLAIN mix. Bump DOOM all day, everyday!

I hope you guys enjoy this, feedback always welcome (im still learning as a producer)

https://soundcloud.com/seanh2k11/sadevillain-chatter-batter-seanh-remix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> K-Rino - Enigma Class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude this is crazy good, sounds like something from Keys to the Cuffs, good job man! didn't know this pella existed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lupe Fiasco - Mural (Lyrics Breakdown) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just finding these hilarious, he reminds me of that student in school that never gets away with anything and always spends lunch in detention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KMD - Black Bastards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh yh, i 'member! 'member Samed Yesil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it doesn't feel a part of raw. The matches are great just no storyline or character development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhmm... hello Alicia fox? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ foley... stop this cringe shouting trying to big something up, it didn't work when you cut that weird hiac promo and it's not working now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the jericho owens "break up" is a ruse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R truth jobbing... eh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooohhhhhhhhhhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha . Recovered well I guess xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping for a good show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another would be Mallrats the Region 2 release. love that movie so much but no special features what so ever, how ether the region 1 release has a lot of special features... wtf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shrooms... not because i rate it poorly (i loved the movie) but a lot of people call it trash. got it the a few quid, can't complain. enjoyable movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 14:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> send me a PM bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Madvillainy? mm...food. DOOMs production on the album is incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you wan't a shitty underwhelming match then sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo the foreign guy, boo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET RID OF THE FUCKING PURPLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More lana please, pretty please... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jericho will blame someone else, it won't be owens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
