<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject250</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that "Texan raised" equates to quality anytime. Texan here though. Looks delish, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I have to admit, I had that song performed in Italian that played as Furio saw Carm stuck in my head for at least a week. And now. 
Crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll say that while Tony has such a large personality, I found myself rooting for Chrissy all along. It was hard not to want to see the progression of Chris develop after his "taking care of" of Adriana. I was genuinely annoyed when he starting fucking up again after seemingly taking a step towards a better life only to die at Tony's hands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite character on the Sopranos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious to see which characters everyone can say "he/she's my  favorite" amidst such an interesting group. Thoughts? Why?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just suggest re-watching the seasons, all of them, once more if you have the time. There area lot of references and plotlines that converge into one amazing, but complex, last season. 

As for fan theories, you'll spend at least a half hour searching the web after watching the finale. 
Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whe else thought this was mint chocolate ice cream on the first scroll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muenster can be your friend, OP. 
Very mild and creamy. 
I'd also recommend some Oaxaca cheese, they use it in quesadillas in traditional Tex-Mex fare (which is my favorite). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Papas con queso and carnitas***
C'mon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's one way to start your day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
