<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 02:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not expecting a change of heart on his end. I know who he is. But I also know he probably doesn't realize that I'm about to walk out of his life because of it. I just want to show him that I'm done bending to his will and done giving him chances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I (25F) tell my dad (49M) that his abandonment of my sister (22F) and I 4 years ago is a big deal and that I am devastated by his lies and lack of effort? Do I just cut contact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 01:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title pretty much says it all, but I'll include a few details: 

- My parents were married 20-something years and, throughout my childhood and teen years, became progressively more toxic to each other and to us. They both deal with mostly-manageable mental health issues and they both cheated on each other for the last year of their marriage. My mom left my sister and I with our dad for about 6 months a year prior, but had the balls to kick him out during the divorce. They separated, then divorced almost 5 years ago. 

- They both started seeing other people VERY quickly - within two months. They're both still with those new partners. But my dad moved out to live with the woman that is now my stepmother. They got married within like a year and a half, she has two daughters who are a few years younger than my sister and I. Initially we all got along really well - they're a lot like us, they were really welcoming. All the daughters were bridesmaids in their wedding. 

- My sister got pregnant 3 1/2 years ago. She knew she didn't have the resources and wanted the baby to have a better life, so she found a great adoptive family. Most of our family was so supportive and helpful but my dad and stepmom couldn't handle it.  Mostly my stepmom. They acted like it was a personal affront to them that my sister was "choosing strangers over them" and begged me to make her stop the adoption and make my sister let them raise the baby. This crossed so many lines and went way too far to me and is really the beginning of where the relationship went sour. We see my nephew multiple times a year - probably 30 times over the last 3 years - and my moms side of the family all goes on vacation with the adoptive family. My sister made it clear that, because of the reaction of my dad and stepmom, that when my dad was going to meet the baby for the first time, she wanted him to come alone. At this point he and my stepmom were newlyweds and this was seen as unacceptable to him. Long story short, she has tried everything short of breaking that one rule to get him to meet his grandson. My nephew is now turning 3 and has never met his grandfather. 

- I was always very close with my dad. Despite our toxic family issues he and I were always very close. I got my first tattoo with him while my mom was moved out, we hung out together, I could talk to him about pretty much anything. Once the divorce happened, this disappeared. He barely texted, only called on birthdays. I had to chase after every family dinner or barbecue or movie night. He would go between wanting me to come over all the time and making plans with my then-boyfriend and I to only asking us last minute, after friends had cancelled plans, if we wanted to come out there. And we ALWAYS had to drive out there. He lives 90 minutes away. He lied to his wife about how often he tried to contact us - I showed her my call logs and texts to prove he didn't call or text nearly as often as he claimed - and she still didn't believe me. 

- He treats his stepdaughters so much better than my sister and I. The year he and my mom split, he said he was going to get my sister and I Uggs, which he'd been promising for years, and yes I know how petty this sounds, but he didn't and he kept lying about it and saying they were "on their way". Two months later he bought my stepsisters both new Uggs. We go over most years for Christmas Eve, and all the sisters open presents at the same time. It has become very clear that not only have they decreased in number, but he basically buys us all cheap shit and buys them nice stuff every year. I know how petty that sounds but it's so blatant - they want us all to open presents together but then it's clear there's an imbalance. 

- He has lied about us to most of our extended family, claiming my mom poisoned us and we hated him and only spent time with her (I never even got along with my mom until a year or two ago) and that we ignore his calls and stuff. All lies obviously. He's apparently been telling these lies since the very beginning, and I only know he was lying at all because I ran into my great-aunt and was super happy to see her (she's one of my favorite family members and genuinely one of the nicest people I know) and she was super distant and weird. I asked her if anything was weird and she basically alluded to what my dad had told her. I almost cried in the produce section. I had no idea he'd been lying. I told her I'd just been at his house twice in the last month and for a whole week the month before that. She had no reason not to believe me, so she was obviously confused, and said that she and my great-uncle had had the usual family parties a bunch over the last few years and she'd always told my dad to extend the invitation to my sister and I and my boyfriend. He never did. In fact, he told them that we made up excuses just to not go with him but that obviously wasn't true. 

- I got engaged in December (yay!). In the early years when my then-boyfriend and I were clearly serious, my stepmom and I used to look at tons of wedding stuff, my dad always asked when we'd get married, they were so excited for all of this and we talked about it all the time. When my then-boyfriend was getting ready to propose in December, he drove 220 total minutes in traffic for an hour at my dads house, asking his permission and talking about the proposal. He said my dad seemed strange. Everyone knew it was coming, even what day, so it wasn't shock. He just seemed like it wasn't a big deal. When my now-fianc proposed, we waited until the next day to call everyone. I called my dad and he just said "cool" and that was one of maybe seven words he said to me. The other ones were likely "I'm happy for you" and "Bye Kate". I tried to get him to talk to me but he just... Didn't. He came to the engagement party a month or so later and even helped us move a few weeks after that, but I haven't seen or spoken to him in over three months. New record. 

And then probably the biggest kicker of all... 

My fianc and I had some money troubles a few years ago, when my dad and I were still close. I have a lot of health issues that prevented me from working for a while. The second my dad heard we were having money issues, he wrote us a check (then another later) and insisted we never worry about paying him back. We're talking a little over a thousand dollars. There was also the matter of another thousand dollars - but that was a deal he and my mom made in the divorce. They were supposed to give my sister and I $2k to help get ourselves a car for work and stuff. That was never supposed to be paid back, ever, it was their "apology" for their rough divorce and including us in those problems. But back to the fianc thing, we were super grateful and tried to pay him back but he wouldn't accept it. He was working a job that paid really well at the time. When he lost that job a year or so later (we were given multiple lies about why) he texted me to ask when I could finally pay him that money back. I was floored. I hadn't expected it, even though we'd just started having issues. And I told him that even though the first $1k was car money (he only gave me half what he was supposed to but I didn't really care at the time and was grateful either way) and would not be paid back, that I would work on paying him back as much of the rest as I could. Shortly after that my health issues returned and I couldn't work. Luckily fianc was working a better job and could support us both, but my dad started to get rude with me when I told him why I couldn't pay him back. He stopped inviting me over or answering texts. It was clear this was about the money and I was devastated and disappointed. Out of the blue, right after his birthday, he started texting again and invited us out for dinner. I jumped at the chance. He started inviting us over again after that and I thought things were changed. 

Here's where it gets weird: About six months later I got a new phone and was trying to make plans with him but didn't have his number. My fianc told me to grab his number out of his phone. I could have just gone to contacts but his texts were already open, so I scrolled down to see my dad (I sometimes texted my dad from fiance's phone to say we were on our way over). But there were unusual texts on the phone from just before we'd started talking again. The last two were my fianc asking my dad "can I come by today? I have something to give you." And my dad saying sure, he'd be home all afternoon. I thought it was off immediately and asked my fianc a few days later. He hesitated but eventually confessed to leaving work early one day, taking all the personal cash he had ($700+) and giving it to my dad, to, in his words, "get my dad off my back".  He knew I was so upset by my dads behavior that he freaking paid him off. It says as much my fianc (you damn well KNOW he cares a shit ton about me) as it does about my father, who was ready to cut off contact with his daughter over money he insisted we never pay back and only started talking to me again after my fianc DRAINED HIS PERSONAL CHECKING ACCOUNT. I told fianc that I did appreciate it so so much, but explained that it probably wouldn't help anything long term. My fianc didn't see it at the time but gets it now. He's not a big fan of my dad anymore. 

I've just been floored. I never expected that this kind of shit would happen. I miss my dad. I miss my stepsisters and even my semi-controlling stepmom. But I'm so disappointed and so done trying. I already know he's not walking me downs the aisle at my wedding - that's for my sister now - and I wouldn't do any kind of father daughter dance either. It's sad. My sister was never as close with my dad (she was moms favorite) so I don't think it affects her as much. But it kills me every freaking day. I broke down to my fianc a few days ago. I can't take it anymore. The constant back and forth. Everything. I'm fairly sick. He never checks in or even sees if I'm okay. I called him to tell him I was in the hospital and he never even texted. 

Fianc suggested I send an email just telling my dad how I feel. Telling him how bad he's hurt me and how bad it's been for me, and that I can't be the only one trying anymore. That if he wants to be a part of my life, it's up to him now. But that I've already accepted that he may continue with this behavior and may no longer be a part of my life. 

I don't know what to do. How to say it. I almost don't care. I almost don't want to send it and give him another chance. I can't believe he left. I can't believe he's so obviously stopped caring and that I missed it. I can't believe he took the money. The fucking money. And then played nice for a few months. I can't buy his time. I won't. 

How do I do this? Should I even try? How do I handle the extended family that all think I don't want to see them? How do I make it clear that my sister had given up and that he'll never meet his first grandkid if he can't shape up? How do I tell him he's gone from my best friend to the person who has hurt me the most? 

Someone please help me out here. I'm at wits end. I go between wanting to make one last effort and wanting to just cut my losses and cut contact. But I would lose two sisters and half my already small family in the process. 

Tl;dr (because this was fucking long I know) title + my dad lies to family about me + doesn't seem to care about my health issues or engagement + accepted money from my fianc behind my back that he initially said we shouldn't pay him back and started making a small effort after the money + is generally destroying our relationship. Need help either telling him how he's made me feel and giving him one more chance or cutting contact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 22:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with a similar BPD/N mom, it sounds like something is up with her meds and stress level. I obviously can't give definitive medical advice without knowing her but the super short swings (some minutes she loves you, four minutes later she's aggressive and back again) sounds like a high stress level that was just exacerbated by feeling left out (she saw the AM time as "special time" with you and didn't get it, on her only kid's wedding day) and feeling like you weren't making it up to her (which isn't justifiable at all, your wedding day and all, but N logic). Is it possible she's switched doses lately? Or that she was eating differently? My friends mom has BPD too and was trying to lose weight for her wedding and it fucked with her, big time. Too many chemical changes. 

Just ignore her for a while. She'll either come around or she won't. I stopped trying to please my mother and she became much more agreeable when I wasn't feeding her that N energy she needed.

It sucks that it had to be on your big day, but it was likely BECAUSE of the stress involved. Don't sweat it too much. And congrats! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 20:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gameboys tho. I want one so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 19:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, that's all! Just those two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 18:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Tarteist Namaste, TF Melted Peony, and still looking...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help us find new music before EDC! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/qYdRF

My fianc and I have attended EDC twice now - 2012 and 2015, soon to be 2016. We're both super busy (crazy jobs, huge families, I have health issues, etc) so we haven't been able to keep up with pretty much anything - and keeping an updated music library has fallen to the wayside. 

I highlighted the artists on the lineup that we know we want to see. Ones we've kept up with and have the newer stuff or people we've started listening to recently. We don't really have time to go through every single artist, even in the mixed genres we both like.

Given the lineup and an idea of who we like - who should we NOT MISS? Who's got awesome sets or just came out with something amazing? Or who's tried and true and we've just been missing? 

Any help is super appreciated! We're so excited for EDC this year even if we haven't really kept up - gives us time to see more around the festival and catch new artists!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25F. I feel you. I dealt with migraines for a while as a kid, then back pain, then debilitating nerve pain before finally getting a diagnosis at 22. My health is only deteriorating further (Syringomyelia, Degenerative Disc Disease, Ehlers-Danlos, Cluster Headaches, Chronic Kidney Cysts, Renal malformation, legs are uneven, multiple food intolerances, anemia, malabsorption issues) and people are always shocked at what all is going on with me. "You're so young!" Yeah, well, you're just ignorant, jerks. Young people get sick all the time. Plenty of people much younger than I am. Get away and let me pop my pain meds and grumble about my pain in peace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 08:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? It was a bit surreal. I was this vagrant looking college kid standing in B N having some sort of "moment". But I love telling this story anyway. Made me feel a lil bit ~famous for a few hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 07:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact, I used to submit to a regional literary journal online. I was maybe 19 at the time this whole thing happened. For the most part, people liked my stuff. Yay! I was in a Barnes and Noble one day and heard two women discussing my latest piece from the next aisle over. It was so bizarre! ("No, wait! That's just who I am onliiiine!") But I heard them mention a few things they liked. And I didn't say a damned thing to them. I could have just popped around the corner like "Hey, that's me actually, glad you liked it." But that just seemed fucking strange so I let it go. Plus these were "professional" looking older women - mid 40's. I was wearing sweatpants and I don't think I'd washed my hair in several days. 

A few days later I was on the forums discussing the recent pieces and this user commented and I just KNEW it was one of the ladies from B N. Her phrasing was identical. I decided to fuck with her a bit and asked if she'd been at Barnes and Noble two days ago. And if she was in the green shirt or the black one. She thought I was a total creep at first until I told her I was one aisle over the whole time debating striking up a conversation. Username checked out as obviously being me, we laughed, she tried to figure out which fellow patron I was, she failed. Probably a good thing. There was definitely a coffee stain on those pants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 07:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest sometimes I myself forget I'm not an early 20's white liberal male...

Then I check in my pants and - spoiler alert! - I'm an early 20's white liberal FEmale. 

*diversity* /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely do that! I got through them because of my spinal condition and they make sure you're taken care of if you have so much as a migraine. They have ice packs and all that jazz. And if you don't want to go that route, you can usually tip a bartender a few extra bucks for ice. Best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be about ten degrees cooler than last year at any given time. 80% sure. Last year I felt like it barely cooled down at night. I can't stand dry heat. It feels worse than humid stuff for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you've accepted your fate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know ONE thing, Jon Snow... But that's fucking IT. And even that's only half right. So. Carry on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 28% straight and can confirm, DAAAAAAMN.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two weeks, fuckers! *screams internally* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 16:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work at Disneyland. A certain "lead" cast member who I never got along with liked to harass me one way or another about makeup. If I didn't wear any/my hair was up, I looked "unkempt". But the kicker was when he argued with me for TWENTY MINUTES about how my lipstick was "too dark to be 'look' appropriate." I wasn't wearing lipstick. I was wearing plain, untinted Chapstick. My lips are naturally fairly dark tinted for a really pale lady. 

It took a (higher up) lead walking by and asking why he was yelling at me for the guy to realize he'd been a little over zealous. I had tried to explain that it was Chapstick. I showed him the tube in question. Nope. But this higher lead guy just shook his head and told me to go do my job and he'd handle this dumb guy. 

Disney is notorious for its strict dress standards but some people just power trip over it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone (then 18F) who dated her camp counselor (then 28M) on and off for a while, I seriously mean it when I say it's not as weird as you think it is. My case was actually fairly similar to yours - all the girls in our program had crushes on Richard, he was super sweet, funny, good looking, etc. - and I was surprised that it was me he was interested in. When I was in the program I was 16/17. He waited until I was more than a few months into 18 and we were in different programs at camp to even talk to me outside of camp in more than a "camp friends on Favebook" capacity. We talked about it once or twice and realized it was a depth thing. He would never have considered any of the other girls because that's all they did - bat their eyelashes and flirt and make raunchy comments. He frequently rolled his eyes and made fun of the leader of the girl pack that was the worst - a sort-of friend of mine who bragged about how she thought Richard was checking her out, how she could get him to kiss her, etc. It was during a leadership camp program that dealt with a lot of emotional topics and seeing how different people handled them. He was impressed at my maturity, which is the thing that made him want to hang out with me after camp. 

After we hung out a half dozen times I still had this itchy feeling like something was off - he must have done this with all the girls, or maybe he made some weird assumption about me - nope. He just continued to date me on and off, introduce me to some friends of his, etc. It was all very... normal. All in all, we probably only saw each other regularly for maybe 4 months over two years. I didn't want to be clingy, he worked a lot (worked in Hollywood) but we had unreal chemistry and it gave me the most incredible confidence boost. 

He's probably just as nervous as you are, judging by what you've told us about his actions. But there's zero harm in going out with the guy if you're also interested in him. He may avoid social functions with the big groups because he's just tired of being hit on. And the fact that he was clear about his professional boundaries up front was as much a reassurance as a stipulation - he doesn't want to burden you with feeling like it's weird, and he doesn't want this to ever be a situation where you could be uncomfortable, and he's willing to just drop the subject entirely if you aren't 100% for it or if he sees that things might get weird in any sense. But he was willing to give it a shot and be super supportive to you regardless of what you answered him with. That's respect. Date the shit outta this guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 06:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only because Jaqen made a girl leave it on the street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc was like "wow it's easy to make credits short when one actress is playing half the characters in a show" 

Tatiana Maslany as Sarah, Beth, Cosima, Alison, Helena, Rachel, Krystal, and Sarah's Magical Hair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 09:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing says romantic gesture like rose petals on a toilet ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They definitely won't let in the spray. You might be able to bring in one of the two lip things but it depends on who checks your stuff. Some nights you get someone who inspects the seal on your Chapstick, sometimes you get someone who couldn't care less. I would bring maybe a glossy/shinier Chapstick or a cheap drugstore lipgloss and not risk the real lip products. Sometimes they'll literally just throw it away in front of you. 

Best bet is blotting sheets to keep the oil and sweat at bay and a tinted Chapstick (think Burt's Bees) that you won't mind losing if they toss it. Either way, also bring a real moisturizing Chapstick, sealed. Don't risk chapped lips. Comfort first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best totem imo
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent so long fighting to protect myself and my sister from my parents. Now that I've been free a while I realize I have no f*cking clue what to do about it. I'm in a Target parking lot with no clue what to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 06:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brief history: myself (25F) and my sister (22F) were raised by a pair of bipolar Ns who frequently switched between being and and Es. Both were on and off medication for mental health issues. I have always been fiercely protective of my younger sister, even though I was the SG and she was the GC and she didn't get picked on much. My parents would get violent but the second they raised a hand to my sister, I physically got in the way. Outwardly we were a great family - active in Girl Scouts and school stuff, super smart kids with a penchant for troublemaking, all very friendly, etc. Our parents worked in tandem - they'd egg each other on. We had many recoveries and relapses that therapy could not fix. Four and a half years ago my parents divorced and I moved in with the guy I'm about to marry. My parents are both still flaming Ns but I don't have to deal with them more than once a month (my mom) or three times a year (my dad, who replaced our family with a nearly-identical-to-us set of sisters and a single mother three hours away). Even after all that crap though, during my childhood my family was very close. We didn't have any cousins or anything so it was just us. We were poor most times and we stuck together, even if it was actually painful. I can't believe I fucking miss that. I miss my family. I miss my violent bipolar emotionally abusive mother and my aggressive opioid addicted father. I miss the good times - the camping trips between phases and the Disneyland days. 

Over the past four years I've held multiple jobs (nanny, personal assistant, cook, waitress, admin assistant, freelance artist, etc.) My current job is the longest I've ever held, at 9 months going on 10. I'm a nanny right now and I generally like what I do, even if my stress levels prevent me from being better at it. I live with my fianc in a tiny one bedroom apartment in the same city I grew up in. Nothing is changing for me. I don't want to go back to school, I don't want a desk job, I don't want to do anything. I feel like the constant encouragement then eventual tear down of any of my goals when I was younger has killed any dreams I've had. ("I want to write for a magazine!" I said. "Do it!" My mom said. "Except you'll be miserable and it's not a real job and it's too hard to get a job in that field", she said.) I rarely see my family anymore, my sister and I see each other every few weeks and text maybe once a week. My fianc and I don't have many friends and we're about to start counseling (which I'm actually excited about) to fix some communication issues. We don't do much - he's overly financially conservative. We're actually going on a vacation I basically just booked and told him about, that I'm excited about. I'm partially disabled (degenerative spinal condition; no cure but mine is progressing very slowly which is cool). 

The littlest girl I nanny for asked me "what are snails even trying to do?". I'm that snail right now. I'm a snail in a target parking lot wondering what the fuck happened that made me realize I have no direction in life. I have become such a boring person. I am bored. I am tired. And I don't even have a reason to be tired because I don't do anything. 

I used to write, and I used to write well. I have nine half-finished novels on my laptop that I'm too ashamed to even open. 

I was basically just given a free pass to go to Target and go shopping because I had a really rough day at work - was late to pick up the kids, who were then misbehaving. I accidentally took their van keys home with me so had to drive half an hour back, then another half hour back to this stupid Target. I could get home in four minutes but what's the fucking point? And anyway, all I bought was Shampoo (I was out) and face wash (also out). I, the girl who can stress shop her way around ten Targets, couldn't be bothered to enjoy anything. Nope. 

So I guess I'll drive home. I still don't know what I'm going to do with my life but at least I don't need to go to a therapist to have the revelation that my parents completely destroyed my psyche. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 01:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alllll of the yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 18:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you on the weird pants thing. I'm 5'8" but I have really short legs for my height and a really long upper body. I have like a 27/28 inch inseam on a good day, and a big ol' butt with a smaller waist. So if I buy a size that fits onto my giant my hips, they're five inches too long and there's a giant gape in the back around the waist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Closer is without a doubt my favorite. So good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 15:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have laughed at me too. I'm leaving it there. For posterity's sake. You know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would give my left arm for this to be true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! I remembered because if I close my eyes he kinda sounds like Steve Carrell. Also I've been catching my sister up on the show and we just watched that episode so the voice was stuck in my head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 08:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have such mixed feelings about Rachel but when Evie said that I turned to my fianc and I was like "I want Rachel to stab her in the face so hard right now."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 07:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so impressed with her hair that I almost didn't cringe at her total debauchery. That hair goes places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 07:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. Scott has been a more dependable friend/lap partner than Delphine. And he's technically been around longer. And also he was never a double agent working for Dyad. Scott is the man, damn it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprise, I have curly hair! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 01:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be overwhelming for a first time. If she drinks, make sure she can have a few to relax. If she's into party favors, go that route. 

Places to take a break/take it in: 

- Ferris Wheels 

- Any ride line really (they're not bad for people watching for sure) 

- Going up into the stands to watch it all (this is a favorite for my fianc and I, especially on the side facing Cosmic Meadow - you can still catch a set while you're sitting somewhere not too loud/crowded when you need a break) 

- Finding a table/bench near the center area is nice too. There are tons of buildings with places to sit and hang out for a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> File a claim ASAP. Etsy isn't stupid, they work with you. Especially if it's been that long. 

Also Electric Laundry is taking orders for EDC until Friday, so if you wanted a badass outfit that's your best bet. They're reputable. I've had two bad experiences with two different Etsy shops regarding outfits. I just make my own now lol but I'm crafty and not everyone can be. Try EL!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I legit almost bought some! My group met up with this one girl's cousin who had a table and kept the bottles coming. I wore heels and I NEVER wear heels. I was dying. And really, really drunk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 22:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm going to a festival in a few weeks and I'm totally copying this, though it looks a thousand times better on your skin tone than it will on mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Girl Scouts for 12 years - just missed my Daisy year. When myself and two of my old friends joined a new troop after my mom disbanded ours (changed work schedules and nobody stepped up) things seemed great - until the leader started playing favorites towards her daughter and her friends, who were two years older. Long story short, we ended up switching troops. We each had about $1000 in individual earned money - the monetary reward of cookie sales since we opted out of prizes over the years, common in our council - and when we left the leader wouldn't give us our money. She kept it and the next year, when the older girls were trying to decide on a senior trip, her daughter got to go on the trip and also managed to spend her money on a "makeover" before college - and I'm talking like $3k worth of clothes, purses, makeup, the whole deal. Wonder where that $3k of "her" senior money came from. Ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word. Five years ago before I got together with the man I am about to marry, I thought of myself as a straight girl who also was just comfortable enough to admit when women were attractive. Five years of maturing and honest conversations about sex with my now fianc and I realize that I was basically delusional :) I am going to go with 5/7ths gay. I only dated guys before my fianc (and plenty of them) but ends up I was just not being honest with myself. Met some open, awesome people who fall on every point imaginable within the spectrum and figured out what was going on with my confused lady parts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 19:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking... *Captain Crunch*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my fianc and I both: 

Tickets: ~$870
Hotel: 6 nights/ ~$1,000
Driving to Vegas: $50 
Shuttle: $178
Food/Drinks: $600
My Outfits: ~$250
Gifts/Souvenirs: $250
Ubers to Shuttle Stop: $30
Additional Activities: $150
Play Money: $500
Total? We'll probably end up around 4k. 

Could it be used for our upcoming wedding? Yep. 

Will it? Nope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My FH and I have a reeeeally similar budget and every time I talk to anyone younger about it they get mad. Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 00:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25F coming from just south of Los Angeles, I'm a full-time Nanny. Fianc (27M) is a Software Engineer. We never get long vacations for just the two of us so a full week in Vegas with EDC at the tail end is going to be amazing! This is our third EDC (went in 2012/"The Year the Wind Fucked Shit Up" and 2015) and our first time going without anyone else. I'm so excited. T-minus four weeks until sweet sweet vacation!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 05:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL I wish I would have thought of that. I was at CG too when the wind really picked up, I saw the speakers sway too and it was like "oh, those giant speakers could probably crush a bitch." They mentioned once that it might delay the next set and at some point my SO and I decided to jump ship and just sat in the stands for a while. I was rolling pretty good and the wind felt incredible on me and I remember saying something along the lines of "I'm not even mad, this wind feels so fucking good right now." 

I would have paid decent money to see some girl tripping and asking for piggy back rides. Good on you for helping her out though, I watched shit get chaotic from the stands and was glad I wasn't down there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was there and it totally blew. Pun intended. One of our friends ended up sticking around and checking out the art car stuff though and had an awesome time by himself lol. Two stages were still playing shit iirc and that was enough for some people but soooooo many people left. Fingers crossed for minimal wind this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SO has a hard time feeling any effects. Dosage help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO and I have rolled together ~10 times over four years. We're very selective users, usually only a really good show or a festival. 

I'm 5'7 and 180ish, F. I take a half pill of anything decent and I roll pretty hard. I am fairly sensitive to MDMA (which is great because I'm a cheap ass). My SO, however, has only really "rolled" maybe twice. Other times he says he feels good/relaxed but nowhere near the same level as I get. He's 6'3 and 220, so that has to have something to do with it, but he also has a hard time getting drunk. He can drink like a motherfucker and be buzzed. The one time he rolled really hard, we split a pill from NL that was super high dosage and were both great allll night. The next time it took him 2 pills to start feeling anything and another one and a half to really feel good. 

How should he dose? I'm not sure on exact mg levels on past rolls because we were noobs and didn't really care. We're about to get decent stuff and split it up ourselves, no pressed stuff this time, but not sure how he should dose so that he can roll hard with me! We're going to EDC in 4 weeks, our first time going without friends, and so stoked to roll together again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it a few times when you have plenty of time at home - either entirely at home or following an event/party. Spending a few hours just talking and being cuddly can carry over looooong after the roll starts. My FH and I have had the most amazing, heartfelt talks that have totally changed our relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 05:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah he usually is but the panic was so real. He's the mutual favorite of my fianc and I so I was like nuuuuuu _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 05:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I didn't hear him and I legit almost cried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 04:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnnd you're dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 03:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnnnd my app chooses tonight to crap out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 01:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way we can be sure is if you redo the whole first part of the movie for us. You know - the sad piano, the dumb songs. The scene where he drops his towel. That kinda thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they both graduated with flyyyyyying colors!~  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to make cards this year but I would forget to hand them out, lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a big raised and glazed donut for breakfast this morning. I skipped my coffee/creamer combo so I could have this treat and I'll watch breakfast and lunch, but... These donuts. You don't understand. They're my occasional breakfast treat and they're worth every damn calorie. I've finally also reached that point where I know how to balance and "make up for it".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE this. I also have a minor obsession with how certain peel off tints look before you peel them off and thought I was the only one, so this was great to see!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 22:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or if by "tailgate" you mean "it's too hot to stay out here lets dump the rest of this vodka into a water bottle we can toss and just chug it in line" then totally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 01:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your shuttle choice. Not sure about Insomniac shuttles but JC doesn't have an official spot yet iirc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SG oldest child - 25F - haven't seen my nDad in months. I was very close with him when I was younger so I'm struggling. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 01:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little bit of background - I'm 25, my sister is 3 years younger. Until I turned 18-20 it was just my parents and my sister. My mom was a vicious, abusive, mentally unbalanced N for my entire pre-teen to Young Adult life. She always took it out on me. Everything. My sister was the GC. She and my mom have always been close. My dad and I were close when I was young - he's a textbook vain/pathological liar N and had some anger issues/was scary but never got as bad as my mom. My mom loved to kick me out of the house, starting around 16, then wait for me to beg my way back into the house. I didn't. Eventually she'd beg me back when it became clear to everyone else I wasn't going to grovel. My dad was almost always my advocate, he'd have these bizarre moments of clarity and back me up or have decent conversations with me. 

When I turned 20, they divorced. It was ugly. It was fucking ruthless. Both of them lied about not having affairs, both of them started behaving totally bizarrely (my mom would have extended Manic episodes and basically reverted to a 16 year old, my dad basically all but disappeared). 

My dad remarried shortly after. His new family is identical to our old one. His wife is like my mom (very overweight, a little gaudy, overbearing/controlling). His daughters are a few years apart and just like my sister and I. They do all the same stuff my family used to do together. At first we all got along great - I'd stay at their house, we went over for holidays, I talked to everyone often. That changed a little over a year and a half ago. My dad has always been a shit communicator but it got to the point that I couldn't get a hold of him without going through my Estepmother. She would make crazy excuses for him, she would say "well he tells me he calls you all the time and you don't pick up!". Bullshit. One time when we went out there, after she'd fed me this line the first time, I showed her my call logs. I don't use my phone to call people often so I had like 8+ months of records. He'd called me once. I'd called him two dozen times. I texted him almost weekly. He texted back four times. When he did talk to me, he'd swear he would tell me when they had a free day, and then ignore my calls for two months. She accused me of lying. She said "well I sit right next to him when he calls you." Who's lying now? Because he NEVER CALLS first. 

My sister had a baby almost three years ago. She was young, it was unplanned. She knew immediately she wanted to give the boy up for adoption. Open adoption, but still. When she told my dad and stepmother, they lost their shit. They told her she was making a mistake, that she'd never see her baby again and he'd hate her, that if she didn't want her child that they'd take him and raise him for her. She was 18. She didn't need that. I told them - firmly but politely - to back the fuck off. That this wasn't their decision to make. Jesus fuck, they wouldn't give up. They called, they cried., they screamed at me and begged me to change her mind. It was an OPEN adoption and my sister and the adoptive mother had been clear that they'd see each other often. We go on vacation with their family sometimes! But that wasn't enough for dad. We see the kid at least every other month, even though they're an hour away. But neither my sister or the adoptive mother were happy with my dad and stepmom when they did this, obviously. He was told that he had to drop this behavior if he ever wanted to meet his grandson. That if he wanted to meet the kid, the first meeting would be him ONLY - no step family. After that we'd introduce more new people. Understandable. My dad wouldn't take it. He insisted his brand new wife, who he'd dated for less than a year, had to be there. That was not part of the arrangement. He would not respect that simple request. He couldn't follow one fucking rule. My nephew turns three next month and he's an absolute joy. My father has still never met him. He doesn't even talk about him now. He avoids him in conversation. 

I got engaged in December. And I realized fairly quickly that I don't want my father walking me down the aisle. It's going to be a hard talk because we were so close and because he's lied to all of our extended family about how we hate him and never want to see him (which I found out by running into my great-aunt in a supermarket and her shaming me. A woman I loved so much as a kid. I just told her there were two sides to every story, that everyone in the family knows my dad is a habitual liar, and that if she wanted to believe that guy over me and my sister, that was her choice.) I called my dad to tell him about my engagement after my FH proposed and he basically couldn't care less. He offered to pay for my dress (but only if I went to this cheap, tacky seamstress his wife went to for her dress that imitates nicer dresses with cheap materials) and then said he'd just contribute. Recently though he backed out again and said they were tight on money but they'd love to help plan. (They just went on like four trips and buy a new car every year, my dad isn't working and his wife sells insurance so yeah they're short on money if they'd living this far outside their means). I'm totally independent and doing all the planning with my fianc. And it's not about the money. I couldn't care less if they contributed. But I texted my DAD to ask if they were planning on contributing and his WIFE texted me back to say they couldn't anymore. A week later after I didn't respond to that, he texted me saying we should have dinner and talk about it. But they want to help plan. No. Also you're tacky. But thanks/no thanks. 

He came to our engagement party in early February and helped us move two weeks later. I haven't seen him since. It's hard. I know he's changed and he basically abandoned us for his new family. I've finally accepted that his initial intentions may have been to combine families and spend time together. But he moved two hours away and never calls me back. He backs out on all his promises and lies to our faces and is never really happy for me. 

I'm not going to chase after a relationship with my father anymore. If he wants to see his biological children ever again, if he ever wants to see his grandchildren, it's his job now. I'm done trying. I miss him so much - how he used to be. The dad that got tattoos with me for my 20th birthday because we were pissed at my mom during the divorce. The dad that built a beer pong table with me and watched stupid shows with me and used to give the best hugs. But he's not that guy anymore.

Oddly enough, my mom has totally turned around with me. I mean she's still a total N but she's actually *almost* pleasant to be around sometimes. If she's bothered by the slightest thing she's a pain in the ass but she actually isn't always awful anymore. My sister still lives with her and we all have dinner once or twice a month. Sometimes she meets me for lunch break on work days. It's actually sort of nice.  

But my dad. Ugh. I'm not going NC. He basically put himself in self-imposed VLC. But I'm giving up. If he wants to keep up that's his thing. But I'm not making any effort for someone who doesn't care anymore. It's just hard. This hurts more than the abuse from my mom did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tropicana is going to be the next closest. We're staying at Monte Carlo and were super bummed when MGM sold out since it's right there. We booked juscollege Tropicana  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 23:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *screams internally* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See a doc about this one. Could be that a hair down there got pulled/irritated and is now ingrown. Infections there cannot be fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 07:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ordered the book, thanks for the rec! Sounds super interesting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 07:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually brought up the above book to him and at first he was kind of quiet but then he was like "could I have Asperger's?" And he's curious. So at least I didn't have to breach that question with him. It's likely that it would have been missed in school since, from what I can tell, he was quiet/had great grades/kept to himself and played a LOT of computer games/built and rebuilt his computer often. His family can be a little weird/detached and his mom is certainly the type that, if approached with the idea, would have laughed it off with "my kid? Never!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! Milia, Acne, nose pores, need a routine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first thought too. And OP, EDS can manifest in many many different ways. It's worth seeing a doctor and at least getting some advice, keeping an eye on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental Health services are covered by MediCal, but they're actually contracted out to another organization, Beacon Help Strategies. MediCal itself doesn't do referrals or anything to do with Mental Health, they just foot the bill depending on the TYPE of care you receive. I myself just scheduled my first Psychiatrist appointment through MediCal this last week. If you have any other questions about it or how it works or the phone number for Beacon, don't hesitate to PM me! They will even work with you to keep your records/history safe so that your parent doesn't see/can't interfere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 04:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! GI issues are the worst with weight loss because it's like doctors told me "eat bland! Go eat crackers and bread" and I was just like bruh no this is not working for me 

We really only work out two, maybe three times per week. Usually just cardio for now until I get a little more in shape. I have to be really careful with my back which is annoying but getting stronger will help that. I have a semi-active job 3-4 days a week as a nanny, so 10 hour days chasing a toddler around, walking places, etc. On a work day I easily clock 10k steps. 

But my biggest thing is food and portion control. I used to be so out of control when it came to food, and it isn't good for my body in any way. Eating really clean and juicing for breakfasts some mornings and lots of tea. Little snacks here and there so I don't feel like I'm going to binge the second I see a bakery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 01:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My #1 goal this year was "comfortable but cool". I got a dedicated pair of comfortable walking shoes to be rave shoes that I can get dirty and smushed up, and they are super cool ~Skechers~. Fianc will be carrying a camelbak that we decorate with EL wire to carry shit so I don't have to. For reference, I'm 25F and a curvier girl/size 12. With that said: 

Outfit #1: 
- Little Black Diamond Outlaw shorts in Black 
- LBD Sequin Halter Top
- Hair up in two high buns, glitter+hair gel on my part for maximum trendiness, smoky eye makeup. 
- Black socks, rave shoes 

Outfit #2: 
- Tie-Dye Halter bodysuit that I'm ordering from HarleyMade on Etsy. These are seriously the coolest bodysuits and they can be made with custom colors! I'm just getting a full pastel rainbow! 
- Possibly the LBD shorts on top if I feel too uncomfortable in just the bodysuit. 
- Tie-Dye crew socks also from HarleyMade, rave shoes 
- Hair kinda braided/flower crown (still haven't figured that one out yet) 

Outfit #3: 
- A LBD bodysuit that I wore last year, but this year I'm sewing EL wire onto it in a cool pattern! 
- White crew socks/rave shoes 
- Hair unknown (buns?) 

Still have some tweaking to do but I have 80% of the stuff bought and ready. I tried doing the whole corset/tutu thing once last year and I was so sick of it by the end of the night. Not comfortable at all. My favorite outfit last year was just high waisted stretchy black shorts and a cool galaxy patterned crop top with a thin bralette. I learned. This year is 100% about comfort first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, true that. I just have a hard time figuring out how to make it stick with him. Sometimes I make it very clear that I'm in pain and I need a little support/hugs/whatever and he just doesn't get it. I know that he can't possible understand the pain that I'm in because it's not in his body and I don't expect him to know. That's something we'll have to address in therapy. 

But last week I was in the ER and he was sitting right next to me and I had to keep reaching out to him/asking him to move closer/etc. And since then he's been better, but this was a big issue for us - I'd literally be in the hospital in so much pain and he'd be sitting ten feet away, distracted, saying "There's nothing I can do to stop your pain". Well, yeah, but you can make me FEEL better, and he wasn't understanding the difference. 

I see your point about addressing it beforehand though. I probably need to give him a clearer heads up, i.e., we're at work during the day and I'm in pain, instead of just saying "Ugh I have a ton of nerve pain today" and thinking that's enough, I should probably rephrase it to something like "hey, heads up, I'm having a lot of nerve pain today and will need a hand with the dishes/will need some more comfort and care" kind of thing. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we both knew before this even that we've got some issues we'd like to iron out before actually getting married. We're not planning on getting married for at least another year, so this IS that time for us. We are genuinely happy together, we just do have some things to iron out over the next 12-18 months. This therapy for us isn't so much "omg we need to go to therapy to save our relationship" so much as "we need a neutral third party who can help us find better ways to thrive in this relationship". I have a very healthy idea of therapy, I've struggled with anxiety and depression for a while so I'm not turned off or worried by the idea of therapy on its own, I'm actually excited to see what it can do for us. I think it took him so long to agree to therapy because his mom/family has a very twisted idea of mental health and 'getting help'. (His mom once said, matter-of-factly at the dinner table, that people with mental health problems shouldn't be allowed to own guns or have children. She doesn't know about my depression/anxiety. No grandchildren for her then I guess.) He's finally seeing that it's a tool, not a life raft, which is great. 

I'll have to check that out. It's weird but over our conversations about this, I have thought about the similarities between my FH's behavior and Asperger's. I've never brought it up with him because it's not really my place, I'm not assuming he has it or anything and that's the kind of thing we can work out in counseling, but a good friend of mine was in a LTR with a man with Asperger's and their reactions/behaviors are strikingly similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My [25F] fiance [27M] of 4 mos, partner of 4.5 yrs, has major trouble with emotional cues/sensitivity. Took months for us to reach this conclusion and unsure where to go from there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little context: I'm 25, a full-time/salaried Nanny for three great kids, I have a number of health problems but for the most part, I'm alright. He's 27, Software Engineer, had never had a girlfriend (or even kissed anyone) before me. I met him through friends of friends at a party. I had actually casually dated one of his friends for a while, it wasn't a secret, but long after the friend and I stopped seeing each other, I met my now fiance and we immediately hit it off. He seemed shy and I'd seen him around but never talked to him before. I continued to think he was just "shy" for some time, and during the honeymoon phase of our first year or so, it was just that. I was diagnosed with a degenerative spinal condition two and a half years ago, it isn't progressive thank goodness but it still causes a lot of pain and problems. We've always had a great sex life, even though sometimes we go a week or so without it. 


After that first year, I feel like we've just had so many minor communication problems that have acquiesced into something far worse. When we fight, or when I express that I'm upset over something he's done, he tends to stonewall me and just totally tune out. He won't even look at me while I'm talking, and I have to sit there in silence for a solid minute and let him think then prompt him with a "What are you thinking?". He just doesn't know how to talk about things that are bothering us, he doesn't know how to apologize. We both get pretty defensive when we argue, we both know that, but sometimes it's like talking to a brick wall. He's said some pretty insensitive stuff in the past (that my job isn't a "Real" job because I make roughly 1/3 of what he does, stuff about how emotional I get, etc) that is pretty hurtful. We make jokes about him being a robot but it's not so much humor as it is a ridiculously accurate statement about the state of his emotional IQ. He just has no idea how to handle emotional situations anymore. I feel like the initial rush of endorphins at the beginning of our relationship showed me this caring, romantic, loving guy, and that guy has slowly slipped away. He seems to think about everything in black and white now, and it's getting frustrating. 


He's made comments about my weight indirectly. We are both trying to eat healthier and lose weight, he knows I'm really uncomfortable with my body, but he seems to think that it's "helpful" to make comments that are sometimes rude about something I'm eating/doing/talking about in reference to getting healthy. Harsh comments about "are you really going to eat that?" and stuff like that, which he doesn't mean to be harsh - I know this - but that are really insensitive, and he doesn't understand why. He just sees it as a roadblock to progress. 


We had a huge talk this last weekend about him shutting down and what he does in these situations. We had sort of an awkward night before (tmi: we were trying to spice up our sex life with a little "game" and we didn't communicate fully what the goal was, so things got awkward really fast when we both got confused) and I just wanted to talk through it so that we wouldn't entirely abandon the idea of making things interesting in the bedroom. At first the conversation went okay, we started talking about a few other things that were bothering us, he seemed to at least be verbalizing, but then he just started shutting down before we could reach any real conclusion. When I thought he'd just reached the end of his communication rope and tried to end the conversation with a kiss and makeup sort of strategy, I just sort of went over what we'd talked about ("I promise I'll just ask next time" and, from him "You need to just tell me to my face immediately when I'm being insensitive"). We were sort of joking around after cuddling, as we are known to do, and he was like "You need to just call me on my shit." I was like "I will try! And you need to call me on my shit too!" (re: dishes, at which I am a known procrastinator) All of the sudden he loudly just says "I can't call you on your shit, you just yell at me and there's no 'right' way to bring things up with you." 


Long story short, this is a concern he's had for a while that is completely justified. I grew up in a difficult household, lots of yelling and blaming and problems, so I'm used to confrontation when it comes to household chores, he's not. If he asks me to clean up a mess I've made, I'll usually put it off. Sometimes, though, he asks when he knows I'm having a lot of pain that day and can barely walk. I think of this as insensitive, considering I need help getting up the stairs to our apartment, how on earth am I supposed to be picking up the bedroom and the living room? Why can't it wait until tomorrow when I feel better? So I get defensive because I HURT, I am in physical pain, and he is acting like I'm just gaffing off. 


So the argument doesn't end well again, and we start talking again, and then he just goes dead silent for several minutes. I can tell he's thinking hard about something, I know this about him, so I let him think. And then he tells me that he knows something is wrong with him. He sees how upset I get when he gets harsh or gets weird and he knows that this is not normal, but he doesn't feel like what he's saying is wrong. He's not defending himself at all, he's just saying that he knows this behavior is wrong, and he knows he's probably being insensitive, even if he doesn't see it at the time. His (almost) exact words were "I feel like I'm missing so many emotional cues that you give me, so I'm upsetting you and being a dick because I just don't understand what these cues are and how to read them." I want to say "well, I tell you when I'm in pain and I've asked you to stop commenting about health stuff approximately 11 billion times" but I don't do that. I know he's trying to fix this. And I know that in the past, I've hesitated to bring up things he's done wrong (I was in a long term emotionally and physically abusive relationship a few years before him, so I still have that mentality at times that I don't want to do anything that could upset him).  So I try to ask him for examples. He brings up our biggest problems - his harsh comments, his lack of empathy, etc - and I feel like we're finally getting somewhere. We agreed that we'd do some research into fixing this (he's going to read a few books, do some research on emotional disconnects in relationships, etc, and I'm going to do the same) and we're going to look into therapy. 


We love each other so much. We got engaged a few months ago and we know we're going to get married and have weird children and it's going to be great. But he's finally admitting that he needs some help re: communication and I'm just so at a loss with where to start. What books should we be reading? What articles? What should we actually put into practice as far as trying to "call each other out" and be plain about when he's upsetting me? I know I could literally turn around and say "You're being an asshole" and he'd be fine with that. But I don't want to make him feel bad about it, I really don't. I want a way that will bring it up to him respectfully but honestly enough that he takes it seriously. I have a hard time standing up for myself and saying "What you just said is really rude" or "You need to lay off because I'm in a lot of pain and you're being an asshole" so it's been building up. I didn't give him big enough cues, he missed them entirely, but the things he said - regardless of cues - were a bit harsh. 


Wow. That ended up way too long. Thank you for reading through the whole thing if you got this far. I'm just at a point where I know we're going to have to put some hard work into this, but I don't know where to go from here. I desperately want us to be better at this communication thing. 


**tl;dr**: Fiance and I have communication issues because he's basically a robot, we had a conversation and he admitted he's lacking emotional intelligence/sensitivity and he doesn't know how to fix it. Wondering where we can start re: books, articles, research before we go into therapy soon so he can see this laid out logically/scientifically and if anyone has any ideas for how to better our communication in the mean time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 04:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what you wear, aim for comfort. I've had outfits that I go all out - corset, tutu, etc - and it's just uncomfortable and it gets really annoying. Never again. My favorite outfits have been the comfiest - high waist black stretch shorts and a cool crop top, and a bodysuit. 

I get 80% of my rave wear at Little Black Diamond. Their stuff is so comfortable and usually really flattering. My bodysuit was from them, my crop top was from them, and this year I have a full outfit that's LBD. Prices are a little higher than some but the stuff is good, they have great customer service, and stuff doesn't take a month to get there like some sites. (PS I'm technically a little bigger than their size chart says they fit, but their stuff fits me no problem. So their sizing is flexible, if anyone is wondering.) 

This year: 

1: LBD Black Outlaw shorts and LBD Sequin Halter Top, comfortable running shoes. Hair up in two lil buns with a glitter part because I am a trendy fuck. 

2: Last year's LBD bodysuit, but I'm going to sew EL wire into it so I light up! Comfortable running shoes. Maybe also lil buns with glitter part. Because that sounds a: cool and b: literally cool, keeping my curly hair off my neck. 

3: Tie-dye bodysuit I'm ordering from HarleyMade on Etsy. Tie-dye crew socks. Comfortable running shoes. Flower crown, hair braided up a bit to keep it up. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At home, we just make it with minced tuna and sriracha. Sometimes adjusting (salt/spice/sesame seeds) if we want. I like it fairly simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 09:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gwendoline Christie is a fucking TREASURE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 08:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fianc and I have a black light bar (he used to rent a townhouse with friends that was v much the "party house") and the first year we went to EDC together, we hopped in the shower after Saturday or Sunday, flipped on the black light, and just gave each other back rubs and hugs and played some music. Switched water temp between warm and pretty cold. Felt so good. 10/10 do recommend even solo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've done two different things:

1. Put each one in a gallon ziplock, blow air into it for padding, seal, and keep them in a separate tote bag 

2. Keep them in a shoe box. 

Both worked fine, tbh. As long as you carry them separately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeeeeah! My fianc and I will be there a full week. Got a pretty good deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Goal Achieved: Onederland and no longer Obese! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 20:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all! So, hitting Onderland wasn't as big of a success for me as it is for some people - my start weight was 203. Two weeks ago I dipped under 200 and then I didn't weigh myself for two weeks for various reasons (see below). 

F/25/5'8"
SW: 203 
CW: 196.8
GW: 125

So my fianc and I started being healthier almost exactly a month ago, started going to the gym straight after work, etc. We've been on and off the wagon for the last two years but this is IT. 

Then two things happened: 
1. A car ran through the front window of our gym, which closed it for several days (it just reopened) 
2. I was in the hospital briefly for health issues (of which I have many: degenerative spinal condition, GI issues, cluster headaches, and more!) 

So I haven't been the best over the past two weeks. In fact, we've been eating just slightly better than we used to. 

But I stepped on the scale this morning to see that I'd lost 2 pounds in the past 2 weeks (less than before but still awesome!) and when I went to track my BMI, I realized that 

1. I've been solidly back in Onederland for two weeks and 
2. As of this morning's weigh in, I am no longer in the Obese BMI range! 

#2 was my first real goal. And becoming Obese was the kick in the pants for me. I'd always been overweight (since middle school, when I developed much faster than anyone else my age and my metabolism dropped out) but Obese was not good. My health and my body can't handle Obese. I know there's a possibility the scale will tip back up and I might cross back over, but I'm going to do my best to make sure that doesn't happen! 

We just found out yesterday that our gym reopened the day before, and we're also starting a Whole30 today (we've done one before with good results and feeling better, meal prep day is today) so I'm hoping I can get these losses back up to speed and kick some butt! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 07:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Varys is playing his own game, and it's not a winning game. 

Littlefinger is playing the long game. He knows what he's doing and he's doing it in a way that he won't be suspected or fucked over. He's a sneaky little dude and I'm rooting for him, low key, even though he does some screwed up shit sometimes. He's playing one of the smartest games out there to do as well for himself as he can, and so far he's succeeded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 04:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it now I'm going to be thinking about Donnie "Geriatric Skater" Hendrix every time I hear that song  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 01:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fianc and I are doing more this year than last year - in previous years we've stayed at a vacation time share thing his mom does so we only paid like $100 a week for hotel. This time we're staying on-strip and doing a shuttle instead of driving, so... 

For two people, six nights seven days: 
Tickets: ~$800
Hotel: $1000
Shuttle: $178 
Food: we're planning on bringing protein bars for "breakfasts" and eating lunch and dinner out on non-EDC days, so ~$400
Alcohol: $40 
Other: $100-150
Extra show: $60 (maybe)
Merch, souvenirs, incidentals: $200 

Low end? $2500. High end? $3000. 

Annnnnnd now I'm glad tickets, hotel, and shuttles are already mostly paid for. Still have like $200 on hotel. We're like 3/4 paid for. Whew. 

We've been together four and a half years and somehow we've never taken a full week vacation just us. It's always with family for a week or a long weekend just us. We decided to "do it big" (as big as our budget allows) and take a real Vegas trip as grown ups. I'm so fucking excited you guys. Not worrying about trying to meet up with people between sets is going to be amazing. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rude parents at the middle daughters school said something awful about her. Don't know if she heard, wondering how I should bring it up to her mom if at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 01:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a family with three kids (9M, 7F, and 3F) in an affluent suburb in Southern California. This is a town of designer shoes, stay-at-home moms, and an educational foundation for the small local schools that pledges upwards of $5,000,000 per year. This is new money, fast cars, bad attitudes. I got extremely lucky with the family I nanny for. They're well off, from what I can tell, but unlike so many around here they're super down to earth, funny, and relaxed. They make fun of the crappy people in the neighborhood with me. Their kids are all amazingly smart, funny, warm kids who (despite normal kid acting out) are honestly a nanny's dream. I make decent money playing silly games and going on adventures. 

The middle, we'll call her Sparkles, is 7. Sparkles is a 7 year old girl, and that comes with the normal set of bizarro behaviors and odd dress sense. She can be sensitive, she can be a brat, but mostly she's just a living personification of a rainbow and I adore her to death. 

However, in this neighborhood, she tends to get picked on. It's not super obvious because it's only really been happening over the last few months, but her group of friends has started leaving her out and saying a few rude things. Girl drama is girl drama. But these kids are different, and the moms get involved. The girls are dressing nicer, maturing a little faster, all egged on by the parents. 

Sparkles has a very... Unique sense of style. Her mom certainly doesn't pick out her outfits, like some of these kids. For example, one of the first days I worked for them, she wore a Steelers jersey, a pink lacy skirt her grandma sewed for her, striped leg warmers, and water shoes. She just wears things, she's not super concerned with how it looks. 

She's also very sensitive but also fairly strong about it. If someone says something that she thinks is unfair, or not nice, she just ices them for up to several days. Straight up won't look at this person. And while sometimes her other "friends" will talk to her, sometimes they don't, and she has a hard week because nobody else will play with her. 

She's fairly confrontational but also prone to much crying. She picks at her face and does gross stuff and can be a little... Creepy. She really is just this sweet innocent kid. And while I know her mom knows about at least most of this, today one of the moms said something that I think is inexcusable for an adult to say about a child. 

Sparkles was running around the school lawn right in front of me with her sister while we were waiting for the brother to get out. One of the moms turns to me and starts talking about them. We talk about the talent show that happened two months ago, where Sparkles did a silly dance routine with her big group of ~15 friends. The mom expressed surprise that Sparkles is such a happy, silly kid. She said she was surprised at how much Sparkles' personality came out on stage and how cute it was. I was just about to gush about how much I adore her because she's so unique and she treasures her individuality when the mom says, verbatim: 

"I mean, I know nobody else really likes her. They just feel sorry for her because she's weird. It's good to see she can still smile." 

Uh, WHAT? This is a first grader you're talking about. A seven year old girl. How would you like it if I told you nobody likes your kid and they all pity her? I kind of gave her a look like "do you realize what you just said?" And reiterated that Sparkles is the sweetest kid I know. Then got up and walked away. 

I know what she said isn't entirely true - Sparkles was invited to her friends house this afternoon and she's there now. But she said it so matter-of-fact and so blithely, right in front of the kid. I'm not sure if she heard or not - she's the kind of kid who would ignore it to save face and then just melt down later. But I'm 80% sure she didn't. 

On the chance she did, though, I'd like to maybe warn the mom re:what was said and by who, so that if she's in a particularly crappy mood later, she can figure it out quicker. But how do I say that to a mom that values and encourages that originality? 

My heart breaks for this poor girl because I was in her exact position when I was young - I had a huge group of girl friends who ditched me for my weird dress sense and dumb jokes and went on to become the popular girls. It was hard. I remember how much it bothered me, for YEARS. ITS SO SAD. She's such a sweet girl and in any other class of neighborhood she'd just be quirky. Here she legitimately gets picked on, even by grown adults, and I have a feeling that she puts on a brave face but I know exactly how sensitive she can be. 

Has anyone had this happen before? How did you handle it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taaaaape club! I use the clear shiny scotch tape, put it on/pull off the back of my hand to make it slightly less sticky, and do my eyeshadow and liner on top of it. I have hand tremors and this is the only way I can stay even. Magic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What technique did you use for the freckles? I have some Med Brown dipbrow laying around and I'd like to try this out! I have a few natural freckles that disappear under my ruddy complexion and foundation and it makes me sad to hide them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loooove this and am definitely saving this for future festival makeup inspo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried the MAC eye gloss as a back-of-hand swatch this afternoon. It's.  So.  Sticky.  D: and it seemed to stay in place fairly well for ~3 hours but then all the gloss was suddenly gone and all that was left was shimmer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have all of these except Mythology and Era. I basically did the same thing - bought the big double sided palette and a bunch of rosy/neutral shades. 

Haux is my shiiiiiiiit! I am a pale lady with lightish green eyes and I just discovered Haux. It's magic. I can't stop using it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My FH's family goes to Kings Canyon/Sequoia every year. We camp at Sheep Creek and I can't remember it ever being full. You can walk down to a little part of the river with nice inlets for kids to play in the rocks/water where it isn't too strong and you can drive down to the lake in ~20 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 22:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, as someone who has been in your girl's situation, let me give some advice. It's going to be longer but I feel like there are some things I agree with re: her behavior and some things that are a red flag. 

My fianc and I have been together four and a half years. He hadn't ever had a girlfriend before me and spent a lot of time with his family. I had some tough family stuff growing up and my parents went through an awful divorce right around the same time he and I got together. 

I wouldn't say my fianc is especially close with his family - they aren't really emotional, they don't really do things on holidays, etc. But they make plans. All. The. Time. Constantly. Towards the beginning of our relationship we were seeing his family maybe four times a week. FOUR A WEEK. And even though that was only a few weeks, it still got on my nerves. It's not that I don't like his family (his step dad is funny, I love his sister to death, his mom can be pretty overbearing but whatever) it's that I felt like he often would say "yes" any time his mom asked. And to that point, it does turn into a girl vs family kind of thing - did you ever say yes or make plans that might involve her without talking to her about it? My fianc did that. He just assumed it would be fine! We were free Thursday, right? And Saturday? And... Yes. We were free. But that's not how a SO really wants to spend their time - tons of time with the other family. I felt like he couldn't say no to his mom, even at my expense, and that we were missing out on other plans or quality time because his mom always came first.  

And coming from a tough background, I can tell you that it's extremely weird being around "healthy" families. It doesn't make sense to those who haven't been there, but it's so weird. We're always on edge, expecting a fight or an offhand comment or some kind of meltdown. It's so so uncomfortable because I know these are people he loves, but if I see them so much as disagree, I tense up and assume bad things are happening. 

Does it make sense to other people? No. But it could also be the case that someone in your family said something to make your girl uncomfortable and that you either missed it or didn't see that it made her uncomfortable, or that it wasn't meant to be harmful. I would obviously assume that your family aren't awful people. My fiancs family isn't awful. But they have some views that they've voiced once or twice that are horribly offensive. I have a history of mental illness (stemming from, guess where? My family!) and have been on and off medication and in and out of therapy since I was in elementary school. His mom once proclaimed that people with mental illnesses shouldn't be allowed to own guns or reproduce. That they should pretty much all be locked up. She sees the issue very black and white and obviously doesn't know about my problems, so while it was one thing that she said in the middle of another conversation like three years ago, it still bothers me. 

When I met my fianc he didn't seem conservative at all but it has become clear that his parents are conservative to the core. This includes a belief set I strongly disagree with. 

See this problem? I have very serious issues with their personalities and alignments. They can be very cool people and I survive a dinner now and then. But one line from his mom, along with a few other hints here and there, things that wouldn't be particularly offensive to others, is something that tarnished my views.

I'm not saying that this is what happened with your girl. I'm saying it's definitely a possibility and she doesn't want to bring it up with you, because who says "hey! I know you love your parents but I think they have no soul." So she just avoids them when she can.  

Whether it's just being uncomfortable or if she's had another issue that you may or may not know about, there's clearly a problem. She may feel like you're choosing them over her. I can relate. 

BUT. I think she needs to be a little more flexible. For example - my fianc used to have phone calls with his mom for kind of a long time. She'd call him out of the blue and he'd talk to her for half an hour, and meanwhile I'd be waiting for him to help me start dinner. Or he'd stop a show we were watching to call her or to answer her call. 

When I moved in with my fianc and we started having our own routine, interruptions to that routine seemed awful. I just wanted to be free from family ties, given my history, and to be able to live my own adult life with my partner. 

Is she right to tell you NO? Not at all. She needs to compromise. Consider sitting down with her and adding a compromise - if you're going to do less with them in person, and only see them every other week, she needs to give you at least once or twice a week to call them and catch up. Even if it's just a fifteen minute call after work. You need to stand your ground on this, because I know how tough this can be for her and she will try to fight it. Tell her you are not willing to completely give up your parents. You need to be able to see them and speak with them. If you need to set plans in advance, do that. This is what helped me - at least 48 hours warning for a dinner or something so I didn't feel like he was pressuring me to say yes to a dinner that night after we'd already talked about having chicken/sushi/whatever. My big problem was that I felt like any verbal communication we had surrounding that specific day was a "plan" and any interruption to that plan was him choosing anyone else over me. If we talked about going out for Sushi on Friday, he learned not to ask me to change that. I like having routines because I was in a very chaotic living environment with my family for 20 years. I like order and rules and set times. 

Has your girl gone to therapy for any of her family related issues? It helped me immensely to see why I was feeling what I was feeling. And to help me find what I would be comfortable with. If she doesn't want to do that, fine, but it might be helpful for her to talk to a friend or even get on Reddit to hammer out some of those issues and have a sounding board on this matter that isn't you. 

That's the other issue here - you need to be able to compromise and stick to the rules that you guys discuss. You're not willing to give up family, but you'll see them x times per month and be able to call them x times per week. Anything beyond that needs to be approached carefully and in advance. Or not at all. You're completely disregarding her discomfort. It is hard to balance family life as you get older and live out of the house with a partner. That is true of almost every relationship. But as much as you think this is stupid, you need to realize you're making her uncomfortable when you force her to accept family stuff. 

If she's unwilling to compromise? That's a problem. And you need to reassess the relationship. But if you sit down with her and tell her that you are willing to make a compromise but you won't give up your family for her, she'll either work with you or she won't. And if she doesn't, get out of there. It won't get any better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 16:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guy is like this. He's like 6'4 and 220 with a fast metabolism, he rarely gets drunk either. He's really only rolled twice, other times I swear he's got to be feeling it because he behaves a bit differently but he doesn't feel it so much. He usually needs a higher initial dose and like two redoses, sometimes three if he splits them up. 

A friend of mine from high school found out he was metabolizing things so fast that by the time he finished drinking, he was already feeling hungover. He'd be miserable before he even went to bed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 08:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was happening to me - I stopped using brushes with this foundation and moved exclusively to a beauty blender. The formula is matte and sets fairly fast/it's pretty thick, so if any time passes between blending foundation and then trying to smudge something else into it... Patches. 

So I typically pat on any color correcting stuff, then tap concealer anywhere that needs to go, then tap the foundation on last. Tap tap tap. Blending with a brush with this formula didn't work well at all but once I started using the BB, it was flawless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 08:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sonia Kashuk (Target) makes a great lash comb that separates lashes so, so well. I don't know how I lived before this stupid thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 08:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding Este Lauder. It took me ages to find a good match as a pale neutral kinda girl. Most lines, the lightest shade looks too dark or too orange on me. I got matched PERFECTLY with EL double wear and there were still two shades lighter than what I ended up with. 

Urban Decay Naked goes pretty light too. I didn't have an exact match there because of tone problems but my palest friend swears by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 07:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Illness/Duration: Syringomyelia, Fibromyalgia, Cerebro-spinal trauma related issues, Arthritis (possibly rheumatoid), Migraines, Cluster Headaches, Renal Cysts, Liver problems, and undiagnosed malabsorption problems. 

2. Tracking of various symptoms. I don't need an app so much for medication management because I don't take a ton of meds, I just need something that can track my symptoms and keep it all in one place. 

3. Tons! It would be nice to be able to add custom symptoms. I.E. Sleep and exercise by hours, temperature by degrees, urine output by color/volume/frequency, responses to digestive issues (like a check list of qualities based on output), a way to track types of headaches and their attributes (rather than just a pain scale, some sort of multi-step thing including region and type of pain, check the WebMD symptom checker if you don't understand what I'm saying). It would be nice to be able to track depression and anxiety type issues too - tracking mental health symptoms would be a god send because I get so brain-foggy that sometimes I don't remember things. Also, tracking that. How's memory? Etc. For women with things like PCOS, there's a horde of issues. I think your best bet here might be some kind of custom add feature for symptoms since so many people need to track different things. 

4. Yes! I don't like carrying around a physical notebook and I'm fairly lazy about tracking my symptoms. 

5. Social would be a big part of it, but being able to print out a sheet with pertinent information to bring to my various doctors would be amazing. 

6. Reddit, Facebook support groups. There are no local support groups for my neuro condition so it would be nice to be able to talk to other people outside of typical social media. 

7. A forum-type thing might be easiest, but a chat feature for one-on-one or multi-member chats would be good too to form a sort of virtual support group. 

8. All the trackers. And printing everything out.

9. 25F 

10. City, and yet somehow my nearest support group for one of my conditions is in the next state. I live outside Los Angeles. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 04:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No meds. I don't like to take anything regularly. I have a pain med I take maybe once per week when I really need it, and that's it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 01:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep that in mind in 36 days when I'm getting ready and I feel like I need more glitter. The answer will be yes. ty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Lots of people missed this because it was buried in the FAQs. I was like wait wtf I'm going to be there for a week, I have no budget room for $70 extra lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the FAQs: 

Will guests who booked reservations before the paid parking announcement have to pay for parking?

If your reservation was booked prior to May 12, 2016 and your hotel stay occurs after the implementation of fee-based parking you will not be charged for Self-Parking.

All guests utilizing Valet parking will be subject to parking fee if they choose that service, regardless of when the reservation was made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: oops, doubled posted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the FAQs: 

Will guests who booked reservations before the paid parking announcement have to pay for parking?

If your reservation was booked prior to May 12, 2016 and your hotel stay occurs after the implementation of fee-based parking you will not be charged for Self-Parking.

All guests utilizing Valet parking will be subject to parking fee if they choose that service, regardless of when the reservation was made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the FAQs: 

Will guests who booked reservations before the paid parking announcement have to pay for parking?

If your reservation was booked prior to May 12, 2016 and your hotel stay occurs after the implementation of fee-based parking you will not be charged for Self-Parking.

All guests utilizing Valet parking will be subject to parking fee if they choose that service, regardless of when the reservation was made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the FAQs: 

Will guests who booked reservations before the paid parking announcement have to pay for parking?

If your reservation was booked prior to May 12, 2016 and your hotel stay occurs after the implementation of fee-based parking you will not be charged for Self-Parking.

All guests utilizing Valet parking will be subject to parking fee if they choose that service, regardless of when the reservation was made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 21:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just went to my local Rite Aid and CVS. Neither had it. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 19:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a rite aid right next to the bakery I'm currently at. On my way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc would looooove this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 09:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just this evening I went to the ER for stomach pain and was diagnosed with half a dozen small problems related to two renal cysts. Seeing blood work changes like this is a serious booster. It's like "hey not only would i enjoy the shape of me a little more, but also my body would stop actively rebelling against me"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 09:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I'm sorry 
2. I'm sorry 
3. I'm sorry 
4. Everybody in this sub is sorry 
5. Marlene is not sorry 
6. Never forget du-rag sad boy Toby 
7. Don't poke the shippers, they bite. You'll know which ones I mean soon enough. 
8. Be ready to want to drink heavily through entire episodes/seasons/their never ending senior year 
9. Run while you still can 
10. Seriously, A/Marlene is coming and if you run now, you might have a chance 

Seriously though I love this show for exactly what it is, and this sub is a whole new beast to contend with. 

As for serious answers:!
1. Ezria is the creepiest and you don't even know the whole story yet. Just wait. It gets even worse. I thought the teacher/student thing was weird. 
2. Not going to spoil that one for you
3. The police only get less competent as the show goes on. It becomes a meme in and of itself. Rosewood PD is useless. Also, that's too easy and it makes for really boring TV. That is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got another diagnosis. Yay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 08:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiding my foul language inside the actual post. 

Fucking hell. 

After years of bizarre pains and headaches I was diagnosed with a spinal condition called Syringomyelia. Basically I have a fluid filled cyst within my spinal cord. Nerve pain, problems, numbness, problems, blah blah blah. It's been almost three years since then. Not dead yet. Haven't progressed too much, which is freakin' sweet. Still have pain, it's chronic and there's no real "treatment" other than risky surgery, but mine is not debilitating. Awesome. 

Okay, so I also have asthma. I've had breathing problems since high school. I just carry an emergency inhaler. Nothing too bad. 

I also get insanely painful headaches and migraines. There's a multitude of things that can cause one to set off on a day to day basis, but I switch between orbital migraines and cluster headaches. Super. Just great. (If you can't yet pick up on the sarcasm... WHOOSH) 

So lately I've been having... Digestive issues. Tl;dr, my stomach is behaving bizarrely and my movements have changed. I feel like every time I eat I'm in pain and I have ('scuse me for saying this) gnarly gas, and then I have problems continuously. If I literally stop eating for ~12 hours it briefly goes away, then comes back. 

So today I go to the ER because my stomach is in knots and cramping so hard I can't breathe. Also I threw up blood. So there's that. The doc tells me A: you probably have multiple food intolerances. I know I'm lactose intolerant but I don't know about anything else yet. She suggested gluten (ack) and soy (nooooo my soy milk) but possibly also an allergy of some sort. I am pretty much always feeling like crap so I wouldn't doubt it. 

She then asks if I want an ultrasound to make sure nothing else is wrong. I mention that I had an abdominal ultrasound about a year ago (similar crampy pain in stomach that was never resolved) and that the test results only ever said "irregular result" near my stomach. Okay. She frowns. Then she sends me for an ultrasound. 

Bingo! There are two fairly large cysts on my right kidney. She has no idea what the ultrasound tech did last time but clearly these things are bothering me. There's also slight inflammation in my liver. A combo of these things can mean that my stomach over-produces acid? Renal Cysts + Liver Inflammation + essentially GERD = happy fucking Wednesday. 

So essentially only my giant stupid nervous system and my weird lungs (one is shaped funny, no clue why) was affected before, but now also my other organs are being dragged into this. Thanks, body. 

/s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
