<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Flynn said that the first thing everyone needed to know was that he was always right. His staff would know they were right, he said, when their views melded to his.

and

...sharing a similar worldview and a belief that America was in a world war against Islamist militants allied with Russia, Cuba and North Korea.

Nice blend of neocon war on terror and the Cold War. Quite the sophisticated world view, too. How Cuba backs Islamic terrorism is beyond me. Clearly what you want in the guy running the NSA, unable to see shades of grey or nuance.

The article is full of concerning occurrences, sharing classified info with Pakistan (Trump seems to like military men who leak classified info), stoking war with Iran, conspiracy theories, disdain for civillian involvement in military matters, not broaching dissent, disobeying superiors etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Flynn said that the first thing everyone needed to know was that he was always right. His staff would know they were right, he said, when their views melded to his. 

sharing a similar worldview and a belief that America was in a world war against Islamist militants allied with Russia, Cuba and North Korea. 

Nice blend of neocon war on terror and the Cold War. Quite the sophisticated world view, too. How Cuba backs Islamic terrorism is beyond me. Clearly what you want in the guy running the NSA, unable to see shades of grey or nuance.

The article is full of concerning occurrences, sharing classified info with Pakistan (Trump seems to like military men who leak classified info), stoking war with Iran, conspiracy theories, disdain for civillian involvement in military matters, not broaching dissent, disobeying superiors etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Trumps Security Pick, Michael Flynn, Sharp Elbows and No Dissent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair, but again, we have no direct reference to Jesus in his lifetime and no physical evidence of his existence. The best we have at are posthumous references to Jesus in early versions of gospels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people are scared of Trump and are fursturated by real concerns and seeming hypocrisy, so people want to discuss it, reddit is not set up for just discussions so people pull iffy articles to create space for that. Paywalls make it harder too limiting article choice.

We saw the same thing during Bernie's run, people felt the media was not adequatelty covering his race, so they posted shit articles to create space to voice their frusturations with the media, the Democratic Party, get his message out, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no primary account of Jesus and no record of him or his execution and the romans kept solid records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is some thought that he may have been a compendium of a couple of historical figures and wandering rabbis/mystics of the time or he adopted some of the previous or contemporary figures stories/teachings/messaging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he was Jewish... looked middle eastern and generally behaved like a hippy opposing money lending and violence, focusing on the poor and destitute. That whole believe in Jesus and get rich thing sweeping mega churches today? He kind of wasn't about that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) not sure which clarification, if it's the wall one Truml team has been revising the giant wall across the entire border to some fencing and wall across a couple hundred miles... a big step back from a corner stone campaign promise.

2) I agree, Melanie trump petition is stupid, a piece regarding concerns regarding the cost and security issues with Melanie staying in NYC would be reasonable. The petition is stupid. Also most of manhattan did not vote for trump so clearly they will be biased.

3) I agree that taking some local Russian politicians stupidity as testimony for Russian intervention in the US election is stretching things. People's concern regarding Russian intervention in US politics and the long term impolicatons is reasonable.

4) Calling Taiwan is a huge deal... sorry no way out of that one. It's a giant geopolitical foot in mouth. It's no 2 dudes having a chat, it POETUS talking to a country we don't formally recognize, then calling out the seeming inconsitincy of our foreign policy on twitter... and generally showing no understanding of the historical and geopolitical forces at work in ASIA.

5) I don't know which issue that specifically references but learning about religions in the setting of history and social studies? Fine as long as it's done empirically and according to secular approaches. Teaching theology on school? Problematic, how to choose which religions, how to do somsensitviely, justifying spending the time on it, taking into considerations athteists etc... it's thorny and has no place in public schools... not a minor issue. Separation of church and state is vitally important.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another repost, you are shameless sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a binary thing, yes or no. And I am telling you it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Europe is too inward looking, it needs to engage the middle east and north Africa culturally using the economic heft of the eurozone. This will have a liberalizing effect on the regions if there is economic improvement and cultural exchange and in return Europe has new markets. A post colonial economic partnership. In isolation Europe will stagnate and is weak against Russian geopolitical games, Chinese investment and economic control, and middle eastern instability. 

Similarly, the US needs to engage latin, central and south america in economic partnerships or we won't solve the immigration issue. Kids from guatemala and honderus want in? who can blame them, if they stay they will be murdered by gangs. 

By raising standards of our neighbors, investing in them, and exchanging culture and technology we grow markets and stabilize regions. 

Otherwise, numerically it is hard to control with an entity like China with 1 billion+ and trying to carve out another 500 million person economic sphere of influence in the South China Sea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refugees will keep flooding in if the conditions from where they come are so bad that its means they will risk all to make it to Western Europe. Europe needs a more aggressive foreign policy that addresses issues at the source. 

That means European leadership and involvement in Syria, North Africa etc. Sorry dropping a few bombs with the Americans in Syria won't do it. Russia is actively using Syrian refugees to destabilize Europe and Putin is manipulating the Syrian conflict to his benefit.

Europe needs to either aggressively challenge Assad or join Russia and restore him to power. Otherwise, people will keep flooding north. Similarly, working on Libya getting a functioning government to stem the flow across that border etc. 

Europe can deride US interventionist foreign policy all they want but you cannot isolate yourself from regional crises and therefore it is their interest to address them (and maybe have the capability to do so without needing America to hold their hands, and provide weapons/logistics/command and control to do it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the guy who allowed the Brexit referendum after campaigning on a promise of a referendum and then lost it... you know what is going to be a major blow to the EU, Brexit... no self awareness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 23:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia does not have the capability for a true projection of force owing to a lack of a true blue water navy... at best they can reinforce an ally with a protected airbase like Syria where they can base an expeditionary force. 

They do have a large ground force and air force that is a threat to contiguous states, as Ukraine already found out. Russia is also very skilled in special warfare, dis-information and control of separatist groups, like in azerbaijian, moldova and Ukraine. Therefore, they have a huge relatively effective force hey can project from their borders. 

They also have a very large and potent nuclear force with second strike capability in case things get out of hand. 

So yes, the army has issues, is probably aside from a few elite units under trained, much of the equipment is old, logistics is iffy etc.. but there is more than enough bite left to hurt people. 

Therefore, we needed a US President who was adept at countering the high risk aggressive geopolitical games Putin has been playing. 

Instead, we elected Trump. I feel like our Baltic, Polish, Ukrainian, Georgian friends are shitting bricks at the moment. Also, Syria looks like it will likely remain a quagmire, which means continued refugees and further destabilization of Europe. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also China would over run Taiwan in like half a hour... unfortunately given mutual defense pacts that would start wwiii. China protests a little when we sell Taiwan an old frigate and used to care more when their hardware was terrible but modern Chinese armed forced are miles ahead of Taiwan.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would mean someone on trumps team would have no Chinese history and Taiwanese history and US policy. For all we know when trump called the republic of china he thought he was going to talk to Beijing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse yet, no experience and no willingness to learn or listen to experts. 


* State department briefings for foreign calls? Who needs them. 
* Scientists on global warming? Trying to finagle grant money.
* No evidence of voter fraud? Well I feel that I won the popoular so there must be millions of fraudulent votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 04:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is still googling one China policy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 04:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, a rich teenager whose daddy can just bail him out whenever... and then make problems disappear... except daddy happens to be retiring and keep moving out of town in a couple months... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically with the system as is the dems need to regain control of the senate in the short term and the presidency in the near term. To do that they need to convince young people to vote (near impossible historically), explain to white working class voters why their vision of America helps that specific voter, or sway old people (if trump and Ryan go for Medicare quite possible). 

The democrats simply failed to explain to the swing state voter why trumps policies would hurt them and demonstrate that trump's promises were empty. It turns out that the voters didn't care as much that he was a temperamental, mysoginist or rascist. 

And young people did not turn out but that is not new. Too many voters were apathetic in general because he dems allowed the republican driven false equivalence narrative take hold.

The republicans played for keeps, the dems were to busy planning the afterparty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the guy and his kids are planning to make a business of the US presidency banana rebuklc style... the Batista of the 21st century, and then wants to surround himself with generals and ruling elites... it's a shameless anti democratic power play but this reddit is going after a pizza place with an unfortunate logo. 

Real unprecedented power plays and conspiracies happen in broad daylight, even Romney bows to kiss the dons ring and no one here blinks an eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling anyone with a different perspective than yours a shill suggests a closed mindedness against the spirit of the sub. It also suggests you have not truly considered others positions. How can you win anyone over if you do not understand their fears, interests, positions? Moreover, how can you be awake or a free thinker without being able to consider the other side? Do you need a safe space and echo chamber? If that's what you want then you are just another sheep, just with a different allegiance than most,  but just as blind and limited. 

If this sub was about intellectual growth, argument, discussion, evidence then maybe people would take the conspiracy theorists more seriously. Until then you are just a contrarian sheep...

I come from the perspective where many I know are still in shock and disbelief about trumps win and are genuinely concerned for the future. Many being well off will weather this ok most likely but they are worried that things they care for will be destroyed. Researchers who need grants, doctors who work with patient with a wide swath socio exonomic back grounds, teachers in the public schools systems etc... and then people who care about advancing knowledge, science or care about civil liberties. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub went for trump so hard, but just wait until he destroys net neutrality, encourages torture, allies with the military industrial complex, deregulates large business (like Monsanto), authorizes spying on US citizens, deregulates banks, limits the first amendment, and maybe starts a war... all things this sub is against? Or is pizzagate the only conspiracy of note ever? Even Wikileaks and assange are fallen by the wayside... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not think ctr was ever as prevalent as advertised. Reddit is full of young, upper middle class young professionals with a liberal alignment... most of them are vehemently anti trump and after Bernie lost they saw an opportunity to push Hilary... who many young professionals, finance people etc back.

Also, I think there were pro trump shills, that if not paid for by the trump campaign were paid for by pacs or even working out of Russian funded operations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is pro hilary in that it is anti-trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sub is not pro-hilary so much as terrified by Trumps' plans, cabinet, lack of presidential decorum, opaque finances, conflicts of interest etc...

People are upset because they perceive a false equivalence was drawn between candidates and now that Trump has been elected his predictably unpresidential conduct, unpreparedness, and the right-wing allegiance are manifestly evident. 

I don't by the popular vote argument, Hilary won by a huge margin - true, the electoral college is likely an undemocratic insitution - true, but they were playing a different game and Trump won according to the rules of the contest. 

Also, all this fantasy about recounts, electoral college overriding the vote, and impeachment on day 1 are fanciful liberal coping strategies. Also, if any of things happen it would be terrifying... like riots and violence terrifying. 

But overall, people are concerned that Trump is showing no restraint on Twitter, surrounding himself with a very right wing cast of characters, and showing now understanding of what a blind trust is, conflicts of interest, and emoluments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry did not see edit, will leave  my post for education of others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe people genuinely don't want a trump presidency?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what evidence is there that trump is a liberal... he is probably best described as self-serving, but the people who are going to be doing the actual work in his administration are going to rip through every program liberals hold dear and expand the military industrial comlex. 

**His brain trust is republican insiders, conservative billionaires and the military.**

* Pence, VP, head transition team: Very right wing on social and economic issues
* Munchin, sec treasury: Banker, ties to wall street and hollywood
* Sessions, AG: Right wing republican senator
* Tom Price, HHS: Right wing senator, wants to repeal ACA
* Elaine Chao, transportation: Wife of mitch mconnel, sec transporation under bush
* Betsy Davos, education: Pro school vouchers, anti public school, faih based philanthropy, ? vouchers for religous schools
* Priebus, chief of staff: head of RNC, right wing establishment
* Candidates for Sec def, nsc, sec state: Mathis, Flynn, Patreus... not exactly going to be reigning in defence spending.

Nikki Haley is an exception but she is still right wing. 


**The republicans are getting ready to:**

* Repeal ACA
* Privatize medicare
* Cut taxes on the rich, raise taxes on middle class
* Gut public schools
* Stop funding climate research at NASA
* Go after Marijuana on a federal level
* End net neutrality

Under anti muslim sentiment get ready for:

* Patriot Act return
* Torture

Also, conservative on the supreme court will mean:

* Go after Roe V Wade
* No chance to repeal Citizens United


How is this going to be liberal??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok legalization is a socio-economic issue, as is rescheduling, its needs to be legalized because people are using it already, and it benefits no one to put people in jail, strip people of jobs, and ruin chances at future employment particularly among poor and minority youth. 

Also, Marijuana is not harmless, it exacerbates some conditions, causes others (cannabis hyperemesis syndrome) and long term heavy use or use by young people may have long term effects on brain development and function. 

Finally, the cannabanoid system and multiple cannabanoids in Marijuana are poorly understood. While it might make people feel better it is unclear on its affect on long term disease progression and mechanism of action. 

Also, if they can create a non-sedating/ or altering version that would be great from people who cannot get high for work/ personal reasons. 

Using the medical argument for legalization is dangerous. If the studies don't pan out, if they isolate a cannabanoid that is responsible for most effects, it will backfire. 

tl;dr: Medical science is slow for a reason and hawking untested therapies can have long term adverse effects. Marijuana legalization is a socio-economic reason and should not be tied to unporven medical use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might invite more study or allow them to narrow which mechanisms and which agents the actually have the anti-inflammatory effects and if it's acting in the brain or at the sites of inflammation. Haven't really tried it to be honest, cannot afford a positive drug test at all or to be impaired at all in my line of work, and cannabis comes up on a drug test for an awfully long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucks, about to start one,  but it's better than when there were no therapies or had only a few even more toxic ones...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a tiny study, short term, they would need a much larger randomized  blinded study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what? Marijuana is not going to completely fix your crohns or inflammation... some small retrospective studies and one small prospective study suggest possible benefit but they are hardly conclusive. 

You are on immune modulating agents because it's an auto immune inflammatory process and these days their are many therapies available with fewer side effects when just relatively recently they had maybe two or three. Immune therapy sucks but it's better than nothing and weed is certainly not an adequate replacement... it's interesting and worth studying but the options for treatment have exploded recently compared to even a decade or two before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even GOP, it's Trump's GOP... it's worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually amazing, they are subsumed by pedo pizza networks... but seemingly don't care about trumps opaque finances, trumps kids sitting in on meetings with foreign leaders, that once more a banker is treasury secretary, 3 potential cabinet posts including sec def are recently retired military, etc...  not to mention actual child abuse, rape and trafficking around the world...

But a made up story about a D.C. Ping pong, pizza joint and music venue... top national security priority. Real conspiracies are unfolding in front of their eyes yet this is what dominates their time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 03:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tweet that at him, all of these... but especially that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or god forbid someone different from you gets something or something more. They would rather we all live in he mud then if everyone is lifted and someone who does not look like them rises higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They voted themselves out of healthcare, Medicare, minimum wage, education... etc. they handed the keys to the agents of the 1% and military industrial complex. Who are trumps cabinet? Generals, billionaires, insiders. And trump is an unstable petulant patsy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will when people are homeless on the streets, crime goes up, people get hooked on heroin and strip the wealthy people's house and car, when consumer demand plummets because instead of flat screens people are buying meds and potatoes.... or god forbid for the professional class, themselves a get sick and lose their job and liquidate their assets for healthcare. 

The system was bad before, now add in underemployment, heroin, worsening income inequality, a shakey economy...

Oh and then aging baby boomers with no savings and privatized Medicare... no good... no inheritance for millenials, grandma needed a kidney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, say she fucked up... do her kids bear the cost too? Just because they were born poor? Or should she have no chance at leading a dignified or productive life because she got knocked up early (because the reps didn't want to cover birth control or abortion)... and then have her kids set up for the same shit because they grow up with no safety net? If you want cycle of poverty, crime, drug use, ignorant electorate, etc... that is how you get it. 

Oh and for all those planners, well life, don't always follow your plans, people get sick, lose jobs, then before aca would lose insurance, so can't get insurance because pre existing, now cannot get healthy because no health care, and can't work... now what? 

It's a total scam, pay insurance for 20 years,  a bad stretch, lose insurance, get sick, oh fuck we are going to price you out of the market or deny insurance... and if they gut Medicare not hope at 65 either.

The aca was put in because the system beforehand was horrendous. It's not great, needs reform, but gutting in will have terrible social ramifications people might never recover from. 

While we wait for trumpists to realize they dun goofed people will die, have their lives ruined, their families ruined. You think the opiate epidemic is bad now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> European/Asian heroin from Afghanistan, most US heroin South America. Not sure where synthetics like fentanyl, carfentanyl etc come from.

As for why people use its multifactorial. Some get hooked from prescriptions after one day breaking a leg. 

Others have some poorly defined chronic pain process and some well meaning physician prescribed an opiate... build tolerance and some underlying psych disease and you get an addict.

Teens in Appalachia try it a party and get hooked or sold to them by grandparents looking to supplement social security.

Shitty life, bad support network, mental illness, no job, bad insurance, crappy friends who use, shitty sig other, lower eduvstion, never taught coping skills and the fact that it's very addictive with a terribaly uncomfortable withdrawal means it's hard to quit. 

It messes with reward pathways and decision making even when not high. People sell all their stuff, steal from friends, prostitute themselves to get heroin making life even shittier, digging the hole... hard to clickb out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No once we have a white right wing theocracy god will fix the rest. If he doesn't it's the impure thoughts of the gays ruining everything and causing droughts and flooding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I got confused, the classified info was from his time as an active duty commander:

Sorry you are correct. She was a reserve colonel at the time but not active. Also this was Patreus as a  CIA director, not general but the classifed info was from his time as an active duty general.

"Petraeus had provided Broadwell access to documents containing Top Secret Sensitive Compartmented Information, had later moved those documents to his personal residence and stored them in an unsecured drawer, and had deliberately and intentionally lied to Federal investigators about both providing Broadwell access to the documents and their improper storage. These facts were acknowledged to be true by Petraeus as part of his plea agreement."

More details:
https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/checkpoint/wp/2015/03/03/theres-code-word-stuff-in-there-case-against-david-petraeus-laid-out-in-court-documents/

"Petraeus, who led U.S. military operations in Afghanistan from July 2010 to July 2011, maintained a number of black notebooks in which he put classified notes, his schedule and other information while deployed, federal documents say. Among the most sensitive information: Details about the covert identities of officers, discussions with the National Security Council and his exchanges with President Obama" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry you are correct. She was a reserve colonel at the time but not active. Also this was Patreus as a  CIA director, not general but the classifed info was from his time as an active duty general.

"Petraeus had provided Broadwell access to documents containing Top Secret Sensitive Compartmented Information, had later moved those documents to his personal residence and stored them in an unsecured drawer, and had deliberately and intentionally lied to Federal investigators about both providing Broadwell access to the documents and their improper storage. These facts were acknowledged to be true by Petraeus as part of his plea agreement."

More details:
https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/checkpoint/wp/2015/03/03/theres-code-word-stuff-in-there-case-against-david-petraeus-laid-out-in-court-documents/

"Petraeus, who led U.S. military operations in Afghanistan from July 2010 to July 2011, maintained a number of black notebooks in which he put classified notes, his schedule and other information while deployed, federal documents say. Among the most sensitive information: Details about the covert identities of officers, discussions with the National Security Council and his exchanges with President Obama" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The narritive is patreus was convicted of purposefully mishandling classified info and violating the code of military justice to fuck his biographer... 10x worse than anything Clinton is even accused of, but somehow this disqualified Clinton from a top executive post but not patreus. 

So Hilary being accused of crime X = disqualified

Patreus accused of crime X^2, pleads guilty to crime 2X = considered for Hilary's old job.

Something is amiss in this logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, they guy who while in uniform put their lives at risk by purposely mishandling high grade info on miliatary ops so he could fuck his biographer... if Hilary should be locked up, Petreus should have been executed for treason. 

Also, kind of a breach of military protocol to let your officers shit talk the commander in chief in front of a reporter in a war zone. Obama took it not better than Truman did from MacArthur. Moreover, if you think Obama is thin skinned, we will see how Trumo would handle something even remotely similiar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just classifed info, highly classified operational info... top secret highly classified intel while in uniform in a combat theatre... it's in the neighborhood of treason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A tub of Christie's post Chinese buffet excrement would be preferable to ghooliani. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? Patreus as an active duty officer knowingly shared classified information (high grade operational info) to a embedded civilian he was having sex with who is not his wife. Basically knowingly and purposefully committing something close to treason to violate the military code of justice... 

how is they anywhere near what Hilary did where she as a civilian unintentionally might have put low grade retroactively classified  info at risk, using a private email like many of her predecessors. Which she did because State department email is slow, clunky and does not work with smartphones and she was trying to get shit done?

**Correction:
Sorry you are correct. She was a reserve colonel at the time but acting in a non official capacity. Also this was Patreus as a  CIA director, not general but the classifed info was from his time as an active duty general.

"Petraeus had provided Broadwell access to documents containing Top Secret Sensitive Compartmented Information, had later moved those documents to his personal residence and stored them in an unsecured drawer, and had deliberately and intentionally lied to Federal investigators about both providing Broadwell access to the documents and their improper storage. These facts were acknowledged to be true by Petraeus as part of his plea agreement."

More details:
https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/checkpoint/wp/2015/03/03/theres-code-word-stuff-in-there-case-against-david-petraeus-laid-out-in-court-documents/

"Petraeus, who led U.S. military operations in Afghanistan from July 2010 to July 2011, maintained a number of black notebooks in which he put classified notes, his schedule and other information while deployed, federal documents say. Among the most sensitive information: Details about the covert identities of officers, discussions with the National Security Council and his exchanges with President Obama" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to Russian space sector, Space X launch costs undercut both Russia and China and if they get the reuse tech working might undercut them even further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Russian space interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musk and Gates each in their own way have really pushed to advance humanity. Bezos is trying too, preserving wash po and with blue origin. Zuckerburg is trying too but his forays seem a bit clumsy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than than just space station supply, Russian launch vehicles were the cheapest relatively reliable way to get commercial loads to space and then even expensive western launch vehicles with military loads often still used Russian engines in at least one stage. 

Space X offers launchs at costs and even China and Russia can't compete at. The space launch sector is a Russian commercial/military/prestige area of concern.

If putin is in anyway meddling with western media through fake news sites then of course space x is a natural target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or literally a majority if not sizable minority of governments are more oppressive. And Cuba is not active beyond Cuban borders.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or space X is s threat to the Russian commercial space industry delivering lower costs and alternative engine technology. Russia always was the lowest cost orbital solution. Also their engines are a part of more expensive western launch vehicles... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe space x is competition for Russian space freight services. They were always the cheapest and even US companies relied on Russian engines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 18:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free markets don't work when the cost of the technology is not borne by the consumer. Their are huge negative externalities with fossil fuels where the cost of global warming, strip mining, oil spills, air pollution is not reflected at the pump or utility bill. Therefore since the price is too low we overconsume fossil fuels resulting in the need for regulations. Alternative energy which has fewer environmental costs is therefore at a disadvantage. 

Finally free markets are just a mechanism, they do not value things like quality of life, the environment, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free markets don't work when the cost of the technology is not borne by the consumer. Their are huge negative externalities with fossil fuels where the cost of global warming, strip mining, oil spills, air pollution is not reflected at the pump or utility bill. Therefore since the price is too low we overconsume fossil fuels resulting in the need for regulations. Alternative energy which has fewer environmental costs is therefore at a disadvantage. 

Finally free markets are just a mechanism, they do not value things like quality of life, the environment, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 06:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of odd. Apolitical weed posts, no r/conspiracy posts, then ventures out for this comment. Seemed an odd pattern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 23:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His campaign slogan would be "tiger blood" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 23:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like the producers or some movie plot in real life... except instead of a comedy is a tragedy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 23:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that does not mean that because it's crazy it's true. Lots of untrue crazy stuff too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 23:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is conspiracy theorists can be 100% guaranteed to overlook any real conspiracy especially one that does not fit what is often a weirdly anti establishment but also at the same time authoritarian world view. 

So Russia tampering with elections? Disregard. 

Large corporations spreading anti climate change propaganda and buying off scientists and politicians? Disregard.

Trumps opaque finances possibly threat to national security and interests? Disregard.

Fake news that army drills in Texas operation jade, is really a take over of America, or some guy on 4 chan decided a pizza shop had wierd logo, or the plane overhead is leaving some contrails which must be chemicals? Call to arms... we must expose these conspiracies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite is when they take 2 unrelated unsourced inoccous data points, and then say "well, I was a skeptic but with this evidence that is the only conclusion that can be reached" and then trot out some insane completely speculative theory.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 05:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enlisted dude would have spent a solid amount of time in jail... probably. The charges against patreus seemed pretty serious, mishandling classified data, violating code of military justice, and doing so knowing all along the significance of his actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole trade package. Trump at every stop would say I am going to tear up nafta. Then he would pick a local industry and say I am going to open this factory again or fund this sector or rebuild the shipyard. In Florida it was NASA, in Indiana it was a carrier plant, in coal country it was the local mine.


 The media covered all the other stuff he said and the things that happened at his rallies. The locals heard trump is bringing back blue collar jobs. Doesn't matter how or if it's possible.

 Meanwhile dems refused to lie outright and talked about education, retraining, taxes and healthcare. All much more abstract. 

Didn't help that 8 years of republican smearing convinced everyone anything Hilary said was a lie... somehow Trumps pathological lying got overlooked and here we are. 

Problem is, with out massive subsidies, even if you get rid of nafta and tpp, not sure how those jobs are supposed to come back... and now what. 

Those people are going to be rather incensed when those factories stay shuttered and those coal mines remain unprofitable and when factories do come back are robotic. When nafta is gone and production grinds to a halt. When Obama care is gone and they are insured. No marijuana for pain control. No clean needles. And tax cuts for the rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't forget the decade long republican anti Clinton smear campaign. And don't worry they will rev that machinery for any other democratic front runner too. We need to stop letting the right wing propogandq machine define democratic candidates. Corrupt Hilary narrative was completely a right wing narrative where they threw things at the wall until emails stuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just that, but people needed to get behind Clinton and get friends and family out to vote too. Instead everyone played martyr and would moan "I guess I'll have to vote for her" instead of "failing to elect Clinton puts the well being of most American at risk in the short and long term". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In practice the performance of the student is set when they are younger and the top tier, I think it called gymnasium, students tend to be from already educated families. In Germany your social support system prevents the same rampant income inequality as the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what is frusturating too, the constant accusations that any pro Hilary post was CTR when we know that the kremlin employees buildings or pro Russia trolling operations. It was a classic
counter information campaign.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly Germany has a segregated almost by class tiered school system so I would be curious whether it's the same at the top vsmlowermlevels. 


Germany is also experiencing rising nationalist and rascist movements... also they have bought left wing fake news on gmos, etc. Sure it's better than America and people actually believe global warming etc... but the American right wing nationalist experiment is heading your way too, and hopefully your civically minded and educated populace does not buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their grandparents were a completely incomparable era with issues like civil rights and access, but comparing millenials to their parents is fine except young people still do not vote in nearly sufficient numbers to make their issues matter to politicians. They are the ones who are going to beat the lifetime costs of a trump presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that? It looks interesting... it's fast, not tilt rotor fast but faster than a conventional helicopter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +/-, you would want nurses, workers, engineers who those that had some management experience and could see the bigger picture too. 

Very specialized people like nurses or workers or engineers don't always translate to good policy makers... sure they might have a more real and immediate sense of the problems but they do not have the training to see things as a broader system, how to organize change, what tools to use. Even doctors who have a slightly broader education and training than say a nurse make generally terrible political leaders, from bill frist, to Carson, to rand and Ron, to stein. Having spent mode of my life around scientists, doctors, engineers and nurses most would not make good political leaders although they are very bright, they are just too narrowly focused.

I do not disagree that lawyers are not better and that a more diverse set of career paths should lead to political roles. Lawyers are an added problem because their idea of truth and reality is based on an artifical legal code based in precedent and philosophy not empirical thinking.

I would also conjecture that we should expect our politicians to be a nerdier less polished lot, with broad credentials and experiences in management etc. 

We need to focus less on who they sleep with, and which church they belong, and if they would be fun to share a  beer with but instead demand clear cut polices and planes and demand the media deconstruct and translate those plans and policies to the American public. 

The American public also needs to get a bit tougher about bad news and actually elect politicians who say things as they are. Trump flying around the country, playing up American exceptionalism and promising to reopen this factory and that ship yard at every stop is also people hearing what they want to hear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the s97 skyraider, no wings, rotor for lift but also pusher prop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the s97 skyraider, no wings, rotor for lift but also pusher prop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 04:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but never know how to take these comments. 1) there are tons of media sources out there, some are better than others. 2) people get their news from largely not vetted sources or word of mouth or from fractured hyperfocused partisan sources.

People's unsavy media consumption is a big part of how this country became so dysfunctional.

There are real conspiracies...   but usually these "very informed" people who get labeled conspiracy theorists are just that... conspiracy theorists and the worst of the lot, following totally unsourced and speculative info from the web from anonymous 4chan posts to info wars. 

So please enlightenmen me as to what gets you labeled a conspiracy theorist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 04:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well also the people who didn't show up and vote. There were 2 sides to this disaster. 1) The people who voted trump despite his basic unfitness for the presidency, lack of real policy proposals or understanding, dangerous advisors and terrible ideas. 2) the people who either felt the candidates to be equally bad and apathetically stayed home or just didn't care enough to vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And windshields not to shatter but people still get glass in them in car accidents. Sure it's designed to minimize shrapnel but mishandled or hit with something it definatly could produce shards. Also if something caused an explosion surrounding debris or rocks becomes shrapnel. So no, it's not a fragmentation device but pieces of it could have ended up in her body. It's odd that not traces of these grenades have been found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is truth to that, but Cheney after leaving power remained pretty vocal. Cheney believed his neo con agenda. 

I am not a fan of the neocons and they played an aggressive, dangerous and ultimately misguided game. But they are not there same existential threat to our country's institutions as bannon is.

 Bannon is the face of an alternative news distribution network with a fascist/ white supremacist flavor. He is dangerous because he has the connections to bypass the news media and create his own narrative while advancing a very fringe agenda. Sure the bush neocons utilized Fox News in a similar way but business interests and establishment interests served as some check on their activities. Bannon has no such limitations and neither does breitbart/ Alex Jones/ info wars etc. 

So while I do not defend bush neocons and their actions while in power continue to cost America dearly, from tax cuts to the Iraq war, they were not so incompet, unbound and extreme as bannon and ilk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumsfield and Cheney were neoconservatives but rational actors. Willing to definaey push the law, from torture, to falsifying a casus with Iraq, to outing plame to eroding civil liberties.  But they were acting from a misguided but nonetheless country first approach. Remember it was not the neocons in bushs administration that can we about the culture war stuff. Cheney is pro gay marriage.

Bannon, he or at least Breitbart and other alt right individuals truly are not acting for country but for a racsist and dangerous ideolgogy. This is new a different although borne of the southern strategy and later rovian election strategies. They are truly evil... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our economy and stability as a country come from bush actually acting for himself and by the end of his second term breaking from a lot of his early advisors... runsmfield and Cheney in particular. It meant a bail out when the stock market crashed and no further military interventions. That's is because I believe that while Cheney was an unusually powerful vp bush was still engaged in the presidency. This a whole new model. Pence runs the show, trump undertakes dangerous demogougery and enriches himself. Back when I admired kasich showing back bone and rejecting trumps offer to run the show or endorse him... I wish he had accepted. Better him the power behind the throne than pence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Child slavery is a scourge that has plagued society for 1000s of years, from boko haram to Norway it's been in the news. 

I hope you are not referring to completely speculative and unsubstantiated pizzagate story. But I guess fake scandals capture your imagination more than real child slavery. Makes people wonder if it's about the children or some moribund fun and obsession on the part of the conspiracy theorists or some glee at hoping to see politicians caught in dark and nefarious plots. 

What demons? And no one kidnapped assange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2016: "And then things got worse" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible explanation for Trump's off and then back on again NYT meeting... Priebus possibly misled Trump on details of meeting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, all this dems and liberals and basically decent people who sat this one out get off their asses and vote him out. A scary number of people vote for trump but a concerning number of others did not show up to vote. It goes both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By western standards, we are a den of inequality with massive  differences in outcomes regarding health, life expectancy, educational attainment, employment opportunities etc. based on socioeconomic, regional, and racial divisions. It is kind of why trump won, because many people are feeling left out, they just do not care who else was left out too. 

But also many feel that the gains of women and minorities have come at their expense. There is also a regional divide where they feel the gains of the costal elites have come at their expense as well.  

As for the special snowflakes, many of the Trump voters and the dear leader themselves are the most thin skinned. 

Honestly, all these coal communities and rust belt communities, raised on American exceptionalism and nationalistic fervor, do not want to hear that those opportunities are not coming back. If they do come back the jobs will be automated and require and different skill set than they have. Also if there is a trade war they won't be able to afford any of the products they now take for granted. 

They lost, and the party that told them that were special blocked any attempts to soften the blow, give them a safety net while they retrain. 

I would be fine for them voting their interests except trumps proposals are not going work or help them, and the vitriol they direct at everyone else. Somehow coastal elites and liberals are unamerican in their eyes, interlopers, weak.

When they repeal obama care, slash government programs, roll back medicare, privatize all the infrastructure, they are going to pay most dearly. Kansas is a little experiment that gave us taste of things to come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair though, the media never faced this before, at least past candidates would do some hand waving and make up plans that the math did not work or assumed a ridiculous economic growth rate but has some fake proposals none the less. Also the media was used s candidate saying things like trump did and it ending their campaign. The got sucked into this vortex and could not move on. They did not know how to cover this. To be fair the public has been demanding coverage of scandal and horse races for years so in some ways the media was doing what people wanted. Also it's cheaper and easier to sit two surrogates on the air and have them argue than to actually do reporting... and as fast a surrogarate like Conway spins lies and deflects, the media does not even try to keep up and fact check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they did not even try. Trump never had a Gary Johnson Aleppo momement because no one ever asked trump about issues in the same determined way. No one spelled out the way they are doing now what kind of conflicts of interest trump would have but we have known this would happen because trump never promised a blind trust and never released his tax returns. The media never went in depth with trump about how he was to help the working class. The details of his wall. How he was planning to deport all these people. Details of the ACA. No theh never really got past the groping women video and other outrageous things he said... which were already litigated in the publics mind because everyone saw the tweets and video front the horses mouth.  Not saying these were not issues but they were only an easily accessible piece of the picture, they missed the rest lurking below. Similarly all this time on Hilary emails, never-ending but no talk on policy issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 07:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, abstained was a problem too... too many abstained. There is no excuse for abstaining unless you genuinely thought Hilary would be as bad... Trump is pulling sketchy shit right and left and he has not even been inaugurated yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 07:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> blind trust

Let's not overstate things. Ivanka is the CEO of the corporation trump owns. It's not blind in anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 06:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isis hates the word deash because in Arabic it sounds like a pejorative term for someone who sows discord... which apparently in a Arabic is an insult. It's funny how the west people thought we were being politically correct and rebranding isis when in fact it was a movement started in the Middle East to delegitimize Isis by using a term that they hated and that also happens to be the proper Arabic term for them. They execute people in isis territory for calling Isis Daesh. We should be using daesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer "whiny little bitches". They seem a rather pathetic lot... their thought process seems to be "Bohoo, no one else thinks I am special just because I was born with a white cock", god forbid they actually earn respect through hard work, learning and dedication.  Nope it's every one else fault and they are always the to victim. If they had any insight and self awareness they would literally have to hate themselves. Such a collection of delicate little snowflakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or actually does some journalism... you know rather than rehashing trump tweets. Do some actual digging and reporting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is already pulling shady shit with Ivanka sitting in on meetings with foreign leaders as head of trump corp. Who knows who trump owes money to... we certainly don't because he released no tax returns. There is risk to foreign powers buying and influencing the soon to be president... that's a real conspiracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job on collecting that GRU paycheck. You should get a 5 ruble per hour raise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it matter? Oil is a global market... we don't buy it someone else does and we just buy it somewhere else... Russia maybe. Oil is a complex market, distribution is driven by matching type of oil to refining capacity to distribution networks. Not buying Saudi just means a slight adjustment and the market will just work around it... in the short run it means higher domestic gas prices and shortages a refineries and distribution networks adjust. The only one hurt is the American economy and consumer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 04:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His critics go stuck on how terrible he was as a person. Turns out Americans did not care. 

The media never really explored his lack of policy ideas or the fact that he is absolutely ignorant on the issues. They never explained to the average swing state worker why Trump's policies would hurt them. 

Turns out swing state voters don't care about what happens to women/ minorties/ gay couples. 

Also they made a false equivalence with Hilary too. They made Hilary look as corrupt and unethical as trump. Since the media and the Clinton campaign never dug into trumps actual plans or preparedness and hoped trumps despicable persona would do the job.

They underestimated how much the average voter bought into the republican 8 year long anti Hilary hit job and many trump voters also probably were not fans of the big tent dem message.

So people voted to fuck the establishment and for the guy who promised them and their kids jobs. It's the medias fault he was never put on the spot as to how he actually plans to get back jobs...

Oh and then a bunch of Americans sat on their asses. They own this too, dem voters that did not bother to vote own a special place in this cluster fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
