<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2632</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arsonist pet tortoise starts fire that burns neighbor's home and causes $150,000 in damage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Facts about Black holes and White holes - Their shapes, types, mass, gravitational pull and more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... thus solving all the problems in the world. 

BTW filipinos spent an average of 12 minutes and 45 seconds on the adult website, almost two minutes longer than a South African, which came in second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine Government blocks Popular Porn Sites after reading Pornhub's annual gathered data. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Zuckerberg thinks telepathy is the technology of the future, and now Facebook is actively recruiting for a number of neuroscientist positions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have come here to chew bubble gum and kick ass...and i am all out of bubblegum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By 2040, the auto insurance business could drop by 80%, unless it finds a way to adapt to the existential challenges of disruptive technologies, such as autonomous driving and shared mobility. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bubble bird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese flip books. use negative space cut out of the paper to make some neat effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WhatsApp vulnerability allows snooping on encrypted messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googles new compression tool uses 75% less bandwidth without sacrificing image quality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft launches StaffHub to connect deskless workers. It's part of the company's push to expand Office 365's utility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 billion tons of stored carbon discovered in Congo peatland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Clearinghouse to Adopt Bitcoin Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A girl googles how to commit suicide, ends up talking to DIG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who are against this: 
Russia, and China has every right to do this. Why do American government and corporations  think that everyone needs to bow down and give them what they want. The whole world is not under Americas thumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia, China and India has every right to do this. Why do American corporations and governments think that everyone needs to bow down and give them what they want. The whole world is not under Americas thumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Russian government has demanded Apple and Google remove LinkedIn from their app stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Russian government has demanded Apple and Google remove LinkedIn from their app stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Google played its cards right in India, and Facebook suffered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US DOD seeks proposals to "Develop biodegradable training ammunition loaded with specialized seeds to grow environmentally beneficial plants that eliminate ammunition debris and contaminants" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
