<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 03:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I know...my genius knows no bounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 04:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://redd.it/17gl5w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 04:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://redd.it/17gl5w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 00:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://redd.it/17gl5w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yo, dude, he took Brewster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 00:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](http://redd.it/16edec)


[Part 2](http://redd.it/16kxtb)


[Part 3](http://redd.it/16uaoe)


[Part 4](http://redd.it/1753qa)

*Let's just get this party started. No music because silence is just so atmospheric. Just kidding.*
_____


Brewsters car rolled up to a darkened church on one of Baltimore Countys smaller streets. A sign with Korean lettering stood in front of the church. The road was deserted.


My grandpas church, Mildred muttered. I forgot how deserted it was.


Well, lets get inside before that thing hunts us down I got out and slammed the car door behind me, tossing the keys to Brewster. I pulled on the churchs front door, armed with my shotgun. Locked, obviously. I had no clue how to pick a lock, let alone bust a door down, but I wasnt going to look like an idiot in front of Mildred and Brewster. I had already shot a monster in the face; might as well continue my descent into badassery.


Brewster stood next to me at the door, frowning. I dont like this, bro


I know, dude. But this is all we can do right now.


He paused, eyes downcast. This is all my fault. Im sorry, Fred. Im the worst bro ever.


I punched his shoulder. Hey, dont be like that. Youre the best bro ever.


But you still condemned your friend to death, Mildred chimed in, worming her way into the conversation. Brewster went back to looking depressed.


I turned back to the locked door and began using the shotgun as a kind of battering ram before Mildred shoved me aside. Idiot. Let me do it. Youre not fooling anyone.


I quailed away as she got busy picking the lock, finishing with a smug smirk and the click of an unlocked door. She cracked open the door, smile turning into a frown. Jesus. I forgot what a dump this place was.


The three of us piled into the church, locking the door behind us. Mildred flipped on some lights and the space illuminated in a disappointing array of empty chairs and a fake wooden podium. It looked nothing like the predominantly white-Catholic churches of Baltimore; it might have well been a multipurpose room. Bowls of what I assumed were holy water stood at random places in the church. A massive Jesus crucifix was poised behind the altar, weeping blood tears.


Mildred flopped down in a seat. Well, here we are. Feel free to start praying. I dont know.


I paced the back of the church. Okay, so, I propose that we create a gun filled with holy water and wine, call it the Baptizer 2000, and then


*Uhhh*, Mildred said.


I turned to her. Uh, what?


She paused before muttering, I kind of lied about the power of Jesus thing.


I frowned at her. Excuse me?


The religion thing? She avoided eye contact. Actually, that was just a guess.


*WHAT*, I screamed.


She thrust up the rosary she had used to choke Garden Tool. My grandpa gave me this from this church, and that seemed to work. I threw a dollar-store crucifix at Garden Tool once and he laughed. I dont know, okay?


Brewster finally seemed to comprehend what was going on. Soyou drove us out here for nothing?


No! I know theres something about this place that must work, its just she gave a little shrug. I saw her face sadden. I was actually hoping you two could help me. You didnt think I broke into your house just because I wanted to help you out, did you?


You dont seem like the most charitable person. I glared at her.


She matched my glare. Ill have you know, I donate


She silenced at a far off noise the sharp, muffled ring of a telephone.
I scanned the room and saw the telephone perched on the far side of the room. I checked my watch. Who calls a church at 4AM?


No one normal.


I started towards the phone as Brewster yelped, Wait, bro!, but I caught the call on the last ring, answering with a hard, hello. I was getting tired of these games.


Static on the other end.


This isnt scary, I said. I live in Baltimore city, for God sake!


There was a pop of sound, before:


*Where are you going*?


NOWHERE, I screamed, that female monotone ringing in my ear. I AM GOING ABSOLUTELY NOHERE. I AM CURRENTLY STATIONARY.


Stay with me.


I understand literally nothing of what youre saying.


*I am alpha and omega, the beginning and the ending, saith the Lord*.


I shrieked like a small child and hung up the phone. Suddenly, there was a bang and the church lights cut to black. I froze, my voice taken away.


Fred, bro? Brewsters far away voice called.


What the FUCK, I responded.


Something slammed into my temple and white-hot pain split through my head. I fell back, my mind going dizzy for a minute, the darkness and sudden sounds of shouting mixing together in my head. I figured that this was what a hangover felt like. I tried to get up but I struggled; after a minute I managed to stumble to my feet again. Something was strange.


The church was completely silent.


I steadied myself on the wall, pinching the bridge of my nose. My head pounded.


*Brewster*? I called. *Mildred*?


Silence; the pain in my head made it hard to think straight and I ended up stumbling backwards. I thought I was going to hit the wall but instead I fell back into a seat behind a heavy curtain. I panicking for a moment, feeling walls around me, but then I thought back to my church days a confession box.


I rested my head in my hands, rubbing my head. Jesus Christ


*Yesss*?


I looked up, eyes wide. That was definitely not the voice of Jesus.


That was the voice of Garden Tool. 


You are *not* Jesus! I yelled in a random direction, blind in the darkness.


Garden Tool rasped a laugh; I realized he was on the other side of the confession box. The stench of rotting meat filled the air.


*You are not religioussss, are you*?


I happen to abstain from it.


*Then you know God will not save youuu*.


My voice hardened. Turn the lights back on. Where are my friends?


*Shed thou no blood, nor cut thou less nor more. But just a pound of fleshhh*.


That cryptic bullshit is nothing to me. First the phone call, then you. I dont care.


*But I have something that is everything to youuu*


What, the Pokmon game? I dont care what you steal from me!


*Return to this church at dawn and I will let him go*.


My heart dropped. What?


The lights suddenly flashed back on. I hissed and squinted before stumbling out of the confession box and throwing the curtain aside.


Garden Tool was gone.


I cursed and suddenly remembered Brewster and Mildred before running to the front of the church. Mildred was just raising herself up off the ground, a hand at her bloodied head.


Brewster was gone.


I feel like I just got hit by a truck Mildred mumbled, still groggy. 


*BREWSTER*! I rushed past her, screaming Brewsters name. At some point I tripped on a chair and tumbled onto the floor, but instead of getting up I just stayed there for a while. I knew my search was fruitless Brewster was gone.


*Return to this church at dawn and I will let him go*.


I eventually got up, Mildred standing over me. What the hell just happened?


I swallowed. Garden Tool took Brewster.


Her eyes widened. What?


I whipped around to her. *The religion shit didnt work, Mildred*! I yelled, kicking a chair. All of this is *bullshit*! He took Brewster! You took us here for nothing! *NOTHING*!


I didnt promise anything. Her voice was hard. I couldve just left you two to die. Instead, I try to help. You should be thanking me for even *trying*.


She threw her arms up in huge movements to show all that she did for us, which added up to breaking into my house, forcing Brewster to cut up a pineapple, asking to go to McDonalds when we were being hunted down, and then taking us to a random Korean church.


I stormed away from her, and, having nowhere else to go, walked up to the altar. I sat down at the front of it and attempted to pray, but no matter how desperate I was, I was still an Atheist. I attempted to be proud of my mental fortitude.


I put my head in my hands and struggled to be calm. All I had to do was face Garden Tool at dawn and Brewster would be fine. Brewster would be fine. Brewster would be fine.


There was still a massive hole in my heart as I attempted to comprehend my own death at the claws of a monster. The fear was there, but no hesitation Brewster was my main bro, my heterosexual life partner. I would take a bullet for him, let alone sacrifice myself to a monster. He would do the same. I looked up at Jesus hanging over the altar. I supposed thats why people coveted religion so much the feeling that someone had your back, no matter what.


A thought suddenly shot through my mind.


My eyes widened and I got up from my seat, effectively standing in awe of my own brilliant idea.


I knew exactly what to do.


Mildred puttered up behind me, giving me a skeptical look. Areare you okay?


Im fine. Im perfectly fine. I turned to look back at her. Hey, Mildred?


What?


...Wheres the closest place we can buy dynamite?


______
*Tune in next time for the thrilling conclusion*!

[THE END!](http://redd.it/17tobn) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 04:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomorrow is the day!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 16:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo, dude, be updating soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 20:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo, dude, I will soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 23:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been called "The Party Monster" once or twice in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 23:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit! Another time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 23:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, I'm enjoying your comment, but my god do you turn me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 23:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You give me the TV network, I'll write the script! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 23:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omar is my homeboy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 23:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if we're both not married by 30... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 05:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it that two men can't hug each other with their legs in friendship!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 23:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but remember- when you come at the king, you best not miss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yo, dude, don't stop me now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](http://redd.it/16edec)


[Part 2](http://redd.it/16kxtb)


[Part 3](http://redd.it/16uaoe)


*Frederick here again. Almost to the time when I started posting on Reddit! Time flies, doesnt it?*


*[Open this background tab](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IFUjwj_RB5o), and Ill continue my story. Sometimes I feel like Im writing a fanfiction of my life for you people*
 
 ____________
*Death has arriveeed*.


When youre about to die, you notice the little things in life. Like the fact that the kitchen faucet was dripping, carelessly left on by Brewster, or the sudden knowledge that you forgot to pick up beef jerky from the store. The little things.


I truly thought that I was going to die. That thing, Garden Tool, stalked into the room with ragged breathing, claws scratching against floorboards. Death was approaching, and I knew that in that moment, we werent infinite.


We were fucked.


I eyed Mildred, muttering to her. Are you absolutely positive a gun wont work against it?


Well, it wont kill it.


Stun?


I guess...


*Commeee out, meattt*


I shot up from behind the armchair and pumped lead into the monster, tumbling back from the shotguns recoil. I attempted to say something suave, like This time, its personal, but all I said was, URFFF.


As I fell back, Garden Tool did too, lurching back with the shots and splattering the room with black blood but just as he rolled on he floor he rose again, bullet wounds filling up with flesh. The blood faded. That was definitely not normal.


I stood, paralyzed, as he stalked forward. The thing cracked a grin, revealing stained sharp teeth, black eyes narrowed. He knew that I was terrified.


*Guns dont workkk*.


Suddenly, I heard a shout behind me:


BAD *DOG*!


Brewster came through for me just this once, hefting an armchair over his head with mighty roar and heaving it at Garden Tool. The monster tried to duck away but the chair was too large and it smashed into his body, trapping him back in a corner. Black blood began to pool around the chair and his twitching limbs.


The three of us stared at the bloodied armchair.


Is he dead? I asked.


The armchair moved and in a split second the three of us tore up the stairs while Garden Tool was incapacitated, stuffing ourselves back into my moms bedroom closet.


Why the hell didnt we run outside? Mildred asked angrily at us.


We cant worry about that now, I whispered. I turned to Brewster. Bro talk. What do we do?


I dont know, man, Brewster sniffed. Tears appeared in his eyes. Im scared, bro. Guns dont work. Chairs dont even work.


Brewster, well get through this. I grabbed his hand. Remember the power of friendship. I love you, brother.


I love you too, dude.


Okay. What do we do?


I got the keys to my car, we just need to get to the front of your house.


How? Mildred whispered angrily, cutting into our heartfelt friendship fest.


A distraction, Brewster whispered. How about I jump out, start flapping my arms and meowing


Garden Tool threw the closet door open, screeching in fury. I screamed and for once in my life, had a good aim I shot him directly in the mouth; he jerked back from the force, screaming in pain and frothing blood.


*EVERYONE MOVE*! Mildred howled, pushing us into a run. We barreled to the front of the house, Garden Tool springing up and tearing after us.


I leapt through the busted front door and shot out into the winter night, stuffing myself into the passenger seat of Brewsters car. Brewster and Mildred followed suite, Brewster taking the drivers seat and Mildred tumbling into the back of the car. I cocked the shotgun as Brewster struggled to take his keys and stick it in the ignition.


Brewster, MOVE! I yelled.


He blinked back tears. Im scared!


I pulled him into the passengers seat, jamming the shotgun into his hands and shoving myself into the drivers seat. I heard scrabbling outside the car.


Garden Tool leapt onto the front of the car and then smashed its head on the windshield. I gunned the engine and floored the car forward; Brewster blasted a bullet into the windshield, missing Garden Tool completely and blowing a massive hole in the car. Glass exploded everywhere; I threw my arms up to shield my face as Garden Tool forced his torso through the broken glass, screeching in my face.


HIs breath smelled like, guess what, surprise, that rotting meat smell that followed him everywhere. He was about to lunge at me when Mildred shot up from the back seat and threw something around his neck, pulling back.


Garden Tool shrieked, choking, scrabbling to untangle itself from whatever was choking it. I caught a glimpse of the rope for a split second, a crucifix charm dangling off of it. A rosary.


Mildred let go of the rosary and Garden Tool fell back from the front of the car. I rammed the gas and the car roared before shooting forward, running over the creature with a satisfied thump and roll of wheels.


We burned rubber onto the street, shooting into Baltimore city. Mildred looked back and saw Garden Tool for a split second, slowly rising from the ground. She flipped him off.


MILDRED, DONT TAUNT HIM, I screamed back at her.


Whatever, mom!


I drove blindly, flashing past side streets and continuing deep into the city. The more people, the safer. Okay, Mildred, where the hell do we go?


Im kind of hungry, she mumbled. McDonalds?


You said that religious items hurt him? All religious items? Whered you get that rosary?


My grandpas church. The Korean one out in the county.


Can you tell me how to get there?


Sure, but well have to bust in.


I dont care. If you think its safe, were going there.


Mildred gave me a look that wasnt the most confident thing I wanted to see, but I steeled myself and turned onto the highway, out of Baltimore city and back into religion.

Just great.

[Part 5](http://redd.it/17gl5w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 05:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a challenge to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Extraordinary Gentlemen of Urban Myths...sounds tempting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DC chillin? Then I'm sure you're fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for reading! Although I'll have to work on looking through pineapples... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nautical nonsense be something you wish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I checked my identity, I am neither of those fellows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have my forgiveness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 22:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you understand, sir. This HAPPENED to me- I was almost killed, along with my friends! And you dare to scoff at my predicament? Shame. For shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 21:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mildred gave him the name Garden Tool. As mentioned in the text, the "grad council of Internet virgins" call him the Rake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 15:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...you mean...you love my unfortunate life more than you thought you would? Oh, I see how it is! Schadenfreude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, for an evil monster, he was pretty damned classy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 23:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/16uaoe/yo_dude_were_gonna_die/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 23:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More on the way!
http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/16uaoe/yo_dude_were_gonna_die/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yo, dude, we're gonna die! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 22:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](http://redd.it/16edec)


[Part 2](http://redd.it/16kxtb)

*Does anyone know any good warrior priests? Asking for a friend...just kidding, I'm asking for myself in order to not get killed. Without further ado...!*
__________


Mildred and I sat opposite one another in armchairs as Brewster struggled to cut up the pineapple into manageable chunks. Mildred wasnt as terrifying as before, now seeing her in the light although she still had chronic bitch face. Im not using that term in a sexist manner she truly looked like she was constantly pissed. The clock ticked on the wall. From the moment she dropped the pineapple between Brewster and me, Mildred had not spoken.


So I paused. Whats with the pineapple?


She shrugged. I was hungry and figured you guys had a knife to cut it up. I was just coming back from the farmers market when I started following you two.


I cringed. Brewster brought over the bowl of pineapple and began to set it down in front of her; she slapped his hand and took it from him, curling up in the armchair around the bowl. Brewster cowered into another armchair. For such a small teenager, she was terrifying. She started eating the pineapple.


Uh, I said. Wed really appreciate you telling us why you followed us, broke into my house and then told us that we were in trouble.


She nodded, disinterested. Yeah. Right. Okay. So. She paused. I hate to tell you this, butyoure being hunted down by a monster who wont stop chasing you until he basically rips you up and eats your dead body. She paused again. Im sorry.


I narrowed my eyes. Excuse me?


She sighed. Let me phrase this another way. Has your phone been acting weird?


I nodded.


Smell ofmeat in the air?


I nodded.


She ate another piece of pineapple. Giant gray dog-man at your door? She quirked an eyebrow. He said your name?


I nodded once more.


Yeah She looked into the bowl. As I said before, youre pretty much screwed. Sorry.


Brewster and I exchanged glances. Uhwhat? Brewster managed.


She snapped a glare to him. And its your fault.


His face fell. Huh?


 You stole my hacked Pokmon game that my idiot senile grandpa decided to leave outside. I hacked that game myself. It had a girl as a main character and everything. Im assuming Mr. Nerd over here she wiggled a piece of pineapple at me. played it.


Brewster nodded meekly, avoiding looking at me.


I gave Mildred a skeptical look. I dont see how this relates to all the shit thats going on.


She steepled her fingers *a la* Doctor Evil, turning to me. Frederick. You and I are not that different. Did you used to sleepwalk as a kid? To weird places?


A lot of people do that, I muttered.


She rolled her eyes. Yeah, well, a lot of people dont see figures at the foot of their bed at night. She mustve seen me look like Id just pooped myself, because she chuckled. Theres a lot of weird things in this world. Ghostsgoblinsghoulsand only certain people are affected by them. And these things are very nasty. They dont respect humans as apex predators. She gestured to the kitchen back door. Like Garden Tool.


I did a double take. Like who?


That gray thing that came up to your door. She rolled her eyes. The grand council of internet virgins uses the name the Rake and writes fanfiction about him. I dont know, its stupid. It was a toss up between Hoe and Garden Tool, and I liked the less vulgar one. More clever, you know?


I blinked at her. This was before I started posting on Reddit. I was never exactly a horror aficionado, but the fanfiction I read never involved Naked Gray Dog Men. That was a subject I did *not* want to touch.


If Garden Tool says your name Mildred made a chopping motion with her hand. Youre good as dead. She paused. Except for me. I attribute my survival to my intelligence and charm. Her eyes snapped to mine. But you have something of mine, yes? The game?


I nodded.


Well, it looks like he followed that scent and has a new plaything. She shrugged. Now both of us are screwed.


I threw my hands out. You keep on saying that so casually!


Its pretty easy to talk about death once youve accepted it as so, she said cheerfully.


There was silence for a moment.


I can try to help you guys out, Brewster mumbled guiltily.


I turned to him. Goddamnit, Bre


The powerful stench of rotting meat hit me and I stopped; Brewster and I both registered it at once and turned to Mildred, our eyes tearing and sleeves over our noses.


Yo, dude, Brewster whimpered. Its that smell!


She wrinkled up her nose, putting the pineapple bowl aside. This isnt good.


What the hell do we do? I asked desperately.


The doorbell rang.


All three of us looked to the front door, still overpowered by the rotting smell. It was about 3 AM. My mom was on a business trip. Who the hell would be at the door at 3 AM?


Brewster jumped up from his seat. Who is it


Brewster, you idiot! I grabbed his arm and pulled him back, picking up the shotgun from the side of my chair.


I inched to the door, looking through the peephole.


Darkness. Not the darkness of night, but pure black with a glass sheen. My mind worked to figure out what I was looking at, when I suddenly realized in horror what it was.


An eye.


Oh, shit! I scrambled back just as the door began crashing on its hinges, battered by something huge. Cracks raced across the wood and I cocked the shotgun, aiming it at the door.


I have no experience shooting a gun, I said, cowering behind my armchair. Meanwhile, I think Brewster wet himself.


Mildred sat up in her chair. We need to leave. Now. Get a car; itll catch us on foot.


The door was almost down. I dont have a car.


Mildred looked at Brewster and he shook his head, trembling. Mines in the front.


Shit. She tried to knock the gun out of my hands. Dont even bother, that wont work anyway.


My eyes bugged at her. *What*?


We need, like, holy water or some religious shit.


*YOU TELL ME THAT NOW*!? I shrieked.


The door fell down with the splintering of wood and a huge crash.
The three of us shot behind behind one armchair to hide, which was both stupid and ineffective. I heard claws scratch against the wood floor as whatever broke down my door walked into my house. There was silence for a few moments, coupled with wheezing, before I heard a familiar, rasping voice. I knew instantly what had just broken down my door.


*Meeeaattcome outtt*.


Garden Tool.


____________
*SHIT GOT REAL! I'm confirming that Brewster did pee himself when this happened. More on the way.*


[Part 4](http://redd.it/1753qa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 20:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you currently dead? I hope not, for my own selfish reasons- I need to know what happens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 17:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
