<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5238</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting hyped for Fantastic Beasts, anyone bought the screenplay? I just want to know if it's as good as the other books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 17:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't trust r/movies anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 07:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching The Nice Guys, a movie everyone on here gushed over and it is boring.  The comedy is flat, the dialogue is self indulgent, the plot convoluted, Gosling's acting and the typical teen girl is annoying, I didn't care about any of it and yet r/movies and most critics loved it.  Personally I think it's either you guys worked on this movie or it's to support movies like this but sadly you've chosen this movie.  Since you guys can't distinguish between a good movie and a polished but below average movie, I'm not trusting your recommendations anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There's a "Rotten Tomatoes" site but for books called Lithub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized I don't read much anymore because like movies, I've become more selective, but Rotten Tomatoes helps me pick, is there a similar review aggregate site for books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got gold earlier this year so I could filter every Trump sub, went back to r/all to see how those subs were reacting and I don't see any in the top 100 links, where did they go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/Starwars must be run by Disney shills since I got banned for praising the original trilogy and prequels but criticized episode seven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The British are a people who actually learned their lesson: they imposed their will by colonizing most of the world and now hate socially imposing on others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the last movie that was so good it gave you the chills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be Zootopia.  The movie was thematically complicated, fun, and every second counted for the story.  Other movies regardless of genre where I was in awe of how they made it are Predestination, Memento, Kingsman, Oldboy, and the original Star Wars.  I'd like to know what your movies are as I think those are the movies to next watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is there no "bridge" species between humans and apes in Africa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't there a "bridge" species between humans and apes in Africa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans making fun of Chinese working in factories is like bosses making fun of their employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you're not going the same direction as your partner, you're going to go apart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is China still a collectivistic society? I've read many reports of people being out for themselves and yesterday went to a buffet with a lot of Chinese and there was line cutting and hordeing of the lobster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innocent guy gets shot and killed by police and it's "news," baseball player dies in accident and it's "horrific news" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 17:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most subs on Reddit have probably been created by shills because I know you people too well to believe you'd spend that much time modding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 06:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only allow professionals to review other professionals instead of critics whether it's food or movies or music because critics don't have a true understanding of the work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have to study for four years to get a bachelor's degree but you can train six months to become a police officer and get a gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you all think that when 4K TVs are affordable and have content, people will no longer go to the movie theaters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 22:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it that some movies like the new Blair Witch seem to have to market so hard to make a few million while a movie like Magnificent 7 seems to not even try and is expected to make around 35 million this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polyglots, how do you remember all the words? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In your opinion, what "simple" book has the most deceptively complicated plot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I remember really liking Nic Cage in the National Treasure series then overnight it seemed like everyone turned against him, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a Bernie supporter, it pains me to say that we need to vote Hillary. America is corrupt but better a corrupt elitist than a fascist, America will never recover its standing in the world or at home with a Trump presidency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Blair Witch and Bridget Jones bombing this weekend, Hollywood reminds me more of Las Vegas: you hit a jackpot then you keep coming back and end up in debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 18:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movies are so forgettable that you've watched it a second time without realizing you already watched it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the first Sin City 2 a couple years ago via streaming.  Then it came out on Netflix, I watched it halfway through when it hit me that I had seen it.  It's amazing that nothing in the story stuck with me which tells me it was a really bad story.  I can't believe I've spent four hours of my life on a movie I probably won't remember again a few years from now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How did Samsung not catch that one of its flagship products, the Galaxy Note 7, caught fire while charging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By repeatedly remaking remakes, the latest being Predator, Hollywood is like the fishing industry, with reboots they're overfishing, but as their catches get smaller, they get desperate and keep overfishing ignoring that the problem is reboots/overfishing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will watch adaptations of other films, sequels, but I will not watch  reboot/remakes like Predator or Magnificent Seven or what's worse, the reboot/remake masquerading as a sequel like Star Wars: TFA and Blair Witch.  Thanks to Ridley Scott who didn't just (re)make Prometheus an "Alien in sheep's clothing" as the original screenplay by Spaihts had done.  

I want original stories especially since it's easier than ever to watch the original via streaming or dvd. 

Now I'm sure some of you will come back and say there's no such thing as originality, well a line has to be drawn somewhere and that is the reboot/remake.  So please if you have a choice between watching a reboot/remake or a new story, watch the new story instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit should let users add an avatar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Koreans all have a retarded brother in North Koreans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British English's "bad words" are harmless compared to American English </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kylo Ren is proof that our generation is spoiled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Facebook friends are a reminder of our life choices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please explain the appeal of Kylo Ren? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 08:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think the movies were better than the book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's many improvements from the books  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys entering into a relationship tacitly agree that they will be yelled at for one week every month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Magnificent Seven is going to be a good test to see if audiences really are tired of remakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gennady "GGG" Golovkin is our era's Mike Tyson, 35-0 record, 32 by KO, but he's been overlooked, check out this KO reel, he's fighting on HBO this Saturday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are more men who casually call women "bitches" than women saying the male equivalent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russians of Reddit, how normal in Russia is a r/anormaldayinrussia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 07:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've accidentally hit yourself, what curse words would you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jane Got a Gun would be a much better if you think of it as a western fan fic of Obi Wan hunting Padme while she's being protected by Uncle Ben, her ex-lover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 06:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Bean is the British Jackie Chan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The more subs I've been banned from, the more productive in life I've become </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In response to Serena Williams whose had fitness issues saying "gender should not be confused with greatness," men are made to play best out of five matches but women are made to play best of three </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations for Korean and Chinese anime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 04:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We teach kids that corruption is wrong, but we expect them to accept it with politicians when they're adults </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The average salary for an animator in Japan is 10,000 dollars a year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the next movie you can't wait to see? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cinemablend.com/new/Movie-Releases-2016-Movie-Release-Date-Schedule-109257.html

I'm excited for The Girl on the Train (love the book), Jack Reacher (first was solid, hope second builds on it) and The Great Wall (Matt Damon and the Great Wall, I'm sold). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you or do you not prefer dating someone in your field and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The zombie apocalypse is here, to join a community you will need three skills that will contribute to it, what are they? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Tinder was more truthful to how mate selection works, guys would only have to post pictures of their bank account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does M. Night Shyamalan deserve the last ten years of hate (since Lady in the Water) he gets from the fans and critics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like the hate started after a journalist's article painted him as egotistic.  Personally, I hated The Happening, Lady in the Water, and Wayward Pines but enjoyed in varying degrees The Last Airbender (not like the show but many adaptations aren't), After Earth (think it got a bad rap with the Smith nepotism story), and The Visit (though sadly it didn't feel like an M. Night movie anymore). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever treated someone bad because of how they looked and they turned out to be someone important? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 23:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a better adaptation, Warcraft or The Last Airbender? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiters of Reddit, which group of people are the best tippers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 07:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nudity is to women as magic is to magicians, show all of it and you become nothing to others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/blackpeopletwitter and r/whitepeoplegifs are probably run by each other's people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 07:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 28 Weeks Later needs to be mentioned more among all time great zombie movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Editing can be choppy but music, story and surprising cast of actors including Jeremy Renner, Rose Byrne and Idris Elba separates it from the pack

Note: this isn't a comparison between 28 Days and Weeks, IMO they are both great films with Days having the edge because it is the original and Weeks follows what it established </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else with Sprint having trouble with a stable GPS signal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Los Angeles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stopping at Fresno soon, heard there's good authentic Asian food, where should I try? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disappointed in Night Market Song, are the other Night Markets any better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordered the Khao Soi, charbroiled pork appetizer and pad thai, the first two had too much sauce, the last had too much oil.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do men's penises get sensitive after an orgasm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were the lives of everyday Romans better when it was a Republic or Empire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We will only pay a few dollars for cow meat but we will pay hundreds of dollars for cow skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about all the things we love about Cursed Child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite things to see was Harry and Malfoy become friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To those pointing out plotholes in Cursed Child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every book has a plothole, some even bigger than the ones I've read are "plotholes" in CC, but since when has that stopped us from enjoying them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the walls in the newer apartments and condos in Los Angeles thicker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick of hearing my neighbors next door and want to move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A layman's question, but what is it about SyFy channel shows more than any other network, that it's cinematography looks flat and cheap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a system for naming people after a place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 23:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, people from New York = New Yorker, Los Angeles = Angeleno, Paris = Parisian, America = American, Canada = Canadian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are seven novels and seven horcruxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did Lawler fall for the most common shot in boxing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the old one-two and Woodley's best shot, forget about Lawler's chin, that right would've knocked anybody out.  The question is how the heck did Lawler fall for it?  And what was up with that BJ-like upright stance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the generally agreed upon flaws in some of your favorite movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oblivion 


Spoilers warning: midway through, the clone reveal gave me a serious sense of deja vu, it felt cliche and in the theater I remember thinking "oh come on!"  But when I rewatch it now, it makes sense if still a little overdone and the rest of the movie is too good to let one flaw sink it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are all number one at something: we are all our father's fastest and strongest sperm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 17:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bringing my laptop to Japan, it has a three prong plug, I'm from America, do you all know a good power adapter to buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 07:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman culture before the Greek influx emphasized hard work, living within one's means, BlackPeopleTwitter is all about cheating and material things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 22:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there movies that you enjoy but have ideas and messages that are actually the opposite of your political affiliation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 02:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain to me why JK didn't just write Cursed Child as a novel instead of letting someone else write a play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 22:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever realized that you were being "negged" and what happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watched Dragon on Netflix and halfway through the film, it starts following another character. In my experience, readers in America would pass on it for not following the rules though it followed what was most interesting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Stuart Beattie, the writer of Collateral, in "movie jail" after writing and directing I, Frankenstein? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't heard from him in a while and I heard Collateral had a very hands-on producer so wondering if Collateral is now being seen as a fluke by Hollywood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got Banned from /HillaryClinton for asking why we should look past her election rigging, so I'm going green! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 09:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Hillary wants us to support her, she needs to address why we should look past her election rigging without mentioning Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 08:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collateral, they don't make movies like this anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 08:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had everything: emotion, acting, suspense, action, big stakes and the world didn't blow up, never even left los angeles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One request for the Wizarding World at Universal, make better shirts, all the ones available look like clubber/metal fans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 05:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you go movies more or less than before? Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 22:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read in articles ticket sales are way down for x number of reasons, but I'd like to hear them anecdotally.  For me the reasons I haven't been going are: 

Work keeps me busy and going to the theater is a trek so staying home is easier

Tickets are expensive, around 10-14 dollars, I still remember paying 4-6 dollars, now I have to think about the price

The image at home is HD so not too bad

I don't want to deal with the crowds when I can be comfortable at home

There's been too many reboots of films whose originals is the only version I need.  It actually makes me mad that there's so many original/existing IP that hasn't been turned into a movie and instead we get remakes like Ghostbusters and Ben-Hur.

I'd rather hang out and do another activity than sit in silence with someone for two hours

I've seen so many movies it doesn't give me the same thrill.  Movie trailers used to wow me, but I think I've seen the Earth and its monuments destroyed every way they can be.

I'd like to see more tangible craftsmanship like models to make the experience feel more real.

The movies themselves haven't been appealing.  The last movie I saw in theaters was probably Star Wars: The Force Awakens.  The last movie I actually liked was Mission Impossible: Rogue Nation.

I don't really like many movie stars and the ones I do like don't make too many movies or ones I'd want to see them in.

Appealing movies like Predestination come out on VOD.  

TV has stepped up their content to be more cinematic.

That's all I can think of, what about you guys and girls?

edit: I feel I should add some things that'd bring me back to theaters.  Cut ticket prices, reduce number of trailers, less excessive use of CG and more models (why I love Christopher Nolan so much), market smaller movies as they would a big movie, more original movies, fewer reboots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you liked Game of Thrones' Battle of the Bastards, check out Warlords on Netflix with Jet Li [US] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What flaws in otherwise great movies would've been used as an excuse to not make it if it had a very picky greenlighter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 08:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to filter movies by genre on Amazon streaming on the kindle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 04:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Hillary supporter here, I really would like to support her again if any of you can justify her rigging the election with Debbie Wasserman Schultz and please don't insult us and deny it happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 03:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We were told not to change our party affiliation until after the convention so Bernie could push for his platform. With the Democratic Convention almost over, when is a good time to leave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Box Office: 'Ben-Hur' Tracking for Alarming $14M-$15M U.S. Debut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some flaws in otherwise great books that readers would use as an excuse to pass on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 08:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will not vote for Clinton until the core concern is ADDRESSED about election rigging against Bernie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 04:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can parade every single celebrity and talk about how unreasonable we're being but they're getting nowhere with me if they don't ADDRESS THE ISSUE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colbert just lost my respect after dumping on Bernie during last night's opening monologue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 02:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He skated over the DNC corruption by saying it's okay because Hillary is a Democrat and Bernie was an independent like that makes it ethical, he said Bernie was "anti-independent women" for running against Hillary, how misogynistic to try and give people better lives and reform a rigged system, he made fun of Bernie supporters crying, and he said Sarah Silverman was right to call Bernie supporters "ridiculous"...I couldn't watch anymore, I am done with Colbert.

[The Colbert Clip] (https://m.youtube.com/?#/watch?v=RvO3qV8kNVA)

[Seth Myers to Bernie supporters: Quit your bellyaching] (http://deadline.com/2016/07/seth-meyers-bernie-or-bust-hillary-clinton-donald-trump-1201793332/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The cost of movies to stream is too high. One HD movie can cost 5 to 6 dollars, why would I pay that when I could watch Netflix, Hulu, HBO Go for a month for double that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when it was $2-4 I'd rent movies without even thinking, now unless it's a big budget movie I just wait until it comes out on a streaming service.  Blockbuster wouldn't have even charged $5-6 and with them you could sometimes get the blu ray with special features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today, Sunday, a random stranger screamed "Star Trek" at me in a parking garage as he headed up to the theater though it premiered Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 07:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to check my shirt to see if I was wearing anything signifying me as a Trekkie.  His gf looked morbidly embarrassed.  I like Star Trek but not that much.  I don't think anyone does outside of conventions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If 4chan is the basement of the internet, then it mirrors where most of its users live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 07:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The DNC leaks show they are the party of the rich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the same time DNC were talking about which highest paying donor to seat by President Obama at a dinner, they were scheming to make sure every dollar donated to Bernie was wasted by rigging the election against him 

https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2016/07/22/117f0574-504f-11e6-a422-83ab49ed5e6a_story.html?hpid=hp_special-topic-chain_dnchack-935pm%3Ahomepage%2Fstory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL An Australian study sent test subjects to bus stops where they boarded with a faulty bus card and asked the driver to stay on. 72% of whites were allowed to stay on, 36% of blacks, 51% of Indians, and 73% of Asians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 07:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few times a day I find myself in disbelief that Star Wars the Force Awakens had the audacity to give us another Death Star and power station and mid-catwalk death and prisoner opening scene and... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've noticed that I've gotten older, bending my knees is one of the hardest things my body can do, why is that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Boyega is the male Leslie Jones, he plays a character who would be white in a female driven reboot of a beloved eighties franchise and they even look alike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you miss Korean BBQ, buy some sesame oil, add salt and pepper, and use it as a dip with your french fries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get all the rappers who rapped about killing cops and who've made it to protest their own songs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 03:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars is like the TV show that has told its best story but keeps making new seasons because of the money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't need to know how the plans to the Death Star were stolen or what happens after Palpatine was destroyed or a rehash of Luke's story or Han's early days especially since you just further ruined his story when you killed him off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If men's breast could make milk, they could no longer go shirtless without women wanting to suck on it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone stop praying for a day and see what happens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone gotten into a fight before the adrenaline kicked in and what was it like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only acceptable name-calling words are against women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the perfect number of seasons for a television show before the quality starts to suffer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't think of the last reboot that I actually enjoyed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the original Spiderman more than Amazing Spiderman, the new Ghostbusters seems uninspired because making everyone a woman isn't enough, The Thing was a prequel but it basically copied the original scene for scene, Memento might be the worst remake idea that's coming, Terminator Genisys was another unnecessary retread.

Just thought of a couple I liked: 21 Jump Street.  I think maybe I enjoyed it because I never saw the TV show.  The Mission Impossible series, too.  As far as I know, they didn't copy the plot scene for scene of the originals, which was hard to do anyway since they're TV shows.  Maybe Hollywood can take a lesson from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon GO will do more to highlight how pervasive crime is in America than anything else could </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The biggest critics of the new fenale Ghostbusters are guys who don't go to the movies anymore and thus responsible for the casting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 07:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I wrong not to appreciate Daniel Cormier's fighting style and guys like him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Cerrone, I wasn't impressed with how he fought Silva.  He laid on him for three rounds and hit him with pot shots.  In my mind, I think in a real fight, there may be multiple guys attacking, or biting and headbutts so Cormier's style of lying on a guy for x minutes won't work, that the best fighting style is on the feet and yes ground game is important but not if you can't advance.  It's like I can't suspend my disbelief but am I missing something that it really is effective in real life and I should appreciate Cormier's style more?

*I appreciate all the comments.  It helped me gain a new appreciation for Cormier's style even though I don't find it appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Ghostbusters getting hate for being a female reboot when Star Wars the Force Awakens was also? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix should give you a personality type based on your ratings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 07:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would love to see an Interstellar 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And see where Cooper and Brand go and do next. Imo, it captures the spirit of Star Trek more than the Star Trek movies have done, of mankind's relationship with space and ourselves and our future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AmericanProblems - I'm watching Andy Murray at Wimbledon on the Fourth of July </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Numb your chin before a fight and you'll never get knocked out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 06:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coat a black man's penis in chocolate and pretend like it's a chocolate banana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 03:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Cameron Used To Be A Star Wars Fan, But Thinks Force Awakens is Far, Far Away from Original Six </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] If you created your own religion, what is the one thing that you'd make sure was in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a good question to ask for an interviewer trying to determine if a candidate is a good person? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new algorithm sucks, no new links after ten hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 09:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shock, Rage And Gallows Humor: A Brexit Backlash On Social Media : The Two-Way : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 21:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Again EVERY post on my last two pages on r/all has become r/nba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 06:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Independence Day: Resurgence' and When Remakes Are Disguised as Sequels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 02:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Gold is Good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 04:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FILTERED:

/r/2007scape

/r/alexandradaddario

/r/anime_irl

/r/arresteddevelopment

/r/Battlefield

/r/battlefield_4

/r/behindthegifs

/r/blackops3

/r/BobsBurgers

/r/buildapc

/r/CFB

/r/civ

/r/ClashOfClans

/r/CLG

/r/DestinyTheGame

/r/doctorwho

/r/DOTAx

/r/DotA2

/r/enoughsandersspam

/r/EnoughTrumpSpam

/r/Fallout

/r/fo4

/r/formula1

/r/funhaus

/r/GlobalOffensive

/r/grandtheftauto

/r/GrandTheftAutoV

/r/Gunners

/r/h3h3productions

/r/halo

/r/hearthstone

/r/heroesofthestorm

/r/hillaryclinton

/r/hockey

/r/iamverysmart

/r/JonTron

/r/JUSTNOMIL

/r/Kappa

/r/KenM

/r/KerbalSpaceProgram

/r/KotakuInAction

/r/leagueoflegends

/r/ledootgeneration

/r/lewronggeneration

/r/linux

/r/magicTCG

/r/me_irl

/r/meirl

/r/MLS

/r/Mr_Trump

/r/mylittlepony

/r/niceguys

/r/nosleep

/r/notinteresting

/r/noveltranslations

/r/osugame

/r/Overwatch

/r/PandR

/r/pcgaming

/r/pcmasterrace

/r/pokemon

/r/polandball

/r/ProRevenge

/r/radiohead

/r/reactiongifs

/r/reddevils

/r/rickandmorty

/r/RocketLeague

/r/roosterteeth

/r/runescape

/r/rupaulsdragrace

/r/shittyaskscience

/r/shittyfoodporn

/r/ShittyLifeProTips

/r/shittyreactiongifs

/r/skyrim

/r/smashbros

/r/soccer

/r/Spongebros

/r/SquaredCircle

/r/standupshots

/r/starcitizen

/r/Steam

/r/Stellaris

/r/stevenuniverse

/r/talesfromtechsupport

/r/tf2

/r/The_Donald

/r/thedivision

/r/TopGear

/r/trashy

/r/trees

/r/TumblrInAction

/r/Undertale

/r/wheredidthesodago

/r/witcher

/r/wow

/r/WritingPrompts

/r/youdontsurf

/r/youtubehaiku
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Roman politicians passed laws in 140 B.C. to keep the votes of poorer citizens by introducing a grain dole: giving out cheap food and entertainment, "bread and circuses", became the most effective way to rise to power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new algorithm has turned r/all into r/nba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/resetload explains why VR is nothing like putting a regular screen close to your eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 16:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Heres the ironythe Bernie people are the Obama people. Theyre all the young people; thats the Obama coalition." - 19 reasons the Democrats will remain divided </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 23:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL "Welsh" originally could mean "stranger," "foreigner," "other," "serf" or "slave" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Road rage fight videos are literally what happens when two assholes collide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I try harder to be witty with my comments so someone will one day give me gold, it hasn't happened yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 06:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders Supporters Cry Foul over Clinton's Suspicious "Secret Win" Email </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders supporters outraged over Clinton's 'Secret Win' image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 00:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My front page post on r/politics, "Voters outraged as media accused of falsely, preemptively crowning Clinton", was just removed for the reason the topic was "already" being covered by the Megathread: "AP declares Hillary Clinton has enough delegates to be Democratic nominee" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're two completely different topics.  In fact, every post about the media's preemptive crowning of Clinton has been removed.  Correct the Record has gotten to some of the mods at r/politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMPORTANT California information: If you got a mail in ballot, BRING it to the polls or else they may make you go home to get it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never even asked to vote by mail but I got one anyway.  I just went to vote and on their rolls, I was listed as having received a mail in ballot. The election worker said I needed the mail in ballot so they could make sure I don't vote twice, that I could go home to get the mail in ballot or get a provisional ballot which we've all seen by now probably won't be counted.   Luckily I live down the street.

So bring your mail in ballots to the polls OR vote by mail postmarked by the end of the day, a witness' signature is required on the envelope.  I recommend voting at the polls so it's counted today in the tally.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters outraged as media accused of falsely, preemptively crowning Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 08:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters outraged as media accused of falsely, preemptively crowning Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 08:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters outraged as media accused of falsely, preemptively crowning Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 07:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters Outraged as Media Accused of Falsely, Preemptively Crowning Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 07:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if people who complain about someone stealing their post is the same person and they're complaining just to not be found out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 05:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone who used to kind of trust the media right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 05:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anderson Cooper interned for two summers at the CIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 07:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Anderson Cooper interned at the CIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 05:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If superdelegate is endorsing Hillary, I'm voting for their democratic challenger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bars are ubiquitous in Western culture because water used to be unsafe to drink but beer and wine were safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Europe is more ethnically barbarian than Roman but we think of ourselves as Romans first </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Some states such as Oklahoma, Texas and Connecticut shun ketchup on burgers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We have become way too PC. I joked in a post on BlackPeopleTwitter that Gorillas Lives Matter and was banned without warning. Mussolini started out on the far left too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 16:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Trump chickened out on debating Bernie, that showed he thinks Bernie is more electable than Hillary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 08:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it Westerners especially in movies seem to identify more with Rome than the barbarian tribes that settled Western Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 02:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reason the Kardashians are popular with women is because they represent the American Dream: none are naturally pretty but have worked hard to make themselves so </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 02:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The British are the world's most unattractive people according to BeautifulPeople.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans are mad at the one percent, Bernie would crush Trump like Hillary never could because of this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 08:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans are mad at the establishment so Bernie would destroy Trump in a general election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 08:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Irish speak English because of the potato famine which killed off a quarter of its population and there were jobs in the English speaking cities and the school system promoted English and new immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 01:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Dutch are taller because of natural selection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 03:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you thought Obama was divisive, Clinton is even worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 06:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/DawnSennin gives a thorough explanation of why r/arrow has turned against their own show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 16:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NO SPOIlLERS] Can someone please explain to the rest of Reddit why and how Arrow has gotten so bad its own sub has turned against it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 08:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As one of many confused outsiders, can someone please explain to us why and how Arrow has gotten so bad its own sub is crapping on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 08:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is r/arrow crapping on their own show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 07:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm an independent voter and want to vote in California's primary: now what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pictures from Bernie's yuuuge Lincoln Park rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 08:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
