<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3700</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame works on authoritarians!  Shame your friends and family who voted for Trump.  Don't let them say they are tired of politics or some other bullshit, shame them at every opportunity.  

Authoritarians are wired for a sense of belonging, if they are being actively shamed and ostracized it will eventually make them break with their leader.  It is like decultification.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build spaceships get away from the range of their nukes first.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so you mean celebrating one's ~~ethno-nationalist~~ culture is somehow wrong?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's aide Seb Gorka tied to far-right, anti-semitic group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump voters buy a lot of catheters looking at the ads shown on Foxnews.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't give interview access to a single member of their administration for 24 hours.  Hardly the same.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polling has shown that those who are more likely to support military intervention are the least likely to know the geographic location of the country they want to bomb.  

We have cosmopolitan Americans with a deep multicultural appreciation of what America has become, and those Americans who continue to support Tyrant Trump and live in continuous fear of any brown-skinned person on the same sidewalk as them.  

We are two types of utterly different people in a single country, America cannot last like this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did the same thing when Reagan was elected.  Conspiracy nuts all of the sudden liked the establishment.  

It is almost like Republicanism and Conspiracy Theories require the same sort of mindset to believe in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Great SoCal/Norcal transportation nomenclature divide.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rich did the same in the 1920's.  Moving to the countryside to be away from the food and labor riots.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The I-5 will be renamed the I-1.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly like how Watergate started to unravel. 

Nixon tried to bully Congress, the FBI, and the AG, and less than 24  hours later articles of impeachment were being drafted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is so scared of the poor rising up against the idle rich like herself that she voted for Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Unabomber wasn't Xtian.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laser Guillotines, spread the word. 

No need for sharpening.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into the mid-sized tech towns w/ unis like Corvalis, OR and Spokane, WA.  There are still sub-100k downtownish condos in both towns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More people live in the suburbs than downtown.  You just implied they aren't people.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess people in the suburbs aren't people.  

Do you ever think about something before you say it?  Try it sometimes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason the factions of the right virulently hate Democrats/Liberals/the Left is because the Left are legislating substantive policies on the issues of the day that work.  Many of these progressive and common sense centrist/technocratic laws and policies go against every single narrative of how government and the economy works on the right.  They have no coherent ideology to offer on the issues of the day anymore -- FFS, Conservatives have been talking about Supply-Side/Trickle Down economics at CPAC today, like it was 1977 -- so they have become base reactionaries to everything the Left has done in the past 70-80 years. 

These are unhappy vicious ignorant people coming to destroy everything built by large liberal majorities over the decades.   They have no unifying cogent worldview, these people are like wild animals lost in a city for the first time.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vote trebuchet over the Potomac.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She'll have a shitty talk show as a divorcee before 2018 is out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the execution method for the federal government?  Just injections?  

The execution method for treason should always be done by beheading or hanging in public, I'm a traditionalist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone thinks Trump is going to have a single loyal friend when the shit hits the fan, they'd be wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at that point Trump would have no friends anywhere in the US government.  The alternative would be Civil War.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonsense.  There are condos on the East side past 99 that still have under 200/month fees for townhouse-style condos with private yards.  

You guys are looking at stupidly over-priced condos made for trust funders.  Of course they are going to scam the trust fund kids, they don't bother to show up to HOA meetings.  That shit don't fly in condos populated by retired folks.  They bitch and complain and keep the prices sane.  Try it, it works.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it is Reason, a garbage magazine for libertarian manchildren.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less soda = less taxes for poor people with diabetes on medicare.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Trump would be the one McMasters and Mad Dog would be deposing by using [the 25th amendment, section 4](https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/amendmentxxv) with Pence.    

If more than half of Trump's cabinet turns on him, then he is done.  There are still legal ways that Trump can be removed from office beyond impeachment in the House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perez is as shady as hell, he is an old school political operative in the vein of Bill Clinton who will say anything to anyone behind closed doors.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clintonism or how to lose almost 1200 elected seats in 25 years while getting rich off corporate speaking fees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was dead before he took office.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is nice, it doesn't change the fact that lifting Russian sanctions will not help the US or Europe.  

What good things has Trump done in office?  He has done almost nothing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidence of shady Trump connections to Russia have been around for nearly a decade.  Sater alone has been with Trump since 2007, a dude who worked for the CIA to stop the russian mafia from selling missiles in SE Asia.  This guy was/is a senior Trump advisor that Trump has flown on his private jet half-a-dozen times and suddenly Trump says he does not know him?  BS.  What kind of person knows people who sell black market missiles?      

There is absolutely smoke, the question is how big the fire is.  

http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-felix-sater-felon-adviser-20151204-story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tonight's Stockton City Council Meeting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting textures.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump/Russia connection is real, and they've been far too nice.  

EDIT: Guys, Trump is as of 48 hours ago connected through his personal lawyer to a Ukrainian facing treason charges in Ukraine FFS.  The time for doubt is over.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portland has pretty active and responsible HOAs compared to other metros.  

Bad, corrupt, inept HOA management gets tossed out on their ears all the time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really care what r/personalfinance says about anything tbh.  

A 150k condo right now in SE Portland is a much better investment than spending the same amount in 5-6 years on rent.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, people still remembered what fascists looked like back then.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still buy a condo if you make 40-50k on the east side.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love what they've done with that subreddit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richmond could be first city to begin articles of impeachment for President Donald J. Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richmond could be first city to begin articles of impeachment for President Donald J. Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hasn't Trump stated in the past that he feared getting dementia?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to ask Trump if he thinks Sandy Hook was real.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he has been lying about that for 50 years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only freedom of speech fascists should get are last words.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby Boomers who watch 10 hours of Fox News a day elected someone just like them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Trump met with the ambassador twice, so Putin had to tidy up that loose end.  

This is like the 5th cliche shitty spy-procedural mini-series plot point we've gotten this week.  

I can't wait until we get to the part where Trump has a car chase with all of the DC police in a presidential limo trying to get to the airport to flee to Moscow.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pull their tongues out and cut them off, then brand the word BIGOT across their foreheads.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't make the claim.  

Either back up your conspiracy theory or stop replying.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like you are why I am unsubbing from this shitty centrist cultspace.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vichy authoritarians.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I don't need to listen to conspiracy theorists gum on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then you are not an authoritarian who demands obedience and groupthink, which is probably a good thing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is more likely a sign of incompetence with Spicer and his staff.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so you have evidence of your conspiracy theory or are you just gumming away?  

If I wanted to talk about conspiracy theories I would call up my alcoholic brother.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you got nothing?  

Why do Clinton supporters believe in such nonsense?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jill Stein has been digging at the Clintons since she has become a public figure nearly two decades ago.  

So now this conspiracy goes back two decades?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think Sandy Hook was a hoax too?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were 5 other people at that table, why don't you make up a conspiracy theory about them too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most adults keep those thoughts to themselves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laugh at your conspiracy theories.  

Next time you look in a mirror, say your theories out loud while looking into your own eyes and see if they sound rational.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, she has spent the last 8+ years being a commentator there about American politics.  What are you talking about?  

Jill Stein is a media whore who since running in 2008 has been on RT almost weekly. 

I see happenstance, you see conspiracy.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a conspiracy theorist I guess.  

In the adult world, where Jill Stein has always been a media whore, her going to a RT event isn't that suspect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so everyone who has sat next to Putin is suspect now?  

Do you want to go down that road?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that supposed to be clever or racist?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No she doesn't, she went to a single RT event.  

Flynn was paid by RT, when was Jill Stein paid by Russians?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did Jewish people call Jews who worked with the Nazis?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush was almost as voracious a reader as Obama actually.  

The last president we had that didn't like to read was Bill Clinton, and I say that as a Democrat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad worked at Fry's Electronics back then.  He had one of the very first PCS phones.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush read two books a week.  Trump hasn't read two books in his adult life.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only good Nazi is a dead Nazi.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Snow is a great interviewer.  

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jon_Snow_(journalist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His face when he had to go into conspiracy mode to deny something looked like my ex-BF when he lied to me about where he had been all night.  

Women have built-in creep detectors, and [this guy sounds like this in my head](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k2VhB7vaZI0). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 22 and I haven't lived in a house with a landline.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI handles domestic intelligence for the most part.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The common denominator is authoritarian thinking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just had the largest demonstration in US history.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presidents won the popular vote back then.  Democrats have had two out of the last four presidencies stolen from them.  They are getting fed up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a shame that the Baby Boomers didn't have one good president in their entire demographic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude just tried to tell the NYTimes he misremembered something that he said 24 hours prior by calling it fake news.    

If no one stops Cohen, then papers, hard drives, and phones will be going through industrial shredders at his law firm by noon today.  Cohen is in the chain for whoever is pulling Trump's strings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is coming fast and quick.  The fact that we are hearing about this means someone has been turned.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is: How long will the rest of Trump's staff stay loyal now that Flynn turning on them is a possibility?  

They would be stupid not to lawyer up right now and go to the FBI.  This train has no brakes.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, Trump will help Western Europe, for a price.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This unrest from the civil service has spread way beyond just the intelligence community.

Trump announced a hiring and wage freeze for all federal workers.  He just pissed off 3 million civil servants.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, and an impeachment vote would never get to the Senate.  Trump isn't going to go in front of the American people for 3-4 months and be torn apart by questions about his loyalties to America.  If impeachment proceedings start, he will resign and take the first flight to Moscow.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have 10 million active users still.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most polarized the country has been since the Civil War.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal Judges would laugh that argument out of court, it is a shame that Trump will be judged by the House GOP.  

None of this matters if the House GOP are traitors too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vanishing History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, so you have nothing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not going to matter if Trump is forced to resign or is impeached.  His people like winners, not losers.  

Nixon expected America's *Silent Majority* to back him up, but they didn't.  They turned on him when he became weak.  Authoritarians don't follow weaklings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working in the NSC also has a paper/electronic trail.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By 1980 almost no one in America admitted they voted for Nixon.  Except they elected him twice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He was born in Portland. An executive order sent him to a Japanese internment camp. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He was born in Portland, OR. An executive order sent him to a Japanese internment camp. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BS Hillary hasn't used a desktop computer, Chelsea claimed she taught both of her parents how to use computers in the 1990's.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they need to?  Everyone in the Trump admin that Flynn has talked to on the phone has been recorded since late last year.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't win elections with centrism long term, it is never a long term viable political strategy in any nation, ever.

First kick out the centrists.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centrists are not liberals, and should be called out for the cowards they are when it comes to defending our civil rights.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck with your cowardice and elitism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this centrist nonsense.  

Civil rights are not negotiable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump vastly underestimates the power of the West Coast.  The I-5 corridor is one of the richest stretches of land in the world.  It is a prime longitudinal slice of the Earth's coastal ecosystems with almost every single mineral resource imaginable in the leeward interior.

American Fascism will not touch the West Coast.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Hillary Clinton cheat at a few of her primary debates with Bernie Sanders?  

Fuck the corporate centrists and Clintonites esp.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn Scandal: Emerging Ties To Russia Could Lead To Trumps Impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is about 3-5% of the nation's clean water supply.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome 56 quietly added Bluetooth snitch API </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demonstrators block northbound I-5 in Bellingham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old days were worse.  There are still republicans from the 1980's who will never admit HIV causes AIDs because that is what the right wing talk radio told them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring your best Washington school funding questions to our Reddit AMA next Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mary Emily O'Hara on Twitter: "Rumored new White House press secretary Carl Higbie compared Bernie Sanders to Hitler. Sanders' ancestors were killed in the Holocaust." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call you guys Connectoids.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
