<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4592</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but just in theory. In practice they end up very differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Klaus is not a president anymore and ODS got pushed pretty far back from their once sure position.

Right now we got Milos Zeman for president (former leader of Czech social democratic party) and center right coalition government with sprinkle of populism on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally its the same thing as with us. Just with more money.
Corruption, populism, denying that there are problems just to look good, regional mismanagement that sort of thing.

As with most things it's not as bad as people want to see it, but it's still not very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If displaced means looking for work in capital then sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of current Austrian ministers is Wolfgang Sobotka. 
Seriously, there are lots of germanized Czechs in Austria and bohemized germans in CZ. 
In 1910s there were more Czechs in Vienna than in Brno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure that her husband uses that word when he refers to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it was called Turks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria's far-right: Hipsters or hatemongers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 09:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the kind of pc culture that empowers alt-right. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was Roman because it claimed heritage of Roman empire. Roman empire which, btw, was also multilingual, multiethnic and for most of its history didn't have Rome as capital.

Yes it was an empire because there is no list of requirements a state must fulfill in order to be an empire. After all Haiti was and empire, Brazil was an empire and France was an empire and no one questions names of those states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That quote by Voltaire should be badhistory by itself. 
Every single time someone on the internet mentions HRE this one quote shows up, as if you could sum empire spanning almost a millennium in one sentence. 

I am so sick of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angela Merkel: "I will continue with policy that empowered far right, caused several terror attacks and is partly responsible for Brexit. Oh, and BTW could you take some of these refugees?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is outrageous sir! How dare you suggest that Yuropeans are in any way similar to those uncultured American slobs? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Google is Yurop company now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I found in the source so far is gif with Doloreses narrative loop.
But that was already posted here, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that's my rug.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that it is good to reinvent wheel. Unless you expect others to use it. 

If its just for you to learn how the wheel works and to better understand whats under the hood you can reinvent all the wheels you like. 

Just don't force your misshapen wheels down other peoples throats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's nice. I mean what is wrong with presenting your work. 

Especially when its such nice machinery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, really nice. Just keep it up, things can go wrong rather drastically if you mismanage them. Just look at Greece and Italy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, but Britain is supposed to be falling apart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tallest Skyscraper Planned for City of London Wins Approval </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is set to begin in 1444. 
The developers chose this date because of Crusade of Varna and breakup of Sigismunds realm after his death.

But, the earlier dates are still there. Up to 1350s I think. All the events and borders are coded. Of course it can't compare with proper start date when it comes to accuracy, but the basics like rulers and unions is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be about the same. At least in the evening. 
If you want my advice don't go in the very center of the square.
The stands there are not interesting enough to warrant the pushing and possibility of getting your pockets picked clean. 
Stick to the edges and you will see more than if you went into scrummage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think faith lost the struggle when they joined Republican party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, boy. You fail to understand the mindset of liberal politicians.

They can not comprehend that others can view them as enemies, at best they think that others disagree with them and if they were more educated they would agree. 

In their mind the world is full of good but sometimes misguided people who just wish to get along with each other and live in our modern society, complete with freedom of expression, women rights , open borders/markets and annual gay pride parades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but what can you want from a woman with no stake in future of her country, or even the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, but there are several problems.

1. European heavy industry almost all privatized. You would have to pressure owners to switch to unprofitable goods or you would have to heavily subsidize the goods you want to produce.

2. Unlike in China, the heavy industry in Europe is heavily regulated. Not just environmentally speaking but also regarding workers rights, safety, community responsibility etc. Because of that our industry can hardly compete on costs with foreign imports. 

Unless strict tariffs were implemented. But that would go against free trade policies that Merkel and EU centrists traditionally push for. Not to mention the fact that it would hit the middle and upper class, you know, the people the politicians are closest to.

3. European heavy industry is in decline for last two decades. At very least relative to the rest of the world and probably even in total output. Numerous factories were shut down and torn down. Workers moved into different jobs, others emigrated and many retired. 
Increasing industrial capacity would not be easy.

4. Last but not least. In short term this policy would be very painful. And elections are coming up in Germany and France, not to mention referendum in Italy. Therefore it would be, to say at least, bold to pursue a policy that will cause discontent among electorate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just his culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does ANYONE HERE have any direct experience with the project, or at very least state schools in Uganda?

Because the article is saying less than nothing and it seems to me like we should have more information before condemning either the government or Gates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Member Fallout?

I love to member Fallout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but 5% chance of negligible contamination should not be a reason to stop using very useful technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because NASA is conservative as hell. 

And it has to be. It's budget is so small, its mission so bloated and its direction so politicized that any misstep can have catastrophic implications for next decade. 

That's why NASA nixes the most innovative proposals and sticks to same approach since the 70s.

For example, inflatable modules for space stations.
Cheaper, lighter, easy to manufacture and replace, oh and also from the 60s. The BEAM module attached to ISS right now is using materials known since 70s and module several times larger (TransHab) was supposed to be part of ISS from the start.

Until it got cut by Congress, BTW both parties sponsored the bill and both parties voted for it.

Edit: Same goes for non-chemical propulsion and non-solar energy sources. First US nuclear reactor in space was launched in 1965, and it was also the last. Imagine the missions that would be possible without such stringent energy constraints we have today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 12:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like you acting like assholes so I acted like a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrats should focus on policies that help rural voters. 
They already have big cities, they had them for decades.

What they need now is to focus on issues affecting rest of the country, farmers, workers, people who care less about global warming and more about next paycheck.
You know, people for whom Democratic party should work.

I am not American, issues in Czech Republic are very different to those in USA. But I think that when a party loses ALL THREE ELECTIONS AT ONCE, it should change strategy. Because this is not working.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could have just asked us. I do understand need for proper scientific process but seriously.

That's like one of most basic things, right there next to sensory overload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 11:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had two chins anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have arrived, and it is now that we perform our charge.
In fealty to the God-Emperor (our undying Lord) and by the grace of the Golden Throne, I declare Exterminatus upon the Imperial world of Pandora.
I hereby sign the death warrant of an entire world and consign a billion souls to oblivion.
May Imperial Justice account in all balance.
The Emperor Protects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are missing the point. 

We are having wrong kind of discussion here. That we should no longer increase emissions is not the issue here. That much is clear.
Well maybe not to certain idiots but, sadly we can not do much about them. Unless you plan to strap them in chairs and educate them Clockwork Orange style.

What we should be talking about is how the hell are we going to put the climate back together, because it is already broken.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House is on fire. Throwing gasoline at it sure does not help, but doing nothing doesn't solve anything either.

At this point we have to face the fact that miracles will not happen. The Republicans will not suddenly become scientifically literate, the China and India will continue boosting their economic output.

In the very article you have linked they say that the emissions fell because of ECONOMIC SLOWDOWN and not just Chinese government getting its shit together. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 16:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I just throw this out in the open?

It's too late. None of us, including president of USA can stop the global warming now. Even if USA had freaking Al Gore as president there would be no way to stop this.

Sure developed world can decrease emissions, but our emissions are no longer the bulk of the problem. The real big deal is that the rest of the world wants to live as we do.

And who could blame them? 
If you think that China, India, Nigeria or Indonesia will put their economies on the sacrificial altar of humanity you are badly mistaken. 
Sure, should they do it the things will work out eventually. But their governments would risk revolutions, civil wars and other stuff in the process. The train is just going too fast now for them to jump out.

So lets pull your collective heads out of your collective asses and stop pretending you can stop this shit. The ecosystem IS FUCKED. 
That's it, baring miracle, there is NO WAY to fix it just by lowering emissions.

We need to get radical. The climate won't fix itself just by us stopping fucking with it. 

No WE FUCKED IT UP, so WE MUST FIX IT. 
Fertilize oceans with iron, genetically engineer new plants to fix more carbon, splice corals to grow faster and to be more resilient. 
Fill depressions in Sahara and Australia with sea water to increase cloud cover.

Build desalination plants and dykes around coastal cities, prepare resettlement of coastal populations. 

Build more nuclear power plants, so what if some reactors melt down. If ten Chernobyls are price we have to pay for our survival as a species then SO BE IT.

TLDR: LETS SCIENCE THE SHIT OUT OF GLOBAL WARMING. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 11:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, it would be nice to actually hurt your enemy without taking his land.

Often the conquest just isn't worth it. Sure I want to break Ottos, but when all I can take from them without crippling myself are shitty North Africa provinces I would rather just release their vassals and make them return some cores.

But then I waste conquest CB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and lots of other stuff was already workable by that time as well. Including electric cars and solar panels.

But alas, neither was economical enough to warrant widespread adoption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your argument is that the other side is stupid, KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT!

I mean this guy had grammar school right? I thought they teach rhetoric there or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serbians should not forget this. 
It is very easy to forget the evil one does, much easier than forgetting the evil done to him. 

We Czechs have lot of experience with this, and let me tell you: pretending it didn't happen does not heal the wounds, it only lets them fester.

But I would like to point out, that the fact that Serbians were brutal aggressors during the wars should not diminish their value when it comes to self determination, or their value as human beings in general.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final Polls Show Renzis Referendum Heading for Defeat in Italy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you have a referendum to worry about? Oh wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My former employer required all paper documents and DVDs to be shredded and all hard-drives wiped.

But they didn't provide us software for the later and after moving we lost our shredders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britains Home Ownership Declining as Young People Grow Poorer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punish them. There is something called High Treason they are guilty of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By force, there is just no other way.

If they break law, they get deported. 

Take their children from them at first sign of abuse. 

Routine inspections of places of worship and community centers even remotely associated with terrorism or funded by foreign nations. 

Ban burka, niqab, and use of drugs from their homeland. 

Put all religious schools under firm government oversight and close those that are even remotely associated with terrorism or antisocial behavior. 

Put all civil arbitration under government oversight, with police present at all hearing and given access to all files. 

All priest etc. would be trained in government institutions and issued permits to preach and work. 

And there are several other things that come to mind, but these are the simplest to implement. Technically lot of it is already in effect, the government just needs to enforce it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yeah PC bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly its too late. Permafrost is melting across Siberia and Canada, all the methane inside is worse than anything USA could conceivably pump out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Member Chewbacca again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she represents liberalism, I am not a liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Teutoburg forest level of bad decision. 
Taking third of your forces into enemy territory, while rest of your forces is already spread VERY thin and when the best you can expect is some degree of information on what is going on and MAYBE some reduction of the impossible threat IS VERY STUPID.

Lets consider the best case scenario.
Watch finds out how many wildlings/undead there are and figure out how to kill the walkers. Great Job.
Well no. Not only would watch considerably reduce its stocks of food, horse feed etc., it would also reveal its weakness to wildlings and the Walkers. 

To make matters worse they left their rear unguarded. The Castle Black was essentially empty, if even a very small force attacked while they were on their scouting mission they would lose the Castle Black and the Wall itself.

But that is not the only problem. The watch had about 1000 men at the start of the winter. A pathetic number for the task they were given. Mormont risked reducing that number even further. And don't forget that he took the very best he had at the time. Each man lost at that point is a considerable loss for the Watch. 

Last but not least, Mormont took majority of experienced officers with him, even if just few of them died the Watch would be decapitated. Which eventually happened.

TLDR: Mormont risked everything for very little possible gain. A good commander plans for the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does everyone miss possibility of genetic engineering? Protheans were more pragmatic and reasonable than Asari dominated Citadel, not to mention much more advanced. 

Even today we can do some pretty kickass stuff with CRISPR, we could do a lot more if we poured money into it and lifted unnecessary regulation.

The guys in trailer could be Protheans, just little adjusted for new environment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes you want to lock yourself under Himalayas and work on webway portal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy's Next in the Crosshairs for Anti-Establishment Wave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Voters Who Gave Trump the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next four as well. Garrison being president and memberberries winning... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just in, /tg/ presented its list of Heretics, the number ten will shock you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck them all to death, you say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demography Slays the Democrats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So democrats are pretty much fucked now. They have lost presidency, senate, congress and several governorships. 

Republicans are fucked because their electorate just voted in guy they tried to get rid of for years. The very same guy who is not very likely to forgive them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People pretty much did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's time to fuck them all to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is nice philosophy but not a good foreign policy. Not intervening would be great if Europe was in middle of ocean and we lived in age before transoceanic trade. But alas that is not the case.

Today Europe is highly dependent on foreign trade, most of our economy is built around either exporting or importing things outside of EU. Therefore ignoring everything outside EU could, very well, economic ruin.  

For example Somali pirates operate well outside EU, and yet they threaten EU citizens and trade routes we need for our countries to function. Would you let them walk free? Let Americans to do the job? Or maybe its time for underfunded and corruption ridden local armies to handle it.
Or we could pull our own weight and do it ourselves. What do you think is best?

Another thing is international terrorism. Say you have situation like today in Iraq, Syria and Libya. Genocidal organisation is butchering local ethnic and religious minorities, sending millions at our doorstep. The very same organisation has stated goal to kill us all if we don't follow their ways, and they have already proven they mean it. 

Local government is on verge of collapse. Time is of the essence. Do you let them fall? It is outside of EU borders. They are not members why should you care? Maybe because it can be your problem tomorrow.

You see it is not cut and dry. Interventions are not a dirty word. And often they are only way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 10:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libya is right next door, we bombed them to shit and left them to their own devices. Western Sahara is giant occupied territory, right next to Spanish land, that was denied self-determination by totalitarian regime and yet Europe does nothing. The list goes on and on.

The last few decades have shown that western Europe is way too keen on blaming Americans for everything, while not even keeping its own backyard clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 10:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let me get this straight. Countries that have consistently failed to meet their NATO obligations, have populations very averse to military in general, lack determination to sort out even very close geopolitical problems (Libya, Western Sahara, Cyprus), are going to match NATO in military power?

That's realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the period is the problem here. Lets face it, the WWII and entire 20th century is political minefield. Already they had to sacrifice immense amount of realism and flavor by omitting, well you know, the genocidal parts. And that's just tip of the iceberg. 
Pretty much anything can offend someone in this time period, especially if it has in-game effects. 

I can see why that makes Paradox less likely to actually put their work into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ask why we must cleanse the xenos. I will tell you. The filth of the alien and the witch must be exterminated to preserve the purity of the Human race, lest we degenerate into abomination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far do you think we are from practical, two way, Brain-Computer interface? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google contests EU antitrust charges on comparison shopping, AdSense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europes doomed Mars lander is seen in color for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Risk of Early Danish Elections Rises as Budget Talks Struggle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volkswagen Scandal Widens as Germany Probes Chairman Poetsch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All western or northern Europe. and approximately 80% either French or German.

Yep the title checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Taborites in Bohemia were essentially theocratic socialist commune. After Communists took over Czechoslovakia Taborites became major sources of symbols and rhetoric for the party. We even had pavise in our seal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's basically Turkish propaganda, it goes along the lines that Romans deserved it and that heroic Muslims were destined to rule over decadent Christians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what if I told you that they then essentially banned Alsatian language in schools and effectively removed their entire culture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be Ubisoft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well new legislation would be needed but that is much easier than changing international law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it wasn't the original intention but that does not mean its not useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turks in Germany are allowed to hold double nationality which other Germans are not allowed to. If I were to take on another nationality, the German embassy could just take away my German passport.

You know that is actually a good thing. If later your government decides to actually take care of its people, instead of rapists, terrorists and religious nuts, they can revoke their citizenship without breaking international law and then deport them. In many ways it makes things easier because Muslims holding dual citizenship are most likely to be disloyal or dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone seriously surprised by this? The EU is game played for national interests and it always was. You don't have to like it but that's how it is and that's why all the nations went into it.

Or do you seriously believe that everyone is in it to promote "spirit of collaboration" and "European ideals"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Czech. There used to be about 3 million Germans in what is now Czech Republic, before the war anyway. Right now there are almost none, therefore there is much less need to know German. Also the WWII and Cold War meant that we lost most of our contact with Germans which are culturally closest to us Austrians and Bavarians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The EU Wants Global Bank Regulator to Soften Standards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turks were slaughtering Christians, Greeks, Armenians, Assyrians. Turkey should have been destroyed back then, properly partitioned. Shame that the allies didn't have the guts for few more years of war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, teaching German stopped being a priority for us about two decades ago. It was second language for my ancestors up to grandparents (from fathers side), my father was fluent and often went to Germany on holiday. And I, well I can barely say where I'm from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 23:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP.
In my case its a mix, it largely depends on what I think about.
Certain thoughts are easier in English and other in Czech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pound Gains Before Brexit Court Ruling, BOE Policy Announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 10:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should not. I hate to say this but Paradox games are NOT historical simulations. They are meant to be reasonably realistic, but buffing Ottomans every patch is NOT realistic. It DOES lead to realistic outcome but in a realistic way.

For example if Ottomans in 1600 got all the land they historically had, cores and all, by an event. It would be realistic outcome but it would be essentially cheating. Just like this is.

Anyway, Paradox should not simulate expansion of Ottomans, Spanish, French etc. they should simulate general trends and key events. But they should not force the game in one direction. Hell instead of going west Ottomans could go and conquer India, Muscovy could fall to Golden Horde and Novgorod, England could win the 100 year war. 

History was often at edge of knife and lots of stuff was possible. In rest of EU4 weird outcomes are possible should happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, however Erben altered them so that they were "closer to original". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was huge but, it was not because its armies were almost invulnerable or because it had constant genius rulers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Londons Killer Air Ruled Illegal by U.K.s Top Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could rebuild it, or at least fix it up like you did with Pantheon(St. Mary and Martyrs).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say he wasn't a dick :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from historical claims there is continuity of administration. Current Catholic church is largely modeled after imperial institutions, after all even Pope has title Pontifex Maximus that once belonged to Roman high priest/emperor, and [Roman Curia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roman_Curia) which governs church to this day is essentially continuation of the imperial bureaucracy. 

In many cases the church was only institution left when Empire fell apart. The priests were often literate and respected, and thus they became administrators of what was left of old imperial cities like Cologne, Trier, Augsburg, Aquileia and even Rome. 

Eventually the bishops became rulers and church turned into essentially secular power where religion often played second fiddle. 
Legacy of this we carry to this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats Czech and from 19th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy had least enough honor not to flee from tribunal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But alas, it is the reason thousands play the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottomans, France is manageable, Spain fragile, Austria easy to bait into proxy wars, Ming has mandate of heaven, Poland is to reliant on Lithuania, Muscovy lacks development, England/GB is over-relying on navy and Brandenburg/Prussia is contained by HRE.

But Ottomans have no easy counter, no strategy that can be applied without relying on luck. When it comes to them there are only two ways.

1. Spend ENTIRE first century focusing just on them until they are gone.

2. Spend ENTIRE last century focusing just on them until they are gone.

Fighting them in midgame borders on masochism, doable but so unenjoyable and stressful that I rather focus on ANYTHING else.

And to add insult to injury those guys are given ahistorical buffs on scale that just does not make sense. I get it Paradox, you want to put history on tracks. 
But that's not how history works. In real life one battle can cripple an empire for century, arbitrarily buffing a nation so that it has advantage it never had does NOT add to the fun. 

+++Rant over++++ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I have nothing against Germans. Hell I think that the whole republic and nationalism deal in the 1918 was not a good idea and actually engendered our (Czech) existence. 

It's just that I feel that your government has gone way overboard with a lot of policies and fails to understand the ramifications of them. And, like it or not, German and French government policies are effectively EU policies. How many times in last few years have you seen Juncker when it came to important Union business and how many times have you seen Merkel or Holland. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sets the bar really low however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not a hard standard to beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To those saying that we should just buy products of higher quality: THERE ARE NONE. 

Yep, seriously. All our manufacturers are either out of business or owned by foreigners.  And we want to buy stuff of the same quality you have, we have to pay more than you do. Yeah that's right, we have less money and if we want same services we have to pay more.

And our government can't do a dick about it, because we have free movement of goods, capital, people and services in EU. So there goes that. And there is almost zero chance for new manufacturers to arise at home, because spoiler alert, we have less money to start businesses and our experts are leaving for greener pastures.

But we do get those EU handouts in form of infrastructure projects, so there's that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Economists Urge EU to Shun Brexit Taboos to Keep U.K. In </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 08:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this guy for real? I mean I am considered to be radical in lot of things, hell some people even called me racist but...

Genetically the aboriginal IS human, he might be wrong in this case and he can be misguided, hell he can even be evil, crazy psycho who hides unspeakable in his basement. 

But he is still human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 08:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An island would explain this. Either man made or perhaps heavily sculpted and sterilized. But if it was me I would release some nanoswarms to kill anything that is not allowed inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 07:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lists of sites on dark web, most widely known is "Hidden Wiki", this one you can even find by google.
Unfortunately most of the sites there are either down, honeypots or essentially useless. 
Because of that you should use Hidden wiki only to get link for dark web search engine, Torch or Not Evil.

But, and I must stress this above all, you should be careful. The links are often very risky, one moment you are looking for advice on privacy, the next moment you wish for brain bleach and hope that what you just saw was NOT what it looked like.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 07:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the gulenist. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poland does not have such restrictions BECAUSE it is weaker politically. 
Germany can say:"If you don't play by our rules we will punish you." That doesn't mean that rules themselves make sense, it just means that German government can afford to act on them without causing their country significant damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of few times Archer made a good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Germany is big. Lets face it, only France, Germany, UK and maybe Italy have enough pull to affect corps such as Google, everyone else is just too small, population and economy wise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh don't worry Merkel will fix that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German guesthouse turns away Israelis: 'Our apartments are not for them' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will probably get worse. If I were you I would be working on contingency plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey detains opposition Cumhuriyet newspaper editor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 09:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey shuts 15 media outlets over alleged terrorist links </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
