<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5181</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you watch movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joke's on you, I'm not a kind person.

I don't believe in tarot but I've had my tarot read a few times and this isn't how it works. Obviously you can lie and make things up, but the cards actually have specific references and meanings. There were times when my tarot was read and I nodded along in agreement and other times I'd be rolling my eyes at how irrelevant it was. I see it more as being like a stopped clock that's right twice a day rather than the Barnum Effect.

ETA: Similarly, I started reading my horoscope in the newspaper about six months ago just to pass the time. Most of the time it's irrelevant but for three days last week it was frighteningly accurate. Coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that Boris Johnson is an American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't. There's a pipe in my bathroom that's insulated but the paint is cracking and the plaster around the ceiling is blistering. Wouldn't want to risk furniture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of kosher food in Antwerp, Amsterdam, London, Paris, Rome, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend bought one of these: https://modli.co/swimwear/swim-dresses.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read the book, but it's pretty obvious that the Internet is different from TV because of its ubiquity. While people definitely watch(ed) too much TV, I never saw anybody walking in the street watching TV. Nobody ever felt phantom vibrations of a TV in their pocket. 

And in the reverse, TV is not interactive. So nobody ever put a picture of themselves doing duck lips on TV. Nobody ever got cyberbullied by a TV program. Nobody ever got doxxed by a TV program.

But people are not fine because of TV. It's one of the contributors to childhood (and adulthood) obesity. The Internet is even worse. That's why it was such a big joke that Pokemon Go actually made people leave their rooms go Outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children's books that were written a long time ago are squarely aimed at children and will generally not be of much interest to adults. It's very different than kids books that are written now that have built in a certain amount of appeal for adults too. 

I think this is mostly about tone. Kids books today are a lot more cynical and knowing, while older kids books tend to be more earnest and innocent.

That said, kids books are short. Even if you don't gain that much from having read them, it's not like you have to spend too much time on them. If it took you "hours" to read Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, you need to practice your reading. It's a 160-paged kids book. That shouldn't take much more than an hour to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that if there were no State of Israel, none of this would be possible, right? 

Half the world's Jews live there, I have a lot of family there. I have been there 3 times, and I plan on going many more times, I plan on moving there one day, and being buried there near my grandfather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God told Abraham to leave his city, Ur Kasdim*, and go to the land of Canaan and that would become his homeland. So while what bh2005 wrote was a joke, the idea is that God chose this particular land for us, and we believe that the land has a holiness to it. It couldn't have been just anywhere or God might as well have just said, you stay right where you are and someday all this will be yours.

*Which is identified as being in various locations in the Middle East. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ur_Ka%C5%9Bdim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks.

As for topics of conversation, I've eaten with lots of different types of families in Israel and America ranging from Chassidish to MO and everything in between and while right-wingers were far more likely to sing zemirot and have a dvar Torah, Torah was never a general topic of conversations, more like extensive discussions about their social life and what other people are doing. Which is the worst.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I had mixed feelings about different aspects of it

For example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Layer Cake?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscar nominations puzzle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this week's The Week crossword puzzle they had the following clues. Each answer is the title of two 2017 Oscar nominated movies. To make it harder, I'm not going to tell you how many letters each answer is.

1. Really digging how bright it is outside at 2 a.m.

2. No words from the king of the jungle

3. Shovel dirt all over your boundaries with your neighbors

4. When your plane touches down in Tinseltown

Answers:

1. [Loving Moonlight](#spoiler)

2. [Lion Silence](#spoiler)

3. [Sully Fences](#spoiler)

4. [La La Land Arrival](#spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as an FYI, Lavie Tidhar is a prominent Israeli-British SF writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radiator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radical feminism tends to go along with smashing capitalism too, so it would look a lot like Sweden crossed with Battlestar Galactica, but hopefully with less war. 

Men and women with equal respect for each other. Women equal partners in business and government. No sexualization. And the main thing would be that people (men and women alike) would feel free to be themselves without any pressure to fit into a neat gender box.

Personally, I agree with feminist Shulamith Firestone who said that the patriarchy stems from childbearing. And that means that until we start growing babies in vats, there will be no way to completely do away with the patriarchy. Even in Sweden more women than men work part time in order to take care of children. 

But even without a patriarchy the world wouldn't be perfect. Utopia is not possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not suggesting anybody actually go out and do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I wrote, what's considered modest is dependent on what non-Jewish women do. Another example, if Jews typically had lived in India instead of Europe, pants wouldn't be considered beged ish because there they are unisex garments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pics or GTFO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way women dress in Judaism is often dependent on the surrounding culture. In the Bible women wore nose rings. If an Orthodox woman today would have a nose ring, it would be a scandal. Similarly, in Israel there is a group of women who wear burkas and they're roundly condemned by all. However, if they were living in Saudi Arabia, they'd be expected to wear burkas just like the Arab women because Jewish women are not allowed to dress less modestly than the non-Jewish women they're living near.

So I assume it's the same thing with wedding rings. Back in the day women probably wore more rings on more fingers, so wearing your wedding ring on your index finger looked normal. But now that general society doesn't do it, it would look weird if Jewish women did.

But since it's becoming more popular/normal it wouldn't look so bad. Though some people might not realize it was a wedding ring - if you have any interest in people knowing that you're married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was lust involved with the coveting, then there was probably sinning there. And jealousy is a bad character trait no matter who you're jealous of. But to convince a Jew to leave a non-Jew and marry another Jew, that seems like a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not dying of natural causes, that's dying of a heart attack.

A young person generally cannot die of natural causes. If a young person had a heart attack, that was a preventable problem and therefore is not natural causes.

Simply put, death by natural causes is a death that is not unexpected. It is not from an accident, a natural disaster, a homicide or suicide. It is also one that is not preventable.

http://nursinglink.monster.com/benefits/articles/117-death-by-natural-causes-explained

As the article goes on to say, if a news article reports that someone young died of natural causes, it's to protect the privacy of the dead person and the family. A doctor would never say that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert Jordan didn't do this. Pretty much all of his characters were unlikeable regardless of whether they were good or evil. Same with Lev Grossman. Many people find Quentin particularly unlikeable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to report it to get the mods to do anything about it. So I reported it and now it's been flagged "inaccurate." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally got my Kind bars after what seems like ages: Dark Chocolate Almond Mint (I don't like mint, so somebody's going to get a gift) and Dark Chocolate Almond   Coconut. I don't know what to make of the taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can walk down the aisle or hold the poles of the chuppah. Otherwise, none that I can think of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 05:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean it's one more thing to keep and show to your grandchildren to explain how different the world used to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're committed to a religious life and want all the conveniences, you'll have to move at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be inconvenient at times, but generally speaking, couldn't care less. This is one reason why it's important to live in a Jewish community - so that things like restaurants and other conveniences will be around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there's been a discussion lately of Hillary running for mayor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What book is this from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to this book, he would make havdalah on Sunday. Sounds like the Tuesday thing is an urban legend. Unless someone can bring a source for it.

https://books.google.com/books?id=5MTcigeJvmwC lpg=PA110 ots=rRtRJlHWQN dq=Amshinover%20rebbe%20havdala%20tuesday pg=PA110#v=onepage q=Amshinover%20rebbe%20havdala%20tuesday f=false </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't edited. You saw what you were expecting to see. I do that all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the question assumed that she was the Democratic Party nominee. Which means Cuomo is out of the picture for whatever reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends who she's running against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not hated, but I loved the Narnia books as a kid and found them dull as an adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The early Stephanie Plum books by Janet Evanovich. They get annoying after a while, but the early ones are gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any books by James A. Michener or Edward Rutherford. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you know how the federal government works. Please read up on what federal grants are. Here's the wiki article for starters: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Federal_grants_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he said he was going to take a shower he was telling you to leave. He was being indirect, not passive-aggressive. Not asking you to leave directly was a way to allow you to save face - so that you wouldn't go home feeling like this guy kicked you out of his home. If you had picked up on your cue, it would have gone like this:

You: No, I have my period.

Him: Argue argue.

You: Still no.

Him: Okay, whatever dude, I'm going to take a shower now.

You: Have fun, see you around. 

Him: Yeah, see ya.

You: Bye.

Him: Bye.

The end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience was nothing like sokpuppet1's. Nobody was freaking out or hugging or crying. 

I was on the Q train and had a bird's-eye view of the Towers burning as we went over the Manhattan Bridge. I got off at Canal Street and walked up Mulberry Street to get to shelter, so to speak, because I couldn't get to my office - they weren't letting people south of Chambers Street. 

On Mulberry Street they were setting up for the San Gennaro festival like nothing was going on. Canal Street was a bit of a madhouse, but it always is, so it wasn't too much out of the ordinary. 

The closest I got to the WTC that day was about 10 blocks away. Union Square is almost two miles away. Everybody who was south of Canal that day was probably in shock.

When they finally reopened the bridges I asked a cop if they needed people to give blood and he said no because there were many deaths but few injuries. So I walked over the Williamsburg Bridge and headed home. The buses were free and the weather was perfect. 

That night I couldn't sleep because every time I closed my eyes all I could see was an image of the Towers burning. It was three nights before it went away. But it took a year before I could look at a picture of the WTC without getting upset; my office was four blocks from Ground Zero - we were allowed back in a week later.

ETA: Just read over my journal entry for that day. 

I watched the movie 42 Up when I got home and I liked it. 

The DSL wasn't working so I had to use dial-up to get onto the Internet. 

I almost fainted in a store two days later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racists are idiots if they voted for Trump because they were voting against their own economic self-interest. New Yorkers may be racists, but they're not stupid racists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't go to the protest, but later in the afternoon I saw a bunch of people in my neighborhood coming home from it. A little girl was carrying an Elmo for President sign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it would be absurd not to tell people that it's your wedding. A wedding is public event. In the olden days the whole community would be invited.

And if you're doing it for Internet privacy, then don't mention it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents got a census form in the mail recently. It wasn't a scam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Only the Kallah and maybe the Choson, so this is interesting.

I assumed he was trying to be tznius about being the chosson. (Which would be absurd, but I wouldn't rule it out as America's next top chumra.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. We had a required writing class too. I think it was considered an English class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sorts of things were on the syllabus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalin, Lenin, Marx, and many other communist leaders were ethnically Jewish

Stalin and Lenin weren't Jewish. Marx wasn't a communist leader.

Edit: You're thinking of Trotsky. And things didn't turn out so well for him, now did they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were the options for Communications? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
