<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't question the binder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love the action scenes in Bollywood films. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several Injured As False Reports Of Shots Fired Spark Chaos Near Coney Island Amusement Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never doubt the Binder. Hicks did it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol wow. Announcers are so bad they possibly missed that fan getting thrown out of the game for touching the Aaron Judge ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. That sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why hasn't the bot uploaded any highlights yet? I missed the Judge triple/homer(?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ricky Martin says he waited to come out over fear of rejection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Alex Haley plagiarized 81 passages from Harold Courlander's The African for his novel Roots. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grindr probably has more money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man sues Grindr after 1,100 strangers show up at his home, workplace for sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harlem woman planning on going to Easter Mass with parents instead finds them dead from carbon monoxide poisoning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There probably won't be another album released today. Lebron got the album early and hasn't said there were two parts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music industry goes to war with YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local sex offender law ruled unconstitutional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draymond Green: 'Steph Curry is light-skinned, so players want to make him out to be soft' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Judge is starting to show his potential </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents protest bullying at area h.s., after recent suicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is A Transgender Learning Gap in the Emergency Room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that pick traded isn't protected. That seems like a bad idea. You don't want to be like what happened with the Nets this year. being horrible and not having that pick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly can the Knicks get in a trade for Melo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a couple threads here that he might have played his last game as a knick. So assuming he gets traded in the offseason what can the knicks hope for in return? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man attacks MTA worker for being a snitch because he told cops guy was urinating between cars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sex offender residency restrictions get council OK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ESPN's Keith Law puts 3 Yankees prospects in top 20 overall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the one where Danny D becomes invisible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several months if I choose it. I am at a point that I never have to go on the internet for porn again if I want to fap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 dead in murder-suicide spree in Houston, Ft. Bend Co. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a well known clip from a scene.](https://i.imgur.com/K9MSP1d.mp4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't seem likely at all. Why would they trade a cost controlled top 3 pick for Melo who could opt out after next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I skip around when I watch porn. I don't sit through the whole video. So I have seen every video. I do often revisit some videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They put effort in the story and make some jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2.24 TB was 1398 of the videos. They have 7531 in total as of this post. I think it was a good deal. I don't really like a couple of their male actors. The Spanish kid who looks really young and Keiran Lee. So out of the 7531 maybe 2,000 had a chance of being appealing to me. Out of those I downloaded 1,400 which is still a lot. I have seen large parts of every video I downloaded.

I think if someone were to download the highest possible quality for every video it would be 10-12 TB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No plans on revamping. Most of the cost comes from the drives. I haven't spent much in total on porn with subs being $5 or $10. I have a couple 4k videos. They are 12 and 14 GB but just like you I can't take full advantage of them. I only have 1080p displays. They are also too large per video. Brazzers files are so large because of the encoding. The corporation that owns them owns Digital Playground. Digital has the same video quality of videos with the 1080p being 1-2 GB a video. I am in to professional more than amateur. If I like a girl it is easier to find more videos with her or get a general idea of the quality of an upcoming scene featuring them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They share non-porn movies with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually still at JBOD. A friend gave me several of his 16 TB My book duo's he didn't need anymore. I store it on there for the offline use. I also have movies/games. That stuff is 14 TB. Brazzers doesn't have a daily download limit. You can download all there stuff if you have the time to do it. The only thing is their files are much larger than other companies. 1080p can be 4-5 GB a video. Evil Angel for example 1080p videos are 1.6-2.2 GB a video. It depends on company for my bangbros section I did that. For other companies I just do it by alphabet order like you saw in the Brazzers screenshot. It doesn't get annoying. I usally search by name and pic a random video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9.95 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I share them on a plex account. Someone asked for more Brazzers and I got a bunch of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got it cheap from a March Madness deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio woman charged with raping, robbing cab driver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman, 23, charged with raping and robbing male taxi driver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some say new Mo. law tracking sex offenders is unconstitutional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I purchased a Brazzers sub and downloaded 2.24 TB of their videos AMA about that and porn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone post a mirror the link doesn't work anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't credited in the videos I have seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USA, Canada and Mexico launch joint bid to host 2026 World Cup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first is Quey Machu she only did 1 video I think. The second one is Heather Vahn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
