<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject757</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, I was just reading your comment history. Either your the best troll alive or the dumbest fucking rube I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the job. The job is to generate revenue in any way possible while writing propaganda to reflect the interests of the owner. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ain't seen nothing yet. 

After he moves the embassy to Jerusalem, you're really going to see the bodies stack up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what that means. Is there someone on the White House staff leaking this stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super high end math here, but let's see, 3M / 319M = .009404

.09404% - You were close, but no participation trophies for this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to rest after trying those mental gymnastics. 

Muslims do just fine making themselves look bad; it's not the "non-Muslims" in ISIS giving them a bad name.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you link the arrest report?

I'm not too encouraged by one of the "journalists" twitter with Trump nazi memes but hey, like you say, if there's no evidence, then things will turn out just fine. The justice system at work... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yeah, Iran is great](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N_huJDggNa0). Agreed, Saudi should have been there too. Probably a harder spout to turn off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the newspeak box in your house as featured in 1984. Propaganda piped straight into your brain from the global elites that own your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sponsored by NYT, Washpo and CNN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is your data? In someone's cloud? I'm sure you fully read the terms of use that stated we can and will turn any and all data over to law enforcement whenever it suits us. Wonder if Google has any data that someone might be interested in? Things aren't so black and white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows. The last we heard he was attacking "332 pages of regulations that he was not allowed to make public". He is a huge proponent of broadband, and especially broadband for everyone, including rural places, so it's going to be interesting to hear his side of things. If he's against bandwidth caps, net neutrality doesn't matter.

Just like QoS (quality of service), it doesn't matter unless there is some sort of limit that you're bumping into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, so the 4th amendment doesn't apply to electronics then, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might a small cross section of liberal minded people that own guns and books and voted for Trump....I know...*mind blown*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing your truth is the only true truth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This country was founded on the idea of telling everyone else to go fuck themselves and the next thing that follows that (the 1st amendment) is the 2nd amendment. It's not an accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter. I'm not calling the shots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To not become a glass parking lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will see another Civil War before you will see gun control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't pretend to know Trump's targets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. That's a fucking warzone and can be routed out in a week and life returned to normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, you move there and fix it then.

This shit isn't going to fix itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At some point you just need to acknowledge reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we're talking about a little shock and awe in an area that has been chalking up deaths worse than global war zones for years. 

Time to go in, impose a curfew, win some hearts and minds, root out some evil and return to normal. Should take a week, maybe two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just really sad this sub found it's way onto Brock's radar so the /r/politics pros and their brainwashed generation have started attacking it like it's their job...cause it's their job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it man, it's hard, really hard. It's not called a mental illness for nothing. I hope you get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Immediate deaths is the only importance? 

That's cute, but obviously not what I said. 

Happy you are reasonable enough to agree with the second point. Good thing there have been and continue to be significant investments in renewable energy and STEM education also! Most recently, it looks like Mr. Musk is finding a way to be successful with Trump at the Helm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my comrade and I would have gotten away with it if it weren't for you meddling kids! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people died in the incidents you're referring to? How would you power the factories to make all of the alternative fuel products? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't be wearing all black and protesting and yell "journalist" when things don't go your way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you legalized it, do you think human trafficking would go down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I was talking about a conspiracy in the conspiracy subreddit; not sure how your random anecdote contributes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is we? The only conspiracy here is what's special about this pipeline that makes it different than [all the other pipelines we walk safely over every day](http://i.imgur.com/nAlelg8.png). Someone is paying and getting paid for this level of opposition. Who's the real money behind the movement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the concern trolling China and MSM. We'll keep leading and let you focus on your hundreds of millions of unskilled bodies that you're so scared are going to wake up and come take their piece from the elites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rest my case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see any relationship between or points or supporting data. Looks like you're trying to rationalize a world view you wish was true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you do, it's about to be illegal to mention that you notice.

HR 6421 - http://www.osce.org/cio/68921?download=true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see someone bring up BLM or Soros in my 13-year-old daughter's class. She would eat them for lunch and shit them out. 

And then I would probably have to pick her up from school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are the proposed guidelines for hate speech as proposed in HR 6421 since they don't mention them directly in the bill.

http://www.osce.org/cio/68921?download=true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. While I lean right, I hate seeing every Trump headline posted here. The only Trump related conspiracies we should be seeing relate to pizzag8, actual Russia evidence (the Flynn investigation is notable, until it isn't), or him starting the 10th Crusade as predicted by Jewish mysticism, or maybe the lawsuit that David Brock just filed.

Nothing about Obamacare or a pussy parade or a press conference or inauguration numbers or what some talking head is spewing; just evidence of the TPTB and the real war happening out of the public eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a gag order, it's a [shitty liberal name for a law](http://nymag.com/thecut/2017/01/trump-reinstates-global-gag-rule-on-abortion.html) that states the US isn't going to help liberals kill babies all over the world.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can disagree with terrorist and sexual attacks but they still are happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did 3 weeks through France, Germany and Italy. We didn't run into anyone that was anti-Trump. Some people were definitely hesitant to speak out at first (funny one that comes to mind was the old guy afraid he was going to offend me by saying they said 'Obummer' instead of Obama...'cause he's like a bum') but I was fortunate not to come across any raving liberals (except a couple of Americans) for the most part.

Getting accosted in the street by immigrants got old fast though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany happily admits that it censors the news for the well being of all...like they are doing you a favor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany and France are definitely hurting. 

Source: my personal visits there. I go about monthly and most recently took my family of 5 for Christmas and I likely won't bring them back to either country until the situation improves. 

It was the second time I had taken my family to Europe this year but we cut the first one short when we were in town for the Brussels bombings and I guess we were fortunate to be at a Munich Christkindlmarket instead of one in Berlin on that day.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5pgzum/israel_begins_ethnically_cleansing_bedouin/dcr537l/) is an exchange I had yesterday that describes what I think is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that was just 3 million illegal immigrants that likely voted in the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is where I'm going to have disagree with you. The overwhelming majority of Muslims (excl. the minority of extremists) do not wish for the 'extermination' of Israel and its people as is often implied, rather consider the legitimacy of its existence as a sovereign nation to be illegitimate. 

I think you're splitting hairs, the end result is the same. Can't really end their country without ending their tribe at this point.

  signal the final nail in the coffin for any hope of a two-state solution or perhaps even the survival of Palestinians in general, and one that would undoubtedly ignite conflict between Israeli and a number of their Arab neighbors 

Yep, this is the part where I think we're at. Get out the way or become a genocide statistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly. I'm a neophyte on the topic. This might fall into just the topic of vanilla Judaism and I guess "Jewish mysticism" to a degree. It's worth learning about as there are millions of people, many of which are in charge, that believe this is eminent and taking steps to make this a fulfilled prophecy. 

The statement was 'divine wrath' btw, e.g. punishment from God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fake news, no sources, no input from the campaign, just speculation.

As someone in DC, who knows some insiders, most of the positions are ready to be filled, and the insiders are none too happy. To quote one of them, who used to be an attorney for the RNC; "they are hiring a bunch of millennial and generally clueless people that have no idea how things work here". That particular person had sent in a resume and is still part of the process. 

My hearsay is still more accurate and useful the hack trying to write a scare article around the single fact that yes, ambassadors are changed out with every President. 

It's not the current administration's fault they were too clueless to realize they were about to be out of a job and take proper preparations but that isn't going to stop a pile of entitled people that have been living off the Government's teet from whining about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To that point, I'm a hard atheist that are started trying to wrap my head around the idea that there are force that can manipulated by humans to a physical outcome. 

Whether it be Moluch, Baal, KEK, Jesus, or what have you, there seems to be something and I'm wondering if I have my head in the sand while this is actually happening and I'm the naive one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you on 99% of these, but this is going to be one of the biggest conspiracies we're going to witness over the next few years. There are going to be a lot of dead Muslims before this is over.

It's not easy to convert to Judaism. You need to find a rabbi and demonstrate a sincere commitment to Jewish beliefs and law. The rules says he must talk you out of it and reject you forcefully 3 times (fight club style?), go before a panel, convince them that you're living Jewish and then you can be converted, but even then, not all Jews will recognize you. 

So you basically have to live as a Jew for a ~year, meaning multiple events per week with the same people, actively upholding Jewish law and basically convince them that you are one of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, NYC style - just mix the bodies into the concrete for the new construction.

Then again, when your neighbors set the rule that either they exist or you do, but not both, they need to be prepared when that doesn't go their way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just the beginning of the 10th Crusade. The Israelis know they have a permit to clean out any Muslim they want with Trump.

As I've come to realize that Israel's neighbors won't settle for anything less than extinction, I've accepted this as the natural course of history...again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everywhere you look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Occultism comes in many ways...trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you contrast that with some of the organizations you deem more reputable please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without any knowledge of your sources, please allow me to set an expectation for you: there will be a small smattering of folks arrested on inauguration night, an overblown woman's march the next day, clean-up on Sunday and back to work on Monday. 

Consider your expectations set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Color me surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live here and I have some experience with how DC can be locked down and controlled using well established procedures. The pros that do this are operating at peak efficiency. People that planned mayhem have realized they are way the fuck out of their league when it comes to this town. This town has seen some shit and as I tell my kids...everything you think...I've already thought about for 3x as long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay 12-day old account, seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An "article" on the comments left by random bots on a Google Maps listing for a building not open. 

Some fucking conspiracy...guess it was the Russians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good. I'm a Trump fan and have rejected the Russia narrative, but that timing can't be discounted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: a 23-year-old told me. I wonder if Murtaza Hussain has any bias on this topic.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub shouldn't be confused for t_d or /r/politics. The MSM political BS of the day that has been posted so often should be downvoted to hell. 

Spoon feeding unsourced MSM headlines in this sub is the ultimate insult or apex of cluelessness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I believe the key point is that there's actually no recourse from a Presidential pardon. It's conclusive in most every way including pardoning people for future crimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if you actually wanted to convict her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm missing the impeachable offense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be the change you want. Start your own sub, get on with your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/politics-/r/EnoughTrumpSpam decided to brigade in light of the good news that Trump said "I take the biggest dumps, nobody takes bigger dumps than me, believe me" in a Russian bathroom with Putin watching while being felated by Andrew Brietbart's ghost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just another proud member of the /r/ets_poltics brigade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've thought about it at least a dozen times tonight and quite honestly, I lose my shit on [this one](https://i.sli.mg/gKKP0P.png) every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you turn on the style sheet? Fuck other people's opinions and make up your own mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I fucking lost it on [this one](https://i.sli.mg/gKKP0P.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, it's an interesting document and deserves examination. 

Let's disprove it with facts instead of trying to fight against the speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no sane world in which the US transfers Uranium to one of the "axis of evil" countries. It's hard to imagine that he's not going to get paid on the back end for some of this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one cares, but I wonder what the point of keeping /r/EnoughTrumpSpam and /r/politics as two different subs is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously. These Russian terrorist attacks must stop! It's amazing how brazenly they state their plan to over populate the west and turn everyone Russian under the fear of death...

Wait...I might be confused... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The liberal tears never stop. California will flood soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant username.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These sorts of things generally don't end well. Someone's going to pay something eventually.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a placeholder, not a literal statement of fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was shot in the video by a tour guide.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was shot in the video by a tour guide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 16:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 42:00 is an efficient starting point. 50:00 is where he gets "metaphysical".

edit: I'm happy this got posted. Shows people have been taking their own red pills for a long time. There is no other group in America that has had structured, Government and corporate funded attacks than blacks. From crack to abortion to Tuskegee to Jim Crow...the people have been under attack since the beginning. One of the biggest conspiracies ever known to be absolutely true. 

I think that the redpill for a lot of folks, regardless of race or nationality, is realizing they are under a constant attack from ideological people. I think the biggest driver of redpills this year was realizing the source of the attack was the MSM (and their puppeteers). It's good to hear other folks stories who have already been walking this path so you can learn tips for how to keep yourself sane and how to keep  yourself on the path of truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It plays well as a dad joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice summary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I was [just there](http://imgur.com/a/iP9z3) and this didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how is she supposed to get her health back?

Come now, it's time to select some special boys and girls for the big event! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They smell like various types of ass depending upon what's traveling down them. Dead fish smells with the occasional "what died?", but nothing constant or overwhelming. Pretty cool place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some fake fucking news. I just got back from there a few days ago. The tide did not do that when I was there.

[Here are some pictures I took that include water](http://imgur.com/a/iP9z3).

I included a fun one at the end that I found on a building. Weird even for a country obsessed with pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't waste our time with this bullshit. We read the originals yesterday and someone twisting the words in their blog doesn't change the meaning or make it a different story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same response as to the last guy that posted this 40 minutes ago:

Which only confirmed what we already knew; Russia had no impact on the election.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Cept Obama did the same thing...so unprecedented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which only confirmed what we already knew; Russia had no impact on the election.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should write children's stories.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, I know the guy funding and building that from Aviano. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They already do. It's impossible to beat the technology, any solution is going to need to be at the meatbag level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone doesn't understand technology. There are servers in some of the most secure locations in the world, with all of the content, those servers will ever talk to a single server at a time, and if anyone ever attempts to log into that server, it will automatically destroy itself. 

That server proxies content to other servers in which someone can pay to Remote Desktop into and then browse the content. The content never touches their own computer, is never seen communicating with the machine they are using and the dots are unconnectable. Technology will always win...but people make mistakes...then what?

I'm truly overwhelmed by the pedo problem I've recently become aware of. It's even more unfortunate that the parents are often the worst offenders and 1/3 of the offenders are juvenile themselves.

This is a real issue without a simple fix. Some percentage of the population is pre-dispositioned to cause harm to those that cannot defend themselves. It has always been that way and always will be.

We can't round them all up and kill them, technology will always provide a semi-safe haven for them and the sick parents will always push the envelop forward in the abuse of their own children.

I've seen a universal 3-strike program suggested before; first, it's half-your-age+7 across the board. Then it's first strike, jail, rehab, restitution, etc...second strike, castration, 3rd strike, outta here, fast track, no appeals, string them up that day.

It provides a clear deterrent, takes steps to work with the the offender, and pragmatic justice when the person cannot be helped sufficiently to live with other humans.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weaponizing bongs and dildo's...duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So has pedophilia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By thinking he has "full-on support for Donald Trump" shows confirmation bias. 

You're a liberal looking for evidence for your confirmation bias. 

If you paid even the slightest bit of attention, you would know JA is a Sanders/Stein fan and simply published the data he had since only one campaign demonstrated tactics so sickening that it prompted internal leaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's hear some of your secrets Mr. Clapper.

He should be hung for treason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
