<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8128</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 21:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're somewhat right. I was interested in all these great comments that you run into so I punched your user name into redective and saw that you post in those two subreddits quite a bit. So that is where all the great comments are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 20:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right about the default sub thing. You are probably used to the more intelligent comments on /r/watchpeopledie or /r/tinder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 01:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't bad but it's a little bit of a wait while they make the pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/HY5xu9p.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Results vary by location. I dont always pay attention to the news but I can get on the internet and see how many convicted pedophiles live in my area. 

Also, in all the places that I've moved around, very few people actually make an effort to socialize with their neighbors, most of the time it's just a neighborhood of strangers. Much different from when I grew up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 22:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's acting normal because she now thinks that you've both entered into a relationship that includes a suicide pact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't go to a gym. My best friend is his personal trainer and he has a home gym. He always screams and slams the weights down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Are comparable results available using photoshop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... have no clue what you guys are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 16:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How do you think she could have got that psychiatric help? As a minor under control by her parents, who were making her go to Christian anti-trans counseling.

It's not very complicated: 

You call 911 and tell them that you're going to kill yourself. They take you to a hospital, not an anti-trans counselor. You talk to the psychiatric representative in the ER and tell him/her that you have a plan and you're going to follow through with it. They probably admit you and your parents can't do anything about it because that's not how it works.

 So when you're judging Leelah as a dick for her suicide method, you're really judging her as a dick for suiciding at all.

Well, I think I'm judging her on both but my main problem is that she was so selfish and unthinking as to make another person take her life, which seems worse than someone just finding the body. You know that being a trans teenager doesn't make you beyond reproach, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 06:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did all the research. Was stepping in front of a truck the best you could come up with? My choice would have been to get psychiatric help, but that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 05:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://lmgtfy.com/?q=suicide+methods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 23:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just avoiding the issue that they likely traumatized another human by making them an unwilling participant in a suicide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://lmgtfy.com/?q=suicide+methods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 22:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take Motrin for all injuries and ailments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 17:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I only made it about 2 seconds into the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to rethink my life choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 18:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I've only ever heard one person get offended by "Happy Holidays", unless you count Fox News. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thathappened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The X is actually short for Christ anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every year I see the exact same thing in the top posts. Are you guys really running into atheists that turn into the Grinch when you mention Christmas to them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 07:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime the premise is based on something that is a blatant myth. 

Example: Humans only use 10% of their brains... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 22:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utilizing some of the same equipment and tactics =/= culture. If you're comparing cultures it's going to get a lot more complex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would not watch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 20:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my dog did stuff like this. She just sheds everywhere and loses her mind if she hears someone walk by the house on the sidewalk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is this Reddit guy? Is he related to that hacker, 4chan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
