<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4332</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 12:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live about 30 minutes from that place.  My wife loves to cook and I've gotten her several gift certificates from them.  They are very helpful on the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 14:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done the egg in an orange at a cooking demonstration.  I'd only eat it if I was really hungry and had nothing else.  Cub scouts think it's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 20:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've thought about going down for a day - people from the place I go to will be there.  I'm about a year out from getting more work done since I just finished my 1/2 sleeve.

I've never been to a convention before and was considering going just to see what they are all about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 13:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a parent with a son who seems to be struggling with many of the things you are (hates being told the whole it's a difference) and just wants to be in his words 'normal'.  You certainly aren't alone in this - not at all.  I see him doing the same things you list, trying hard to fit in.  Not letting himself fall into a new obsession, etc.

How good that will end up doing either of you I have no idea.

I wish I had some great advice, it's a shitty situation you find yourself in.  I'm not on the spectrum myself but I had a really crappy adolescence and it did get better for me once people got past the immature pick on each other phase.

What really bothers me is when people we know mention or compare him to other 'examples' of people on the spectrum.  If I hear one more person compare him to Sheldon Cooper I think I may punch them.

Good luck, I wish you the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 17:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found 2 copies at the Walmart in Harleysville, PA - 1 left now.  Leaving the sub until I'm finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 12:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried both the Bechtelsville, PA and East Greenville, PA Walmart over the weekend - nothing at either.  The books sections are so small in both stores I find it hard to believe they would even stock the book.  I may swing by the Quakertown, PA Walmart today during lunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 16:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post some more pictures of the total set up?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 13:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this and figured I would throw my thoughts in before reading the thread to see if my ideas match the group or not.

18 years married - 20 together, 5 children (14,12,11,5,2).  I think the most important attribute that my wife possesses is that she is strong in areas that I am lacking and vice versa.  She is the details person while I am the big picture.  Our childhood experiences were very different and because of that I think our children get a great 'balanced' approach from us.  Despite our differences we mesh well and I believe that is because we both know that the other person provides things that we can't or won't for ourselves.  I think the balance we provide to each other is the biggest reason our relationship is still a success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 18:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try giving Brian Garber a call at Wizard's World of Tattoos in Stowe - it's about 20 minutes up the road from where you are going in traffic.

http://wizardsworldoftattoos.com/

Brian works in the Stowe location.

http://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.1837811989629.2090608.1370370834 type=3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 12:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was.  Six months ago we went and stayed in the family camping side.  My boys had such a good time they went back to their Troop and suggested a trip there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 21:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.dcnr.state.pa.us/stateparks/findapark/rickettsglen/index.htm

This state park has a great one half day trip around a series of waterfalls (over 2 dozen I believe).  There is also a nice set up for both large groups and families.  They have additional hiking trails for people that want to go further than a half day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiking in Ricketts Glen State Park Pennsylvania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 21:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article on seasoning all cast iron - not just dutch ovens.  I used her technique on my dutch oven as well as on a dutch oven owned by our Boy Scout Troop and the seasoning is now amazingly durable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
