<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5987</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is you're from Florida? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shocked at how such a large segment of the population can become so schizophrenia-level delusional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ that's depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mapping the United Swears of America - Where in the US certain swear words are more popular than others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maps of where in the US certain swear words are more popular than others [1020x680] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A giant, evil 2-year-old in one of the most powerful positions in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massachusetts felt bad about hogging all the coastline (Maine was part of MA then) so we gave NH a little bit out of pity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The parties were also totally different back then and popular in the opposite areas, they shifted during the "southern strategy" in the 60s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it says something about that in the article too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, that would make too much sense. Ban them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesusland and Snobberia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 13:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should ban Arkansans from traveling to other states "until we figure out what's going on". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 13:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 13:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from January 12th, I wonder how much it's changed in the US in the past few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I have no idea where that thumbnail came from lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL George Washington feared the growing influence of political parties in the US. He thought that it would lead to "the alternate domination" of each party, taking revenge on each other in the form of reactionary political policies, and that it would eventually cause the North and South to split. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gladys Zielian, 1919 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We eat a lot of seafood in New England too so I wonder if that helps with preventing heart disease. Especially considering that Maine has a relatively high obesity rate but is still low on heart disease on this map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say it really just comes from the South, although the Midwest has pretty high obesity rates too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I'm not at all surprised that it's highest in the South. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean they *will* order an emergency stay or are they just talking out of their ass? And if there are two opposing emergency stays, which one overrides the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is turning out to be a fucking bloodbath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad buys stocks, he said the stock market is doing really well under Trump since the election. Not because of anything trump did, but because stock investors seem to think his "pro-business" stances will be good for the economy. That doesn't mean they will be, it just means stock investors think they will be, so if they aren't it'll likely cause a crash. But we won't see the effects of that for a couple years probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Customs and Border Protection tells airlines they will begin reinstating visas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt they would. The main reason they get so many votes in the southern and middle states is their social conservatism. The Democratic party used to be dominant in the south back when they were the socially conservative ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to admit it but I wish the country would split into two. We could each have what we want and there wouldn't be this exhaustingly massive political change every 4-8 years that each side disagrees with so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, the irony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of other cops too. And when you call them out it's "cop hate". Ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm describing you, not insulting you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PBS in the US is like that too, but it's only partially funded by the government and the rest is through donations and things like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and his supporters wouldn't understand it. They'd think South Park was legitimately praising him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hateful, sad little basement troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This fight is not over, not by a long shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you honestly think you're winning anyone over by insulting them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hasn't, he's been forced to let in people with visas, but that doesn't mean anything because all visas have been revoked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Visas Revoked For People From 7 Barred Countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But vast majority of Americans who live in places that actually get immigrants are against the ban. It's not like bumfuck, Missouri gets a huge amount of immigrants. *It doesn't affect them.* But it won't stop them from forcing their will on the parts of America that actually *are* affected by this and *don't fucking want it*. Not only is it hateful and completely pointless, but it damages the economy of northern and western states and cities that pull talent from these countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But vast majority of Americans who live in places that actually get immigrants are against the ban. It's not like bumfuck, Missouri gets a huge amount of immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black America Since MLK: And Still I Rise (2016) - PBS documentary about the battle for equality in the black community in America since the 1960s, including the civil rights movement, black power movement, and the planned inequality and segregation that existed in the North as well as the South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jazzmania Quintette - A few short songs [Jazz] [1927] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early short sound film from the 1920s featuring the Jazzmania Quintette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're the fucking ones who started the American Revolution, you fucks. You're the fake Americans. You go against the basic principles this country was founded on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas - Carry On My Wayward Son [Classic Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Marty Walsh showed up to the protests at Logan airport](https://youtu.be/WOKC8zhP4NQ). Elizabeth Warren, Ed Markey, and Maura Healey showed up at the protests too. Even Charlie Baker condemned it and supported the lawsuit. I'm happy we have people in our state government willing to fight for what we believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump, according to the report, accused Australia of seeking to export the next Boston bombers.

As a Bostonian who knows people directly affected by the Boston bombings, I hate that Trump keeps using them to justify his shit policies that pretty much none of us agree with. We voted 10 to 1 against Trump, and [this was the scene of the protests against his immigration ban,](https://gfycat.com/DirectIdleGentoopenguin) **less than a block away from the bombings.** The whole Commonwealth of Massachusetts is suing Trump over his hateful pointless immigration ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Bostonian who knows people directly affected by the Boston bombings, I hate that Trump keeps using them to justify his shit policies that pretty much none of us agree with. We voted 10 to 1 against Trump, and [this was the scene of the protests against his immigration ban,](https://gfycat.com/DirectIdleGentoopenguin) **less than a block away from the bombings.** The whole Commonwealth of Massachusetts is suing Trump over his hateful pointless immigration ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so, they've been trying to turn Reddit into a fascist shithole for years. I hope we prove we're better than that and they give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And obesity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess it that's because of the large amount of non-practicing Catholics in particular in southern New England. Also, I think I would be included on that map as "religious" since I was baptized as an Episcopal, but I'm agnostic and other than weddings and funerals I haven't been to a church since then. I'm also sure my parents would say they're Catholic and Episcopal respectively if asked but they aren't religious either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: [the first seal of Massachusetts Bay Colony used until 1692 had a Native American on it saying "come over and help us".](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seal_of_Massachusetts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's especially a huge Portuguese population in Bristol county. See- [this stereotype map](http://i.imgur.com/bzeiYdA.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind Baker and I think he's a decent person, but if a half-decent Democrat runs I'm voting for them. At the same time, I wouldn't trust Reddit sentiment as reflective of the whole state, Republican-leaning older people vote more often than any other demographic. When I went to vote in the 2016 election in the suburbs it was 90% hunched-over old people with walkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as Brexit happened I knew Trump had a strong possibility of being elected. History repeats itself and the UK and US seem to have similar political sentiments most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're still stuck with his Supreme Court nominee for the next 50 years. And if Ruth Bader Ginsburg dies, god help us all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This was the size of the protest against Trump's immigration ban, less than a block away from the site of the bombings.](https://gfycat.com/DirectIdleGentoopenguin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Syrians and Bostonians responded to the Boston Bombings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dabbing died when Paul Ryan did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought "lit" was kind of on the old side, my roommate in 2015 said it constantly. And dabbing died when Paul Ryan did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course nobody noticed, it's Nebraska. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie's Song (Spiders) - Always Sunny in Philadelphia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, he didn't, that's a straight up lie. Second of all, this is just the new version of "but Hilary's emails!!!". You don't have to love Obama to hate trump. I judge the president based on what they are doing, not based on what their predecessors did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for putting your country above your political allegiance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. He and Kellyanne Conway are Trump's personal propaganda machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life in prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Despite being so common in English as to be known as "the Chinese curse", the saying is apocryphal, and no actual Chinese source has ever been produced. 

It's known as the Chinese curse, I'm not saying it's an actual Chinese curse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're legitimately *still* saying this. Trump even said it again about his immigration ban. 

Wait and see= allow it to happen without complaint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought it meant like when everything is autotuned and sounds artificially smooth, to the point that it loses its character. I need a word for that if that isn't it, because it bugs me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "May you live in interesting times" -the Chinese curse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the expression "May you live in interesting times" is known as the Chinese curse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "May you live in interesting times"

-the Chinese curse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't do that in states that vehemently oppose that, can they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R's have been doing the exact opposite of leaving us alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2021. Or 2025 if we're really unlucky. 

I'm turning 20 this year, I'll be turning 28 in 2025. That's most of my 20s under a fucking trump regime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently we're going to have a flu pandemic next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's t_d's spam brigade response, they always have one when stories like this get out. You can tell because they all say the exact same things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/nVCtRlPp_qc

Trump's advisor Kellyanne Conway later defended Spicer by saying that rather than lying he was telling "alternative facts". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see his statement about the size of the inauguration crowd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've seen this happen before to plenty of other countries, including Russia and the Philippines where Putin and Duterte are shockingly popular. Unfortunately, people seem to love authoritarian dictators. Though people would like to believe otherwise, the US isn't really that different. We could easily fall down this path too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What might happen instead is the right is pushed even further right because they think the actions of a puppet controlled by the white supremacist head of an "alt-right" (fascist) website is within the realm of normal. And the left ends up just trying to stop this country from completely turning into a fascist shithole. Then the new "moderate" norm for America will be *only a little fascist*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other legal residents in the US than Green Card holders. People with visas for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a puppet for a white supremacist head of an "alt-right" (fascist) website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woops, you're right. Edited my comment, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She should get a medal or something. We need more people like her, not less.

She's being replaced by *Jeff fucking Sessions*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao I really don't know. I told him they most likely aren't going to do anything differently. He just said "I know, but there's a chance they might."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole range seems awfully recent. Where I live in Massachusetts there are a lot of houses built in the 1600s and 1700s, and people still live in most of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to show that the dark blue states had both condemned and issued stays on the immigration ban, but in retrospect I can see how it would be confusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically BC is like the west coast, Alberta is like Texas, between there and Ontario is like the midwest, Ontario is like New York, Quebec is Frenchy, and the Maritimes are like New England. And the far north is a barren wasteland where baby seals are clubbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is awesome! I visited recently and it almost feels like a city in Europe, especially with everyone speaking French around you. It's a very peaceful, safe city and I was shocked to hear about the shootings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I object to where the "New England" arrow points because New York wasn't a New England colony, it was a middle colony.

Interestingly there are some towns in northern New England that are largely French speaking, but it's mainly because of Quebec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grew up in Mass, ACTs are pretty much irrelevant here and not looked at by most schools. The vast majority look at SATs. They did tell us it would be a good idea to take them if we were going to a school in other areas of the country though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, I accidentally Delaware :(

Edit: [Fixed version with a Delaware.](http://i.imgur.com/vt0lhKi.png)

(The New Hampshire AG also condemned the ban earlier today) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't even accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> States that have officially condemned or blocked enforcement of Trump's immigration ban [OC] [2550x2100] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lou Reed - Dirty Blvd. [Classic rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas in rural New England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other cities in the US and Canada that [used to have walls but don't anymore or have small portions](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_cities_with_defensive_walls) are Boston, Charleston, St Augustine, New Orleans, and Montreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Quebec City is the only city in the Americas north of Mexico that still has fortified city walls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean black people did move to other whiter areas to escape slavery though. See- Underground Railroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame government figures aren't held to the same standards of decency as sports figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss wholesome comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm from Massachusetts, so probably. The distance from Boston to Worcester would be a trek to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even by US standards that's a long-ass commute though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ziggy Marley and Chance The Rapper - "Arthur" theme song [theme song] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ziggy Marley and Chance the Rapper play the "Arthur" theme song on Stephen Colbert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woody Guthrie - All You Fascists Bound to Lose [folk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marty Walsh protesting Trump's executive orders at Logan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Philadelphia has a huge metro area compared to Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The west coast is warm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video from the scene.](https://youtu.be/z4woha4_gWY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video from the scene.](https://youtu.be/z4woha4_gWY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crowd in Boston protesting Trump's immigration ban earlier today. It got even larger later in the day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parallels between the response in Boston to the 1850 Fugitive Slave Act and Trump's recent executive orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there was a huge amount of resistance to the 1850 Fugitive Slave Law. When bounty hunters from the South came looking for an escaped slave couple in Boston, Bostonians put up wanted signs with sketches of the bounty hunters, who were then harassed, threatened, and heckled until they gave up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought you were being serious, it's hard to tell with reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free healthcare as a human right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So banning muslims/ brown people is fine to you, but not banning white people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who voted for DT but now oppose him, what was the tipping point for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditors who used to support Trump but now oppose him, what was the tipping point for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who used to support Trump but now oppose him, what was the tipping point for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giuliani: Trump asked me how to do a Muslim ban 'legally' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyers are advising Green Card holders to fly into Boston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, that's funny because whenever my dad orders fries he asks for them "extra crispy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just disgusting that some places in the US have the death penalty at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post needs more attention, this is absolutely horrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
