<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I started hating him a little after Legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice on running </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In almost all cases, no. If your friend is writing some code outside work, for e.g., on Github, then it might be a different story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, you should have put the *TLDR* at the top!
Anyway, it's totally OK to not know lot of things in the beginning of the job. What is not OK is that you don't put effort to ramp up, something that is fortunately not the case with you. So, I'd say, 'Relax! And take it easy'.
Also, it can be overwhelming to learn so much in such a short time. Rather, start slowly, first with technologies that are needed in the short term on the job, and gradually move on to more things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you there live on *this* video? Or another performance of the same song somewhere else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you could have heard a fucking pin drop. And then they went mental.

Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that one guy from the audience, clapping his hands over his head, with Gilmour in background. Wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me back in time to listen to this live, and I'll be your slave forever.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the situation is as grim as what you have in mind.

For e.g., Amazon, Adobe and Microsoft all have their 2nd biggest offices in India and its working great for them. Also, the quality of work is on par with what they have in US.
It is totally possible that moving some work to India might accelerate the growth of your company, which in turn would turn out good for you.

And anyway, as noted previously, doing this and its repercussions to reach you would take time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, will start with these right away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, didn't know about this website at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are *official* videos posted by Adobe. Have you tried them? Are they worth investing time? (I'll also check them out myself, but nevertheless wanted your opinion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I even to learn what to learn from other folks. I don't even know the basic terminologies such as hue, saturation etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 08:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a few managers in my company, who could easily be replaced with robots and no one would know the difference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
