<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3600</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this awesome response! Part two is linked at the bottom of the story now. I hope the intro to that helps answer some questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Grandmother and the Rabbit Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [1st Story: My Grandmother Was a Witch] (https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/55o192/my_grandmother_was_a_witch/)

[3rd Story: Things My Grandmother Taught Me](https://m.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/560k6z/things_my_grandmother_taught_me/)

[4th Story: My Grandmother Isn't In This One](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/566swv/my_grandmother_isnt_in_this_one)

I can try to answer a few questions everyone had from the previous story. I never intended to make a series, but remembering my grandmother is comforting, so Ill dredge up a few more of her tales for you all. Thank you for the awesome response to the first tale.

A few readers asked how the scarecrows became her and my protectors. From things she taught me years later, Id wager a guess that it was the magic in the stitching. Her embroidery had real talent in it, and its a task that lets the mind wander. Maybe in her thoughts she wished for something to change in her life, or for someone to stop the abuse. Maybe she prayed for her grandchildren. Who knows? But the scarecrows faces seemed real when she finished her work.

Were there ghosts in the strawmen? Or was it just her magic at work? Im not sure. The way spirits flocked to her, I always assumed it was the first, with just a dash of the second. Ghosts sometimes like pretty things, and if her prayer for protection eked into her stitches, someone had to answer.

Her magical talents were dormant for many years, slipping out when least expected or most needed. I suspect the Scarecrows came to help when they did because her husband hurt me, and no one messed with the grandchildren. She didnt much care for herself. Her magic workings were subtle, but had strong results. Most of the time we didn't even know we were working up anything. But that's the way magic is.

One last thing before I start the next story. Someone (SwiffFiffteh, I think) noticed I never called my grandmothers husband my grandfather. Its true that I never acknowledged that man as anything but my Dads dad, and an abuser. If he had a grave, I wouldnt leave coins on it. Let him wander for eternity.

Thank you again for reading. I hope you enjoy the next story. My grandmother sure didnt.



**My Grandmother and the Rabbit Man**

Theres a reason my family doesnt keep rabbits.

Before the Scarecrows, before my birth, before the sons left home, and before the corn had been sown for the first time, my grandmother stood in the field of what would be her husbands final resting place, and sighed. She was six months pregnant for the second time, and hoped this one would stick. Several yards ahead, her husband turned the plough and started down a new aisle.

As she lifted the garden hoe to break up more of the dirt clods, her eyes focused, and she took in the disturbed rabbit den the plough had revealed. The mama was dead, cut to pieces under the plough, as were two kits. Four bunnies survived unscathed.

Im going to be frank here. Rabbits are great eating to poor farmers. A little small, but free meat is free meat. My grandmother gathered up the living kits and placed them gently in her apron pockets. They werent bigger than her palm, and the heat from each other would help keep them alive. Once settled, she gathered up the dead mother rabbit, but left the two dead kits for the dogs. Shed have the mama rabbit for supper.

Hanging dinner out of reach of the dogs, she dug out a chicken cage from the barn. Straw decorated the bottom of the makeshift bunny hutch, before she laid the still breathing babies inside. Luckily the goat had just dropped a kid, so theyd have plenty of milk. If they lived, she could breed them easy. She spent the rest of the day caring for the kits and skinning supper. It was light enough work for a pregnant woman and she welcomed the break.

She had the meat laid out on the counter, ready to be seasoned, when she saw a stranger kneeling in the field. He wore a nice suit, and a large flat-brimmed Panama. The hat was odd for this part of the state, where all shed ever seen were handmade straw affairs woven by women to protect from the sun. This strange man had money. Why was he in her field?

He must have felt her gaze because his head turned slowly to the window. The hat blocked the sun from his eyes, leaving everything above his mouth in shadow. His lips parted into a wide smile, and my grandmother jumped at the blood that dripped down his chin.

He stood, long legs untangling from beneath him. In the next moment, he was before her window, face pressed to the glass peering in. Pinprick white dots in black irises met her gaze, as she screamed. The man dropped from sight, but a blood smear remained on the glass.

She grasped her butchers knife, and turned towards the door, expecting the stranger to be inside at any moment.

Long minutes passed, and her heartbeat slowed. No man trespassed in her home.

Were she Catholic, she would have crossed herself before stepping out the kitchen door and into the driveway. No one was there. It was then, as she looked up at the bloody glass, she realized the man would have stood more than eight feet tall to look in as he did.

She darted into the field, one hand under her stomach to support my uncle, another waving a butcher knife in the air. What her husband made of the sight, well never really know, but Id bet he thought retribution was coming as she ran him down, screaming.

Babbling didnt really explain what had happened, so he helped her back to the house, cursing crazed pregnant women. As they passed over the little buried bunnies, my grandmother looked down to see large footprints in the dirt. She froze and pointed, and her husband glanced over to see the kits dug up, and mangled more than the plough could have managed. The dead rabbits had been skinned cleanly, the meat and bones chewed up, and blood spilled around the soil. He muttered about the dogs, and continued dragging his wife along.

In the cool of the kitchen, he sat her down and tried to ask what happened. But her eyes were locked on the cage that held the four live kits.

They too had been skinned, blood splattered in the straw, the bones sucked clean of all the meat.

She made chicken for dinner that night instead.

She called him the Rabbit Man. He never came back, except in her dreams. She carried dried beans in her apron pockets at all times, to throw at any bad spirits, and hung herb bundles tied together with thread above every door and window. I think her stitching did more to keep her safe, than the clover and blackberry leaves.

But I saw him once, before she ever mentioned him to me.

Like every country kid in the 90s, I got a pair of rabbits for Easter one year. I called the big grey one Bugs, and the little black one was named Bun, because it was all my brother could scream every time he got to hold her. 

My dad even promised to build a little hutch for them. But until he finished it, they lived in the kitchen in a dog kennel.

I did a lot of stupid shit as a kid. Who hasnt? Paired with the fact that I was a terrible liar, I got into a lot of trouble because of the dumb stuff I pulled. I generally just didnt think before I acted.

The night after I got the rabbits, my night light stopped working. Mom promised to drive into town the next day and get more bulbs, but Id have to do without for one night. I didnt much like it, but at seven years old,  I didnt get a say in the matter.

It was late, the house asleep, when a creaking in the hallway woke me. My bedroom was the last room in the hall, so unless Mom was checking on me, there shouldnt be anyone close to my room.

Tell the Rabbit Man that, though.

My door opened, and someone walked by, a shadow in the dark house. I tensed, but when nothing came for me, I got curious. I padded barefoot into the hall and past the bedrooms, where my parents and brother were sleeping, obvious bumps under their covers.

Someone moved in the kitchen. I moved slowly towards the noise.

The scariest movie Id seen at that point was Jurassic Park, and while it left me with an intense fear of the dark, I doubted that a dinosaur was in our kitchen. Of course, if I were wrong Id be dino-chow.

That thought made me pause, and I was about to turn back to get my parents when the Rabbit Man stepped around the corner and into sight.

He was tall, the top of his hat brushing our ceiling. He had to duck under the doorway as he came into view. His long limbs went on for miles, and his dark suit blended with the shadows. He smiled wide, white pinprick eyes leering down at me. Blood dripped off his lips.

I screamed.

The hallway light banished him. Mom scooped me up from behind, as Dad cleared the house with a rifle. He found no one, but the scene in the kitchen gave him a shock.

Bugs and Bun had been skinned, bones sucked clean of any meat, and the newspaper lining soaked in their blood.

None of us slept well that week.

Mom recounted the tale to my grandmother the following Sunday. She grew pale, as she told us her own story.

Suffice it to say, none of us ever owned rabbits ever again.

[And my kids sure as hell never will either.](http://fb.com/subject3600writing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
