<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8542</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 15:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I have been interested in Buddhism for years, but I only recently began attending actual meditation services and Dharma talks. I did some research, made a list of all the centers near me that seemed appealing, then wrote down dates and times for the ones I wanted to attend. 

Keep looking around and trying different options until you find a teacher who resonates with you. Most places expect new people to drop in sporadically, so don't feel nervous about going for your first time. If you're like me and you get easily anxious about new places, call or email them ahead of time to see if there are any particular services for newcomers.

Hope you find something that feels right for you. :) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 14:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work as a full-time traveling volunteer. My service term is finished in April, and then I'm going to finish getting my bachelor's degree in social work. I eventually want to become  certified in mindfulness therapy. I generally just want to help people who have a difficult time helping themselves. 

On a similar note, Tricycle actually has a pretty good podcast episode on finding meaning in jobs that may not necessarily seem meaningful on the surface: http://www.tricycle.com/sharon-salzberg-real-happiness-work :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 13:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, if I'm feeling particularly overwhelmed or anxious, I'll pull out a post-it and write in detail how I'm experiencing each of the five senses at that moment. It almost always helps bring me back to what's happening around me in that moment, rather than becoming fixated on what's going on in my head. 

The hard part is usually recognizing that I'm unaware of my surroundings in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realized that I've gone more than a month without seriously thinking about hurting myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 19:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I catch myself with similar anxieties sometimes. This is a particularly good guided meditation that asks the listener to envision pure goodness and light emanating from themselves and the world around them: http://www.omvana.com/meditations/six-phases-meditation-by-vishen-lakhiani

I listen to it on the subway when I start feeling anxious about the sheer amount of people around me (and thus start thinking about how vulnerable I feel living in a major city, how easy it would be to become a target, etc. It's very calming.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was raised a Pentecostal Christian. Around 16, I started to fall away from that, and I claimed to be an agnostic a year later. Felt like there was "something" out there that was bigger than myself, but just kind of pushed it aside for awhile. 

I began undergoing a type of counseling called Dialectical Behavioral Therapy almost 2 years ago, and it draws a lot of its practices from Buddhism: analyzing the root of our suffering, meditating as a means of coping with negative emotions, using mindfulness in everyday life, etc. I decided to pursue those practices further, which brought me to studying Buddhism and eventually deciding that it seems to feel right for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ a lot of great points here. There is a huge misconception that BPD is some kind of death sentence, and that those of us who suffer from it are doomed to a life of self-harm, mood swings, and unending feelings of abandonment. 

Personally, DBT and the habits I've developed as a result of DBT have hugely changed my life; like you said, it is indeed possible for those of us with BPD to radically change our lives. Even my family members and close friends have noticed a huge difference in my personality since beginning counseling. 

And I would agree with your statement that we don't necessarily become incredibly attached to people or things, even though it may seem that way on the surface-level. Rather, we become attached to the thoughts and feelings conjured up by that object; for instance, I don't necessarily become attached to romantic partners, but I do become attached to feelings of affection (hence why I used to recklessly date anyone who paid attention to me, regardless of what type of person they were). Fortunately, this sort of mental   emotional attachment certainly can be and IS addressed both in DBT and most Buddhist practices. 

I would say, without a doubt, that the teachings of DBT have improved my condition far more than any other treatment I've had, professional or self-improvised. 

(p.s.: shouts out for being a mental health worker who doesn't spout out the usual ignorance surrounding those of us with BPD; we need more of you in the psychiatric industry!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, that's fair. Like I said, I realize that Christianity and Buddhism are incredibly different, but I could see why drawing comparisons between them could unintentionally cause me to feel uneasy about certain teachings, especially since I don't have very developed knowledge on much of this already. 

(I have ADD, and so any time I use online resources, I end up in a rabbit hole of sorts until I have 30 different tabs open, all with different articles...oops.)

Anyways, thanks for making that point.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to liken schools of Buddhism to sects of Christianity, how would you do so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously there are countless differences between Buddhism and Christianity, but I thought this could be fun to see what people say. (i.e., which school of Buddhism would you liken to the rigidity of Catholicism, which would you liken to the intense spirituality of Pentecostalism, etc.)

I'm somewhat new to practicing Buddhism, and I'm still learning how to distinguish the major branches. I was raised a Christian, so I thought paralleling the two in this way might be helpful. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: I attended the Shambhala Center's "Intro to Meditation" session on Wednesday night. I immediately felt very comfortable in their center. There were informational books and pamphlets everywhere, all of which explained the basics of Shambhala, so I didn't feel like I was imposing on an unfamiliar space. There were people shuffling around the room from other classes, and everyone seemed very friendly. The woman working at the front desk didn't pressure me into donating a particular amount when I checked in, nor did she bat an eye when I could only give a few dollars rather than the full $10. 

The session itself was great. The teacher was very friendly, calm, and approachable. He taught us basic meditation techniques, interspersed with brief historical context. By the end of the class, everyone felt comfortable asking questions and discussing their thoughts. Nobody felt stupid for raising their hand and saying, "Hey, my foot fell asleep. Is that normal?" 

I'm planning on going to their Sunday 1-hour sitting now that I have a feel for the place. I also found out that they offer a weekly meditation and teaching session for individuals who suffer from trauma-based mental illness; as someone who suffers from PTSD, talk about a perfect fit. 

So glad that I was encouraged to look into them. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
