<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 15:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do and as the Wire pointed out, this has absolutely EVERYTHING to do with the War on the American people, I mean, the War on Drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 15:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or everyone saying the same shit about Cumberbatch in Star Trek: Dark Crap Rising </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 13:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice $2,000 statue (assuming $15/month x 12 = $180/year x 10 + various costs of the expansion packs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 13:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they're saying this so we'll be surprised when they show up in the end for a cameo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 13:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it's discontinued because NSA is doing it for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 13:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a GREAT movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 03:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, the case does still reside in the hands of actual people who can make their own educated choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 03:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No pants subway ride. One of my favorite memories from the early 2000s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 23:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about fucking time Holder did something good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 23:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pivotal to this is that they're using confidential informants as foils to break the law, something which as a practice is just abhorrent, but it's the only way to satisfy the quotas being demanded by stat-obsessed politicians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 23:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please, yes. If Twin peaks is coming back, so should the X-Files. Carter can finally tie up like, 10,000 loose ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 20:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the judge will now increase the cost per barrel to compensate for this unprecedented environmental apocalypse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 21:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Towelheads are going to get themselves eradicated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 00:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the one. Has a much better ring than mechanical reproduction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 22:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wallace for sure. Danielewski for House of Leaves as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 22:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I'd heard it translated as reproducibility, but nonetheless, good share and great read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sex was good, something about the dress and the room, honestly it was such a fucking relief for the door to be shut and for the ceremony of it all to be over ... but whatever I'm getting divorced soon so take that for what you will.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constitutional Convention. It's what the founders envisioned and something that the status quo fears more than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Useful waste of resources, if nothing else. Chances of the feds honoring this is effectively zero, but it's good to get on record as many abuses of federal power as necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who Young Leek be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 14:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also make it a bit more interesting for back country camping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 02:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who fucking cares?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 06:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was killed for being black and because the people who called the report in were scared of a black man with a gun in walmart. That's the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 13:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 13:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that's meant for things coming out, not things going in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 05:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except when you get raped or fondled or just intimidated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And be white and male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 22:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll learn. LE need low-hanging fruit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 02:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Hollywood, Everyone's Gay once in a while; or how to continue sucking dick to remain relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 02:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should be in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 02:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retroactive immunity signed by Obama for everything, it's part of the deal. Look that shit up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 17:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is untouchable. Both him and Bush II have retroactive immunity from prosecution so this is only going to impact lesser people, like all of the ruinous decisions made by that vile administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 15:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason they're putting this through and making it legal is because there wasn't any significant outrage from the Snowden leaks, I mean sure some people were upset online and there might have been some phone calls and letters written, but people weren't out protesting in the streets like they have been for police abuses (Ferguson, Staten Island, etc.) so they government is like, fuck it, we're doing it anyway, time to make it legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 07:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a fucking stupid waste of life, the dude who killed Lennon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 05:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAT Ruler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 05:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on, what now?!? We're going to do what?!? WHERE??!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 00:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next President could be a monkey, so long as it's a relatively competent, charismatic Latin woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 00:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYPD straight up murdering people now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 14:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presidents should be Presidential and this one has lowered the fucking bar enormously. Won't be long before we have a professional wrestler President. Or like, Dr. fucking Phil as President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 14:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we have a culture where cops are venerated above practically all else and most people are terrified of large black men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow nicely done.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That she was a crazy religious bitch who wanted to control every last thing I ever did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do it, not unless you're like 1000% sure. Just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, as David Foster Wallace said, after he finishes writing a thing, to him, it's dead. It's just language at that point, which readers can and will interpret however the fuck they want to interpret it. The fact that people were praising his work without reading irked DFW, but being a writer isn't an easy thing, as this RB episode encapsulates quite well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 02:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such unbelievable bullshit, goes only to show there is one set of laws for cops and another set of laws for everyone else. This was ruled MURDER and a grand jury failing to indict him is absolutely fucking ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm a guy and I was raped. Thing is, I liked the chick a lot, but reality is, if the script was flipped and I was the mostly sober one and she was the blackout drunk one, it would be, or could be, considered rape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the first episode was any indication of what's to follow, there will be no just killings, just more travesties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh...time to build some new franchises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 14:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every movie studio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 14:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, this is happening in every entertainment aligned industry, jobs that a few years ago were providing living salaries to experienced professionals are now being done by unpaid interns and people wonder why standards are falling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 14:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame that this isn't illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 02:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 02:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learning that you didn't know a tenth of what you thought you did about, well, pretty much anything. That and less virility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 23:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 23:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PGP should be mandatory. Mutli-sig should be mandatory. Anything less should be unacceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 23:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First holiday of the rest of your life, buddy. As someone still reeling in my own way, I have to say, congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 18:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man is a war criminal who engaged in not one, but two wars of aggression and occupation and the deaths of thousands of innocent lives is on his head and the heads of those who followed and enabled him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 15:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One can only imagine the type of shit that would have emerged from taped sessions in the war criminal Bush II's administration, inane religious ramblings about Gog and Magog and how inspired our righteous crusade against the heathens in the Middle East is all done to glorify God... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 15:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move on. Don't continue this relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Littlefinger I couldn't disagree with more, he'll be around until the endgame because he's the type of manipulating character who succeeds in the kind of world that Martin has created ... having said that I think he's going to be out of his element at some point, but he's a survivor and will be crucial towards the formation of whatever comes next ...

Bran is absolutely going to figure into the endgame with the walkers and will likely end up sacrificing himself in order to ensure the survival or another Stark ... Rickon perhaps.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've been reading too much dark tower. GRRM is displacing tropes and I doubt he'd end with anything as repetitive as that, although I do think that Rickon will figure into the endgame in same manner, albeit one that we can't possible imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could happen, with the events of the series leading people to distrust monarchy or nobility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robb. That shit was wicked. Fucking Freys need to get eradicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 04:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Se la vie, I freaking suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Official according to your speculation? I'm not saying it's coming back, but unless you have some inside information this is purely speculative and nothing more. Granted, the points you make about customer service are valid, but that doesn't necessarily mean TMP is done, it's had periods of downtime that exceeded this before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 17:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Undercover agent from Homeland Security Investigations (HSI) wasn't just perusing goods on the new sitethe agent was on staff, with access to special discussion forums and technical data."

Assume everything is monitored at this point and that mods on this site are in fact, agents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 16:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of society suffers from mental delusions, the concept of money itself being just one such societal delusion, to say nothing of the delusion of infinite growth, underpinning the whole "for the kids" mentality on a global scale of finite resources, but couldn't agree more that it's none of our business really what AB's mental state is at this point in time. I'm not sure how she's exactly newsworthy, but I think some of her behavior is what I would constitute as a rational response to the insane amount of focus put on her every move. Hell even when the girl doesn't do something (like change her hair or whathaveyou), everyone notices ... I think that kind of attention would drive any sane person into a strange, if not toxic place, but that's just me and some celebs seem to handle it just fine, then again, for AB at this time, maybe this IS fine. Hard to say, microscoped at her age, I'd be called troubled at best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 15:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking towelheads are going to get themselves eradicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 14:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends whether their ultimate endgame was ... remember this was largely a PR move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 14:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and they also have virtually unlimited resources and computing power at their disposal...it's just terrifying what they are going to do as they escalate their operations, thinking about that old Nixon line that if the President does it that means it's NOT illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 23:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even, drunks are venerated in our culture, witness Cheers, Homer Simpson, Drunk Uncle, etc. etc. etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
