<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with the word cringy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me its one of those Twilight Zone films where a simple idea is dragged into a feature length, without the requisite story detail or intrigue to actually justify a feature length. On a rewatch its pretty boring for the most part, there just isn't much depth of character or subtlety. I really wish it had been a much more non-linear film, going to town with the time concept and showing the relevant stuff of the first half in flashback. I also agree with your last paragraph and feel that Split falls into this category.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, they sort of went "pop idol" on us and squeezed the fun and low key vibrancy out of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's awesome that you actually tried one out! I've been watching them randomly, out of sequence (there's no connection between episodes). Just as a warning, I personally found the very first one my least favourite, it just doesn't seem to have the same quality or intrigue as the others. I wonder how many got turned off watching the first episode without realising how amazing the rest are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a theme its more about instinct colliding with technology (or the evolution of technology going faster than the evolution of the mind). Which ones did you watch? I'm trying to think of three that are about sex and degeneracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess theyre like modern day TZ (which I love too). Only a few TZs approached genuinely eerie. When you think about why something is scary, its always because of a core fear (eg death, lack of control or something). Some films harness an element of that pretty well (eg It Follows). Black Mirror takes genuinely frightening ideas and delivers them well. For example, in the christmas one, in a brief scene a man gets "blocked" in the vision of everyone else he meets. Its just a brief idea, but such a terrifying thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a film, but try the series Black Mirror. I found most of the stories to be more unsettling, and horrific, than most horror films. I mean that in a genuine way, intelligent, well produced and acted stories that really get under your skin and linger in the mind for days (if not weeks/months) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing I like about the first is that its like a metaphor for this woman, who cheated on her husband, but then keeps cheating to try and minimise the guilt of the first, but it just makes it stronger. The thing I like about the second is its creativity - it just keeps going, with no restraint, in creating so many weird and wonderful ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that written by a content bot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love those "business development" stories that channel raw human nature, like Social Network and the steve jobs biography. So I'm looking forward to this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 10:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's hard to find a fuck to give, much less give it.

Then don't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or have that chick from Wolf On Wall St tell us in a bathtub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, I haven't even heard of that. Maybe I stumbled upon it one night. Now I'll have to get it. Well done for figuring it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes ok tristypooz, I meant inspired not based.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats interesting. My crowd were stooges, which is what impressed me afterwards because they looked so normal and varied. Money was flying around thick and fast as i approached, everyone was getting handouts. Its crazy how "automatically" the mind absorbs such suggestions and gets into a whirl, believing I could win also despite how ridiculously irrational thr idea actually was outside of the context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this trailer on a film reel! Its the only film reel I own. I once thought wrapping the reel to make a cool lamp shade but didn't want to ruin it for something tacky. One of my favourite films. The screenwriter, Bruce Joel Rubin, wrote a few films about facing death e.g. My Life, Ghost, Deep Impact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't, it was an original script by Bruce Joel Rubin, based on a short film called Occurrence at Owl Creek which was used in Season 5 of the original Twilight Zone series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got scammed out of $40 betting on that stupid Monty con in New York City when I was a lot younger. I felt sick at the time (it was all the money I had on me at the time), but afterwards learned a lot about the con and actually admired how well they pulled it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 10:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree the first scenes are rewatchable in a different light, as well as the later scene where she starts having flashes (around the time she dreams of an alien in her quarters). But the rest of it, i.e. all the bits with Forest Whitaker, approaching the ships, going in, the usual "yep that just happened" quips, the aliens and all the language stuff, everyone looking quizzical and bemused - all of that feels very pedestrian almost like a TV pilot for a new show on the syfy channel.  

I agree that normal quirky timeline films are rewatchable, but Arrival really doesn't go far with its central idea, the total running time of all those moments is probably less than 10 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy Lee Jones narration at the start of No Country For Old Men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hype and oscars can definitely affect peoples perception of a movie. They falsely project that the film itself somehow thinks its that good, so they watch with a "well, I'll be the judge of that!" contrary attitude. I've seen it happen time and time again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weirdly I can remember seeing this, but I have no idea what it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop spamming this shit you twat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember feeling the same way and having the same thoughts exactly. Also, am I right in remembering the opening scenes being shot like a car commercial? Theres loads of shots of an Audi or BMW or something gloriously winding its way around country lanes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw most of them as free previews or as part of Odeon UKs Screen Unseen series (where they show mystery films for 5 ahead of release).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised by people who like Arrival that much. I love that a film attempted to explore determinism and the physics of time, but Arrival didn't really do it justice. It just seemed bogged down in a distraction of linguistics and alien intentions. Also, its not at all rewatchable, there's nothing to really absorb (as with say, Prisoners) on a second viewing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still humming Drive It Like You Stole It. That says something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 99 Holmes - is that the one with all those clones of John Holmes and that girl?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which surprises me as I think Arrival is his weakest film by far. It really doesn't hold up well to rewatches, in terms of cinema and story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I will say is that his performances as the various personalities all reminded me of Matthew Rhys from the TV show The Americans - who also acts a range of different persona's in the show (as a spy). As a Welsh guy originally, playing a Russian playing many different Americans, his acting is phenomenal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread gets brought up time and time again. I'm curious why you can't just read one of the other threads, being that you've already mentioned how often Kingdom of Heaven gets brought up on this sub?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his character in Social Network did have a good depth and range. He went from privileged supportive friend, to excited hopeful, to cautious controlling, to frustrated angry, to devastated/heartbroken/rageful, to repressed courtroom testimony. It was a great performance. Similarly in 99 Homes, it was a truly unconsciously convincing and engaging performance, subtle to the core and absolutely captivating. I'm not sure how you're not seeing that, perhaps you just have something against him (in the same way I expect Daniel Radcliffe to be bad and can't see otherwise).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it at the cinema a couple of years ago and loved it. There are lots of "disfigured" films out there with predictable twists, but I love how it was reversed here in that we know the twist but he doesnt. It had some good explorations about identity, perception and the influence of expectation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 99 Homes and Eye In The Sky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd like Pup Friction, the sequel to Reservoir Dogs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short Circuit 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you've massively underestimated Garfield. Have you seen 99 Homes? For a fairly low key story, it got truly under my skin because of his performance. Also Boy A, and The Social Network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Serbian Film had a "quite unpleasant" one towards the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you also think that Four Lions glamorizes and sympathizes with terrorists?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing that delights me in TI is how they manage to set up identical clones of Ewan McGregor as being heroic, and then the villain who we want to see killed. Its almost satirical in terms of the black/white hero/villain hollywoodism that they actually use clones to stage a fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Dev Patel for Lion. Its okaaaay, but its a very oscar friendly film, and I think there are better performances out there.  

I'll be sad if Hugo Weaving doesnt get a supporting actor nom for Hacksaw Ridge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pain and Gain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, did you see in theatres or downloaded?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of real life looks artificial and contrived, what's your benchmark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye In The Sky is a good example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it would have been much more interesting to keep him conflicted, rather than turn him into a "villain" for a tidier ending. It was like the Breaking Bad of the nineties, before TV had the balls (and running time) to really go to town on character and inner conflict.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For such a long time, that was my favourite all-time movie. I even have the poster, and original ex-rental VHS. I've seen it such a stupid amount of times, but its such a rewatchable and brilliant movie. I love the music too, it perfectly encapsulates that weird late-night nightmare feeling where nothing feels right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is one of the rare times that someone actually followed someone's recommendation on one of these threads. And fast, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The core concept of time being a solid block, and predetermined, is interesting, especially when tied to physics (which the short story does a little more). For example, how electrons seemingly "know" the potential paths available ahead of them before "choosing" which paths to take. I'm dying for a film to explore these concepts properly, because they really do undermine what we believe about ourselves, and the illusion of free will.   

Arrival tries, but its best ideas are so, so buried under a bunch of guff about alien language and overly sentimental emotional heart-string-pulling pap about her daughter, that the film doesn't really explore them all. They're reduced to a kind of "a ha!" twist and idea.   

I tried rewatching Arrival to get at those core ideas more, but it was so dull. All the military/alien stuff really is boring as hell on second watch, there's nothing really thoughtful, interesting or atmospheric  about any of that stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to commend you for a nice introspective post. Its always nice to see some humanity and individuality applied to perceptions of film.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really think about the acting in that way, just how I feel when watching a scene. When I feel what the actor is (supposed to be) feeling, then I think they've done a great job at tricking my brain into empathizing completely. Its bit like CGI compared to practical effects (when done well) in terms of feeling unconsciously congruent. But the lip quiver seemed perfectly naturalistic to me, having seen plenty of people like that talking in documentaries about sad subjects.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILERS

Yes of course, but to me it felt like a trite and forced-twist add on. The story was done by that point, its not like it was cleverly weaved in. The link the woman makes to Mr Glass was tenuous as hell, and really didn't make any sense. It just all felt like a one-take, "hey guys, lets just quickly do this" naff way to link the movies. People laughed in my cinema, for how shoddy and silly that scene felt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugo Weaving's performance in Hacksaw Ridge was amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting to be blown away by Andrew Garfield again after his excellent performance in 99 Homes, but instead it was Hugo Weaving who surprised me. The scene at the dinner table was electrifying, it pulled me into the scene and the emotion with such force. I rarely see performances that are so embodied they project the kind of automatic, unconscious nuances that you see in everyday life. Terrific film all round.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you were watching a dodgy download! No wonder your experience was a little off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wasn't that impressed at all and am really surprised by the amount of people who are. It just felt tacked on almost like an afterthought. The woman's link ("oh, that reminds me what happened to that guy who died in prison 15 years ago, what was his name again?") before panning to Willis is so ridiculously weak and tenuous. Why would she remember the incident but forget such an iconic name? What does the implied incident have to do with what she had just seen on TV, being that Mr Glass has absolutely nothing to do with DID? And Willis's face, doing his "hey everyone, its me!" face from Expendables, Planet Terror and everything else in recent years. I don't see how an implication, like "hey, its part of the universe of this other film!" changes anything about the actual film/story itself to make it somehow "fucking phenomenal".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mockingjay, parts 1 and 2, are absolute boring horseshit by the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually agree. I saw an early preview last year and seemed to the only one who didnt think it was amazing. I also found the handling of the twist forced and annoying, although I did find the central idea of it interesting (not that the film really did it justice in terms of an emotional exploration). I saw it again months later to give it another chance (sometimes my own life events/expectations might filter my perception). But it was actually painfully boring the second time. It doesnt reward rewatches at all - the characters are flat and uninteresting, Adams spends the whole film looking bewildered, the alien and language stuff just feels repetitive. Once you know the film and its mechanics, there really isnt much more to absorb at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So if you could speak grammatically without time frames, a similar effect could be theorized as to what happens in the movie.  

You do realise it was a science fiction, right? I dont think any language is going to allow what happens in the movie. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why be sorry? Do you really think your own obtuse opinion is going to influence someone elses huge appreciation for the film?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good spot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flight of the Navigator  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I always took it to be about how easily we forget ourselves, our true worth and value. Underneath all the distractions, self-doubts and noise, we're all (mostly) amazing people and capable of feeling and giving so much. So, to attain those special states of zen-awareness and gratitude, its not about acquiring or striving, but letting go and seeing through the noise. Something that's available to everyone at any time.   

I met her briefly last year and was shocked at how young and talented she was. She was such a normal, down to earth girl that you might pass in a store, but on stage was so brilliant at performing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found some old VHS tapes of TV recordings from when I was 12-14, oh those pre DVD/streaming days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought one for 99p in a HomeBargains store in UK. The company is http://3d-vr-viewer.com/, maybe they're doing them super cheap (especially in bulk).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the Fiits because I find the individually adjustable lenses fiddly. For some reason (and I have no problems at all with the Z4) my eyes have to be really close to the lenses, and occasionally knock them out of focus. Or, rubbing away mist messes up the focus. It just gets annoying. The Z4 is by far the most user-friendly unit, especially the later editions with the longer headphone jack and nice pvc padding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to predict in four years there's a film called "Glass" directed by M Night Shyamalan, a sequel/prequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and a Captain K(angeroo)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just can't agree with that. I generally do like to watch most films in one sitting, but I have absolutely no problem at all with breaking a film into multiple sections, even across weeks.   

Here's the thing. After a duration, even if you're paying attention to a film, certain things start to get taken for granted or glazed over. At the beginning you might be paying attention to all sorts, but then by the end not so much. I find that when I break a film, when I return to it, I tend to be much more sharply engaged than if I'd watched it all in one go. I have a harddrive loaded with films for the bedroom TV, and I frequently will skip to a random part of a film to just watch from there. I really enjoy doing this, I sometimes notice new things because I'm so into whatever it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, its not like all films are Tarkovsky works of art! What about old Bond films, Gremlins 2, Kindergarten Cop, Die Hard 3, who cares if we chop them up a bit watching in chunks over dinner times or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked your review, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 11:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James McAvoy has been a dissociative identity of Shyamalan all this time, and we didn't notice because we're all dissociative identities of Shyamalan too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 11:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a trailer for this before La La Land, and thought it looked pretty terrible. Even Woody had a kind of "I can't believe we're even attempting to release this" vibe. It looks like a joke project that would be part of another film, like where Woody is playing a desperate B-list actor trying to find a new audience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 11:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can I say... knitting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, just a moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good points. Just to clarify on why I found those bits immature - so there's a whole back-story to the girl that slowly unfolds via flashback, which serves one sole purpose - to tell us (eventually) that she was abused, and then self-harms. Its taking a heavy subject matter (that shouldn't be taken lightly, considering the frighteningly large proportion of girls who have suffered some kind of sexual abuse), only to use as a plot device when the beast decides she isn't sheltered enough to warrant killing. He calls her "pure" instead. It then seems incongruent that the girl would hang out with the two popular girls, accept a ride with a man she doesn't know, and a bunch of other stuff. It just seemed a tacky way of using the context of abuse/self-harm, making all sorts of implications about it (almost glorifying it in terms of her being saved, and being prioritised above the other girls in terms of the story), only to serve a silly plot-device before whisking the audience away to the silly final scene.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I don't think much of a Shyamalan film? What are you, 12? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved McAvoy's performance (as I think everyone did), but outside of that it wasn't very imaginative or interesting at all. The psychotherapist was ridiculously cliched and stereotyped, providing endless (and boring) exposition. The girls were smarter than your average movie captives but those scenes were still very samey (after seeing 10 Cloverfield Land, Room, Green Room etc). The shoe-horning in of heavy issues like sexual abuse and self-harm felt really trite and immature in what was essential a black comedy comic book movie. Really, I think it was an average shitty film outside of McAvoy's performance, unless you're a mid teenager perhaps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say he's back to his old magic. Its just an ok film - McAvoy's performance is fun and interesting, but beyond that its pretty lame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my mum, it was The Truman Show. We watched it together, and she somehow ended up watching the actual Truman Show TV programme, glazing over all the bits with Christof, and wondering why it was just a soap thing about an insurance guy married to a woman who collected household utensils. When weird stuff started happening, like the light falling from the sky, she just had no idea what was going on and thought it was all getting a little weird and abstract.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braindead (Dead Alive in US). I'm thinking of the scene where the old lady zombies pimple pops and squirts into the guys custard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, you asked me to elaborate, so I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 10:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its one of those films that plugs the message "be free! Do what you want!" in a dishonest way, because it appeals to a certain demographic (ironically the kind who hate their lives and fantasize about escaping, so the film is more a tease in the same way that superhero films are a tease to people's unconscious wants for more power and control over their oppressors). The guy has a good job but smugly walks out on it. This teaches that you have to keep running away from things to find yourself, rather than just have the courage to accept yourself. He could have made so much more of his opportunity at work, and found lasting happiness that way. But no - this is Ben Stiller - so within his little vanity-fest are more useful lessons for the young and impressionable, like how its hilarious to fly a helicoptor drunk, or skateboard down a huge hill without training as long as you're listening to cool music and "feeling alive, man!". Then, the film blatantly rubs a bunch of sponsorship in your face by way of Papa Johns, just to remind the audience "hey, whilst you're all suggestible to this nonsensical, contrived whimsy with no basis in real life and without a message that means anything useful, don't forget that we're making a bunch of cash from your ticket, and all these sponsors. You suckers!" Its almost like the film equivalent of a Tony Robbins seminar - empty, vacuous tripe masquerading as something life-enhancing, who's only purpose is to make a bunch of money.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 10:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find his agent (won't be too difficult) and just write and ask for one with a SAE. I did this for Christina Ricci when I was about 12 and I had a signed photo back. I think it would be better writing for one than buying one on Ebay because then you have a little story, and the envelope it came it, and its (slightly) more credible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 10:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Secret Life of Walter Mitty made me feel angry at what a contrived, egotistical and overly-sponsored film it was. The only way to enjoy it is as a satire about the ignorant whimsy of millennials.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The director made another unknown, obscure film that is never mentioned called The Moon (1983) and is also David Bowies cousin's dog groomer's housemate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Kate Beckinsale when she was super-young in a little Brit film called Shooting Fish, and thought she was cute enough to look up and read about. Later, I watched in awe as she effortlessly became the star of the Underworld franchise and endless bargain-bin Netflix kinda films.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She represents American values </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was one that I uninstalled after a couple of minutes. VR tunnels are always great, but having to avoid the stupid red things kills the fun, its just too annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No comments about the Trent Reznor soundtrack?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend using the Revolut card/app and saving commission fees and charges, it will help offset against the rates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I felt exactly the same and stopped at the same bit. I got frustrated when rewatching the Bourne films last year with how corny and forced the sense of action and urgency was. The last film then just seemed like a spoof. The opening scene reminded me of something from Hot Shots Part Deux.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D.A.R.Y.L. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I get the bluray for a film I have on DVD, the DVD no longer holds any value at all for me. Sometimes I just want to get rid of a bunch of them, and don't have the time nor inclination to list it all separately on ebay/gumtree/amazon, and deal with moronic questions, flaky buyers, going to the post office for one-off items, people claiming stuff didn't arrive or whatever else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So funny, I was just listening to this before throwing my On cd out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just about to list a bunch of DVDs. Its heartbreaking seeing a good collection go for 5-30p a pop. Even my Stanley Kubrick boxset in perfect condition is only worth just over 1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stanley Kubrick's The Killing will be your cup of tea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manchester by the Sea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this entirely comes down to hype. I saw a preview of it in UK where the audience didn't even know what the film would be, and it was amazing. The atmosphere, music, style, slow panning shots, dreamy nightmarish feel to the whole thing, it was just awesome.   

After release, buzz and hype, people I've shown it to mostly don't gel with it. I think people immediately put their guard up, with a kind of "ok, come on then, scare me" mentality, rather than really being in sync with the film and what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The robot woman in Superman III.   

In UK, we had these one hour Children's Film Foundation films in the 80s, and there was one called Haunters of the Deep about ghosts in cornish tin mines that gave me nightmares for a while. Such a claustrophobic environment to start seeing ghosts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its remarkable how well Pulp Fiction has dated. So many other 90s films that were influenced by it look terrible now, but Pulp still feels like a classically shot, robust film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really isn't. It starts well enough, then you start getting frustrated at the cheap jump scares that go nowhere, then the last act becomes incomprehensibly stupid in a way that makes the earlier jump scares nonsensical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going back a while, but the original trailer for Twister was atmospheric and intriguing as hell, which left people really disappointed in the actual movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooonce, there was this keeeeeed who </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to get to that level, I really do. I love picking apart Lost Highway. But with IE, I lose faith that there is anything to "do" in terms of deciphering or pondering, I get the feeling Lynch was just doing stuff because he felt like it (a product of his meditative brain storms) and the audience then falls over itself trying to inject arbitrary meaning and subtext. I just dont know if Im pissing up a pointless tree, basically. Have you reached a place where youre confident it IS all intentional and purposeful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 11:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll shoot for David Lynch's Inland Empire. I love a lot of Lynch's other movies, and whilst people take IE as classic Lynch, I just find it *fucking boring*. I have tried to watch it again to see what I missed, but its just too boring. There aren't enough hooks to make me care about a single damn thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 11:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first heard Supremacy without knowing the background, it screamed Bond, and in hindsight I think they tried a bit too hard. Weaving the actual Bond theme into the background of the verses was overcooking it a little. I preferred Radiohead's version for Spectre as a Bond theme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see FMJ, but I did see Whiplash, and I imagine the reaction to be similar. Nervous, quiet acknowledgement, because there's a vicious undertone, and you empathize with the people being barked at (who are nervous as hell) rather than laugh along with the barks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People said "The Visit" was good when it was released, and it was so shit I got angry and crushed cans. So I just have a blanket distrust of Shymalan now, regardless of what people say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
