<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7087</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I literally said "insist" implying that it is wrong, you know it is wrong, but you've chosen to do it anyway.  

If we lived in a perfect world everyone would do everything by the book, but we don't.  

People leave their cell phones on when they shouldn't, they leave for break early, etc.  People are people.  They do lazy or dishonest things that dont always hurt anyone.  

Not saying I do this, but I've witnessed people fail to bring a new employee in on some harmless thing they weren't supposed to be doing and end up causing the new guy to get in trouble because he didn't know it was wrong to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you and your co-workers insist on secretly cutting corner or other activities that aren't within company policy, be sure to properly inform new employees early to avoid them unwittingly outing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never done this before, how does publishing work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm writing my first book, and I haven't ever formally written a complete novel before.  Upon completion what should I do about publishing?  How does that whole process work?

I've been considering just releasing it digitally and making a website for distribution with conversions for every format.  I was thinking that this way, instead of charging for my book, I could simply leave an option to leave a donation if readers liked my work.

Is this a feasible option?
Would I have to worry about plagiarism?

Any advice is welcome. I work a full time job, but writing is my true passion and I really want people to enjoy my stories.



EDIT: thank you all for the great advice!  I really appreciate the assistance and you've given me peace of mind.  I now just have to choose what path I want yo take!  Research, research, research huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 04:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enlisting in the army to get away from my family.  I met my wife, had two children, got out, and had the means to move somewhere else. 

No more poverty, abuse, violence, theft, drugs, or crime in general.  Gonna raise my family right and work an honest job and draw benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People in "Tiny" homes are commonly viewed positively, but single-wide trailers have commonly been viewed as a sign of poverty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 15:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 15:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the advice!

A couple questions I have though:

1.) What about summertime?  When school isn't in session and you aren't taking a full credit load you can't utilize the GI bill or collect on any benefits right?

2.)  What about healthcare?  How did you keep your family insured?  My wife has to take medication for depression so this is an incredibly important factor for my family.

3.) Who can I speak with to get more information on what I'm eligible for? (State, School, VA, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Got out of the Army in June and I'd really like to go to school, but I have a wife and 2 kids to support. Really need guidance!(double posted to r/ veterans) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!
Sorry if this gets long but I know specifics are necessary when it comes to benefits and what not in these situations.
I'm a non-combat vet (just never got deployment orders,) who served in the US Army Infantry for 5 years. I ETS'd Honorably and I'm still waiting to get appointments from the VA to get my disability percentages worked out. 

I spent my last four months of enlistment in a program called The VIP program (Veterans in Piping.) Basically I got a years worth of apprenticeship classes and training for the United Association of Welders, Plumbers, and Pipefitters. I have now started this apprenticeship but not everything that was promised is happening as quickly as they make it out to. I still don't have health insurance for my family, Im supposed to be able to draw my GI bill since it's an apprenticeship (Can't make ends meat without it actually,) but that hasn't happened yet, and I've already been laid off and out of work more than I have been collecting a paycheck. 

I'd like to get a degree so I can get something a little more secure and provide for my family, but I'm not really sure how I could keep my bills paid and my family fed whilst going to school here in northern Ohio. Rent for my current home is 875 a month (3 bedroom double wide) and BAH rate for an e5 with dependents here is only about 1250. 

How do Vets with families get an education and utilize their GI bill and other benefits?

I appreciate any advice or direction. 

Id like to add that im an intelligent person. I scored a 91 on my ASVAB and my GT was 125. Actually going to school is not something I would have a problem with. Im merely having trouble working out the sustainability of a path that involves higher education as opposed to construction labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Got out of the Army in June and I'd really like to go to school, but I have a wife and 2 kids to support. Really need guidance! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!
Sorry if this gets long but I know specifics are necessary when it comes to benefits and what not in these situations.
I'm a non-combat vet (just never got deployment orders,) who served in the US Army Infantry for 5 years. I ETS'd Honorably and I'm still waiting to get appointments from the VA to get my disability percentages worked out. 

I spent my last four months of enlistment in a program called The VIP program (Veterans in Piping.) Basically I got a years worth of apprenticeship classes and training for the United Association of Welders, Plumbers, and Pipefitters. I have now started this apprenticeship but not everything that was promised is happening as quickly as they make it out to. I still don't have health insurance for my family, Im supposed to be able to draw my GI bill since it's an apprenticeship (Can't make ends meat without it actually,) but that hasn't happened yet, and I've already been laid off and out of work more than I have been collecting a paycheck. 

I'd like to get a degree so I can get something a little more secure and provide for my family, but I'm not really sure how I could keep my bills paid and my family fed whilst going to school here in northern Ohio. Rent for my current home is 875 a month (3 bedroom double wide) and BAH rate for an e5 with dependents here is only about 1250. 

How do Vets with families get an education and utilize their GI bill and other benefits?

I appreciate any advice or direction. 

Id like to add that im an intelligent person. I scored a 91 on my ASVAB and my GT was 125. Actually going to school is not something I would have a problem with. Im merely having trouble working out the sustainability of a path that involves higher education as opposed to construction labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://discord.gg/sy2vj 

I was referred to this discord server and it has been awesome!  

They are super welcoming and friendly and can show you the ropes and catch you up to speed!

Just download the client, log in and get started! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 00:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://discord.gg/sy2vj    I got on it earlier and its the bomb.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
