<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1935</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People aren't pissed he is minimizing his taxes, they are pissed he shipped them out of the country at the lowest point of the recession. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone signed me up for a Daily Mail subscription, I'd be pretty pissed. I'd be even angrier if I couldn't then cancel the subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happened. She also went on the US TV show I didn't know I was Pregnant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl from HamsandwicH stole something like 14 grand from BT2 over a couple of years.  [Got probation but promised to pay it back](http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/the-terrifying-cycle-of-debt-can-lead-you-to-a-very-dark-place-26529676.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ken Levine of Bioshock fame was working on a script at one point. he made the same point as you. Good concept horribly realized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah, let's base our conclusions on anecdotal evidence and isolated exceptions.

Literally this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I could tell you about a male bartender low five figures I know who dates a six figures female doctor, or the male out of work actor who dates a female executive, but you aren't going to know those people.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I go to a restaurant I sit in front of a table. The tables run the restaurant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not seeing Max Payne mentioned anywhere. The dream sequences and drug levels were pretty creepy. Not to mention the fun house level in MP2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for my parents. It was never about nutrients or wasting food. They saw it as wasting money. Sorry mom, but I don't need three potatoes on every plate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this and may use it in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the directors commentary on Little Nicky they weren't paid anything by Popeye's. They just thought Popeyes sounded funnier than KFC or generic Fried Chicken.

That's the honest truth. Why would anyone admit to listening to the Little Nicky directors commentary.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Batman sold more in merchandising than the film actually made there was a huge push in toy sales. In the original film they have shots of all the toys you can buy. Then the TV commercials for the toys told kids that they had to look for the JP logo otherwise their dinosaur toys weren't real Jurassic Park toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Oh bullshit. It's a fucking dinosaur movie. It was intentional to make more moeny

That's what he said, so he made that the plot. You can hear talking [about it here](http://nerdist.com/nerdist-podcast-chris-pratt-and-colin-trevorrow/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it and it kinda suits the setting. The director was approached to make a Jurassic Park movie. The first brainstorming session was why on earth would anyone want to make another Jurassic Park movie. They decided the only reason to do so was to make lots of money, so they decided that would be the plot, which is quite meta if you think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple are horrible for placement and always have been. I think the worse example of it was in the movie Fanboys. The movie was based in 1998 but released in 2009, so they forced iPhone references into the opening trail. It was so blatant.

Other offenders include constant references to Spiderman 2 in Knocked Up, that giant sign in Superman 2 and everything in James Bond movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd be the bad kid in a lot of classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also your anecdotal evidence is not indicative of anything.

This whole subs philosophy is based on anecdotal evidence. All it takes is a single anecdote to disprove most of the BS being spouted here as axiomatic truth.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The examples I gave were from after they were famous. I chose celebrities because they are examples you can reference. You believe in these rules but if the rules don't fit, you just say they don't count.

Hopeless really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 11:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also has a tendency to arrogance, elitism and narcissism which doesn't make a good surrogate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are looking to rent it out, a family home in the sticks might not be the best bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 08:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malcolm is an uber smart kid but acts like one of the bad kids in class instead of a nerd. Not really a blank slate. He probably is the most human character but he isn't really what a lot of people can relate to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first game was released in a pretty post 9/11 world. The Assassins were a Muslim group, the Templars were Christian. The disclaimer was put in place to show it was a fictional story that wasn't trying to make a comment on religions points of views or any current political situation. In Syndicate they had their first transgender character. The disclaimer was put in place to show it was a fictional story that wasn't trying to make a comment on religions points of views or any current political situation.

It's not that stupid. It is just saying that this game features a fictional story with people of different outlooks and views, but that is okay because it is made by a bunch of people with different outlooks and views. It's asking the players not to get their panties in a bunch because in real life there are lots of people with different outlooks and views and they can get along to make a game about something similar. 

Then people decided to get their panties in a bunch about the disclaimer. Is it PC gone mad, or did Syndicate feature an outlook and view that wasn't featured in previous games and just updated the disclaimer to include that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (And genders and sexuality since Syndicate). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 16:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest problem is the when you coil electric cable like that you create an electro magnetic flux which drains power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mako on Ilos was crazy. Hit a tiny bit of unlevel ground and the Mako was twenty feet in the air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the one thing ME1 had over the second game was the seamless transition from battle areas to normal areas in the game.

In ME2 you almost always had a loading screen, then you started the next section with your guns out. In the first game you could be walking in an area that is usually a shopping area and get in a gun fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This mad lad is mental! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They thought that was too much like the Matrix, so they got the arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the movie was a fun diversion, but after 10 years of playing the game it is easy to forget how batshit insane the plot to the games are.

So Templar v Assassin's. We have seen that before. That's just Dan Brown. You can pick that up easily. Then the Animus. Okay, so you can relive memories of ancestors, but only genetic memories right. That's a bit confusing but I get it. So why would we ever want to do that. If you are an historian I suppose. Oh no, we are looking for an Apple, what's that? Well the Apple is an artifact that was created by a civilization that came before man and was probably used as a way for man to spurn its creators, the previous civilization who is probably the people refereed to as God or gods in our holy texts. Wait slow down. And the Templars wish to control free will of the general populous to make society a better place, but the Assassin's think that is too big of a price to pay.

And tell that in 2 hours. I saw a lot of the reviews mentioning the plot was all over the place and that's true. But it always has been. I think fans of the game are used to that where a film critic with no prior knowledge that's a lot to get your head around. Also, while I love his movies, Justin Kurzel is a pretty bleak director, so we knew this wasn't going to be like a Marvel movie or even Star Wars. it was going to be pretty serious, which is a bold move for a video game adaptation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The server is the person who creates the dining experience.

They are just one part of the experience. The food, the atmosphere and the company are really a far bigger factor. McDonalds could bring in waiters but the dining experience would only change marginally.

I would say it is pretty egotistical of the server to think they have the majority stake in the experience. If find in US restaurants they spend too much time at your table, are overly saccharine and have a habit of interrupting you while you are having an important conversation.

The only interaction I really want with a server is drinks order, food order, bring food, check in once to see if everything is okay, bill. I good server could have this done in 7 minutes at a two people table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, it's also opinions on laws, freedom of speech, etiquette, corporal punishment, homophobia, racism... All of which are pretty similar between Ireland and America.

They really aren't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's true for a lot of Trump's America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were sitting beside me I would hate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I'm sure someone from Japan would be fawned over by some Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much assimilation. I'm from Ireland and was living in America for a while. The most culture forced on me was being taken to In n Out burger. But everyone talking to me wanted to have drinks with me and talk about Irish culture and Irish music and Irish Traditions and to tell everyone what the culture was in Ireland. No one said I should start listening to Springsteen, or get a gun or go bowling.

Lets be honest, some cultures are valued over others. So in my case I came from Ireland and people thought that was cool so no one was asking me to assimilate. If I came from somewhere like Romania or Nigeria or Argentina I'm sure more people would be demanding me to assimilate into American culture. But as an Irish guy people got off if I talked in Gaeilge or told them about hurling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even so, the guards say around 200 people. The 'witnesses' in the article mentioned say 100. Why would you print a headline with 250 unless you were fear mongering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Indo just republished this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's still short by 25%. That is a significant discrepancy.](https://www.reddit.com/r/ireland/comments/5m56oa/terrified_shoppers_attacked_as_250_gang_rivals/dc1421l/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really the point I'm making. I'm saying this article is trash because the facts in the title aren't even collaborated by the facts in the article. No one even claimed to see 250 people but they reported it as such. In essence they are guessing the facts and adding flourishes where they see fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dublin Live

Looked at the Dublin Live article, which got its data from the Independent. [The Independent article](http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/terrified-shoppers-attacked-as-250-gang-rivals-battle-in-facebookstaged-street-riot-35343400.html) is the same article as this, word for word. So does the LovinDublin article. 

So the single source is this article. And this article has anonymous accounts.

To me what happened was there was a large crowd of young people on the streets. Police asked the crowd to disperse. They refused and it ended in a single arrest. To me, this article is making it sound like a riot-cum-gang war happened on St. Stephen's Day despite the fact nobody in the press, on Twitter, reddit or Facebook or any other social media platform reported it (until now, two weeks later).

So apart from some anonymous security guards and shopkeepers there was no proof of a mass fight. From what I can gather from the quantifiable, verifiable facts in the articles I have read, was that a bunch of youths, who probably also happen to be black, congregated in large numbers and were acting rambunctious as crowds do, like at football matches for example.

Guards were called, people were asked to move on. One person gave lip and was arrested. Hardly South Central, LA. Dr. Dre couldn't make a rap out of this.

Maybe something larger did happen, but this unsourced piece of shit article does not convince me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's still short by 25%. That is a significant discrepancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where the number 250 comes from because the people in the article mention no more than 100. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mention on Twitter or Facebook. No one recorded it on the phone. Pure Yellow Journalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title says 250 but people in the article mention 100. It was arranged on Facebook but no screenshots. No video uploads and no one here seems to know of it happening and only one arrest.

I think this whole article is sketch. They mention it as an ongoing problem yet The Hearld couldn't scrounge up a single photo. I also like the mention of an anonymous shopper who was black and could be mistaken for being in a gang. This is a thinly veiled hate piece. *Black youths are pulling knives on shoppers and others*. It reads like the Mail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tayto win on nostalgia alone. If you really like your crisp, you know that they are greasy and flaky. I know it is a crisp for protestants but objectively Walkers is the best on the market by all standards for your mainline crisp. Hunky dory if you are going a little bit more leftfield.

Also Marks and Sparks do a good in store brand crisp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with data formats, data transfer seems to be a big issue in Star Wars too.

Do they have WiFi in Star Wars? Jyn gets to send her email at the end of Rogue One so the plans are moved, but a crew member needs to digitally download a hard copy to hand to Leia. This motif is continued in A New Hope. At the same time BB-8 is carrying around a thumb drive with Luke's location on it. 

Obviously this is a throw back to 70s where the idea of sending data over the air might have seemed more implausible than the Force (even though Hedy Lamarr had laid the ground work in the 60s) but data storage and transfer seems to be widely contradictory in the SWU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Tape Drives to Memory Orbs, the Data Formats of Star Wars Suck (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 09:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually would hope not. While this guy is obviously in the wrong here and completely insufferable, I could imagine that charge could be tacked onto anyone and would be pretty hard to defend yourself against. in most cases it would be he said she said bullshit but it of course the court will always take the guards side. It could technically give them free reign to detain anyone they thought looked at them sideways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 09:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pronounce it gasping hole of despair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not one person has yet to mention The Re-Animator. 

Shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So seriously, does the Congress just have a print shop and graphic design department. I don't see this in any other government parliamentesque place, but Congress always seems to have big high quality printed board. Is it all done in house? Do people like Bernie hire staffers whose sole job is Photoshop, fixing and servicing CMYK printers and just churning these boards out? Or is it a shared resource? Like the guy who printed this out was previously working on a high res version of a bar chart for some Republican before hand. Please tell me.



Do they do revisions? Do they post on ClientsFromHell? Who are these people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vectors have a huge processing overhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story wise, there is no real good game to start at that isn't AC1 and then play straight through. 

AC is a bit retetitive but the modern day story elements are pretty crucial. Then you are pretty much stuck up until AC 3 to finish Desmonds story. Even if Revelations is filler, there is a lot fo background stuff that is important and it also has Desmond coming out of his coma.

You could start at 4 and play through to Syndicate I suppose, but then you miss AC 2 and Brotherhood. So start at the first game or the fourth game. The only game you can really skip is Unity. Syndicate does a good round up of the modern story so far with the WWII stage so maybe you could start there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good catch. Phrased better now. Speed limits will still be relatively low (and should be) in areas with people, or potential people crossing the road. Only motorways will have higher limits and they will still be kept artificially low to prevent road damage or collisions with animals or suicidal people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 20 years, you will have a car the same way you have Netflix or Photoshop.

[Also this is worth a listen](http://boingboing.net/2016/11/23/car-wars-a-dystopian-science.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But speed limits aren't limitations on speeds you can safely drive at. Speed limits are set for various reasons. One reason is income for a city. Another is because people are less likely to have a squishy death at 50 kpm than they are at 60 kpm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underpowered graphics isn't a problem. If Layton want to animate a hand-drawn sequence, it is suddenly for HD instead of the 400 pixels of the 3DS.

Also the Switch is obviously marketed as a TV console with a portable experience like the Wii U, not a full blown handheld like the DS line. It looks too big to be truly portable. A backpack system, not the inside pocket of a jacket system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it was a joke. I think it should stay canon for the 20 minutes of continous unsubtitled Wookie conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It introduced Boba's look, so it stays canon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say she died of a burst ventricle, but I know it was of a broken heart.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phising is a type of hacking. So is social engineering. Hacking is the broad term. It includes phising, using scripted exploits or using the book on Ozymandias's desk to guess his password. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movies make hacking to be mostly scripting but if you read about the early days of phreaking, the social engineering aspect has always been the most effective way to hack something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not likely, as as soon as those games are on a grown up console, they will be competing with AAA games. People will see it as a choice between Layton and CoD or whatever the third party pushes. So it will either kill the market for those hand held scope games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The games fall into a nice little bracket that suits handhelds perfectly. They are too deep for mobile apps and they aren't big enough for a full blown console experience. 

A game like Layton with its cute animated scenes and puzzles that work really well with touch. Move that to a big screen, suddenly all your cutscenes need more fidelity which costs more money. Same with the puzzles. Now a game that shifts roughly 2 million units a release needs higher production values and it will eat into its profit.

But Layton isn't a Nintendo game, so what about Pokemon? Put it on a larger console and now it isn't just being compared to other gameboy RPGs, it is competing against Final Fantasy or Skyrim or other main console releases (obviously we don't know what releases are coming to Switch yet, so these are examples). The Pokemon models are pretty simple and maybe have a handful of animations. The maps and the overworld can be bare bones. That works fine on handhelds. Put it on a console and people want to know why can't they see wild Pokemon in the grass or have a whole team of Pokemon follow the player.

Pokemon is really popular and will sell loads no matter what, but again all this upscaling comes with dev costs and eats into profits.

Fire Emblem has really simple animations and pixel art elements. People will wonder why not full 3D models like Breath of Wind or something.

If Nintendo don't continue with other handheld systems we are going to lose a whole type of game. The smaller, often experimental games that are great to play on a bus, or train or fun to play in short bursts, but offer more depth than mobile games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no proof that there won't be another handheld. I can't imagine Switch is a good place for games like Layton, Pokemon, Phoenix Wright, Fire Emblem, Nintendogs, Picross and a bunch of other franchises. It doesn't offer that middle ground for the sort of games that thrive on the DS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But these are job creators and we punish the employees if we punish the company harshly. Also it is too big to fail.

How is it under that rock?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great. And who will pay rent and feed my kids while I'm out of work.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well by reshell I meant they rebuilt the hardware, not just the case. It's not an upgrade. It is the same device. There was no GameBoy Advance Micro only titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I agree. In game demonstration and then a manual for reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except in Rogue One it seems where they send a data file wirelessly, something that would have saved a lot of time in A New Hope and The Force Awakens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 12:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What I want to know is, if they can send digital data wirelessly, why do they constantly rely on using bots with thumb drives to send messages. Send an email. They could use a dish to send a message to space but had to physically hand Leia a hard drive?](#spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference between open ended gameplay and directionless. Even in open world games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I  games with a reverse funnel approach. You lock down the early parts of the game, so you can learn characters, motives, plots and maybe in game tutorials. Then the game opens up more and you then decide what you want to do after all that is established. FO1 felt like it was tunnelling you into the rope vault, but I never would have found the rope without a walkthrough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how improved graphics is coddling, but Uncharted is pretty much an apple to oranges comparison.

If you compare it to something modern like Shadowrun, which has different but similar elements, you can see how dated Fallout really is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why you are getting downvoted. Maybe tone. Loads of other posts point out how bad the UI is and the clunky game mechanics. Far from ageless.

As for no one playing it today, I'd disagree, but it would be a niche title, or more likely a V1.0 would be released but people would complain about UI, confusing elements and it would either eventually be much more playable or a horse built by committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me 'still holds Jo's would mean that it plays in a way that is similar to modern games. I would say games like Super Mario Bros. and Sonic still hold up because a 10 year old could still play them and have fun.

I would say a lot of PS1 games don't hold up because their control schemes seem clunky. I would say a game like Deus Ex only slightly holds up but can be improved with mods. I would say Fallout doesn't hold up because in the years since release almost every aspect of the game has been improved on. 


That's not to say it is not a classic or you won't have fun with it if you put in the effort. But that is the thing you have to put in effort, whereas if you played the game on release it would have been a lot more fun without added effort.

I think Metroid is a good example. If someone asked me if Metroid was worth playing, I would say they would probably enjoy Metroid Zero Misson more. Not that Metroid is not fun, but it is missing things like maps, saves, the screen might flicker at times that is extra effort for the player without it adding to the experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best way to learn a game is through in-game tutorials. I can read and reference a manual all I want but nothing beats a story guided tutorial. Like playing a board game the first time. The quickest way to learn most of them is to jump right in with someone who played before.

Fallout is built so that you need to restart the game fresh a couple of times because you mess up important stuff early on. Compare that to Deus Ex (this title is from a later time but I choose it because it is one I'm very familiar with) if you Fuck up and put all your points into swimming, you are not going to have to start fresh because you are still learning the mechanics. Even Fallout 3 had the early vault so you know what you are getting into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the interface is a good reason why it doesn't hold up well. Even if you get used to the interface and its weird take on turn based movements, the game itself is a little too open ended.

I've attempted to play it around three times and given up after about three hours on my most dedicated play through. To get me through the initial confusing guide a looked at a walkthrough. Pretty soon I found I wasn't even playing the game, and I was just following the guide. Not only did I have a problem with figuring out what to do next, there was a big problem on how to do things next.

I've played a lot of old school point and click games so I'm used to games that seem really open about what your next steps are but Fallout just bamboozled me. I don't think I could recommend the game. The Civ games are easier to pick up and play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Micro was just a reshell like the DS Lite or 2DS. I imagine there was a third pillar plan, but after the success of 3DS any new handheld would eat into their market lead and divide third party devs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like a mild inconvenience at most. Is there a reason you can't provide this information?

If none of the bill's are in your name it can be a hassle, but I presume you are on a lease or mortgage application or something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to their influence on our tiny nation, I have an interest in how places like the US and the UK are run. Even if I pay indirect taxes, I probably don't have the right to tell them how they are run because I'm not a citizen.

I think residency should take priority over passports when it comes to voting. Not just in Ireland. If I planned on living somewhere for a long period of time, I would like the opportunity to have my say.

I might make an exception tho the Presidency because of the nature of that role as a figurehead for Ireland and Irishness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heresy is technically a sequel to the existing book line, hence the ability to assume people are familiar with the world. The book takes place before the events in the film and like the film is considered in game Canon to an extent. It is also worth noting that the author has also written the movie novelization. This means the AC book series stretches from Alitair, right up to Callum Lynch, and includes an extra story focused around Joan of Arc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rikken and others are from the game and are described as the Inner Sanctum. Can't get much higher. A passing mention of the Animus project Vidic and subject 17 would have been cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My take was they were referring to the Aquilar Apple. I also presumed that they know about the Izu but Sophia Rikken isn't fully privy to all the details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was no retcon. They don't explicitly say there is only one Apple. They just conveniently forget to mention the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to fit. Other Assassins have had plenty of emotion and a lot were driven to revenge through personal vendettas (Ezio, Connor, Shao Jun). These Spanish assassins hold the creed above revenge or personal feelings.

When I die today, do not waste any tears on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to your theory they shouldn't have been with these guys in the first place. In many cases they traded down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J Lo is married to a backup dancer, so is Madonna. Keri Russell was married to a carpenter. Evangeline Lily was going out with  production designer on Lost. Christina Aquilera with a set worker from Burlesque. Scarlett Johansson has a child with a journalist. That's practically not even a real job anymore. Brittany Murphy did too. And that guy wasn't what you'd classically call a looker.

It took two minutes of research to find that. Virtually no effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was unemployed renting a single room in a shared house living off unemployment, I got laid way more than I did when I was working. Why? Because I had more time to go out and meet people and build relationships with women.

You've just made an excuse and are sticking with it. The reason you don't see beatiful women with janitors is because the janitors you know don't have beautiful wives (in your opinion). You don't have the opportunity to see a bunch of a janitors on tv to rate them. How many janitors do you even know? Have you met their wives.

You also need to remember that every wife of an  athlete you see, probably just had her make up done by a professional on top of their field and the clothes they are wearing are all fitted and designer.

Put the janitors wife in a designer fitted dress and get her make up done, she will probably look a lot better. And the athlete's wife probably looks drab in a Wal-Mart hoodie too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but that has literally no bearing on my comment what so ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think RTE have a youth market problem. They've just axed their kids division. So I haven't watched in years because I am an adult with no children but the Den could always hold its own against Live and Kicking or Ant and Dec back in the day.

My parents will watch Brown's Boys and Tubs but no one in the seventeen to forty market will. They had a go with Can't Cope Won't Cope, which was uneven at best and I think they had that Asking for it doc which had some broad appeal, but I can't think of much that they have done in the last twelve months for the under forty demographic. Conversely, the Irish Film Board have been doing gangbusters recently, so lack of talent isn't the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or they could just Joker it and never mention her again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the Mom died in The Sopranos they had about the worst scene in the entire show of her just mumbling random lines to Tony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 12:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ally McBeal's marriage was halted because RDJ never showed up for filming. Turns out he was in jail, so they quickly spun out a new script and made Josh Groban a star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 12:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Axle Rose is notorious for walking out or delaying shows at the slightest hiccup. Also Carey has been doing this for the last twenty years too.

A rock performance can get away with being a bit more sloppy because it's louder, faster and more manic, with the exception of a technical genre like prog or mathcore. A performer like Carey has to be pretty much note perfect each time.

You might not be a fan of her music and that's fine, but you obviously have no idea what you are talking about.

/r/lewronggeneration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 12:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She directed a movie this year. I'm sure she's doing fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailer was like that but in pretty much the first scene they spell it out when Mia says, it is not so much a ghost story, but a story with ghosts in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The have copyright over their depiction of Pocahontas. I can make my own cartoon (and many have) of Pocahontas and as long as I have a new script, different songs and don't include talking trees, I'm probably fine. Same with fairy tales.

That's why there are always a tonne of rip offs when Disney release a new animation. I don't know how many Rapunzel DVDs I saw after Tangled and a bunch of Ice Queen cartoons after Frozen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mickey is a fictional character, not a historical one.

Universal Studios and Buena Vista  were able to distribute Hollywoodland which in a round about way features Superman without permission from WB or DC, but did have to remove some items which could be copyright infringement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
