<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9767</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 06:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's outside in full sun. Florida sun is quite intense so I have to make sure it doesn't get too hot or I put it in the shade for the hottest part of the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update on sundew! Finally getting some dew! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 01:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 06:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PMed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> in need for dental assistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 04:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello I'm Zach Westerfield. I'm 21. My teeth are getting to the point to where they are starting to rot out. I have a condition where I have no roots. Basically, my roots are all flat which means my teeth would fall out quicker than a normal person's would. My teeth are constantly killing me and I'm afraid I'm going to get an infection. I brush my teeth daily but my family has poor dental hygiene. I don't smile anymore because I'm afraid people will see my teeth. I've lost faith in myself. My self-esteem has gone out the door and I don't feel like myself anymore. I need root canals done, bridges, fillings, some tooth extracations, some crowns, a little bit of everything, (don't know what else), possibly even taken all teeth out which I really don't want. Basically most of all of them need some type of work done on them because of my root condition. I already have 2 teeth that's already about to fall out. I can't afford to get this work done. I need help. Soon. Any donation is appreciated. Thank you very much for reading my story. Any donation would be helpful! Thank you and God Bless. Here's my GoFundMe page: http://www.gofundme.com/zacharywesterfield </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 10:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an examination of my teeth and they told me all of my teeth needed to be pulled because I have flat roots and they were going to eventually fall out 1-2 years and that was a year ago. They gave me the other option of having work done on them (root canals, teeth needed pulled and implanted because some are completely destroyed already.) I had Medicare at the time as well. Now I don't qualify for it because I live in a different state and most of all of my money goes on bills and can't afford it and save up for a trip to the dentist, trust me, I would if I could. So it's either get all my teeth pulled or try to get help, really. I wished I had another option. It's not just one tooth, like you said. All of my teeth are starting to rot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need dental assistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 09:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assistance with dental! All donations appreciated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 08:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20, I work. (I don't get dental through work either) I make too much to qualify for Medicare, but not enough to have my own dental insurance and I can't get it. My teeth are getting to the point to where they are starting to rot out. My teeth are constantly killing me and I'm afraid I'm going to get an infection inside my mouth. I brush my teeth daily but my family doesn't have good teeth so it's probably genetics. I don't smile anymore because I'm afraid people will see my teeth. My self esteem as gone way down hill and I don't feel like myself anymore. I need root canals done, fillings, some tooth extracations, some crowns, a little bit of everything and 2000 (wild guess) should cover all expenses. I need help. Soon. Any donation is appreciated. Thank you to anyone who is willing to help. Here's the link to my GoFundMe page: http://www.gofundme.com/zacharywesterfield </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 08:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're an ass then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 07:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 07:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I have no idea why she thought this, but..) My roommate told me when she had sex for the first time, she thought the climax was her urine. So she urinated in a guy's mouth. I know, very gross. True story, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 06:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being yourself and not giving a fuck what others think. Be you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] pizza for me and my 2 kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 21:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two kids, they're my angels. I lost my job at the call center I worked at. They laid of 200 people and I was unfortunately one of them. My check was going on food but now that I have to pay that all in rent because my check is going to be less, I have no food. I'm in a panic and I'm trying my best to not breakdown. a pizza or two would get me and my kids through the next 1-2 days while I figure out something immediate and while I try to get back on my feet. If anyone is willing to help, that would be so kind and I'd be very grateful as well as my kids would, thank you for taking the time to read my short and sad story. We live in Florida and we have Papa Johns available for delivery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina cracking down on poachers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 22:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me happy. A new law was signed into law Thursday now makes it a felony punishable by up to 25 months in prison to steal them. This is wonderful news as these plants grow in a 70 mile radius. These are beautiful, unique plants that deserve to have crucial laws protecting them. Here's a link to the article if you wanna catch up: http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/09/19/us-usa-north-carolina-flytrap-idUSKBN0HE00L20140919  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 20:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure is!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Received my Sundew today! Glad this one doesn't go dormant to keep me occupied, lol! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 04:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 06:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just say Northern part of Florida, not that I think you're a stalker, you never know about people anymore, you know? I think Miami is like 14 hours from me though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 06:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! Yes, of course! I'm always up for new friends! :) Yes, I live in Florida, such a beautiful place! how old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 03:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love video games, the beach, love animals, love being outdoors, love music. Pretty much anything :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flight, Flubber, The Increasingly Poor Decisions of Todd Margaret, Sassy Pants, Short Term 12 are a few of my favorites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20/M/FL Need a friend! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 22:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm Zach. I'm 20. I love meeting new people. I consider myself funny, I love making people laugh. I'm a very good listener. I'm a non-judgmental person that loves when people tell me about their day or something that happened to them that particular day. I'm a very down to earth person that enjoys life. A best friend would make it even more enjoyable. I love music, Netflix, animals, the beach, pretty much anything to occupy me. I'm really mature and I know how to handle myself as well. With that being said, if you're interested in having a loyal, honest, "count on me" best friend, please message me or comment. We'll see where it goes. Oh, and it doesn't matter male or female either. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the pot has like 6 holes at the bottom for drainage. The pot drains every time it rains. I'll keep them out for sure it if helps washing out the left over nutrients. I'll keep an eye on the pot and keep you posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 17:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been keeping them out when it rains here. Sometimes when it rains, it rains a lot in Florida lol. So I'm thinking the soil didn't have enough chance to dry out which is causing some rot. Maybe I should start putting them in shelter until the rain clears?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 17:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I definitely will. Thing is, they've only been in this pot for about 2-3 weeks with fresh peat moss and perlite. I do keep them out when it pours here in Florida maybe I should put them up when it rains for a long period of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 20:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I was getting so worried. Somebody in another forum said the sphagnum moss growth was inviting fungus gnat or whatever that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green stuff in my sphagnum moss. Mold/fungus? Am I doing anything wrong? :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 20:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 07:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should upload a picture of it! I'd definitely like to check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 04:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have this species? :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 00:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.petflytrap.com I recommend this vendor. Very fast shipping. Got here within 3 days. Packaging was superb. As you can tell, received a very live and healthy plant. :) Not to mention they have cheap prices as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Received my King Henry today! (Dionaea Muscipula) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 07:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the tip! Can I grow these under a grow light during winter? I live in Florida and it stays pretty much 50's mid 40's during winter, so I don't know if I should bring it in or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 06:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got it from Lowe's and it only had one pitcher when it was in dormancy. This particular plant hasn't grown any new pitchers so hopefully this coming spring it will have more to sprout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just bought this little guy. It'll be here soon. :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 06:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Drosera capensis. Very excited. Do I treat these the same as my pitcher plants and traps?
Picture: http://imgur.com/Cq7TMHo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that are having trouble with SwiftKey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To find it: For some reason it's not popping up in search in the App Store just yet. Go to http://swiftkey.com/en/keyboard/ios/ on your iphone and hit download on the Apple Store at the bottom. This should direct you to the correct app.

To install: Go to settingsgeneralkeyboard. Then go to keyboard and hit add new keyboard. You'll see SwiftKey under Third-Party keyboards. Tap SwiftKey. Then hit SwiftKey - Swiftkey and allow full access and hit allow. Then from there go to messages. Go to an existing text or create a new message and the stock iOS keyboard will come up. Hold the world icon and then slide down to SwiftKey as this will default the keyboard. Enjoy!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your app name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my comment above ^ Have you tried that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason it's not popping up in search in the App Store yet. Go to http://swiftkey.com/en/keyboard/ios/ on your iphone and hit download on the Apple Store at the bottom. This should direct you to the correct app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold the World icon and keep your finger on the screen and slide down to swiftkey. This will default the keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to settingsgeneralkeyboard. Then go to keyboard and hit add new keyboard. You'll see SwiftKey under Third-Party keyboards. Tap SwiftKey. Then hit SwiftKey - Swiftkey and allow full access and hit allow. Then from there go to messages. Go to an existing text or create a new message and the stock iOS keyboard will come up. Hold the world icon and then go down to SwiftKey. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 23:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really excited for spring! I can't wait. I did buy a non-dormancy Sundew to keep me occupied lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 23:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the mid 70's here every night. I live in the northern part of Florida, so it's pretty mild. Although the temperature has dropped at least 10 degrees than what it has been which I assume has to do with summer is almost over. I'll keep an eye on it for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about tall Sarracenia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 21:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first got the plant, it didn't have a brown spot. About 2-3 weeks ago, it developed a brown spot on top of the hood. Have I done anything or what can cause this? 

Image: http://imgur.com/WeGIzNx (sorry for the image quality. couldn't get it to focus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 21:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent coloration on that spider and those plants!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 02:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent point. ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 23:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered from amazon and predatory plants as well as petflytrap. I'm hoping for good results. :) thank you for the suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to get plants online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 22:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know of a website/company that sells cheap and healthy plants and has received a healthy plant from them? I'm so skeptic since I haven't ordered a single plant online, I'm afraid it might die. I've really been wanting me a sundew and a large venus fly trap plant though and my local stores don't sell them. Suggestions would be great. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you all for the wonderful comments. Glad my plants are thriving in this hot Florida weather. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update on carnivorous plants! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 20:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I repotted my plants into one pot about 10 days ago and here they are. They seem to be doing well. 

First picture: http://imgur.com/mtUhKGw
Second picture: http://imgur.com/dHz1X17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repotted my carnivorous plants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 04:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally got another pot and the right soil for them 50:50 organic peat and perlite with some sphagnum moss on top. So now they're outside for good. I'm going to acclimate them as well. Thoughts on this pot? Also, I have a question as far as dormancy goes. It stays pretty much warm here year-round then gets down to 50's-mid 40's in winter hence Florida weather. Will they still go dormant?  Here are some pictures:

First picture: http://imgur.com/M349XcS
Second: http://imgur.com/m0GFigT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 03:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter. You can join! Shoot me a request! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 03:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot me a request? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we aren't strict. We know what fun is lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (PS3) Recruiting members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 13:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our crew is very mature. We do death matches, races, free roam, pretty much anything every single day. We don't care about your level, so don't worry about that. We are a fun, talkative crew that would love new members. Also, we don't kill each other. :) Add me on psn: bigheartedboy
Also this is our social club page if you want to check us out: http://socialclub.rockstargames.com/crew/blainecountypsychos/gtav

We are Blaine County Psychos. Join us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (PS3) recruiting members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 13:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our crew is very mature. We do death matches, races, free roam, pretty much anything every single day. We don't care about your level, so don't worry about that. We are a fun, talkative crew that would love new members. Also, we don't kill each other. :) Add me on psn: bigheartedboy 

Also this is our social club page if you want to check us out: 
http://socialclub.rockstargames.com/crew/blainecountypsychos/gtav

We are Blaine County Psychos. Join us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 06:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blaine County Psychos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 10:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blaine County Psychos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (PS3) recruiting members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 23:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 13:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, you're allowed one post a day. I never thought to put up my crew name up because people can't find us when searching on the social club but I can do that for reference. As for the guy saying we kill our own crew members, we do not. It's strictly prohibited. We've had to kick 2 NEW members that were obviously completely ignorant to our ONLY rule is to respect your crew members. They are gone and they got on here and said things on my post to make our crew look bad. That's all I have to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 13:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search Blaine County Psychos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 13:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't kill members at all. Ask if you can get a bounty off someone's head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 13:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alrighty! will be looking for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Ps3) recruiting fun members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 21:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our crew is very mature. We do death matches, races, free roam, pretty much anything every single day. We don't care about your level, so don't worry about that. We are a fun, talkative crew that would love new members. Also, we don't kill each other. :) Add me on psn: bigheartedboy
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (PS3) recruiting fun members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 21:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our crew is very mature. We do death matches, races, free roam, pretty much anything every single day. We don't care about your level, so don't worry about that. We are a fun, talkative crew that would love new members. Also, we don't kill each other. :) Add me on psn: bigheartedboy
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 20:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll fit right in shoot me a request!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (PS3) recruiting members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 02:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our crew is very mature. We do death matches, races, free roam, pretty much anything every single day. We don't care about your level, so don't worry about that. We are a fun, talkative crew that would love new members. Also, we don't kill each other. :) Add me on PSN: bigheartedboy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 02:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot me a request! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 02:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We killed YOU, because you were KILLING others. It's funny because you were the only one killing people, therefore, your statement is false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 12:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright! I'm on every single day just shoot me a request! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
