<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5571</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has Obama been doing all this time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for advice on introducing a male pup to a year and a half old female? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whippets, like a miniature greyhound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best way to introduce a male pup to your two year old female (same breed)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sky and her favorite treat... Broccoli. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL most women can't achieve orgasm through vaginal penetration, despite popular belief. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has there ever been a 150/151 hack of pokemon yellow that allowed full evolutions of Alakazam/Gengar etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't waste time on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What childhood event still affects you as an adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice Wanted: Is there a way to receive Amazon orders that don't normally ship to Ireland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 09:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You catch more flies with honey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to get to a point where you either trust science or not. If you go down that route you can basicly legitimise anything. "I can't see the back of my head so..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flat Earthers of Reddit, how do you justify your theories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What awful thing have you done that you could never admit to in real life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amateur Combat Sport athletes, what advice would you give to someone stressed about an upcoming rematch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we get dark circles under our eyes when tired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree. But what about two teenagers, one calls the other a racist name. It turns out that the victimised student uses this word as his screen name on the PSN. It's still a a case of ignorance but is it the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically if one person calls another a racist word. It then turns out that that particular word is his PSN Screen Name and was meant innocently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How does someone justify punishing a student for racism when the victim doesn't take offence to the word? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How can I justify punishing a student for racism when the victim doesn't consider the word offensive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your worst breakup story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 10:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds brilliant thanks I'll definitely keep that in mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only received a notification from the vets for shots this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice Needed: My Whippet won't drink water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 14 month old Whippet has stopped drinking water. She doesn't show signs of sickness or dehydration but we never see her drink anymore and we're quite vigilant. She's been a diet of mince mush and veg for three months occasionally with duck carcass, human grade meat from a BARF supplier. Any help would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice Needed: My Whippet won't drink water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 14 month old Whippet has never drank much water. However lately she's essentially stopped altogether. We're quite vigilant and we haven't seen her drink water really in the last week. She doesn't seem dehydrated though. We've also had her on the raw diet for the last three months with no issues. Any advice would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non Christian Redditors: What do you believe happens after death? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burnt toast and starchy foods linked to Cancer risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Bono and The Edge pay their taxes in the Netherlands to avoid paying Ireland's higher tax rate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's birth rate increases after "One Child" policy change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Thank your SO for the littlest of things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was just in relation to males no? I never thought about that, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That horses are responsible for more deaths than any other animal in Australia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 10:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What becomes of the broken hearted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who have met their heroes in real life, what happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Rock stacking is endangering wildlife and preservationists want it to stop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime I hear this statistic I inherently think "Yes. Absolutely." I have no dreams of extravagance or anything like that. To be able to support my family worry free and have a little extra for fun would be perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that makes so.much more sense. I was aware of these sub breeds (I'm sure thats not the correct term) in other dogs like labridors but not whippets. I imagine she's of show breed because where we live (the west of Ireland) the few whippets we see are all working farm dogs and we got her from the east which is show dog country. It seems obvious now lol. Thanks that was great advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What small change to your job would make it infinitely better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume that's sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is good. When someone turns around and says that man in general are sexist gamers you can point to this study and say no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks she's generally healthy, we noticed that she was the smallest one in her litter so it could be just as simple as that, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that men who perform poorly at video games are more likely to make sexist comments about female gamers than successful male gamers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inquiry: Why is my Whippet is slightly smaller than normal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a healthy one year old bitch who is 10kg and 17" in height. I know she is of pure breed and she has been spayed from 6 months. I know that males are somewhat larger but compared to other whippets we've seen she's just a little smaller. Does anyone know why this could be? Is the idea of the "runt" real?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Atheists who found God, why did you convert? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who didn't attens their parents funeral. How did you feel afterwards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Is it ever acceptable to not attend a parents funeral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do pop up adds with misleading "fake" exit icons that try to dupe you still have a real "x" or exit symbol? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so yes. A rape in the past is as wrong to me as it is today. I understand cultural practices and beliefs are different but I think it's not unreasonable to have a moral viewpoint on a historical event. I also  understand the fact that war is written by its Victors. Conflicts would be taken with a pinch of salt on both sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always the quiet ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the big factor is whether or not bacteria recognises the flesh as dead and to what extend their eating humans goes towards regeneration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair slavery was thriving long before the US got involved. And on a greater scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought about the pathogen aspect. That could be susceptible in itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't know of there is one. Not all crimes are equal in all eyes. But I guess you could click with the basics. Rape, enslavement, theft, land grabbing, genocide, murder, erasing culture etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true actually. They would still be susceptible to decomposition and weathering and without regeneration they wouldn't last long.

As someone else here pointed out it would probably end up being the way they infect hosts that would enable them to continue and not their own capabilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps at best they would come out all raggedy and when the thaw comes they would rot faster. Might keep them going in colder weather just a little but the frost would do its own damage. I'm going somewhere hot if it ever happens then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So really the only thing that would allow them to continue on effectively would be through hosts like you said. Individually they would just fuck themselves up regardless of strength or capabilites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Parliament to decriminalise domestic violence to preserve tradition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which nation, past or present, has committed the worst atrocities? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But again were assuming that they're going to be clunky and ineffective. If we're talking about the same zombies from 28 days later, Z Nation or walking dead they're the predators. And tbh even the slow ones would be a nightmare. With no preservation instinct they would go through an enormous amount just to get at us and pan probably wouldn't be a factor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good man Darcy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're assuming that they need heat and proper regulation like we do. I would have thought the cold weather would have slowed down decomposition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But surely if they're dead then there's another force keeping them mobile hence they wouldn't be zombies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless of course the eating process extends their lifespan. And I mean whether permitting colder climates might have it harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep using that word. I do not think it means what you think it means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall-E. It was probably a lot more accurate that most of the serious stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long would zombies physically last if there was an Apocalypse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that Bob Ross is dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made a lot of sense, never thought of it like that, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teachers of Reddit, what has been your worst experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are the lanthanum and actinium series not left in with the traditional table of elements? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the old Swiss family Robinson approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US tanks and troops to begin arriving in Poland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What advice would you give someone who was planning on building their own house for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL about Mark Pollock: the blind and paralysed adventurer and athlete who became the first blind man to race to the South Pole and is the founder of the "Run in the Dark" project. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL about Mark Pollock: the blind and paralyzed adventurer, athlete and founder of the international "Run in the Dark" project and first blind man to race to the South Pole. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what winners and childhood traumas are made of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your worst experience at school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 09:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I didn't know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds selfish of them. I'm not trying to be cruel and I apologise for the bluntness but it sounds unhealthy for you to be in that relationship. Having said that it's none of my business, I wish you well though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Or madam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'll do nicely. Thank you kind sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's not been proven. When the vast majority of society doesn't belive something it cannot be considered a proven theory. It may be true but it's not a theory that's been proven. Also 911, seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cop on to themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus what? That seems to be an awful situation but how is it inevitable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, how do they have the balls to be like "no you can trust us" now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When in History has a conspiracy theory ever been proven to be true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, actually an English teacher so you picking up on that was a highlight. Also people seem to freak out over the weirdest shit so you can't be too careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty shitty under the rock to be honest but at least we had spell check under there. And moss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bastards  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those my options? I think ide rather go vegan now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you know how Luke felt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. And not just about the spaghetti. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
