<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8515</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 23:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if Portal 2 multiplayer is peer-to-peer or hosted on servers. If it's peer-to-peer, one or both of you have high ping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 22:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Mario 3D World is the only one I couldn't complete 100% no matter how hard I tried. The game is mostly really easy but that final level is ridiculous and I couldn't beat it with all 5 characters, only Rosalina.

Sunshine is difficult but I've played it enough times that I no longer find it challenging whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 10:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because he knows and recognizes Arya when she shows up at the House of Black and White, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 07:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to shoot the exploding bulb things (can't remember the name) at them. It's one of the new abilities you get in the Definitive Version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 06:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was one of the most interesting characters in season 2. But then seasons 5 and 6 happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 06:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've been playing since S2 and haven't found a particular role you like best, why settle on one now? Maintain the ability to play every role as long as you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 08:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Sherlock too but I definitely felt like that holiday special was a big letdown after such a long wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit. Makes sense but it doesn't mean I'm happy about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 11:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! More to come in the near future :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is brilliant and needs to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't watch RLM and I only just discovered YMS recently. This is more based on CinemaSins and JonTron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 - Literally perfect and I want to watch it on repeat and/or talk about it for the rest of my life
9 - One of the best films I've ever seen, hardly any flaws and resonated with me deeply
8 - Above average film, generally very high praise with perhaps a few reservations
7 - Below average film, plenty of redeeming qualities but it just didn't work for me as a whole
6 - Pretty shitty and/or non-enjoyable film, sometimes a fun watch with no substance
5 - Bad enough that I complain about it for weeks
4 - Bad enough to give me a headache and make me regret watching
3 - Complete trash, not worth mine or anybody's time
2 - How the fuck did this get made
1 - Star Wars Holiday Special

The highest I've ever ranked a film is 9.2. I've only ranked three films 9 or higher. 7.8 is what most good movies get; a bit odd but it works for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heath Ledger as the Joker (TDK obviously) and J.K. Simmons as Terence Fletcher in Whiplash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. :D I took inspiration from YMS, IHE, CinemaSins, and just a hint of JonTron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally had to buy the game three times (3DS, Wii U, and PC) so I could have a version that worked properly. The Nintendo ports of this game are shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's supposedly a moment when Athena scans Casey's DNA into the pin. But then I just think, that makes the stalker-child recruiting process a lot creepier. All these little kids running around stealing DNA samples while trying to avoid being seen... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D'awww thanks. Means a lot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually not on the hate train for that film. I don't think it looks good but I'm willing to give it a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're my spirit animal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like The Jungle Book either. (Zootopia is brilliant though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge CinemaSins fan so that means a lot. Thanks so much. :)

And Chard is what people called me in high school. I hated it for a while but it grew on me. Also, Botham rhymes with Gotham so that's cool or some shit idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 20:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once in the theater, once as a hate-watch with my family, and once to write the script for this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 20:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/9DQbeebxUcM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Force Awakens personally. But I can definitely imagine a Brad Bird version being superior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's completely fair. Thanks for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my bad, then. I've seen the film three times and somehow never noticed that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could argue the pin thing for hours, but you said yourself you don't want to defend it so I'll avoid that.

I would like to know what you would have me do differently, though, for the sake of future videos. Keep in mind these are supposed to be JonTron and/or CinemaSins-esque videos where I'm not critiquing so much as nitpicking in a semi-comedic fashion. After all, the point is for me to hate on it, not to be Chris Stuckmann.

Obviously if you don't like that style of video, that's totally fine. But if you do have any feedback for what should be different about it, I'd love to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, that speech is brilliant. Unfortunately it's one of the maybe three good things about the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watch the attached video I think you'll see that I dislike this film for reasons way beyond that. The writing, pacing, and characters all have loads of issues and the story has too many inconsistencies for me to take it seriously. Somebody else in this thread mentioned how "The Martian" is a film about optimism that portrays it through competent storytelling. Tomorrowland screams optimism in your face and backs it up with nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate "Tomorrowland" so I made a video tribute to its stupidity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This is the only one I've done so far but I'm really hoping it catches on. IHE was definitely an inspiration for this, so I'll try that, thanks again. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha sorry, my original script mentioned The Iron Giant but I think I took it out because it messed with the flow. It's also been forever since I've seen it so I can't really speak to its quality, although I loved it as a kid.

And that's a fair point. I tend to avoid CinemaSins videos for films that I love for that same reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're still using phrases like "she can fix it" 90 minutes into the movie without Casey (or the audience) knowing what "it" is. The entire film mostly revolves around that, so naturally people are going to feel like it's directionless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. It's stupid how the film puts such an emphasis on imagination and creativity, but their big idea in the end is "just drop a bomb on it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any of you hate Tomorrowland as much as I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 10:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't love it but I certainly didn't dislike it. I was a big fan of the book when I was in elementary school and I think a part of me just wanted to see a version better than that terrible animated one from the 80s.

This is one of the most visually impressive films I've seen in a long time and Mark Rylance was brilliant in his role. The girl who played Sophie did quite a good job as well. My praise mostly stops there, though.

This is probably the most thematically shallow movie I've seen this year. Aside from a beautiful portrayal of friendship, nothing in the storytelling of The BFG interested me. The palace sequence in the third act was especially cringeworthy and overlong, and the climax was too quick and scattered. I thought Sophie was going to try and remove the "no forgiveness" part of the dream at the end, which would have left a good message about everyone deserving a chance for redemption, but nope, those giants are permanently screwed. It was oddly dissatisfying for me.

Overall this is a good film that I never need to watch again. 7.3/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 10:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure the picture is clear and the movie titles are easily readable, and then send it to @andysignore on Twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 06:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Game of Thrones*

The Winds of Winter has replaced Ozymandias as my favorite television episode of all time. A perfect ending to another great season.

*Better Call Saul*

I've put off watching this show for far too long. Finally watched the pilot tonight and really enjoyed it--not as much as Breaking Bad's pilot, but obviously I wasn't expecting to. The last ten minutes in particular were really strong and I'm excited to keep watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 06:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackwater is fantastic, but it's actually my least favorite of the four major battle episodes. You've got some incredible stuff coming up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BYANONE SCHTOWB NEESHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 08:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only reason I never got Real Platinum God in the Wii U version. Shitty Lost runs and no efficient way to get Meat Boy and Bandage Girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hOI!
im tracr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 07:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think season 4 is the best full season, but The Winds of Winter was my favorite individual episode of any television show ever. Bloody magnificent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MAIN SPOILERS] Rank the six seasons of Game of Thrones! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 06:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that we have another fantastic season on our hands, I'm curious to know where everybody ranks it among the others. My ranking from best to worst is as follows:

4, 3, 6, 1, 2, 5

"The Winds of Winter" is now my favorite episode of the entire show, and last week's "Battle of the Bastards" is definitely somewhere in my top three. But I felt that the rest of season 6 was slightly lacking--definitely good, but not as great as the buildup episodes of seasons 3 and 4. Regardless, these last two episodes put the whole season above seasons 1, 2, and 5 for me, and by a pretty significant margin.

But I want to know what everybody else thinks! Some are calling it the best season of the show. I haven't heard anybody call it the worst, but if that's your opinion, make it known!

Post your rankings from best to worst below, along with your thoughts on season 6 and why you placed it where you did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He took "King's Landing" a little too literally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 01:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mission companion told me about an incident in which somebody in our mission got up during district meeting and bore his testimony against the Church. Supposedly he'd been reading anti-Mormon material. It made me curious. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 07:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BYANONE SCHTOWB NEESHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 07:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I get it for Bastion, which is probably even more pitiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't just the theme park ride. I think it was an entire book sequel to E.T. about him and his best friend Botanicus growing a spaceship out of a turnip and going on adventures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metal Gear Solid V is on sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can confirm on Binding of Isaac: Rebirth. 600 hours and counting, and that's only the PC version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 05:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you call an Irelia who goes top lane? I don't know, BUTCHA BETTA GETTEM OOOOUUUTA HEEEERE AYYYYY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I'm pretty sure even Christopher Nolan had no idea what that line meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa whoa whoa guys, let's all just calm down... and go watch my new show Fresh Prince of Bel Air. Starring me Carlton Banks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well technically you don't start with Wooden Nickel until you've beaten Isaac with him. So you have to get most of the way through a Polaroid run without that advantage before you ever have it.

Basically he's like The Lost in that he can only take two hits before he dies and can never obtain more health, but The Lost is guaranteed to get the Holy Mantle proc in every room, while Keeper isn't necessarily guaranteed to get a coin every room. This also means The Lost can safely explore Curse rooms while Keeper cannot. The Lost also has flight and spectral tears and can take devil deals for free--Keeper has triple shot (and therefore a shit tear rate), no flight, no spectral tears, and can only take 1-heart devil deals without dying. And after that, he can only take one hit, so really you can't even take those deals unless you have a Strength card (gives a permanent health-up to Keeper) or a health-up item laying around somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Finding Nemo is better by a pretty decent margin. I really enjoyed Finding Dory but I didn't think it was quite as well-paced or as perfectly structured, and it didn't have as many memorable individual moments or scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zootopia 2: Electric Bugaloo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ex Machina is my favorite film of all time. I love it so so so so much.

(Edit: stupid autocorrect) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie stands out to me as the only film I've ever watched that I hated while watching and didn't realize how good it was until the credits rolled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an entire list of CinemaSins-esque complaints about the last 20 minutes of The Door. Let me know if you want them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 03:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, same here. Ironically, this is the only episode of S6 I've actually tried to watch at the exact moment it released.

What is hype may surely die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But for real though, I just hit 600 hours the other day and I've only ever seen two of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 08:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made two dollars and five cents off of that. I'm a millionaaaaire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 23:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PeanutButterGamer is obsessed with Zelda and Animal Crossing, and he does Pokemon stuff every once in a while too. Super hilarious guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 07:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy is a prophet

White like all the rest

Fuck the other prophets

Tommy is the best

World in endless turmoil

Prophet, help us out?

"Faith and prayer, you heathens!

It will all work out!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seriously will get there if you like the game enough. I'm almost to 600 hours with literally nothing left to do (1001% on all three saves) and I still play every week simply because of how fun this game is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 09:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, all the point-and-click stuff is done with the gyroscope instead of the sensor bar, which makes it different than every other Wii game, as far as I know. But I think the calibration still relies on the sensor bar. I know I had issues at the beginning of one playthrough because I was sitting too close. Not sure how that all works technically, but yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of hate out there for Skyward Sword but it's actually my favorite game of all time. The biggest complaint I see is that the motion controls suck, but I completely disagree. The trick is being the correct distance away from the sensor bar; if you're too close or too far, you'll spend the entire game being too pissed at the lack of functionality to enjoy it at all. Do yourself a favor early on and find the sweet spot, and then enjoy an incredible game with no technical hassle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
