<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4900</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your site suffers from an 8+ loading time, there's likely a lot more issues than just a bloated theme. 

Having a really clean, efficiently coded theme isn't going to solve issues like bad hosts, poorly written plugins, etc. 

And if your site is as minimal as you're trying to portray it as...it's almost certainly things other than the theme.

Even the most bloated top selling themes like Avada aren't so bad as to cause 6+ second load times by themselves.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His cabinet picks are virtually the worst possible candidate for each job.

It's almost as if he were intentionally trying to sabotage the entirety of the American government. 

It's almost as if he is playing directly into the hands of a certain foreign power.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro whats you're problem? 

You're not buying that OP simply decided to abandon his sure fire way of making millions in order to develop a service that would teach others how to take over this sure fire business for him?

Instead of spending the last few months expanding this sure fire money making business to increase his revenue, he decided to start a SaaS business that would actually directly compete with his business model of selling Amazon Merch....

I mean it's pretty clear that he ISN'T trying to simply get his SaaS blog post to Rank 1 by stuffing this post with garbage image links every other line.....

OP is a natural teacher...a humanitarian...he clearly enjoys teaching others how to succeed more than making $$$$.

Also, don't be distracted by the fact that OP can't design a website that doesn't contain broken links....

I'm sure his ability to run a SaaS is completely independent from things like making sure the basics of his website works.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep...he's basically advertising that he needs to be "persuaded".... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given everything he's said...I'm sure he sees himself as virtually untouchable once he takes office. 

I mean look at what he's done so far and how his base has responded. He literally could kill someone on national TV and the GOP base would rationalize why he was justified to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO at the people who think this is fake/4chan info....

Carl Bernstein (half of duo who broke Watergate) is on CNN right now discussing how McCain got the documents and gave them to Comey.

You think CARL BERNSTEIN is going on national TV without confirming this? 

But yeah really....John McCain is really a shitposting 4chan user....he's just trolling everyone.

edit: Kellyane Conway just confirmed the brief is real/exists but questioned if it was 100% accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siteground shared hosting was extremely slow in my experience. I had the growbig plan and load times were 3.5+ seconds consistently for months with minimal traffic as the site was brand new.

Spent some time looking up info on Reddit, reading Digital Ocean tutorials, Googling, etc. and set up my own stack (1 gig VPS on Digital Ocean)...

Now the exact same site/theme loads under 1s consistently. 

If you don't have the ability/desire to DIY (and I probably wouldn't with an ecommerce site), I'd look into a managed VPS (not Cloudways though). Sorry don't have anyone to recommend (other than skipping Cloudways) because after a very bad, brief experience with Cloudways i just decided to do it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
