<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3508</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't he just issue an EO to make his family a protected class? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, is there not Dem party in your town? I was kind of meaning them. If they are jsut sitting there letting the GOP get away with that, they ain't doing their job.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> study for the mid term in 2018 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is is my job to educate these stupid hillbilly fucks? Why is it my responsibility to bridge the gap when these people are the ones without the facts?

It is not your job specifically. But it certainly is the job of your local party organizations. If people in your area are voting without the facts, ask the people heading the party at that local level why they are not doing their job to educate voters. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary represented a rapist. 

I mean to say that this is really pushing it a bit. Lawyers are lawyers and without them defending the bad guys, no-one will be there to defend te good guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone should tell Trump to name it back ! (Obama would never have the guts to do that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, mate. That must have come across wrong. I'm entirely sympathetic to people who have not got a break. And I'm plenty aware that many such people live in cities.

Probably I should not have emphasized the "rural" voters. Basically, I'm trying to make the point that a lot of people have dreams - like say to visit the grand canyon travelling from somewhere east of the mississippi - which are completely *normal* dreams to have and they find them unattainable. 

and both dems and republicans are to blame for the fact so many people live paycheck to paycheck and can never quite achieve that vacation they are dreaming of. 

Or they just cannot afford that decent car they've always wanted - not even an expensive car, just a decent one say in the 12,000 range. 

Or they simply want to be able to afford to eat better. 

thos people have been left behind and Sanders tried to reach them and Trump did reach them. Many of them- I'm really not trying to paint in broad brush strokes.

and to tell the truth, i think it's probably easier to live on a farm with no other real resources than to live in the city without much in the way of resources.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly does

http://i.imgur.com/h0EQqgP.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> confirmation bias. everyone else thought it was for sure florida. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  have arguments alone with my car. 

I'm really curious what side your car takes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would certainly be nice if Billy Bob could sit down and think about long-term consequences. But he can't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can a patriot like me get a COAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be frank, I fear you are wrong.

The facts are that neither the Rs or the Ds have accomplished anything in terms of improving BB's life. So, the fact that it is guaranteed under Trump to not improve in 4 years, does not mean BB will think "Gee, I guess the Ds were right, I'd better vote for them".

And the facts are that the rural voters you are talking about do in fact have a different reality. I'm not saying the facts are different, but they have a completely different views of things based on what they can observe in their own lives. 

Sure, they are uneducaed and influenced by alt-right TV and radio, but the fact is, Billy Bob has been living paycheck to paycheck for as long as he can remember - 8 years under Bush (R) and 8 under "Obummer" (D).

And he will tell you that you and I are in a state of perpetual outrage over things (like gender laws, Net Neutrality, voter intimidation etc) that are unconnected to (his) reality.

I mean there was a vignette on CNN I think where the Kentucky family or W Va family's biggest dream in life was to take the family to see the Grand Canyon.

Probably you and I would just save a bit here and there and then go. But we live in a different reality than them.

Trump of course is not the one to bridge that gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I hear Billy Bob is 100% happy with Trump and hopes Clinton DIAF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is: does Pepperidge Frams remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is just as abhorrent as Stephen Miller's statements that the president's authority cannot be questioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, these stories should certainly come out.

Russia: if you're listening, leak whatever you've got on this Stephen Miller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can mods see IP addresses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders should run with Warren as VP. I don't think that would happen, but I think it would win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hopefully, the next target is bannon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally subscribed to /r/politics in the summer just to stay in the loop during the campaign. On Nov 8 I went to bed (I live in Europe, so no vote returns were in yet) thinking, well that sure was a bumpy ride, I guess it'll be over in the morning. Wonder if I should watch Hillary's win speech from a politics link before I unsubscribe.

And then I woke up in the morning -  to see how much she had won by - and the goddaam CNN website was shouting at me in bold bloc letters, "TRUMP SURGES". 

That really fucked with my day.

hehe, "my day"... fucking wish the sun would set on this already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want you to name no fewer than 10 presidents greater than Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you need to add two numbers in your head like 53 and 87, start by adding the *tens* not the *ones*. You'll get there faster and it's easier.

5+8 = 13, so duh, that's 130 right there (easy to multiply by 10). Then 3+7 is another 10 and *woo-hoo* now you have got 140.

Now, you probably already do this in your head. You go to the store and buy four or five things, wonder if you have the cash on hand to buy it - don't tell me you add the *pennies* first, then the *dimes* and so on.

You don' do that, do you? 

So, then don't complain if they start teaching you kids how to do this in school. Yet a ton of people complain about "common core" and "new-fangled math". Dipshits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, fuck me silly...

http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/trump-rally-melbourne-florida-235061 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> geopolitical aikido </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't have a fucking clue what I'm talking about, but Bibi is the last guy I talked to, so I'll go with what he said." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no loop, no loop, you're the loop! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would invite her on and ask only the simplest of questions like, "what is you favourite colour?" "Dogs or cats?" "Best memory from high school..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, there is not, and never has been, any plan in this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flinging that shit with panache, mind you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary should completly troll Trump by posting Instagram pictures of herself just doing laid back 100% female, completely benign things - like getting her nails done, or relaxing in an easy chair with her head wrapped in a towel after a shampoo, lying on the floor playing with her dog or even just doing a crossword at breakfast.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want someone to gift him a segway podium a la SNL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why do i find this more than plausible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tough shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck no, bitch. and get your damn longbows out of my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you even imagine how pissed Pence must be?

And at the same time can you imagine Kasich on his living room couch watching CNN and thinking, "dodging that bullet was a fucking good call". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh you just watch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well then, okie-dokie, that sure took care of itself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eww, forgot about that part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we are waiting for Arya to show up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cersei is pretty dumb, actualy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ That is one of the very best puns ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is broke, he goes to the Iron Bank. Which turns out to be Moscow, not Venice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean, pelican, a republican is an invertebrate living in de Nile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really want someone interviewing Conway to ask her - right at the point she says Flynn "misled Pence" - to shoot back at her - "Well, maybe he was just giving Pence alternate facts?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  maybe it is some kind of diversion? Notice how no-one is talking about Bannon anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lemme get this right - basically, you are absolutely correct. 

i really want someone interviewing Conway to ask her - right at the point she says Flynn "misled Pence" - to shoot back at her - "Well, maybe he was just giving Pence alternate facts?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was brilliant. Thanks.

I do think he could have pressed even harder. He culd have put the question like this:

We know the White House learned that Flynn could be compromised by the Russians. Trump kept him on, because as you say Trump is loyal".

So, it appears to me that one of two things must be true:

The White House Counsel did not relay the information about Flynn being vulnerable to compromise to Trump, and so the president of the united states was unaware of this - excuse me - massively influential piece of information OR

Trump did get that information and decided to keep Flynn on anyhow.

Which of these two was it?

She could not have answered that question at all. lose-lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> linky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does this have to do with US law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But all those companies that get moeny from Netflix are also going to suffer and they won't want to suffer long. So, they and Netflix will negotiate and work to keep up with the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The copyright and licencing agreements will have to change going forward as they must comply with EU laws. 

I mean the content providers would probably be thrilled to split the US into different regions so they could charge huge amounts in NY and CA and lower amounts in Arkansas. 

But afaik, they cannot do that because of US law. The EU is trying step by step to move that direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The mainstream media has been far too willing to give the administration the benefit of the doubt 

I take solace in believing that the intelligence community appears to be doing the exact, polar opposite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a very scary thought, really. i don't think the world needs that kind of chaos. i just wish we could wake up one day with russia in its entirely replaced by an ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, it does not. Personnally, I think this is simply as close as Trump could come to an actual ban on muslims without explicitly doing it.

So, sure, you can be technically correct.

But taken in the context of the election campaign and Guilani's admissions, it's clear Trump *wants* a Muslim ban. His supporters certainly do.

And that together with the fact that the EO was so poorly thought out makes it easy to label.

And the fuckers could have done it "right". Just let in anyone from those countries who *already* has a visa/green card and stop all interviews with anyone else. none going forward.

they really shot themselves in the foot with this by doing it like a bunch of amateurs. and it just looks stupid when they don't ban saudi arabia, too. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, Abe look at a map, russia will never give up those islands. they form a ring in whcih russia can place its nuclear subs and fire at will.

they are not about to hand them over to a US Ally, even if Trump is president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i meant releveant as in it has a pretty big impact on the world, whether or not they find it interesting enough to watch.

for example: is global warming relevant to most people or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isn't the headline news on the FOX website often quite different from what they are actually talking about on the TV set?

or are they actually reporting this on TV and making it a centerpiece of their talking heads shows, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3d chess right there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do they do what they do with terrorists though?

i mean, if you call a guy tey know is a terrorist, they start monitoring your calls, too, right?

so, were they aware when they recorded flynn's alking to the russians and able or willing to follow that up by immediately starting to record his other calls, too?

or did they only realize later they had his calls to the russian ambassador and miss the chacne to record him reporting to Bannon/Trump/anyone else that "It's okay guys, i've calmed the russians down about the latest sanctions."?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my line of reasoning and questions:

if the IC was monitoring the calls of the Russian ambassador, this is no surprise. it's just part of spying.

so, in the course of monitoring, they find this citizen - flynn - violating the logan act. 

they get that on tape. 

so far, that is where we are. now i kick into "if i was the spy, what do i do next?"

since they have found a US citizen doing damage with the russians, do they get to now monitor all of his calls? i mean that's what they do, right? guy talks to known terrorist, he gets on the list of "suspicious types? right away and they start looking next at *his* contacts?

So, if they did then begin monitoring flynn's calls, do they have anyone on tape with him talking about the russian deal?

Like maybe they have him talking to someone and reporting on 
"how it went" as in "did you get an agreement with the russians?"

and if so, who the fuck is that guy?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ONCE AGAIN - no one is dissing the bernie supporters who ended up holding their nose to vote for clinton. it's the fucktards who did not vote for her or did not vote at all who piss people off.

so, no-one is mad at you. you did the right thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doesn't fucking matter if they also did not vote for clinton. if they stayes away from the polls pouting, well, trump is what the whole country ends up with.a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's the people supporting bernie in PA, OH, MI, FL who did not vote at all when they *should* have voted for Hillary that everyone hates.

No one is claiming all bernie supporters are stupid, petty shits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny, because starting with NSA Advisor is already pretty damn close to the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should falt out ask him - We've notices your NSA guy is gone. Did he die in the Bowling Green Massacre? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actaully, I' say it's pretty relevant to most people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] What's the best "Amazon" on-line store for electronics in Slovenia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm moving soon and will need to get some electronics like a 27" monitor, stuff I don't want to ship with me, but rather sell and then buy againt there.

I don't speak Slovene so it's really hard for me to google search, but once i've got a good site, I can read it. So, what are the best options for ordering stuff like that? Or is it better (chearper) to just go to a store? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Seems to Side With Russia in Comments on Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and Poroshenko discuss the Donbas and future cooperation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What 2560x1440 monitor should i buy to go with a mid-2010 MBP running sierra 10.12.3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any that "just work"? Right now I have a Dell U2713HM which worked fine with my MBP running 10.9.5, but which has stopped working. Since I'm actually going to be moving soon, I can sell it and buy a replacement. But what should I get? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have a mid-2010 MBP and a DELL U2713HM monitor using a Mini-DP - DP cable, but can't get 2560x1440 resolution. Is anyone using this set-up with no issue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, how? 

I just updated to Sierra from 10.9.5 where all worked with no problem after the patch-edid.rb fix.

One major problem to the switchresx solution is that I cannot access the terminal from safe mode, as for some @# ! reason, the trackpad and double-click refuse to work there and I cannot get to the menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just updated to Sierra. What is the deal with 2560x1440 monitors? Has Apple *still* not fixed this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the searches I've found point to the early Sierra releases, but I just installed 10.12.3 and my Dell U2713HM refuses to move from 1920x1080 to 2560x1440. 

Has the problem before with Mavericks, and it fixed with the "patch-edid.rb" installed in the home directory and setting the Dell to disable DDC/CI.

but this time none of that seems to be working. 

EDIT: Just to add that of course I backed up 10.9.5 before upgrading and so, rebooted on that to see if all was well. It was. 10.9.5 sees the monitor fine. 10.12.3 - does not.

Here's the funny part. When I rebooted back to my installed SSD with 10.12.3, I had left the monitor plugged in. And when it came up at 1080p *again*, I went to system prefs/displays to try to change and it would not toggled between "default for display" and "Scaled" at first, and then when it did scaled showed "2560x1440" - I swear it did - but the selection did not hold, it automatically went to the radio button "default for display", flickered, and when I went back to "scaled", 2560x1440 could not be seen.

EDIT: Did it again! don't know how - but here is proof: http://imgur.com/a/T8OmY As soon as I selected 2560x1440 though the window changed to giving NO resolutions at all. Unplugged the monitor and plugged it back in and back to step one. Seriously, why has Apple not fixed this?

Meanwhile, I am unable to access Utilities -  Terminal in safe mode, as the track pad refuses to respond. I even learned that in normal operations Control+F2 automatically wakes the menu and arrow keys can be used to navigate, but this appears to not be the case in safe more. Can anyone comment on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very interesting Tweet re Trump "distractions" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Apple make a jumbo tilting touch *screen* like the Surface Studio to hook up to an MBP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they are apparently getting out of screens, and macOS would have to be rewritten for that. But am I that insane to wish one might come on the market within five years? Am I alone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What countries' citizens can make short visa-free trips to Belarus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article ( http://www.zautra.by/art.php?sn_nid=23610 ) talks about visa-free entry for a lot of countries for short stays.

     80 ,  ,        .       :           .

Where can I learn more? Where is an official publication about this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney talks Trump, Secretary of State cabinet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Written sign language - has it ever happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 10:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any sign language communitites ever developed writing based on their sign language? Rather than based on the alphabet/writing systems of the spoken language prevalent in their locale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: Russia tests anti-satellite weapon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>        </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 10:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine: Five Troops Killed In Clashes With Separatists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I listen to news on-line in Slovenian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 09:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For better language practice. Moslty, I am interested in world news because that will be easier to understand (comparing to world news in other languages) but any TV is good, too. 

EDIT: Thanks to all. All these links are going to be a great help.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How have 'new archaeological sources' discovered over the past 30 years changed how we understand late antique and early medieval social systems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prompted by this comment https://np.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5hl7ba/its_1900_or_so_and_im_a_proper_accredited/db29jbx/ and this particular sentence:

the past three decades have witnessed an explosion of new archaeological sources, and this has totally changed how we understand late antique / early medieval infrastructure, mobility, and lots of other aspects of social systems.

First, what are these sources? How were they discovered?
And how and what "totally changed"

What are specific (and hopefully eye-opening / colourful?) examples of "used to believe this" while "now we believe this"?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia behind hack on German parliament, paper reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia behind hack on German parliament, paper reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with Piontkovskiy where he mentions Trump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 11:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to write an Apple script to automatically send a screen-shot to imgur? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never even used an apple-script, so I don't know. Can anyone say if it is possible and if so, kind of explain how?

Ideally I'd like a small pop-up window to ask, "Send this screen shot to imgur?" or some global hot-key that would do it automatically, but i'd like to be able to use the shift+command+4 to capture a certain part of the screen, too.

have no idea if this would work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bannon as a problem for Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dawned on me, and I wonder if I'm just way out there, or this is a real risk. 

the issue:

Bannon will continue to have Trump's ear in "strategy" and he is also know as a far-right racist. What are the chances that he will bend Trump's ear to convince him to meet regularly with a lot of far-right European politicians a la Le Pen? And that by letting these people be seen with the US president as a matter of fact, give them legitimacy and really further their prospects at home back in Europe?

Trump knows nothing about geopolitics and say Bannon invites a lot of euro-sceptic MPs to the White House, perhaps even including some that visit Crimea on a regular basis, what is that going to mean for Europea and by extension, Ukraine?

I'm not 100% on board with the idea that Russia is using Bannon directly, but goddam if they aren't happy right now.

And does a Trump/Zhirinovskiy photo op seem crazy now or possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How exactly did the elite during 1848 spring of nations decipher what was happening to their establishment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask this in light of the current US election, Brexit, and other political events which often cite racism as the underlying reason, but it seems more and more to be an anti-establishment movement (perhaps poorly articulated by the people moving it who appear to be low-educated).

So, my question is this, if the 1848 spring of nations was anti-establishment as I think it was, how did the elite reason/explain it in their minds? Did they see it immediately as anti-them, or did they think there was some other unaddressed reason - I don't know "outside forces" or something?

I mean in Europe and as it was happening and immediately after. 

Side question - are there other, similar anti-establishment "revolutions" in world history in any place or time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] Mods, can we get some flairs in here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 05:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I would like to see a [personal story] flair because I want to read more personal anecdotes than meltdown posts from T_D (though a lot of those are fun, too). 

Other possibilities

[T_D melt] for comments posts from T_D

[alt-right] for meltdowns as articles/op-eds from alt-right media.

[pundit melts] Like if Hannity or some other "main stream" media figure has a meltdown 

[Trump family] for Trump jr melting down.

[Trump Himself] for the 3am tweets once he gets his Twitter back.

What do you all think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did it become a thing for countries to receieve refugees to help them out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 11:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose there was some kind of refugee programs that might have been unofficial or non-governmental - maybe church based? - before immigration laws became a big deal? Was there some kind of transition from that to a more government-sponsored/controlled and legal implementation?

I'm obviously thinking about the more recent times say post Enlightenment, but anything along the same lines that predates that is interesting too! Are there any good stories from antiquity or was refugee aid not really a thing back then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOS VENTILOS - how popular are they? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peugeot fends off monsters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poroshenko: Ukraine will not implement the political portion of "Minsk" before the security package </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 12:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] Do historians ever do anything in the present day to help later historians understand their world in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean time capsules are a thing, but is there anything historians do to leave behind a good, reliable idea of what was (is) happening in their present world?

Like is anyone collating sources on this year's presidential election, or are hisotrians just leaving it up to journalists to record it, and to future historians to determine what sources are good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the Panama Canal come about? Specifically, did academic papers prior to the project impact it's "political viability"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 12:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, what led to the Panama Canal? Was it more a solution for trade or military projection? What were seen at the time as its pros and cons? (prior to actually beginning to build or "in the discussion stage") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "UPVOTE" is ORANGE, the "DOWNVOTE" is BLUE. NUFF SAID. REKT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 17:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did a cyclops deal with the lack of depth vision due to his having only one eye? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, what makes a lack of depth vision a viable option in the thread of evolution?

EDIT: This has been of immense help! I think we are really onto something with the travel in pairs, echolocation and lasers angle.

Has anyone read any journals commenting specifically on cyclops travelling in pairs that may allude to devastion likely the results of lasers that was evidence in their trail?

I'm especially keen to know if there are any ancient Greek epics that might indirectly support this thesis, especially if the stories in those epics note that these roaming laser-wielding cyclops pairs were as active at night as in the day.

Point for discussion - do you think these "pairs" might have been actually threes, because then they could triangulate? And if you think this hypothesis plausible, what does that tell us about Cyclops' mating habits?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sierra screen shot request of Calendar... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly, I'm way behind on updating my OS. So, I have a kind of strange - but very easy - request. Could some kind soul who has a 2560x1440 monitor post an imgur of a screen shot of a maximized window (not full screen, but maximized) of how the Calendar looks in Sierra. I've google image searched but not found exactly that and kind of need one for some mock-ups 

If the kind soul is really super kind, I'd love shots in year, month week and day views, but just the month would be enough. Also, showing the sidebar on the left (can't remember if it slides to hidden or not, but I need to see that). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> East Ukraine: Leaked E-mails Show Correspondence Between Moscow and Separatists [in German] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Websites for children - reading level 4-5 years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I'm looking for any websites that have little stories for children aged 4-5. Things like fairy tales, etc. for my own reading comprehension. Also, any websites where you can download pdfs of schoolbooks for Slovene-speaking children to learn english, probably a little older, say children 7-8 years old.

Anyone know of any? Thanks!

EDIT: I'm loving these links below; they are going to be so helpful! Now, second question, are there any places where I can read along with audio/visual? (I'm giong through the links below, maybe some of them have that, but I'm too excited to not ask anyhow!)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   ? 

EDIT:    ,        ,      .

  

EDIT 2:  ,  - 

 24 minutes ago 5.6 magnitude, 88 km depth
Nereju Mic, Vrancea, Romania 

   /u/TechPriest06     !

  today's earthquakes http://earthquaketrack.com/recent

 - http://i.imgur.com/yAW6gCb.png

  ( /u/iBaraban )- http://ds.iris.edu/ds/nodes/dmc/tools/event/5194232

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Trump campaign chair steps down after her unhinged rant blaming Obama for racism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A big, red house" sounds better than "A red, big house" Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 10:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is the case, but cannot remember why or what the phenomenon is called.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the 538 election forecast page load so slow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear, it's always got to hang Firefox (48.0.1 on a MBP running 10.9.5) for like a second and a half, before it loads completely. 

Drives me nuts, but maybe you guys can tell why exactly it does that?

http://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2016-election-forecast/#now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on The Forgetting Moon by Brian Lee Durfee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 09:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, Apple: The iPhone 7 camera is not better than Samsung's Galaxy S7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind the scenes of Azov. [a fairly balanced review of what Azov is up to politically] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 09:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How different is Slovenian dialect spoken in Koper/Piran from the Ljubljana dialect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title has pretty much the entire question. I'm just interested to know what quirky traits the Koper/Piran dialect might have that sets it apart. Is there a ton of Italian influence not found in regular Slovenian? Or what else? Examples?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polish Defence Minister: The goal of Russia's actions was to see the Tu-154M crash near Smolensk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>      11-17 ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 09:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  -   -?   ?          ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Foreign Ministry threatens Ukraine and the West for "the deaths of Russian servicemen" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin accuses authorites in Ukraine of terror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Russia's] FSB accuses Ukraine of attacking Crimea and the death of a Russian serviceman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Joocemann explains confidence in one single line you'll never forget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [LPR leader] Plotnitskiy's vehicle blown up in Luhansk [Plotnitskiy in critical condition] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 10:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine, Westinghouse agree construction of new nuclear fuel plant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 14:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the terrorists brag on the Internet about new arms from Russia [original title] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 09:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
