<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if this is a joke. No shit a movie that takes place in dreams uses dream sequences in the trailer. That's the point of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Salvation.

The fucking trailer ruined what could have been a cool plot twist, but instead we got 45 minutes of having to watch lies, then we still saw a big reveal anyway.

 HE'S A ROBOT. GUYS, THIS MAN IS A ROBOT. A ROBOT, THIS MAN IS. HE IS A ROBOT LIKE THE TERMINATORS. DID WE MENTION HE IS A ROBOT? BECAUSE HE IS (A ROBOT, THAT IS).

- Actual line from the movie's trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sunk cost fallacy applies to time, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we really need more Leto Joker though? I mean I disliked the movie, don't get me wrong, but I think it was better off with less Joker, because holy shit that was terrible, plus he didn't have much to do with the plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  20 zombies bust through window towards them

 "We should depart now!"

Love me some translated dialogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donnie Darko is fucking awesome and now I have to watch it again, damn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, not really. Most comic book movies I've seen aren't very faithful to the comics. Not saying that's a good or bad thing, it's just true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 08:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand this. Yes, he hit his wife. You know who else hit their wife? Reed Richards, but no one cares because he's a more well known character.

Not that that makes it more understandable, but the double standard pisses me off. What does make it understandable, is the context of the **single time** he hit his wife. He was under a lot of pressure and crazy for a while, and she wouldn't leave him alone. And, immediately after he hit her, he apologized profusely and hugged her. And it never happened again.

Hell, Jim Shooter (I think) even said Pym's reputation as a wife beater was stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 08:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a lot of comics and, before the movie, I'd only heard the name a couple times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 03:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you telling me I've been reading 440 pages of exposition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 09:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm like 5/6ths of the way through the book right now and I'm loving it, but it seems like nothing is happening. Its just looking at these people's lives as things happen to them, with no overarching plot or anything.

Its cool, but I thought it was supposed to be about feuding brothers or families or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 09:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading comprehension. Learn it, use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2euphoric2furious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you got that I was being sarcastic, fuck those guys. Tears of the Sun and Shooter are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha fuck you for liking a movie that isn't what you're supposed to like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 06:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artist is Chris (Simpsons artist) for anyone curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 05:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the same as a role model.

Plus if its about looks and not characterization, then why would it matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 05:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are poison rounds so good with Abe and Crow? Curious because Abe is my main. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it probably just left people with negative feelings towards Joker and Harley and WB definitely didn't want that.

God forbid people dislike the villain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of a fucking problem if girls are making her a role model regardless of abuse or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it I was gonna start saving $6 a month and you ruined it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam Rockwell was the only part of the movie I liked.

"I'd love to, honey, but I'm in the middle of a very
awkward exchange with our realtor right now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 07:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would probably be better off finding it online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 07:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I was gonna ask this girl out but then my boss was like hey you're my bitch now, work later and I was like I am powerless to you so I did and then I missed the chance and I'm just gonna ask tomorrow but I was all set to do it today goddamn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 07:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judd Apatow has made some pretty good stuff since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched it the other day too. God I loved that movie more that I thought I would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide Squad: ~~Movie Edition~~ Rebirth

I'm also considering dropping the Flash. I was hoping for some Barry/Wally moments but instead its just YOU GET THE SPEEDFORCE, YOU GET THE SPEEDFORCE, AND YOU GET THE SPEEDFORCE, EVERYONE GETS THE SPEEDFORCE! and that's just kinda boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 05:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm alone on this, but that's my favorite HQ costume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 05:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My headcanon is that all the cops in the games are either clones or cyborgs.

The advantage is it makes more sense as to why they are so durable but dumb, why there are so many, and why they all look and sound the same. It also makes me feel less evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you care? This guy's a dick, and its not like anyone's doing anything about this anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I want a recording.

The parts I could hear were hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 06:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's what I mean. He explains it in his comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 06:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care if you people say this isn't real it fucking murdered my sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 06:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or...you could read the top comment and find out how it was actually found out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree its not cool to share that info, but Brock did a MTV Cribs-style thing where you can see where he lives if you know the area. I don't think he's *too* concerned about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a good recording of Isaac Brock's Moda Center story from the Modest Mouse show on Sunday night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 19:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was hilarious and I wanna hear it again, but I can't find it on YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, why start making good movies now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow comedy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to play the game with my friends.

*But you can play with your friends and be a mon-*

No, shut up. Of course I can do that. I can also play Battlefield with them and join the opposite team. But why would I do that? I want to play *with* them, not against them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You use the word literally a lot and un-necessarily.

Anyway the justification for both characters is proof that they don't fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just watched Dr. Strangelove for the first time and have a couple questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Kids these days, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah because kids in the past never killed themselves due to bullying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, pretty sure its Alex Maleev. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off, you know that's not the reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's even two Wally Wests now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 19:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago I noticed clicking whenever I moved my jaw. Didn't do anything about it.

Fast forward a couple months, and I'm at a friend's birthday party, paintball. We'd taken a break for lunch, and I opened wide, put a burger in my mouth...and couldn't bite. People were asking me why I was taking so long to take a bite, but I couldn't respond. I just held the burger partly inside my mouth and panicked. For a solid minute I couldn't do anything.

Finally my jaw relented and I got it to move. I took tiny biyes of everything for weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 09:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Empire Strikes Back


That movie has it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 09:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the series got really fuckin weird after the second movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 22:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let them know what major cunts they are, and find new friends who don't suck.

Depending on where you are in Oregon, you could hang out with my friends and I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 21:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What I want is more important than what you want.

Fuck off. I don't care about custom characters but its not all about what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 06:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the whole "hunt down thus race of people (synths)" thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 07:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the food at the theater is desert food! You can't eat your popcorn before your meat! How can you have any popcorn if you don't eat your meat?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 07:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought it was a weird but acceptable transition.

Then I realized the pictures are ordered fucking idiotically and I feel bad for OPs parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 07:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of something you might see on /r/Ambien. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What edition of Eraserhead should get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 06:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've really been wanting to watch this movie for a long time (I haven't seen it yet so please dont tell me anything about the movie itself) and normally if I want to see a movie I'll rent it but I know I'm gonna end up buying this one anyway. Thing is, even used copies on Amazon are pretty expensive, so I figured I might as well just buy the best version. I'm guessing it's the Criterion one? DVD only, please, no Blu-rays for me right now.

Also, can anyone tell me what Eraserhead 2000 is? I keep seeing copies of it online but I don't know what it is.

Edit: SHIT HOW DO I FLAIR ON MOBILE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 03:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about m8? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 03:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty heavily hinted at that Abe has a crush on her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 20:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thank you so much! That clears up a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 20:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you're gonna get shit on for this but its true. Not that that's a wholly bad thing because we could use a bit more diversity but it is an odd trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 05:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you're offering...

What the hell did Cyclops do to piss everyone off so much? Where did the mists come from? Is there an explanation for why it kills mutants or is it just that way? How are huge clouds of visible gas so dangerous? I feel like everyone knows about them by now and it would be simple enough to track them so mutants could just hide/go away until it passes. And do we know how many X-Men/mutants are left? I feel like there's only supposed to be a relative few, but it seems like there's the same amount as before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone give me info on how to prevent muscle loss? Like say I can't go to the gym for the month for some reason, can I just do light bodyweight stuff to keep my muscles working? Or do I need to push myself all the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For your health.

https://66.media.tumblr.com/4d8759bf73609b0004be8d62a494cf1e/tumblr_mto1lq2AA21qmk3pno1_500.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's a dude I guess I'm gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's only like one audiobook of the Catcher in the Rye that I've ever found and its clearly read by an old man with an annoying voice. I struggled to enjoy the book myself after listening to that recording because I read it in that guy's voice and it just pissed me off. I finally got rid of that though, and now I love the book.

Also, I never read the Star Wars Legends book *Death Troopers* and I imagine I wouldn't enjoy it very much if I had read it. But the audiobook was actually really creepy, listening at night while really tired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for making a decent post about this.

Most of the "complex" stuff people are citing are either

A) slightly nuanced things you should be able to figure out in a few matches, as with most games, or

B) meta-game bullshit than is complex in every game.

Fuck off, everyone. Sure, its a bit more complicated than Call of Duty 19 but don't act like we're playing Age of Empires 2 or Street  Fighter or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I would be honored to get a bag of shit mailed to me from Ditko.

He seems like such a curmudgeon and I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really interested in this because I just read like 40 issues of Inhumans and X-Men in the past week and I have no idea what's going on because I never really followed either before, but I hope Kuder's art isn't like that on the interiors.

It's so...bland, and almost Dillon-like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK THAT MOVIE

I'm going to try to keep this brief, but the thing that I hated most about that movie (other than existing and being what it is) was the thing the dumbass little kid says at the beginning. He says (and this is meant to be a serious fact) that there are more people alive now than there are dead people.

Who thought that would be good to put in the movie? Did someone just make that up and no one fact checked it? It only came out a few years ago, the internet was there for that very reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't, mostly.

Source: Am 18. I know three other guys around my age who read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if I see a movie that looks interesting, I look it up on IMDB. The extra time is worth not reading the smug and not even slightly funny descriptions, because most of the time they make me think the movie is going to be about something else anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked that movie unironically.

*Tear me a new one.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 06:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's handy. Two books is better than four or five. Thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 09:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do, thanks for checking though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 08:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any word on a collected edition of Darth Vader? I've been meaning to get into it but I'd rather get an omnibus than multiple trades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't voiced by Lithgow was he?

I'd be able to tolerate the terrible animation if he was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't like the 4th but the "do the roar" thing is still hilarious to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if that's a joke but I could kinda see it.

Also, I doubt they would bring the character into a series that kind of caters to families, but his voice and past would make him a really good fit for Slapstick in my mind. If Slapstick's too dark for a movie, put him in a Netflix show.

If neither of those work, he could be an Inhuman. Doesn't matter which, there's a fuckin million of them now anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I could care less. The only example I could think of that would matter is if she was stereotypically upper class and treated other people poorly because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick with it, and you'll be glad you did. It's one of those classic story arcs that you'll start seeing everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  literally hundreds of millions

That's not how you use that word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 06:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a key point of the series though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 04:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks, I might look into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 04:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its because your comment made you sound like a dick (I don't know if you meant you are downvoting him or what, but I think that's how most people took it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 06:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do volunteers do at the Gilbert House? That sounds interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 05:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you have one thing in common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 05:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jay from It Follows has to be first, but the sister from Friday the Thirteeth Part IV is up there, along with Sidney from Scream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 05:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted Ash in a Mortal Kombat game. He'd fit in well and they like to do horror movie crossovers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 04:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I liked Rescue a lot, and Nest was a good change of pace. I never tried Defend, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if that's always true. For example, when your flamethrower runs out as Hyde, the damage from your minigun isn't worth the time it takes to switch back to flamethrower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 09:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 09:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about starting to play assault and when I played months ago, Torvald seemed really good, but no one's mentioned him yet.

Has he gotten worse (relatively) or was I just wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 05:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I should pay better attention because I never noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 05:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn that art is gorgeous.

Anyone have any good Deadman arcs I should read in preparation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that seems kind of pointless. Why not just say how many SKs?

Anyway, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 02:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how most games like this work. Dirty bomb has more characters and I think it changes every two weeks, plus the free rotation is only 3 characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 02:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I think the free rotation should give you a good idea. After all, there's not so many characters and you get 5 at once. Just save keys for a little while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 02:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask what the crates are? I got two and I don't know what they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just want to say I love you, TRS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 02:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to play Evolve a bit on Xbox, but I quit because there were never enough players where I wouldn't have to wait forever for a match. Now, its free on Steam, and I can play a match with friends, and if they aren't online, I can play with randos without having to wait forever (usually).

You guys seem to actually give a shit about the quality of the game (a patch made with player input just a few days after the game came out), own up to mistakes (I saw one of the devs apologizing to a guy who got a bit screwed over by the patch that broke his game), and are working on making the game playable before monetizing it, unlike just about every other beta/early access game on Steam. All this shows a lot of integrity, which I don't see a lot of in the industry lately.

I just wanted to say thanks, and I'm excited to see where the game goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the fuck are your eyebrows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted to like this movie when I watched it a few months ago. Not a fan of Spike Lee but it seemed like it would be good.


**Spoilers ahead**


But damn it, I can't. It was good until the climax. Everyone riots and destroys the pizzeria. Turturro's character was a shithead, yeah, but why was his family's business destroyed? It makes no sense.

My biggest problem with the movie though, is that, when asked whether the destruction of the restaurant was warranted or not, Lee said it doesn't matter either way, in the wake of Radio Rakeem's death. What? Yeah, it sucks, but does that mean another wrongdoing is now okay? Of course it doesn't. The message of the movie is really shitty and distracts from the enjoyable aspects of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 04:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin brutal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no ur dumb obvisly its a very plot simple about driving somewhere then coming back u dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I hate these questions. "Let's simplify this complex movie down to the very basic premise and make it seem silly with very little effort, despite the fact that this can be done with literally 95% of stories."

It's fuckin terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
