<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3505</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in or near a city of 50K or more you should be able to get a lot of what you want for free OTA with an antenna. Use TVFool.com to find out what is receivable in your area.

See the /r/ota subreddit to inform your antenna decision. If you use a DVR you can watch what you want, when you want, and skip the commercials.

Many of us no longer think in terms of channels. We focus on on specific content and watch via streaming-on-demand or from our DVR as our interests lead us. 

If you add a set top box (STB) like a Roku you watch a lot of interesting content for free or a modest fee. The Roku now has over 2500 "channels" of content. Among all that you should be able to find 20-30 that interest you or members of your household.

If you absolutely need cable-like programming, you can subscribe to Sling TV for $20/month and get a lot of the more popular channels streamed through your Roku or other STB.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 06:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it! Thanks.

I found I had to execute the key sequence as quickly as possible to get things to work. My prior attempts were rather leisurely.

For anyone interested I found a web page posting a number of different hidden screen access codes for various functions. http://streamfree.tv/roku/roku-secret-screens/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 04:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Roku XS   a Roku XD. Both have the occasional freeze-up problem. I tried this sequence on both   did not get to any special screen. I'm guessing that I'm not doing it right.

Just to be clear, is
the forward button the one labeled 
and the backward button is labeled 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 02:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See the related item I posted here. Vice will also be available for streaming via Roku   other STBs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 02:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly how much content will be available via Roku   other STBs without a cable/satellite subscription authorization is a bit obscure in this article. Once things come on line it should be clearer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 22:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! I have a Hauppauge WinTV-HVR-1250 and was not aware of this very useful software. I see I can download the latest version for free   use it with my tuner card. http://hauppauge.lightpath.net/software/utils/hcwsigmonsetup_33310.exe

"The WinTV Signal Strength Monitor displays the relative strength of the digital signal on the channel you are tuned to. It will show the Signal to Noise ratio, the number of Received Errors and the number of Uncorrectable errors."

It will work with ATSC and QAM digital TV channels on most Hauppauge digital TV tuner boards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 11:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ported my home phone (VoIP over Comcast broadband) from my very glitchy NetTalk service to Ooma. The process through Ooma was fairly simple, but it took NetTalk about a week to get it done. When completed, everything worked great. I really like Ooma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 21:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The complete Comcast list is here: http://mydeviceinfo.xfinity.com/

I'm using an older Motorola SB6121. Works fine. If it failed   I had to replace it I would probably go with the latest   faster Motorola Model MB7220. Currently $80 on Amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 04:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said, seems like something used for microwave or industrial communications. Could be for signal backhaul in a private phone or industrial application like dealing with a fleet of taxi cabs or cement trucks.

Value? If they are made of aluminum you should be able to sell them for scrap.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 01:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The frequencies listed on the label are way above US broadcast frequencies. This seems like something used for microwave or industrial communications. What you have is not a TV antenna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 23:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should post physical measurements for the device: length, width at widest point, etc. Also any manufacturer's label or brand name.  Hard to conclude much without that info, but it does not look like a TV antenna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You intend to "Save video from an OTA antenna feed plugged directly into the machine" but you don't have a tuner in your system build.

Recording OTA is a great way to get content, but you should check local availability (TVFool.com) if you haven't already done so.

Also, I agree with Tessaray. You should consider a dedicated DVR like Tablo. Great way to manage   distribute OTA stuff around your home.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 00:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a big iTunes fan, but that is one way to get AVexcel podcasts. 

Here is a link explaining how to add iTunes podcast capability to a Roku.

http://www.groovypost.com/howto/itunes-podcasts-channel-roku/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airs on PBS this evening, February 24th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airs on PBS this evening, February 24th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airs on PBS this evening, February 24th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airs on PBS this evening, February 24th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 06:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no getting around the high latency when using geostationary satellites. Physics. Phone conversations would be difficult at best. 

But many application are not much affected by latency. For instance uploading or downloading files, streaming video, web surfing, texting, email, etc.

Spectrum could be used very efficiently by relying on frequencies in Ka band or above and having lots of spot beams. The same frequencies could be used over   over (similar to cell phones) with good design of the spot beam configuration. A satellite with a CONUS slot could have a combined downlink footprint with coast-to-coast coverage all the way from the Yukon to the Yucatan.  

The data cap issue is a separate concern. That may be a function of the power generation capacity of orbital assets and the cost of getting some very big   expensive satellites into orbit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a deal like that back when there was still subscription programming on C-band satellite. I think it was "pick any 15 channels for $20/month". Additional (non-premium) selections were $2/month each. If you paid for an entire year at a time you got one month free. Not a bad deal. Of course, you had to have several thousand dollars worth of satellite TVRO equipment to be able to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quoting the article:  if people have a Picasa account, "the easiest way to still access, modify and share most of that content is to log into Google Photos, and all of your photos and videos will already be there."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 21:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could use a Roku 1.  It has an AV composite out option.

https://www.roku.com/products/roku-1

However, since it sounds like your TV only has a coax rf input, you will need to run the Roku output through a modulator to give you a channel 3 or 4 signal. You can still find rf modulators on sale at many places. Here is one from Amazon.

http://www.amazon.com/RCA-Compact-RF-Modulator-CRF907R/dp/B0014KKV7W/ref=sr_1_2?s=electronics ie=UTF8 qid=1455826721 sr=1-2 keywords=tv+modulator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 07:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that there is a lot of terrific HD science/nature/history long-form programming available for streaming from PBS. For free. I watch with the PBS app on my Roku. Also available on other streaming devices   at PBS.org. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 23:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBSN is definitely worth a try. I watch it on my Roku. Great picture, decent content, and you can't beat free.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note that Windows 10 folks could always watch Hulu in a browser. This just adds a bit of Live Tiles bling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a long discussion of 5G here:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/5G
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me as one of those who watches CBS via an antenna. I DVR my shows   skip the commercials when I watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 08:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that. I didn't encounter a paywall when I accessed the story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 06:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an extra charge for retransmission rights for signals that are broadcast free to air. These are signals that many of us can   do get for free by using an antenna.

One potential problem with retran fees is that they introduce a perverse incentive for broadcasters. If they run the transmitter at the lowest power allowed by their license they can reduce operating costs and the propagation of the broadcast signal. That might cause the station to be unwatchable for many households in the DMA. If they get cable so they can watch the station they will now be paying an extra $60/year for the "free" signal. That money goes directly to the broadcasters   their networks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful news! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 02:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rude name-calling is not an explanation of your objections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 02:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phillip Swann has been writing about broadcasting, television, cable   satellite for at least 15 years. (That's how long I have been reading his various analyses   predictions.) 

You can read about his qualifications here:
http://www.tvpredictions.com/about.html

The fact that you don't like or agree with content does not automatically make it a scam.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As noted in the article, most of the money goes to three large companies.

CenturyLink Inc. will receive the most CAF II money in the state, $330 million, or $55 million per year, for projects aimed at reaching about 129,000 locations  which typically are households or businesses.

Frontier Communications will get $186 million, or $31 million per year, for 76,000 locations.

AT T Inc. will get $54 million, or $9 million per year, for 24,000 locations.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As noted in the article, most of the money goes to three large companies.

CenturyLink Inc. will receive the most CAF II money in the state, $330 million, or $55 million per year, for projects aimed at reaching about 129,000 locations  which typically are households or businesses.

Frontier Communications will get $186 million, or $31 million per year, for 76,000 locations.

AT T Inc. will get $54 million, or $9 million per year, for 24,000 locations.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As noted in the article, most of the money goes to three large companies.

CenturyLink Inc. will receive the most CAF II money in the state, $330 million, or $55 million per year, for projects aimed at reaching about 129,000 locations  which typically are households or businesses.

Frontier Communications will get $186 million, or $31 million per year, for 76,000 locations.

AT T Inc. will get $54 million, or $9 million per year, for 24,000 locations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 08:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly seems like an ad to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 01:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon has take the position that the Net Neutrality rules do not apply to their actions. So far, no response from the FCC.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a deal like that for a year. This is how Comcast has been trying to keep their TV subscriber stats from eroding further. They make you an offer you can't refuse.

After a year I returned my cable box   remote, still in the shrink wrap   unopened. I now have Comcast broadband   "phone service" for less than the cost of broadband alone. I declined to rent the special cable modem necessary to actually get Comcast phone service. I continue with my regular Ooma voip service.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree; 4K on a laptop is kind of silly.

I currently use VLC   like it. I'll have to check out potplayer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 08:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely no mirrors!

Thanks for the photo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 01:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This item is listed on Amazon as: "Currently unavailable. We don't know when or if this item will be back in stock." 

My guess is that Amazon pulled it because of all the seemingly illegal program content offered for free in the product description. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 23:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My January bill has a lengthy privacy policy statement. My bill for December has a detailed list of services offered   prices. It states that the disclosure is required by federal rules. 

Interestingly, for most of the broadband tiers Comcast does not list any information about speeds or data caps.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 20:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would avoid Movietvpix.

http://www.scamadviser.com/check-website/movietvpix.com

The phone number is a Panamanian VoIP service provided by an anonymizing business. 

[Alert Result] The owner of the website is using a service to hide their identity
[Alert Result] This website is 197 Days old
[Alert Result] The website expected life (365 days) is relatively short.

Analysis Details:-
Although this website appears to be based in Netherlands there are other countries involved and you should review this information carefully and decide if it is as you expect.

This site is using an anonymous service - which prevents us from identifying the site owner. 

The website has been newly registered with a short life expectancy, which follows the pattern used by many fraudulent and fake selling websites. Please be vigilant and take extra care before providing any payment information.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 11:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will need an antenna   a converter box. You can find a variety of converters on offer at Amazon. Search for "Analog-to-Digital (DTV) Converters".

Please post a link to your TV Fool report so that folks can advise you about an appropriate antenna.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was entertained, but there are many plot problems. For starters, how could there be enough water and food in the local environment to support a human population of that size? The top of a mountain in Appalachia is not water rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 08:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any business needs at least 2 backup copies of data held locally, and another copy stored off-site. You are hedging the possibility of burglary, fire, tornado, hurricane etc., any of which could destroy the original and local backups. Cloud services are one way to do off-site storage. (In this case it was quite expensive.)

Myself, I take that third copy on a 4TB drive and put it in a safe deposit box at a local bank. Every few weeks I swap out with a more recent copy and recycle the one I remove from the vault.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 08:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My read was $158 for the 60 GB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 02:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clubland_TV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FCC application identifies the following cities as potential sites for the service: Boston, NYC, Washington D.C., LA, San Francisco, Dallas, Houston, Philadelphia, Detroit, Atlanta, Miami, Minneapolis-St. Paul, Seattle, Denver, and Chicago.

https://apps.fcc.gov/oetcf/els/reports/442_Print.cfm?mode=current application_seq=69226 license_seq=69930
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FCC application identifies the following cities as potential sites for the service: Boston, NYC, Washington D.C., LA, San Francisco, Dallas, Houston, Philadelphia, Detroit, Atlanta, Miami, Minneapolis-St. Paul, Seattle, Denver, and Chicago.

https://apps.fcc.gov/oetcf/els/reports/442_Print.cfm?mode=current application_seq=69226 license_seq=69930
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure the numbers reflect some behind the scenes manipulation. I used to have a Comcast broadband subscription that included basic cable + broadband for less than the cost of broadband by itself. I had no TV hooked up to cable, but Comcast got to count me as a video subscriber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the tone of this article's title, but the data are of interest. Perhaps the ability of TWC subscribers to dump their cable box and use a Roku might be one of the reasons for the subscriber gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the tone of this article's title, but the data are of interest. Perhaps the ability of TWC subscribers to dump their cable box and use a Roku might be one of the reasons for the subscriber gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 20:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story is paywalled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good stuff! I really enjoyed the film. Thanks for posting about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 10:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you have Amazon Prime you might want to do your Showtime subscription through Amazon. You would save a few bucks. The Amazon price for Showtime is $9/month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 10:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not be a subscriber at any price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can read all about the Sinclair Broadcast Group here:

http://sbgi.net/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 23:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodwill Houston is a 501(c)3 charitable organization, i.e. not for profit. The same is true of Goodwill Central Texas (Austin) where this program is being implemented. 

The organization has a relatively high rating for efficiency   transparency.

http://www.charitynavigator.org/index.cfm?bay=search.summary orgid=12002#.VXtOoPlVhBc
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 18:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the comments in the r/diy post I found out that the amp is an SMSL Q5; it puts out 50 watts over 2 channels.

http://www.amazon.com/SMSL-Q5-blackQ5-Amplifier-Optical/dp/B00PD49I10
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my take on the situation too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! I love the step by step photos   commentary.

Any idea what kind of amp went into this gizmo?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 01:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to clarify, the Tablo program guide subscription is $5/month or $50/year or $150 lifetime. 

https://www.tablotv.com/tablo-products/tablo-guide-data-subscription/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 23:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key Point: The "or else" only applies to Windows 8. If you have Windows 8.1 you still have well over a year before you need to consider the move to Windows 10. Read the details in the article.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 22:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a listing by satellite   broadcaster of all Ku FTA content for North America. Much of the programming is in languages other than English.

http://www.global-cm.net/US%20KuBAND.pdf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like you can't stream any of their programming unless you live in specific markets.

http://americansportsnet.com/schedule/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 08:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the person building a gaming PC for the living room, but what exactly has your research revealed? New hardware is ALWAYS coming out. What did you find worth waiting for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Multiple TVs can access a single Tablo.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. There is substantial functionality without a paid subscription. It will function much like an old-school VCR. You set the channel   time for each recording.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 23:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $5/month, $150 lifetime fee for the enhanced program guide. The TV programming is without fees. 

For details see
https://www.tablotv.com/tablo-products/tablo-guide-data-subscription/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 22:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news. The Roku app for Yahoo video is still working. All prior content seems to be available.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 22:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uverse is distributed in a hybrid system. AT T has installed "fiber to the pedestal" (very local neighborhood nodes). From there data   phone signals travel over traditional copper wiring, usually less than 1000 feet. The shorter distance over copper allows greater bandwidth than traditional DSL. Here in Houston these neighborhood nodes are about the size of a jukebox and are deployed every other block or so in someone's front yard near the curb. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 04:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could have been worse. At least the files weren't on 8 inch CP/M floppies.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 01:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like your building would be well served by a Master Antenna TV system. This is where one or two antennas are placed at an optimal location on the roof of an apartment building and the signal is distributed by coax cable to all apartments. This is generally an undertaking by the building management group.

You can see an image of such a system here:
http://www.lopol.org/article/master-antenna-tv-system-matv-in-electrical-construction-works

The other obvious alternative would be to sign up for the much-anticipated $25/month cable TV skinny bundle that is supposed to roll out across Canada this year.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 08:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do a Google search for "replace roku remote". Lots of choices for less than $15. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 08:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading between the lines in the article, my guess is that much of the surface of the monolith will contain paid advertising of some sort. This will fund the service and pay millions each year to the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternate url if you hit a paywall.

http://www.chron.com/business/technology/article/Can-you-download-me-now-NY-payphones-become-6731664.php
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please post a link to your TVFool report so we can assess your situation and make appropriate suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Its rather long. Is there a paywall issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 21:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the labor costs to support a la carte will be about the same as what they are now. Much of the process can be automated with back office   customer-facing web software.

The big savings will be in reduced programming fees for content that is currently bundled. For example, in the US ESPN is contractually bundled into almost every cable   satellite package. That is an estimated $7/month ($84/yr) per customer that the cable company has to pay ESPN. In an a la carte world every customer that did not select ESPN would be $7/month less that the cable company has to pay ESPN. I see that as a cost reduction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is it actually costs cable companies more money to provide everybody with 20 channels (or whatever) of their choice than it does to provide all 200 channels to everybody. There is no cost savings involved, so I can never understand why people think a la carte will be cheaper for the average person. 

Why do you say that it would cost more?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 20:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a Roku 2 or 3. Simple, capable and affordable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 08:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your antenna will not stop working in 6 months. It will be fine. The CSR is delusional. You will not need a "box" for your antenna.

You might want to buy a DVR for your antenna channels. You can use it to time shift programs and nuke commercials. But you don't need one to get programming from an antenna.

Read about antennas using the links in the Cordcutter Guide box on the right side of this page.

Run your location through the TVFool.com web site to see what kind of antenna might be required for your area.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 02:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Longmire. Action, suspense and great scenery.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 08:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drive has returned to its $139 price. The sale is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Most folks don't need a connection that fast. I think this rollout is mostly about Comcast marketing   image. Most customers would be fine with a lower speed, lower price and no cap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 06:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Hard streams "free" on Encore. It is also on offer for $3 from the usual streaming rental sources.

There is an Encore channel on Roku; it requires a subscriber authorization, but seems to work quite well on my Roku 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 06:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Hard streams "free" on Encore. It is also on offer for $3 from the usual streaming rental sources.

There is an Encore channel on Roku; it requires a subscriber authorization, but seems to work quite well on my Roku 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find that info in the article either. It is discussed in an earlier post on that site. The DOCSIS 3.1 devices are designed to deliver 1-10 Gb/s over existing cable coax infrastructure. The general expectation is that Comcast will offer at least 1-2 Gb/s service when it rolls out to regular customers. 

http://consumerist.com/2015/07/24/comcast-to-begin-testing-super-fast-cable-broadband-this-year/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 02:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be one situation where you should consider a basic satellite or cable package. That combined with a DVR to skip commercials might be your best option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 05:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't Roku that imposes a subscription requirement. That comes from the Comcast-owned USA Network.

A Roku owner might benefit from the availability:

1) To stream USA Net to a secondary TV that did not have a cable box;

2) To view programming without a cable subscription using a logon credential from a family member.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very interesting   entertaining show. Strongly recommended. The plot kept surprising me (a good thing). 

Also, I can't stop humming the Tina Charles song "I Love To Love". If you've seen the series you know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen the movie version. Those who have seen the movie are posting positive comments.

I am enjoying the serialized Netflix version.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Gangs of Wasseypur series has now been added in the US   Canada. I just put it on my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 20:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Gangs of Wasseypur series has now been added in the US   Canada. I just put it on my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 20:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! Thanks for posting. Unogs is a very useful tool.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you run into a paywall problem try googling "That day I told my husband we could get a new TV" and click on the suggested link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you run into a paywall problem try googling "That day I told my husband we could get a new TV" and click on the suggested link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I deleted the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you run into a paywall problem try googling "That day I told my husband we could get a new TV" and click on the suggested link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 06:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm. I didn't have that experience. Try googling "That day I told my husband we could get a new TV" and click on the suggested link.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 05:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long range, that is a very good idea. But the current bottleneck is mostly a "last mile" problem. Most broadband ISPs are in unregulated monopoly or duopoly markets. There is no functioning free market   no effective competition.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 00:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much, unless you have a friend with cable. 

Hint.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 09:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the pick from The Wirecutter:

http://thewirecutter.com/reviews/best-wi-fi-router/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 06:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first four episodes are streaming at syfy.com. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to know. My logon automatically reflected my previous authentication, so I assumed it was required. I'm glad that's not the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 23:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad but true. However, you can still stream through your web browser from syfy.com. (Requires authenticated logon.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 22:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some excellent background material on the nuts   bolts of the Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 22:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some excellent background material on the nuts   bolts of the Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 08:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two possibilities. (There may be more, but these occurred to me.)

1. They couldn't sell the time at the rate they wanted to charge.

2. The stream was also an international feed to foreign broadcasters who did not want commercials CNN had sold for their own distribution.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 03:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where were they shooting? British Columbia?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 03:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the legality of Comcast's monopoly move has yet to be determined. Aggrieved customers should continue to complain. Since customers cannot respond by taking market action (opting for a competing ISP), legal and political action is the only choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 21:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 21:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.timeinc.com/

Scroll down to the bottom to see a list of the company's iconic brands including Entertainment Weekly, FORTUNE magazine, Money magazine, PEOPLE magazine, Sports Illustrated magazine, This Old House, Time magazine and many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Same thing on my setup. Shows loading screen, then goes back to the Roku home page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 23:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been a fair amount of advertising in the right hand billboard on the Roku home screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 07:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your comment. Those links look great. I will be giving them a try once I finish my home theater PC rebuild, currently in progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to live in Bloomington, In. I know the feeling.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 10:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERY news story on this says that the 8 part series would become available in the US   Canada in the first week of December. So far it hasn't, and there doesn't seem to be any follow-up reporting asking when it will be available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 10:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warner Instant Archive is a service I would love to have. Unfortunately, their $10/month subscription is way too high for me to spend on the somewhat limited selection of films on offer. I may give it a go for a few months to work through the catalog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 10:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turner Classic Movies would be my choice, hands down. I'd want it to be a Netflix-like SVOD subscription that would include (as an option) all the hosted introductions   commentary, plus the films, specials, short subjects and major interstitial items.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not seen it yet, but the critic's reviews have been more positive for season 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 16:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed the police drama River. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 08:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) Comcast paid for a sponsored table at the event; this is not cheap, but it is a deductible business expense.

b) Prior to working at the FCC, Wheeler worked as a venture capitalist and lobbyist for the cable and wireless industry, with positions including President of the National Cable   Telecommunications Association (NCTA) and CEO of the Cellular Telecommunications   Internet Association (CTIA). 
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom_Wheeler
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> River, definitely. One of the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where Yahoo tries to break new ground is with discovery   utility. The app can make suggestions based on things like mood, and it will only recommend content you can access with apps already installed on your device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 11:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't make stuff like this up!

Apparently the departed will still be able to get on line.

This gives new meaning to the notion of bridging the digital divide. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 11:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't make stuff like this up!

Apparently the departed will still be able to get on line.

This gives new meaning to the notion of bridging the digital divide.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 06:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is one of those shocking bureaucratic decisions that defies logic. 

As I understand it, the cable industry got themselves a law which says that it is presumed that cable does business in a competitive environment, so there is no need for local jurisdictions to regulate basic cable. (A Bush era law previously took away the ability of local communities to regulate cable offerings beyond basic.) 

If a community thinks that there is no competition in their market they have to petition the FCC to get permission to regulate the basic service tier by rebutting the presumption of competition. In this instance a community's petition to regulate the local TWC system was denied because the FCC said the community did not offer convincing evidence that there was not adequate competition. 

Kind of takes your breath away!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 05:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Loved the landscape image, hated the Suburu ad in the lower left quarter. I uninstalled the theme. Problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 02:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the movie was a wonderful re-imagining of the classic noir film. The plot, dialog, camera angles and general cinematography had many classic noir elements. And of course, there is the title, the constant wet streets with reflected lights, and the fact that almost all of the movie takes place outside at night. This is a great find for the classic film enthusiast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like you should be able to get a full set of network affiliates. What are your concerns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 23:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those affluent souls who are buying a 4K TV this year and wondering what they will be able to watch, you can add this to the list. Netflix, Amazon, Youtube, DirecTV, (coming soon) 4K Blu Ray, and now Ultraflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 06:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! IE did the trick. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 01:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy a replacement remote from eBay or Amazon for $12 or less.  Google "roku replacement remote". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 01:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, but no joy. Get same brain dead screen. Perhaps the server at cnn.it/roku has a problem.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have installed the channel, but the activation process goes into the Twilight Zone. I've been looking at a spinning graphic   "Authenticating..." for 15 minutes so far.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 03:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respectfully disagree.

The information was presented by a defense professional at a military security conference. The focus was on the vulnerability of US DOD satellite communications assets.

https://crows.org/conventions/2015.html
 
Regardless of who is doing whatever jamming was detected, US military communications satellites seem quite vulnerable.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 01:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One Community Broadband Network resource is put together by the Institute for Local Self Reliance.

http://www.muninetworks.org/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 01:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seeing some interesting coverage from Fox 11 in LA streaming live.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 00:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of bugs in the Pluto offering on Roku. Mine crashes a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 00:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched this film. Two hours of my life I'll never get back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. The headline writer was a bit sloppy. The reference is to 95% of the earth's population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 10:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some cities have set up a pay TV system using an encrypted signal broadcast using OTA bandwidth leased from local stations. They offer Starz, Showtime, and some other standard cable fare. The system uses MP4 compression and you need a special MP4 box hooked up to an antenna to receive   decrypt the signal.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 19:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 08:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered the unit with 4 tuners. I'm looking to simplify my current DVR setup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 08:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a Pluto app for Roku 3   4. It seems to have a lot of bugs that make viewing problematic. 

Keep in mind that you don't need Pluto to watch the 3 channels you named. Those three   many similar channels are available through other Roku applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 19:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roku devices can access over 3,000 streaming services, including the three you named. There are some Black Friday deals for Roku.

Roku is selling a new, limited edition $25 Roku SE player starting on Black Friday through its own site as well as via Amazon.com, Best Buy and Kohls.

Rokus web store will also sell a $80 Roku 3 (usually $100) and a $40 Roku Streaming Stick (usually $50).

Frys will sell the Roku SE for just $19, the Roku 3 for $68 (usually $100) and the Roku streaming stick for $34 (usually $50).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 10:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still used in the high-end units. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 10:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hawks" is a verb, meaning to sell aggressively. 

http://dictionary.cambridge.org/us/dictionary/english/hawk

"hawk" verb [T] (SELL)
 to sell goods in public places by calling out to people: She was hawking flowers at the parking lot exit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 02:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another evil Comcast scheme. They very pointedly exempt this streaming from any data cap. Monopoly power on display once again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news for everyone. One small step to encourage last mile competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news for everyone. One small step to encourage last mile competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 21:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my thought!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 07:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to http://www.titantv.com and select broadcast TV. Enter your zip code when requested and you will see a program guide with all your broadcast stations. There are numerous digital sub-channels in Philadelphia, so you have tons of choices.

To see the broadcast signal quality   where to point your antenna from your location, check out http://tvfool.com/. Just enter your zip code to get a report.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 06:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled "stream Fox News" and that link was an option that did not require cable authentication.

I tried it. It works. Beyond that I don't know anything about it.

I don't watch Fox or any cable news services except BBC, DW, France 24, and Bloomberg. Just trying to be a good citizen   respond to the OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 23:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can watch Fox News streaming live on-line here:

http://vaughnlive.tv/newzviewz
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 23:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to consider this Monoprice HDMI switcher with digital audio output.

http://www.amazon.com/Monoprice-TOSlink-Digital-Coaxial-Channel/dp/B005E2XLI2

Switches 4 HDMI inputs into one HDMI output and also gives an optical audio output from the active input. I use one of these to switch a Roku3, Blueray player, home theater PC,   satellite receiver into a single HDMI going to my TV. The digital audio output goes to my a/v receiver for surround sound.

I really like mine. Works great.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 08:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AcornTV is a favorite of mine. I've been a subscriber for several years. A heck of a deal at $50/yr ($4.17/month), and no commercials. Really interesting content that is hard to find elsewhere.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MHz Choice has been added as an official Roku Channel. You can now add it from the Streaming Channels/Channel Store option in the main menu. No need to do the private channel thing to get it on your Roku.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 21:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This includes a lot of technical details that for some reason were omitted from the Clearleap announcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a Roku app. It works well. The Roku stream seems to have ad breaks without ads; the screen reads "CBS News: We'll Be Right Back". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 20:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting results. I would be more confident about the findings if they had reported the sampling method, sample size, and margin of error. 

From context we can guess that the interviews were conducted in July - August 2015. But we don't know if it is a US national sample or international. Indeed, we don't know for sure that it was a probability sample, nor do we know sample size. It is very hard to interpret survey results without those parameters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 08:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No harm in putting up an antenna to see what you can get. But you may have to go with a minimal satellite or cable subscription if you want network signals.

What kind of Internet access can you get at your location?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who has 3 Rokus hooked up to TVs, I've been interested in this for quite some time. Nice to see progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 00:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that might cause problems with their advertisers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fargo is a favorite of mine too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Weather Nation. Works great on my Rokus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 21:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked my address (and a few other neighborhoods) in Houston and found that I am eligible for "up to" 18 Mbs for only $65/month. Oh, and there is a 250 GB data cap. So instead describing of fiber to the premises, this announcement seems to be mostly "fiber to the press release". It is not a product most folks in these cities can buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 07:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fire up your computer   give this a try. Set it for your local broadcast services or your specific cable company.

http://www.titantv.com/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 01:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a lifetime subscription back in 2005. Still going strong; no regrets.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google is your friend.

http://www.gizmolovers.com/2011/09/01/moca-and-deca-whats-the-difference-or-is-there-one-at-all/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 21:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem was in the headline; it was correct in the story. 

Usually the folks who write the articles are not the ones who dream up the headlines. Most news organizations have a headline specialist who does that for many stories. 

I'm glad you spotted the usage problem. I would have fixed it had I noticed, but of course I didn't see it until your post. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 16:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBS News has fixed the error. It is now "lose". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 22:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Only those with a CNBC cable or satellite subscription login will be able to stream the event live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 08:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like an interesting service; it's always good to have more programming choices.

On the down side: the price is $15/month, I couldn't find any list of exactly what plays are on offer, and they do not support Roku or Amazon Fire streaming devices.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 15:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is only being broadcast in the cities of the 2 teams that are playing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 01:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did Netflix customer service say when you asked them about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 09:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too true! My solution is to record everything and use the DVR to skip all the commercials. Suddenly, you can watch an "hour" of TV in 42 minutes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 08:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried an antenna   a DVR? That works for many in the US.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
