<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists decades-long fears are now here: The collapse of the ice sheet in West Antarctica have begun and is almost certainly unstoppable. A rise in global sea level of at least 10 feet may now be inevitable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 19:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What time will the Pack's draft pick be announced tonight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone know the exact time (or a good estimate)? 

thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOAA Researchers shocked to find global warming induced ocean acidification decades ahead of predictions. See animals are literally dissolving to death in an increasingly corrosive ocean climate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what is the best format to save in WordPad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 18:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using WordPad is a word processor and it gives several ways of saving it. I want to save it so it's most compatible and easy to use with word.

What is the best format to save it in? choices

Rich text

Open office XML

Open document

Text document

text document MS-DOS

Unicode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I get good topsoil delivered to my house for gardening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 18:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just wondering if anybody has a good information about where I can get topsoil for container gardening at my house. I need it delivered to my house, I need maybe about 1 cubic yard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downloaded printer driver but computer doesn't recognize it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded printer driver but computer still doesn't list my printer as an option.

what gives? yes i restarted

windows 7, delll olptiplex 760

canon imageclass printer
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Open Office': totally compatible with Word? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 19:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is Apache's open office completely compatible with MS Word? 

can I transfer word processing docs saved from Word to Open Office? 

thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to find quality wild caught salmon in Madison? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 19:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looking for some good salmon. Must be wild caught, NOT farmed.

I mainly thinking about buying it raw at a grocery store/butcher shop. But if anybody has a good recommendation for a restaurant that serves wild caught salmon that would be great too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grand Budapest Hotel: Big question about Zero's story about how he came to own the hotel. The painting What gives? (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 19:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap and/or sliding scale and/or pro bono counseling/therapy/psychologist in Madison? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 17:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for inexpensive and/or pro bono counseling or therapy or psychological help in the Madison area.

I'm not attached to a school at the moment. 

Subject matter: psychological issues surrounding physical disabilities

Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beep code for my gateway says "motherboard timer not opertational." what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 22:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> posted problem earlier here 

http://www.reddit.com/r/techsupport/comments/20t1w4/computer_keeps_randomly_shutting_down_is_it/

this time when it shut down, listened for beeps 

4 beeps, which according to this site is  "motherboard timer not opertational."

http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:EkZ98lJ_s0sJ:support.gateway.com/s/servers/compo/motherbd/wme859199/wme859199faq2.shtml+ cd=1 hl=en ct=clnk gl=us client=firefox-a

what does that mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer keeps randomly shutting down? Is it overheating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 13:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> randomly my computer just shuts down.

The screen will freeze up, with a sort of strobe flashing. No ability to move mouse or anything, completely frozen.

I wait for a while, started up, and it starts up normally and works fine nothing has been lost nothing has been destroyed.

Seems to only happen after I've had it on for a while. A couple of times a sort of loud beeping has occurred, but not every time.

Is that overheating? What do I do about that? Do I need a new fan or something?

this is a gateway desktop running windows 7, Intel 3.3 GHz

Computer shows My hard disk drive has got 917 GB with 853 free

RAM showing 6 GB, 5.88 usable

 EDIT:

Well now it just did a weird thing. Screen froze up for one second, then the computer rebooted all by itself. I get the black and white screen that says the computer did not shut down normally and gives me three options to reboot

the computer had only been turned on about 10 minutes at that point. And had been shut down all night. I don't think you can overheat in 10 minutes right?

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'Black Stone' that sits in the Kaaba in Mecca: is it the same stone that was put there by Mohammed? Or was it replaced at some point in history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just wondering about the Black Stone at the center of the Kaaba, which for those of you who don't know is the cubic Temple that sits at the very center of Mecca and is the most sacred location in all of Islam

Allegedly there is a stone inside that Temple that was placed there by Mohammed himself

Wondering if the stone that sits in there right now today is the same stone that was put in there by Mohammed?

Re:

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Black_Stone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VA subcontractor fucked up my wheelchair. I'm pissed! what can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 18:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am rated 80% disabled through the VA

I have an electric wheelchair issued by the VA.

The corrupt incompetent dumb ass subcontractor that the VA uses to fix my chair screwed my chair up majorly. Big time . So much so that now it doesn't work and nobody wants to work on it because they don't want get involved in the mass that he made

I'm beyond angry. I went to the patient advocate about the wheelchair so they are working on getting it fixed. Patient advocate says they're going to get on it I don't know if that's can happen or not. The person at the VA in charge of fixing the wheelchairs threatening to not fix it and basically take it away from me. I just went on a 20 minute rant with the patient advocate I'm not really sure if he's worth his salt or not. Quite frankly he didn't really seem like he cared that much.

My question is about the subcontractor. What can I do to make sure he doesn't get any more contracts? This asshole screwed me big time and I'm about ready to lose my mind.

 Wheelchair doesn't work I'm stuck in this house looking at these four walls losing my freaking mind

I swear to God I'm going to my Congressman If these asshole's don't fix this pretty soon. I'll bet if these fuckers had to sit in a house staring at the four walls for days and days on end they actually get off their ass and pretend like they care about doing their jobs

Mother Fokker

Sorry for the rant but I'm losing my freaking mind over here. I swear to God if something doesn't happen here pretty soon somebody's going to lose their freaking job over this

oh and by the way VA head of prosthetics (department in charge of fixing the wheelchair) just told me this is all my fault and then hung the phone up on me. Hung up on me!

This asshole has some nerve. I swear to God he's going to regret this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you recommend a good flavorful tasty hot sauce? Something that actually has FLAVOR, not just super hot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like hot sauces these days come in 2 styles

1. Super extra oh my God holy crap 17 alarm burn the roof of my mouth off hot!

Or

2. Ultra vinegar flavor with a bit of hot beneath it

I'm looking for a hot sauce that's definitely hot but also that has flavor. It actually imparts some kind of taste and flavor to the dish other than just super hot and/or vinegar

flavor could be sweet could be savory could be whatever. Just as long as it's nice and tasty and flavorful

Recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We broke the jet stream: Study- global warming likely has destabilized the jet stream causing severe weather across the globe and 'stuck' weather patterns that last for weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The US drank 48 gal. of coffee per person in 1948, but today only drinks 23. Partly due to soft drink companies marketing sugary sodas as healthy, and coffee as a poison that caused heart disease and birth defects in the 1970s. Soda is now a leading cause of diabetes and obesity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 18:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Induction stovetop: can't find nonstick 1  1.5 quart pan that works on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 17:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a 1 quart or 1.5 quart nonstick pan that will work on a induction stovetop

this is the one I have

http://www.amazon.com/Cuisinart-GG19-14-GreenGourmet-Hard-Anodized-Nonstick/dp/B0025UQDEK/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8 qid=1391875817 sr=8-3 keywords=Cuisinart+1+quart+nonstick

Does not work on the induction stovetop

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A credit card offer came in the mail today With my personal information in it - ripped open! Should I be worried? Do I need to do something here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 17:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so yes I got mail delivered that was clearly ripped open

The envelope contained one of these credit card offers that let you transfer your credit card balance to another card with zero interest for one year.

It has these "checks" with my real name and my address on them that allow you to fill them out and transfer funds. It doesn't look like any of the checks have been used

Do I need to be worried here?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland may have just found its own renewable energy Holy Grail: For the first time ever a stabilized borehole is producing energy directly from volcanic magma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I get rid of my wood-burning stove can I just cap the chimney from the inside? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've got a wood burning stove that I never ever use and I want to get rid of it because all is doing is sitting there taking of real estate in my living room.

It's got a Round metal pipe chimney that goes up through the Living room ceiling and through the roof.

If I get rid of the stove, can I just cap off the chimney right there near the ceiling and leave it for now? And then get a roofer to remove it proper and shingle over that part of the roof at a later date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Yale researchers may have discovered the true root cause of depression: Not too little serotonin,rather it's too much of another neurotransmitter called acetylcholine. A secondary effect of SSRIs is they reduce acetylcholine, which May explain their antidepressant effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 00:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> maybe a long shot but Anyone know anything about garage door openers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 20:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably posting in the wrong forum, so feel free to point me in the right direction

Anyway, the remote opener for my garage door got wet and no longer works so I got a new one. Great. Except now my garage door is closed So I can't get in. And in order to get the new Remote to work I have to press a "Learn" button on the garage door opener itself in the garage.

I don't have a Side door to the garage. The only way in is through the main door that the opener controls.

so can I just yank open the garage door? I'm guessing not

How can I program the controller to open up the door without pressing that button ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Less than 2% of Americans get the USDA of potassium. That means almost all Americans suffer chronic potassium deficiency which can result in low energy levels, constipation, and heart problems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 18:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Coca-Cola (and other sodas) get volatile oils (Flavoring oils) to dissolve in their water-based sodas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so allegedly "this American life" uncovered the secret Coca-Cola recipe. Whether or not this is the real recipe is somewhat irrelevant. It's obviously close . 

So what I want to know is how do they get things like cinnamon oil and orange oil to dissolve in a water-based substance like Coca-Cola or whatever other soda?




Alleged secret recipe of Coca-Cola:

Fluid extract of coca

Citric acid

Caffeine

Sugar

Water

Lime juice

Vanilla

Caramel

Alcohol

Orange oil

Lemon oil

Nutmeg oil

Coriander oil

Neroli oil

Cinnamon oil


http://www.cbsnews.com/news/this-american-life-reveals-coca-colas-secret-recipe-full-ingredient-list/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding neurogenesis as depression explanation - is there anything scientifically proven to boost neurogenesis in the brain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Chrtien de Troyes invent the myth of the holy Grail? Or was he retelling an already extant mythical story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So supposedly Chrtien de Troyes was the first person to write about the myth of the holy Grail

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chr%C3%A9tien_de_Troyes

What I'm wondering is Did he pretty much invent the story himself? Or was there already some kind of holy Grail myth circulating and he was the first person to put it down on paper?

Also, I know the myth was most likely influenced by some pagan stories (Like the cauldron of plenty for instance), But being influenced by something and retelling it already existing story is not the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could ibuprofen be used topically? If not - why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 18:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> monitor image suddenly is washed out with terrible color? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 17:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this just happened in the blink of an eye. Sitting here Redditing when suddenly the monitor image becomes all washed out with really terrible color

It's like somebody put a white frosted opaque screen over my monitor

Is it dying? Is there anything I can do about this?

it's a Dell flatscreen 19 inch screen. It's not HD or anything special or amazing. using the Gateway desktop computer with Intel and Windows 7

damn, now it's back to normal. Color is fine and everything is fine. Any idea what the hell is going on? I didn't do anything to it

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: O'Brien Jumped to the NFL because he grew weary of 'Paterno people' at Penn State. "For any 'Paterno person' to have any objection to what I'm doing, it makes me wanna put my fist through this windshield right now." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 01:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These lawyers always advertising on TV (Like Hupy   Abraham) - is that good or bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looking for a lawyer to represent me in a personal injury case and getting all of these Google results back from lawyers that I constantly see advertising on TV

Are those lawyers were checking out? 

I am in Wisconsin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why am I getting " IP address from which you are browsing is not permitted to access the requested Web site" on my home computer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 02:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to access a website and I keep getting this notification

"The IP address from which you are browsing is not permitted to access the requested Web site."

I've never got that notification before. Any idea why?

By the way the website is 

http://www.confessionjunkie.com

I don't know if that makes a difference or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Nazi memorabilia sales are booming and prices are skyrocketing. Items estimated to be worth $1k or less are selling for $45k or more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 17:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US has stunned the world by overtaking Germany as the world number one in solar power installations. Residential solar is up 45% with strong continuing demand in a record shattering year for the solar industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 18:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Silverdome (Lions) cost $55 million to build in 1975, And was sold in 2009 for $583,000. It was financed entirely by taxpayers who continued to pay for the stadium even after it was sold and no longer in use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 00:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A man-made famine in the Ukraine caused by brutal Soviet (Stalin) policies killed about 5 million Ukrainians in 1932 - 33. Russia denied the genocide happened for a long time, and it still causes conflicts between the two countries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 21:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new World Trade Center emits an eerie haunting wail when conditions are right. Neighbors are not happy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 17:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Cannabis was outlawed internationally by the 1961 UN convention on drug control. That means any country that legalizes marijuana will be in violation of an international treaty ratified by 180 nations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 16:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL McDonald's once owned all of Chipotle restaurants and sold them in '06 for $1.5 B, thinking they had peaked in value. The chain is now worth $13 B and is the hottest restaurant chain in the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 20:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice re: marinating a steak. How long is too long? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 19:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I got me a nice 8 ounce ribeye steak. I want this to be as tender as I can possibly make it

So they tell me the way to do this is marinade

I've got some vinegar and some spices. Now what?

Do I just rub the spices On the steak and drop It in a bowl with some vinegar? Do I cover the entire state with the vinegar?

And most importantly How long should I do it for? How long is too long? Is 24 hours too long?

Thanks

found this

Don't ruin expensive steaks by marinating them; quality cuts like rib-eye, porterhouse, T-bone, filet mignon, and NY strip are great as they are don't need to be marinated.

 Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A neuroscientist accidentally included his own brain scan while studying the brain scans of serial killers and diagnosed himself as a psychopath. He's related to 7 accused murderers including Lizzie Borden. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 19:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charter cable in talks to take over Time Warner, bringing the cable and Internet industry that much closer to an actual monopoly. Comcast also in the mix. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 04:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Koch Bros. funded a hand picked climate study they hoped would finally disprove man made climate change. It proved the opposite, with study leader having 'total turnaround' on the issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 19:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some medications can pass the blood brain barrier, others can't. Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 17:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fluconazole and intraconazole are two very similar antifungal medications That treat almost the same things. The first readily passes through the blood brain barrier, the second doesn't.

Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Goldman Sachs made big money helping to falsify Greece's EU application, hiding massive amounts of debt. They then used that inside information to bet AGAINST Greek bonds, and made a killing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't determine if a specific product has a patent on it or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 16:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> possibly the wrong sub forum, but the only other forums that might be more geared towards patent issues are completely dead.

Anyway, I'm having the darndest time trying to figure out if a specific product has a patent on it or not. I'm like 90% sure that the product was initially patented in 1971, and that the patents expired in the 90s.

However, it's possible that they tweaked the design and renewed the patent on it. I can't find that information.

There is no patent number listed on the product itself, or on its packaging. The company website does not claim the product is patented, nor does it claim is not patented. The company website has other products on it that It does claim to be patented.

searching for patents on .

http://www.uspto.gov/patents/process/search/

Brings up a lot of patents that are similar, but I can't find one that definitely fits the bill here.

Is my only choice here to pay $500 for an attorney to answer this question?

I mean, I like to save that money for prior art search, although I must say as time goes on and I keep searching and searching I'm sort of winding up doing my own prior art search.

Ideas? Thoughts?

could I just call the company (multinational Corporation) and ask?

EDIT: I am in Wisconsin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Various cultures eat cow brains on a regular basis. Is this not dangerous? Why isn't there a high rate of BSE in these cultures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe I'm just ignorant? But I thought eating brains was a dangerous thing to do and carried the risk of contracting certain types of diseases Like bovine spongiform encephalitis? yet these cultures don't seem to have a high rate of that disease.


Re:
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beef_brain.

Beef brains and veal (juvenile beef) or calf's brains are used in the cuisines of France; Italy; Spain; El Salvador; Mexico, etc. where they are called sesos in Spanish and are eaten in tacos and quesadillas; Pakistan, where they are known in Urdu as Maghaz; Portugal; Indonesia; and in the United States, especially in St. Louis, Missouri, and the Ohio River valley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 'Nanook of the North' is world-famous as the first feature documentary ever made, and was a box office smash. Turns out, much of it was faked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL During a coal miner's strike Rockefeller hired thugs to strafe the workers camp with machine gun fire. They then burned and looted the camp, killing men, women and children in the process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 17:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Chicken wings used to be discarded as waste, but a creative restaurant owner out of food barbecued and served them in '64, creating buffalo wings. Named after the city, not the animal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 21:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 3 week timetable for Rodgers is pure speculation, could be longer: I have a fractured collarbone, and we have not talked at all  regardless of whats been reported  we havent talked at all about a timetable or anything." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 22:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As plagiarism accusations mount, Rand Paul says he wants to have a gun fight with his accusers: I take it as an insult and if dueling were legal in Kentucky, if they keep it up, you know itd be a duel challenge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 03:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doris Kearns Goodwin seems to have had a kind of weird relationship with LBJ. What's up with that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 18:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she herself tells the story of LBJ getting up on a regular basis early in the morning, crawling into her bed, and talking to her for hours. What?

She insists that nothing inappropriate went on, but given that LBJ was a notorious womanizer and Doris at that time was a young, good-looking woman I think it's only natural to be a bit skeptical. Or maybe not? I don't know.

Either way, it seems she was besotted with him. How can she be objective and write historically objective books about a man that she seems to have been enamored with, even if nothing sexually inappropriate ever happened between them?

The whole thing seems to be a bit weird. But then again I'm not a historian. Maybe this is perfectly normal? I don't know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has any veteran jumped teams late in his career in order to "get a ring", and then Actually got a ring? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 19:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we all know the sad tale of Tony Gonzalez, the best tight end in football the last decade, goes to the Falcons to get his ring and we were all pulling for that. Now it's not going to happen.

I'm just wondering if anybody has an example of A player doing what Tony Gonzalez did and then it actually turned out that the team he went to went to the Super Bowl and won it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> if gray hair is caused by a buildup of hydrogen peroxide, why can't it be treated with topical application of an antioxidant like vitamin C? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 17:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are most probiotics made from Lactic acid bacteria and bifidobacteria when there are other types of bacteria that are more prevalent in the human body? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 16:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other bacteria in the body that are more common than these two types of bacteria and yet those are the only kind of bacteria you ever see In probiotic type supplements.

Why do we never see probiotics made from Eubacterium or bacteroides?

Re:

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC91833/

In the human intestinal tract, Eubacterium is the second most common genus after the genus Bacteroides and is more common than the genus Bifidobacterium </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese city breaks ignominious record today: Highest air pollution readings ever recorded - over 1000 pm, safe level is 25 PM. Visibility is terrible, City shuts down, buses stopped running, factories shutter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 20:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan on the brink: Japanese young people have stopped having sex, aren't dating, and the already low birthrate is plummeting. Nobody really knows why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 15:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are famous works of art stolen when they can never be sold or displayed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 16:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching something about the Isabella Stewart Gardner Boston Art Museum heist of 1990.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isabella_Stewart_Gardner_Museum#Art_theft_of_1990

To this day it's unsolved and they got away with several very famous artworks. the works have never been recovered nor have the authorities come across any information that they've been sold.

Why steal works of art that you can never sell? Why steel works of art that you can never display?

What is the point of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL When legendary African King Shaka Zulu's mother died, He ordered no crops could be planted for the year, Pregnant women were to be killed, no milk was to be drank, and then slaughtered 7000 people who were insufficiently grief stricken. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 16:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Canadian government has abruptly decided to keep Fukushima related ocean radiation levels a secret. Previously the readings were public knowledge. They insist levels are still safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 20:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ominous news: A $32-million commercial fishery has inexplicably and completely collapsed off the Canadian coast with no warning. Fishing vessels coming back empty, scientists have no answers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Solana solar power plant quietly did the impossible: It chugged away at full power six hours after sunset. The new plant uses cutting-edge thermal storage technology and potentially rewrites the book on clean energy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 15:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archeogenetics Study Shocker: Most Askenazi Jews (~80% of all Jews worldwide) NOT descended from the Middle East, but come from Europe and were converts to Judaism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there certain types of arguments which have been shown to be successful at changing people's long-held seemingly intractable opinions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this could be in regards to any context however what got me to ask the question was having multiple discussions with people who adamantly oppose the notion of man caused climate change.

It seems like there is virtually no argument you can make with these people that will change their mind. It seems like there is no amount of information or evidence or proof or scientific studies that you can show or demonstrate that will make them say "oh now I see, good point, maybe all these experts and scientists might be right after all!"

So I am wondering if there any kind of scientific studies which have shown that a specific type of argument, or a specific manner of presenting evidence is more successful at getting people to change their minds regarding strongly held opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A study done by Stanford Marine ecologist has shown that every single bluefin tuna caught off the coast of California has tested positive for Fukushima radiation isotopes. Every one of them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 17:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Two cops who worked for the NYPD's organized crime unit were secret Mafia hitman, carrying out extortion, kidnapping, and murder on orders from Mafia bosses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 03:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A koi fish, named "Hanako", was owned by several individuals over many years and lived to be 226 years old, dying in 1977. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 04:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm on VA disability. Its past midnight, NO MONEY in bank account? Anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 07:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf? 

any thoughts

UPDATE: it posted! money is there 

everything is ok for now! 

thanks people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Many atheists who have had an NDE (near death experience) have experienced a radical shifting of their perspective about the afterlife. Most report that their religious beliefs didn't matter in the afterlife, but how they treated other people did. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avast going crazy! Alerting me to malicious attack on every single webpage I click on including Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 20:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf is going on? Avast is alerting me to malicious attack on every single webpage that I click on including Reddit

so I logged out of Firefox and logged into Internet Explorer and guess what? It doesn't happen

So somehow my Firefox browser is contaminated? What's going on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Artist Damien Hirst set an art auction record by selling one of his works for $19 million in 2007. The entire work is just a glass case with some random pharmaceutical pills in it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 15:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's the deal with this "pause in global warming"? Is it real? It's getting an awful lot of press recently. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 16:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first heard about this "pause in global warming" from publications like daily Mail etc. so I just ignored it

But now mainstream publications like the LA Times are reporting that even the IPCC acknowledges this is a thing and are scrambling to try to explain it

Is there really a pause? Are climate scientists "scrambling to explain it"? Is this a monkeywrench in the accepted theory of man-made climate change?

Re:

http://www.latimes.com/science/la-sci-climate-change-uncertainty-20130923,0,791164.story

It's a climate puzzle that has vexed scientists for more than a decade and added fuel to the arguments of those who insist man-made global warming is a myth.

Since just before the start of the 21st century, the Earth's average global surface temperature has failed to rise despite soaring levels of heat-trapping greenhouse gases and years of dire warnings from environmental advocates.

Now, as scientists with the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change gather in Sweden this week to approve portions of the IPCC's fifth assessment report, they are finding themselves pressured to explain this glaring discrepancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Yakuza (Japanese Mafia) have been sending debtors to work the extremely hazardous cleanup at Fukushima to pay off their gambling/drug debts. Most don't have the proper training to do the job right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 20:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are any point-and-shoots do a good job with macro close-up photography? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 17:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any point and shoots out there who do a really good job with macro photography? Or would I be much better off with a micro 4/3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Specifically how do coal emissions cause asthma, emphysema and lung cancer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 17:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coal power plants emit a wide array of different pollutants, most notably mercury and sulfur dioxide. Is there one specific pollutant that is responsible for causing asthma and lung cancer etc. in people who breathe coal emissions?

Or is it just the increase in particulate matter that people are breathing that causes lung congestion and eventually leads to various lung diseases?

RE:  http://www.lung.org/press-room/press-releases/power-plants-epa.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dammit - Madison's best used bookstore 'Frugal Muse' is going out of business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 19:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> source: just swung by there and they have a going out of business sale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If substance X kills pathogen Y in vitro, and is generally well tolerated by humans, does that automatically mean it will kill that pathogen in vivo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 14:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are trying to treat an infection of pathogen Y In a human being. You do an experiment in vitro and discover that substance X is highly effective against that pathogen. 

It's previously known that substance X is generally well tolerated by humans.

So is that it? Does that automatically mean that this substance will definitely be effective against that pathogen inside the human body?

Or are there all kinds of other complications and things to consider and the only way is to really do a live run with a Mouse/rat and then eventually a human being? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could you change the climate of a desert area by massive treeplanting and other re-greening efforts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 16:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about large areas of say for instance New Mexico (which for those who don't notice is experiencing a record-breaking drought).

I mean you can turn what were formerly lush green areas into deserts through clearcutting and soil degradation. So Can you do the reverse? 

Let's say you take a large land area Of New Mexico, plant massive amounts of trees, grasses, and other plants. The plants are going to draw water up from the ground, That water then is released into the sky through transpiration, which helps form clouds which may actually cause rain etc.

I mean is this feasible? if so, why don't we do it?

Found this interesting article on the subject:

http://www.irinnews.org/report/97428/will-more-trees-cause-more-rain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help choosing point-and-shoot: Aperture? Megapixels? What's the most important thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 15:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I'm looking to buy a point-and-shoot camera, something nice that Takes pictures I could maybe even blow up a little and frame.

Most likely be taking mainly outside landscape shots, maybe a little bit of inside possibly lowlight shots

Do NOT care about zoom, if it has a nice zoom fine, if not fine

Price Range $200  $300 give or take

Considering the Olympus XZ 1. It's got a great f/1.8 aperture, but it only has 10 megapixels. How much will that limit me as far as blowing up the pictures?

 http://www.amazon.com/Olympus-Digital-Camera-3-Inch-Monitor/dp/B004G8QSTO

Also considering Nikon cool pix 310. Great aperture, great price, but apparently it has a small light sensor

http://www.amazon.com/Nikon-COOLPIX-Digital-Camera-NIKKOR/dp/B0073HSH08/ref=wl_it_dp_o_pd_S_nC?ie=UTF8 colid=20RLJHQLJ6OR coliid=I3CIYVAYSGW32J

another one considering Canon power shot S 100. Gets excellent reviews. Everything looks great but LOTS of people across the Internet complaining about various technical issues and hardware malfunctions

http://www.amazon.com/Canon-PowerShot-S100-Wide-Angle-Stabilized/dp/B005MTME3U/ref=wl_it_dp_o_pC_nS_nC?ie=UTF8 colid=20RLJHQLJ6OR coliid=I7WH227KPO8NY

thoughts ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinions on buying Manufacturer refurbished electronics? (Specifically cameras) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 03:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at buying a factory refurbished camera (Nikon cool pix p 310) 

An eBay shop as it at a really good price "manufacturer refurbished"

This shop has over 500,000 sales, with 99.6% positive feedback, so not exactly fly-by-night

is this just a crappy used item they're trying to pawn off? Or is it worth it to buy manufacturer refurbished items?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TransCanada has hired Baptist preacher to minister to landowners families, and use that leverage to convince them to sign away their land rights to the sludge pipeline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 04:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In just a week Bakhtiari has gone from 7th or 8th lineman to bona fide contender for the starting job. At a minimum, he's the backup plan to Bulaga at left tackle, an impressive feat for a mid-round rookie." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 18:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eddie Lacy looks great in Packers first full contact scrimmage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know a good treeplanting charity I can donate to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The prosecutor in the Amanda Knox case was convinced she was part of a satanic cult and the murder was a sacrifice to Lucifer. This prosecutor believed the same thing for other suspected murderers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 15:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3-Year Camera Accident Protection Plan? Is it worth it for a $250 camera? cost is $37 from amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 22:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  3-Year Camera Accident Protection Plan for Canon PowerShot SX500 
$36.97

    3-year coverage from date of purchase: drops, spills, hardware failures
    Fixed or receive full replacement cost in 5 days or less - guaranteed
    Free 2-way shipping for repairs
    100% parts and labor covered with no deductibles
    Fully transferable with gifts. Cancel anytime, full refund in first 30 days.

---------

what do you think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Wikipedia has seen donations soar over the last few years. Last year it reported a 'profit' of $4 M, with income of $46 M, and expenses of $42 M. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 17:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona electric Co. is proposing charging customers who install rooftop solar panels $100 or more a month. A move that could devastate the state's solar industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Neil deGrasse Tyson is not an atheist, but is adamant about being an agnostic. He even changed his own Wikipedia page from atheist to agnostic, but it got changed back to atheist. He was not amused. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The SEC was repeatedly and explicitly warned about the Madoff Ponzi scheme for 10 years by a forensic accountant. Over and over again they ignored the warnings and did nothing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 15:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avast: should I re-up my paid subscription ($20) or just use the free version? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 02:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also got malware bytes, and MS security essentials

running Windows 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A 2008 study found that fast food hamburgers were made up of only 12% meat. The rest was water weight, bone, cartilage, plant matter, and parasites. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A simple DNA test can determine if your up to 30 times more likely than average to develop Alzheimer's, or much less likely than average to develop the disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what can I do with my freshly minted awesome credit-rating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 02:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for years and years my credit rating was crap, but finally I got It all cleaned up And squared away. Bought a house last year, and started stacking credit cards (that I haven't used) so that my available credit to actual credit used ratio is really good.

So Now what? Can I do anything really cool with my great credit rating?

I mean I already own house. Besides buying a bunch of stuff on credit (which I have no interest in doing) is there anyway I can use this credit rating to my advantage that I'm currently unaware of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Study: Grass diet may have led to larger brains as humans evolved." What? I thought humans could not digest grasses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 17:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Las Vegas is teetering on the edge of full on water emergency and has instituted the nations harshest water restrictions. Meanwhile the fountains at the Bellagio use 12,000,000 gal. of drinking water per year because it looks pretty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 19:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does ' 22 : 6n-3' refer to in regards to Brain phospholipids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 01:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I'm reading through this study about the effects of thyme oil on aging rat brains and I come across this sentence

The proportion of 22 : 6n-3 in brain phospholipids, which declined
with age in control rats, was also significantly higher in rats given either supplement. This latter finding is particularly important as optimum levels of 22 : 6n-3 are required for normal brain function. 

What does that mean exactly? Here is the link for the study, PDF alert

http://journals.cambridge.org/download.php?file=%2FBJN%2FBJN83_01%2FS000711450000012Xa.pdf code=60838bb92399fe508eb4aa14d4bda045 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Legendary Sci-fi author Philip K Dick spent most of his life broke and in obscurity. Just before his death, he saw the first cut of 'Blade Runner' and marveled "I recognized it immediately. It was my own interior world. They caught it perfectly." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 20:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Legendary cult Chessmaster Misha Tal got up from his deathbed, snuck out of the hospital, beat World #1 Garry Kasparov in a chess tournament, and then went back to the hospital to die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 02:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL LBJ received massive cash payments from defense contractor Brown   Root, a big supporter of the war in Vietnam. Later they made BILLIONS from the Vietnam War. Today that company is called Halliburton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 14:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since gray hair is result of the buildup of hydrogen peroxide at the roots, Why can't it be cured with a topical application of a strong antioxidant, like say vitamin C? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 01:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Univ. Wisc. system has a $650 million budget surplus. So they did the only logical thingthey proposed a tuition hike. Over the last decade Tuition has been raised 134%. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 15:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you sell a film treatment alone without writing a full complete screenplay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 18:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the first recorded use of sarcasm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 20:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Mothers required to pay child support are much more likely to be deadbeats than fathers who pay child support. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 19:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Ginger extract has proven to be extremely effective cancer killing agent, and can even kill the cancerous mutated P53 gene that radiation cannot touch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 17:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Greenhouse gas levels highest in 3 Million years". Okay So why were greenhouse gases so high 3 million years ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 16:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re:

http://www.smh.com.au/environment/climate-change/greenhouse-gas-levels-highest-in-3m-years-20130428-2imrr.html

Carbon dioxide concentrations in the Earth's atmosphere are on the cusp of reaching 400 parts per million for the first time in 3 million years.

The daily CO2 level, measured at the Mauna Loa Observatory in Hawaii, was 399.72 parts per million last Thursday, and a few hourly readings had risen to more than 400 parts per million.

''I wish it weren't true but it looks like the world is going to blow through the 400 ppm level without losing a beat,'' said Ralph Keeling, a geologist with the Scripps Institution of Oceanography in the US, which operates the Hawaiian observatory.

''At this pace we'll hit 450 ppm within a few decades.''

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A PhD Psychology researcher, who authored many highly publicized studies, was found to have completely fabricated all of his work, fooling 55 different academic journals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 03:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you recommend a really fascinating nonfiction book to read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 16:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it's summertime and I'm getting my reading list together!

Looking for good ***nonfiction*** book recommendations

can you recommend a nonfiction book that you found absolutely enthralling? I'm talking about a book you picked up, thought maybe possibly could be slightly interesting, and you wound up not being able to put it down.

no limits on subject matter whatsoever. I only ask that it be

1. Nonfiction

2. Absolutely fascinating



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad sleep? Try some "pink noise." Study: listening to pink noise increases deep sleep, enhances brain waves, and improves memory in subjects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 15:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> keep getting error message "a script in this movie is causing Adobe to run slowly", But I get it when I'm not even watching a movie. Very frustrating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 16:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so like I said I keep getting this error message over and over again, both when I'm watching movies and when I'm not. It gives me a choice to stop the script or not, sometimes when I stop the script everything is fine and I can continue on.

Unfortunately sometimes my computer freezes up completely and I have to open task manager and then I have to Select flash plug-in and end the process which then unfreezes my computer. Unfortunately it also crashes any movie or media that I happen to be watching at the moment.

Any ideas why I keep getting this error message? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the oldest company/corporation that is still doing business today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 15:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rats that received fecal implants from rats that had gastric bypass surgery done rapidly lost weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 23:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suddenly pop-ups are getting through my ad block? Why is that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 16:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have used Firefox with Ad block for years, and it's always worked fantastically

Now seemingly overnight a number of pop-up ads are getting through. But most of them are just blank screens, the ad content is technically getting blocked, but the blank pop-up screen is still pretty annoying and I wonder why all of a sudden overnight they are getting through like that?

Anybody have an idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great piece on the 2012 free agent class and how many of those signings turned out to be complete and total busts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL NBA player Latrell Sprewell (famous for choking his coach) turned down a $21 million contract offer claiming it wasn't enough to feed his family. He never played again and went bankrupt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Clayton: Number of teams interested in Brian Urlacher is about zero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 17:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't have a link for this, just heard John Clayton on SportsCenter right now. He said there is essentially no interest in Brian at the moment, his agent has fielded no calls

He said maybe maybe possibly Denver might be interested depending on how the Elvis situation pans out

I really think this dude has massively overestimated his worth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Thinking things like "I could drive straight into oncoming traffic and kill us all" or "If I drop this baby she would certainly die" out of the blue is actually quite normal- it's called 'Intrusive Thoughts' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 03:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any evidence that stimulating telomerase (an enzyme associated with life extension) activity in humans increases cancer risk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 21:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been researching telomerase a bit and I noticed that every time anybody suggests stimulating telomerase activity in human beings, instantly people jump in and explained that increasing telomerase activity will almost definitely certainly lead to increased cancers

But is there any actual studies are evidence that this is what happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Safe shyster's' wife comes clean, explains the back story to the 'What's in the safe' scam. "I may be married to the guy and love him to death, but yes, OP is a faggot" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why such wintry weather this spring? Answer: A massive high pressure system over Greenland that could result in the highest atmospheric pressure ever recorded by man, and end Arctic sea ice for the first time in modern history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 18:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Packers LB AJ Hawk's Took a $7.25 million pay cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 23:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Selenium performs incredible functions in the human body: it destroys DNA damaging free radicals, kills off precancerous cells, and (perhaps most amazingly) induces the body to repair damaged DNA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 16:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The CIA gave Howard Hughes $350 million to build a special ship to recover a Russian nuclear sub that sunk in 1968. They recovered the nuclear missiles, but they broke off halfway to the surface and crashed to the bottom of the ocean where they still remain today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 04:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ATT Report card: Paid CEO $21 M, paid NO federal taxes, received $420 M taxpayer-funded subsidy, ended customer reward program, while earnings up 84% to $7.3 B </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 15:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Of 'Project Thor': a terrifying weapon system that is shockingly simple - 6 m. Tungsten rods launched from near Earth orbit, invisible to radar, could strike anywhere on earth, impact speed of Mach 10, impact equal to a tactical nuclear bomb but with no explosives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 00:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A study showed that one diet factor could significantly reduce not only heart disease but virtually every known cause of death - sodium:potassium ratio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 15:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A study shows Omega-3 fat (marine sourced) Intake Creates healthier DNA. Specifically it creates longer telomeres which are DNA strands that govern cell replication and govern life expectancy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 18:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists able to successfully predict when heart patients will die based on measuring the length of DNA strands known as telomeres </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the oldest thing on the planet that I could touch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 01:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After vehemently denying he would be a lackey of big business during his Senate run against Elizabeth Warren, Scott Brown now joins a law firm that lobbies on behalf of big banks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen DeGeneres nuzzling and cuddling the lion cub named Cous Cous in 2010. Today that same lion mauled to death a 24-year-old zoo worker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 22:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Multiple studies have shown that psychopathy may very well be genetically inherited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 04:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Los Angeles was hit with a devastating and deadly series of intentionally set fires in the 1980s and 90s. They finally arrested the arsonist who turned out to be The Arson Inspector charged with investigating the fires. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 17:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AIPAC (Israeli lobby) pulling out all stops to save US aid to Israel from sequester cuts. Pressuring to move Israeli aid to Pentagon budget which would then be exempt from the sequester. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 05:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The W Virg.coal mining strike of 1912 became open warfare between the company and miners. The company quarantined the mining village, intentionally starving to death women and children. Main demand was company discontinue corrupt coal weighing and stop Stealing wages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 01:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why your medical bills so courageously high? THIS is why: $24 charge for  a single  5 niacin capsule, $18 for a $1.75 diabetes strip, $1.50 for each acetaminophen cap you can buy on Amazon for one penny, And on it goes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 17:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quickest way to ripen up an avocado (or other fruit)? paper bag? Plastic bag? Room temperature? Hotter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 20:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local grocery store sells absolutely rockhard green avocados.

googling around it seems most people just tell you to put the avocado in a paper bag on the counter top and wait 

Is that the quickest way to ripen it Up? Or is there anything else I can do to accelerate the process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Tobacco plants have a special affinity for concentrating polonium 210 (HIGHLY carcinogenic) found in certain fertilizers. Nearly every cigarette contains small amounts of polonium which is 250,000 times more toxic than cyanide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 20:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salon: Seth's We Saw Your Boobs Oscar sketch "celebrates rape." Do they have a point? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 03:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Turmeric (found in curry powder) has been surprisingly effective against Alzheimer's symptoms in multiple studies, and currently out-performs any known Alzheimer's drug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 18:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 70 years ago today Sophie Scholl was guillotined For treason. She led a heroic, though doomed, nonviolent resistance movement against the Nazis.The allies later dropped millions of copies of pamphlets she had written over Germany by plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 22:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Combine flashback: In 2005 Matt Jones Electrifies combine watchers with incredible performance, rockets past Aaron Rodgers in the draft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 16:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Eleven well reported medical studies show cigarette smoking actually LOWERS Alzheimer's risk. However, 10 years later, it comes to light Every study was done by scientists with UNDECLARED connections to the tobacco industry.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 00:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Each year about 14,700 murders are committed the US, the murder solve rate is approximately 63%, that means around 5,400 people get away with murder EVERY year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 21:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threesome gone wrong: North Dakota man stabbed after refusing to switch positions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 01:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The risk of a birth defect when first cousins have children is the same risk as any woman over 40 having children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 23:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN's parent corporation, Exxon, Pfizer among those who donated to Republican gerrymandering efforts, ads unions of "destroying Our children's future" other anti-union efforts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 01:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN: Dorner attempted to escape out the back of the burning cabin but was "pushed back inside" according to the US marshal service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 04:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LAPD changes story on Riverside officers shot by Dorner. Now admit officers were in active pursuit of Dorner at the time of shooting, and were not ambushed as they stood originally asserted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 17:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Gen. Custer was offered Gatling guns before the battle of Little Big Horn, but refused saying it would "embarrassed him" and that his men can whip any Indians, no matter how many. US government covered up his incompetence claiming he was a war hero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The brains of psychopaths show dramatic biological differences compared to average people. Their amygdala, where fear is processed, is deformed and significantly smaller. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 19:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Executive Producer and head writer for the series 'Dexter' was also the screenwriter for all of the Twilight movies  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 18:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Despite being massively wealthier ($15 trillion GDP vs. $60 billion GDP), the life expectancy in the US is the same as that in Cuba: 78 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 22:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Stan Lee (Spiderman etc.) went bankrupt in 2001 after his business partner was sentenced to 10 years prison for stock fraud, and he is now suing Disney for billions of dollars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The bicycle is one of the most efficient inventions in the history of mankind, getting the equivalent of 912 miles per gallon (388 km/ltr) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 02:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Thomas Edison and Lord Kelvin both adamantly declared human flight was impossible, and the effort to design an airplane was a waste and should cease immediately.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1889 a customer wrote to the railroad complaining of terrible bedbugs on a rail car, they wrote back, apologized profusely, but accidentally included this note: 'Send this s.o.b. the bedbug letter.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 21:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you replace a 20-year-old furnace that's working great? Just got a home improvement loan I need to make this decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 19:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out I qualify for the five-year forgivable home-improvement loan of $7000. the money can only be used for very specific things.

I live in a very small house and about $3800 of the loan is going to go towards putting a new roof on.

My furnace is 23 years old and I'm considering spending $2200 on buying a newer more efficient model. However, the furnace repair Man told me the furnace looks great, the heat exchangers look great, it's not leaking any carbon monoxide whatsoever, and that he has seen this type of furnace last 30 or 35 years. it's also got a brand-new ignitor in it

Do you think I should spend the money to replace the furnace or spend it on other things like insulation, window glazing etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
