<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 06:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid of making her feel like I'm not on her team. I don't want her to have to go through this whole thing alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 06:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it can't be undone, kids are still (unfortunately) not off the table. We decided on the procedure after a pregnancy scare, and our finances weren't the best at the time, so my parents paid for it - on the condition that I freeze samples.

I tried to talk to her about her arthritis, and what that would mean in terms of taking care of a kid, but she won't talk to me about it. She shuts down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 06:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a big thing I'm worrying about. Maybe this is just because of the depression and will go away when she gets better, or maybe this is something she needs now. And there's a part of me that would have kids to make her happy, but there's another part of me that thinks that would just make me the depressed one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My (30M) wife (28F) of 1 year was diagnosed with depression and decided she wants to be a SAHM. She's pressuring me to have my vasectomy reversed. Advice wanted. (xpost /r/childfree) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 years ago, I met the most amazing woman I've never known. Let's call her Claire.

She was adventurous, intelligent, and incredibly talented (she's a violinist). We've been together since we met and married one year. 5 years and 10 months of that time has been absolutely blissful. Starting a couple of months ago, she started to develop aches and pains when she practiced for a long period of time. After I poked and prodded her for a while, she went to the doctor and was diagnosed with rheumatoid arthritis. She stopped giving lessons a couple of weeks ago, and then she had to give up her chair in the orchestra she played in, and then she stopped playing altogether.

Since she stopped playing, she's become very depressed (and this isn't a self diagnosis - she goes to a therapist weekly now and she's on antidepressants). There were whole days when she was at her lowest when she didn't leave the house. She's told me that she feels like she doesn't have purpose anymore, and I hate that. Then, after she started the antidepressants, she decided that her calling in life was to raise children.

We've both been committed to being childfree since we met. After our wedding, we got all the "when are the kids coming" comments, and she hated them more than I did. Now she's totally changed her mind, and has told me that it's really important to her that I have my vasectomy reversed. She's brought it up once or twice every day for the past week.

I hate kids, but if I honestly thought it would help her, I would become a dad. I don't, though. I think she lost something really important to her and is looking to fill a void that can't be filled. I've tried talking to her about this and she broke down crying about how I wouldn't "give her children". I just don't think it would help. I think she's be just as depressed, but we'd have a kid to take care of on top of it.

I don't know how to help her. If having a kid is really what she needs, I don't want to keep her from that - but I don't think she's in the right place to make this kind of decision. A year ago she hated kids and now she thinks she needs them. I don't know what to do.

Before anyone says "divorce her bruh", I'm absolutely not willing to consider that. This woman is the love of my life, and I'm not willing to leave her when she's already hurting.

TL;DR: Wife is a professional violinist who was diagnosed with arthritis. She's become depressed and feels like she has no purpose, and wants kids now when she (and I) hated them up until now. I don't think having a kid will help and talking to her about it makes her break down. Help.

Edit: Woah. Good morning, Reddit. I'm headed out to work now, but I'm really looking forward to reading all the replies - the ones I saw last night were very helpful. I'll try to respond some while I'm at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. This hit hard but I think I needed it. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess this wasn't completely clear from the post - she hasn't *had* to stop playing. She can't play on a professional level anymore because her hands just can't do the more difficult stuff (not a musician so I can't speak eloquently to what that is), and she can't spend hours at a time doing it, so she can't teach lessons. She doesn't play anymore because it makes her miss being able to play well. Her quitting altogether is more depression than arthritis

Edit: I also didn't know that doctors who treat musicians were a thing. I'll try to find one on our insurance but our insurance sucks so this unfortunately may not be possible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
