<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1395</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't venomous if that's what you're asking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A breath of fresh air  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool idea, and they look pretty unique too. My question is why did you use TRRS? You could have just used mono jacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 23:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, did you mean to post this elsewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 05:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for some of this stuff for a while! Thanks!

Edit: Speeds are eh :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, that's cool, but this is a pretty simple thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally they're pretty good in residential areas, though I might avoid bear hill if there's any ice. That's a scary road to lose traction on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. Yes. Look at the wallpaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've become entirely spoiled by Brandon Sanderson. He writes two books in the time it takes me to read one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrible picture, but ESD band?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tywin Lannister? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Braid gripping intensifies* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That being said, nobody has mentioned Ruin or The Stormfather yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 21:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking skublovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were right. Definitely the naming. It doesn't help that some of the episodes are labeled things like "Space Pilot 3000", putting that episode in Season 30...

I'm having a bit of an argument with Filebot over Java issues, but I hand-named the first season and I'm looking good. 

Thanks a lot man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic. 

This should definitely fix it I think. I have been experimenting with different filing conventions, and I didn't know Plex had a preferred one. I'll give this a shot and ring back if it doesn't take care of it. 

Thanks so much. Couldn't go without Futurama any longer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help getting shows to display properly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a few shows that seem to be stacking multiple files in one episode. 

For instance, Futurama, I have every episode, but it says I only have Episode 1 of Season 1, but the info that that file displays episodes 1-13. 

I'm sure I'm not the only one with this issue, but I searched and couldn't find any similar threads. 

Thanks for any help you can provide! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my bad. Clearly I need to deliver the coup de grace. Kidding. Thanks for the heads up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead. Got about 40gb here though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 12:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I'm never buying Bose again. I worked for their customer service for two years, but they just laid off that entire wing of the company (lots of us were contract too, so no severance) and sent the jobs to Manila. Following this they have stopped offering exchanges on home theater systems. 

So there's a good chance that when you lose audio in your left ear on the QC35s (common issue) you will be up shit creek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not heard this referenced in like ten years. Nobody gets my 8bt jokes anymore :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This update has me feeling... uneasy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok got it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you suggest to plug in a DAC? Do you think audiophiles are going to trash their old gear in exchange for Lightning enabled DACs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you that sad a person? If so I'm sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nostalgia porn. Plain and simple. He injects so much random 80s crap into the narrative that has no bearing on the story and it's hard to tell what is even relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 11:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cringey characters and progression too, but it scratched the itch for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 00:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of weird, but Ready Player One by Ernest Kline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vomit/Prolapse? It wouldn't be fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you close your eyes and just sail through. The second you turn on your blinker or stop to comprehend why seven streets meet with no light, it's all over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can safely say that if Kelly square hasn't killed me yet, no mortal can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went there yesterday on a whim. Best burrito I ever had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, Catapult. Not Mage Hands or Teleport. Read the comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked customer service for Bose for two years and this is still my least favorite thing. People think everything is surround sound in spite of it having the most descriptive possible name. Ugh. Triggered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adafruit has tons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm betting on "some idiot braiding it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I tried them when they came to town and ended up spending like $20 a pizza? Haven't tried since then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search YouTube for router chamfered rounded square holes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. It was good but not good enough for me to go back. Had a pizza there a few months ago and it didn't wow me. Franco's probably has my favorite Moody St pizza.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you can get the 5 pound limit past your DM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 19:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feed it to somebody and floss them to death? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recall an old Galaga style game called Lose-Lose where the enemy ships are files on your computer, and it deletes them as they explode. If your ship gets hit it formats your hard drive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 12:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, but it takes three books to really get going - and it's a trilogy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have taken baron instead of bother with Akali ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 22:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thundering sleight of hands?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he has zero scaling. I hope they add some dumb useless ap scaling during assassin rework. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2DS repair question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, so I'm not sure if this is relevant in this sub. If not, let me know where to take my question! 

I fell on top of my Nintendo 2DS yesterday, crushing the screen(s). The unit will not power on anymore (blue light on for a second, then off). I am able to replace the screen fairly easily, but I'm not sure if it is worthwhile. Would a broken screen cause the system to lock up like that? The main PCB looks fine - I'm just trying to save $35 if the screen isn't going to do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very nice hat. 

YOU LIKE IT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 11:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played a Totemist in 3.5 once. If you bind Blink shirt with essentia on it you get blink as a move action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 11:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IEC what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more along the lines of the detective thing, but Dresden Files? 

There's a second Legion novella too I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or trying to snipe someone from an airplane. I am often guilty of this. Cries of PTFO only urge me onward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You flipped your ratio by accident! It's all about that gin taste, not the fizzy bubble crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it. Don't forget the Easter eggs in Borderlands 2, Overwatch, Witcher 3, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Da Lat, Belmont Vegetarian, Hotpot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting MPG issue! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So at work I run the local television stations. One of them is a movie channel, and the schedule for what movies I play is made elsewhere. September's schedule says I need to play a movie on Saturday that I don't have! My DVD of the movie won't rip because it's encrypted I think (multiple .VOB files?) so I'm looking for another option. I managed to get a .mkv version from a friend, but my TV software (Leightronix WinLGX 7) only seems to accept .MPG. 

As far as I understand, MPEG4 should work, but I only know how to convert with a container, a la handbrake. Can someone explain how best to make LGX recognize this file?

EDIT: This is gross. We need to upgrade. 

https://drive.google.com/open?id=0ByLTkA-eco-XWTl4RlpRUHN1czg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 19:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars Edge Of The Empire. I even bought the funky dice. My friends just aren't nerdy enough (a daily regret I have). Anyone in Boston area want to give it a shot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't standard trading cards though. And so far, /r/pokemon has no idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cards have other Pokemon on the back, for instance, the Eggsecute card has Horsea on the other side with the same background color and holofoil style. They belong to a friend, but I was curious so I've been doing some research. They somewhat resemble the 1997 Pokemon Carddass line, but don't have "POCKET MONSTERS" in bold at the bottom. That being said, the Japanese on them reads "Pocket Monsters Board Game" which may possibly lead to [this game](https://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/1381/pokemon-master-trainer/credits), but I can't find detailed pictures. 

Edit: Nevermind on that board game, german version doesn't have those cards, assuming this is some other promo item.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to figure out what these Pokemon collector cards are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think they are stickers. The backs are the same as the fronts, but different Pokemon. Oddish/Nidoran(M) and Eggsecute/Horsea, etc. They share similar holofoil style to Pokemon Carddass line, but these have little mons in the foil in order. Still hunting through google.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No these are definitely spongebob squarepants battle cards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend found these and I have no idea what they are. Help identify? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 04:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The compilation book is called The Necronomicon. So you kind of need to buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damnit Jeremy you are out of control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, what do you predict they designed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 00:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it would be fun, but balanced if it made a noise or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 00:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been hoping for the vector since black ice. I like the flashbang idea though. Just wish flashbangs were more useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 00:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or better yet, op that can use glitches and exploits that have been patched already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any early guesses on the Japanese ops? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 23:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking through options trying to figure out what Ubi may do for their last (?!?!) season release. 
It looks like the existing Japanese CTU ( Tokushu Sakusen Gun) pretty commonly uses the [HK416](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/97/HK416.jpg/300px-HK416.jpg), the [FN SCAR](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/bd/ARMS_%26_Hunting_2010_exhibition_%28331-26%29.jpg/250px-ARMS_%26_Hunting_2010_exhibition_%28331-26%29.jpg), the [Minebea PM-9](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/3c/9mm%E6%A9%9F%E9%96%A2%E6%8B%B3%E9%8A%83_%288464077981%29.jpg/300px-9mm%E6%A9%9F%E9%96%A2%E6%8B%B3%E9%8A%83_%288464077981%29.jpg), the [Remington M24](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/d/d0/PEO_M24_SWS.jpg/300px-PEO_M24_SWS.jpg), and the [HK USP](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/a/ac/HKUSP.png/300px-HKUSP.png). 
(Reference - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special_Forces_Group_(Japan)#Weapons)

Personally I'm expecting a FLIR scope? Maybe some way to make kill holes in reinforced walls? A climbing character? What about a bouncing betty gadget? 

As long as it's not overly weeaboo, what are your ideas or thoughts on the next round of operators?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also 99% fire and magic resist!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, this worked terribly. I mostly did it for the funny picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, just a cheap pink one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the av booth in a children's hospital auditorium. Something about not logging into your children's hospital id for presentations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 21:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I said I'm using these because I left my *head*phones at home. I generally bring my HD280 pros to work because I don't want my good cans stolen or damaged. But thank you for your input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dernit. Reposting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you work at a hospital and you forget your headphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you work at a hospital and you forgot your headphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't want to be that guy, buuut... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd do whatever. I'm personally familiar with D D 3.5/5e, Pathfinder, 40k, EotE, Risus, but I'd be willing to learn something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, I would actually do a one-shot where everyone had to make their character with this site. Anyone want to DM? Roll20? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theeeeeere's antimony arsenic aluminum selenium and hydrogen and oxygen and nitrogen and rhenium and nickel neodymium neptunium germanium and iron americium ruthenium uranium... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tchaichanka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, what is --random-wait for? I pretty much use that exact string otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 05:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  7 segment display

Wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 05:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Within the sequence, if you cut it down to one tile, vertical sums of the lines go 5555565766. That's probably what you were thinking. Ok done, mark it solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help me here, are the random white/gray pixels between lines relevant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Character lines in XIII?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 13? Uh. That's all I have so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it the amen break? I know it's not because of the sustained notes, but that would be cool. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone stole the gas cap off my Pontiac once (No fucking idea why...) and I used a gatorade cap. Fit perfectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 06:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AvE doesn't lie. 

That I know of. 

Ok maybe a little.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rJm9iCha-jM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 05:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely going to finish this soon :)
Try DS3! It's not too bad. You can respec so you can cast Hidden Body, then just speedrun the whole thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 05:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strongest boss in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **   ** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mistake. For some reason I was thinking of clearance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they? I feel like I'm checking ranks in pregame lobby every game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 06:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good buff for Tachanka. Horse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why he can't just be a 1 armor character, but still goes as slowly as a 3 armor with his shield on. That way body shots take him out faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel-Day Lewis is also a madman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be frustrating to learn that you basically have the same karma in 2021 that you did in 2016 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding Gaff. Great bar, good food, medium sized place. Avoid open mic night (Tuesdays I think) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joco's is good, a bit small.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I've probably watched through it over 10 times. It makes me sad that my girlfriend will probably never want to watch it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget West Side Steak   BBQ in Worcester! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started my new job, and I haven't been paid yet, but I really would love to be able to play! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have probably never coming closer to murder than when someone walked up and yanked out my in-ears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you Ubi! (Shout outs to Epi) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad to hear the good news about BattleEye! 
I adore this game - I have been playing on and off on my PS4, gotten to around level 80, but I just found a bunch of my buddies play on PC. I am 100% buying this game a second time (with a second season pass), because it really shows that the dev team cares about the game and the community. 

Thanks for making an awesome game and being an awesome community! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 15:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing. The Anonymous shit is so fucking cringey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
