<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friends aren't part of the relationship and aren't a reason to stay in it if you're not in love with this girl anymore. She is going to be sad if you leave her, but she's going to be more sad if she finds out 10 years down the line that you've stayed with her all this time because breaking up would be inconvenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to be with this guy long term, do you really think hiding your emotions from him because he ignores you when you're upset is a healthy sign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would tell him how you feel. Even if he doesn't feel the same way you'll at least know where you stand and you can move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really sounds like you aren't in love with this girl and aren't happy with her. She deserves somebody that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 06:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem :) Good luck and make sure to always wrap it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 06:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The doctor would be able to tell her if she had a tilted uterus, and it wouldn't completely obscure the baby, it would just be more difficult to see. It's not like the baby is hiding in the corner of her uterus holding up a piece of tin foil so that the ultrasound waves don't detect it. If she has her period, she's not pregnant. It really just sounds like she wants attention. My advice is to get out ASAP. Her need for attention is only going to escalate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 05:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had an internal ultrasound and it was negative.. There is no baby. By 6 weeks they can see the baby, that story you listed is probably a lie. Has she been getting her period? Sounds like she has a stomach ache and wants attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 05:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's cheated on you twice and you're still with him? Why, exactly? It doesn't sound like this guy really cares about you enough to put effort into the relationship. He only stopped talking to the second girl because she didn't feel the same way, not because he knew it was wrong. He has depression but makes little attempt to manage it. This guy sounds like a loser, to be quite honest. You need to find somebody that is emotionally mature enough to commit to you, completely. And not cheat on you, even if it's just emotionally. Fool me once... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 05:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you brought these feelings up to your therapist? I would also let your boyfriend know how you're feeling, if you haven't already. I struggle with anxiety as well, and self talk helps me. You need to remind yourself that he's with you for a reason; if he didn't love you and find you sexually fulfilling, it's likely he wouldn't be with you. You were also in a bad relationship previous to this, and that seems to have impacted your self esteem. Again, I would bring this up to your therapist. I hope things work out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Hey __, I know you're in for a rough day and I just wanted to let you know that I'm thinking of you and you can call me at any time to talk. We should meet up the next day for beers if you're feeling up to it. Good luck, I know you can do it.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanilla extract. Made the mistake of drinking some when I was 8 because my friend Steve told me it tasted exactly how it smelled.
Fuck you, Steve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've been broken up for longer than you were together, it's time to move on. This girl said she didn't want a relationship, so you need to accept that and find somebody that does. You're going to be in college soon, and what if she ends up going somewhere else? Or, if you stay together throughout college, who says you're even going to be compatible? College is a huge growing period, a year from now I doubt you'll recognize the person you are right now. You need to keep busy and focus on school and your friends and stop thinking about this girl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that you mentioned you don't want to see a therapist or talk to a stranger but you really, really need to. Your girlfriend also sounds like a really awful person and I'm sorry that you have to deal with this pain. You can't make homes out of people, and you did that with her. It's important in a relationship to have your own life, your own interests and own things going on so that if it ends you still have all these other things going for you that aren't tied to that person. I really suggest that you try to speak to somebody about your past, even if it's just an online advice website, kind of like a suicide hotline but chat style. Please don't kill yourself over this, you're going to find somebody that will accept your past and love you entirely, and your girlfriend just wasn't that person. You need to work on yourself and become stable and accept the things that happened to you, and deal with those feelings, before you involve another person. Good luck, OP. You can always PM me if you want to talk. You're going to get through this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 00:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sounds like a creep. You dodged a bullet, breaking up with him. I think you need to go as no contact as you can - block his number, call a cab if your car breaks down. Try to expand your social circle and find people that don't know him, and stick near them during parties he's at, or don't go to any parties for a while. I would also try getting in contact with a counselor at your university and explain to them that this guy has been harassing you, maybe something can be done by them, or they can get campus security involved as well. Good luck, I hope you find a way to ditch this loser! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
