<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7666</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Twitter is running into potential buyer after potential buyer walking away from the deal. They need to accept that as long as they provide a safe haven for abuse and harassment they're just not an attractive prospect.

I think Twitter is going to have to move toward some sort of verified account to add some measure of accountability. Which won't stop the truly dedicated, of course, but it might help slow down the casual idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The LoK fic I read, by the way: [Icarus and the Sea](http://archiveofourown.org/works/2808119/chapters/6302432) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wrote good stories :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Pulltogether once recommended a Zootopia fic when I asked for funny fanfic suggestions, and I enjoyed it before I saw the movie, but I'd been planning on seeing it eventually anyway. That just made it better when I did :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Field and McKee books will give you formats and basic tips.

Read "Save the Cat" to get some basics and form, but please don't follow it slavishly. All it teaches you how to write are cookie-cutter scripts with the same story arc, over and over and over. (Although, granted, a lot of those sell so there may be something there if that's the sort of movie you want to write.)

I'm an avid follower of "Scriptnotes," the podcast by John August and Craig Mazin, and as mentioned here already they have an [archive of their FAQ answers](http://screenwriting.io/). They're good at telling you which rules are vital and which ones (like "no camera angles/movements") can often be ignored.

Maybe not a beginner's book, but a useful one: "Screenwriting 101" by Film Crit Hulk. Teaches a lot about motivation and making audiences care.

But the best thing? Read a lot of scripts. Read scripts to movies and shows you know very well to see how they were translated to screen. Read multiple versions of scripts when you can get them to see what changed and try to figure out why. Nothing helps like seeing how working writers are already doing it. Here's [a list of downloadable Oscar-nominated scripts for 2016] (http://www.simplyscripts.com/oscar89.html) and there are plenty more there and elsewhere online. Look for versions that don't say "production" in the filename. You want to read early drafts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has a fic ever gotten you interested in a show, book or movie you've never seen before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never seen anything from "Avatar: The Last Airbender" or "Legend of Korra." It came along after I heavily geared back my TV watching and it never really piqued my interest enough to come back to. 

But after I found a fic writer who was writing stuff I really liked in my own fandoms, I started checking out her other work and just finished a [lengthy and fantastic LoK work](http://archiveofourown.org/works/2808119/chapters/6302432) that weaved in and around the official story and now I want to watch it to catch up on all the references I missed.

Have you ever stumbled on a fic that got you interested in the original work when you hadn't been before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Visit to a Weird 'Verse Re-revisited](http://archiveofourown.org/works/7967575/chapters/18224860)

"Firefly" knowledge maybe not required? Totally self-indulgent fic from years back of Nathan Fillion on Serenity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My house is way too crammed with crap for me to make a case against material goods :)  But we've been making an effort the last few years to make everything as digital as possible and to get rid of stuff we don't actively like. 

I'd upgrade the computer, absolutely, and our ebook/music/movie library would go nuts, but no one would see that. I suspect gradually our cars and clothes and vacations would improve, but nothing drastic. We like things and we like enjoying ourselves, but neither of us likes to stand out, if that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no doubt I'd have an excellent computer, a much larger ebook, movie and music library, and other things we could accumulate that wouldn't look surprising. There are absolutely positives to wealth, not the least of which is knowing that a sudden medical emergency won't leave me homeless.

I think should this happen and I managed to keep it secret, we'd eventually pick out a slightly nicer house, with a little larger yard. But we're pretty private people now, I don't think our lives would change dramatically. I might be fooling myself, for all I know. I've certainly done it before.

But I'm middle-aged and not that far from early retirement, or a buy-out. My kids are grown and out, my house is paid for, I have no major debt. I already buy myself things I like without too much problem. Shiny cars don't interest me much.

(That said, I could see better photography equipment tempting me, and that escalates quickly. But my dislike of suddenly having people calling me constantly, coming up with lawsuits, openly begging me for money... if you called it a phobia you wouldn't be far off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not that far from early retirement, and I like my job. Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if the quality of my life was based solely on material wealth, I'd agree. 

There is also privacy, ease around friends and family, the comfort that comes from knowing no one is likely to want to rob you or kidnap your family members any more than anyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? I like my life. I like my friends, I like my family, I like where we live. It gets announced that I won, say, $250 million? All that's over. Some good things would come, certainly, but also an awful lot of the kinds of problems I really don't want to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entirely possible. I suspect I'd gradually slide into a higher style of living. But I think it would take awhile, largely because while we're not buying new cars we're not in debt and the house is paid off. We already eat out way too much :) and we indulge ourselves with cheap AirBNB driving vacations when we can.

I think we could manage a slow upgrade in our lives without causing too much upheaval. Becoming abruptly, publicly wealthy? Nightmare. Nightmare with some upsides, yes, but nightmare.

ETA: And I thought my state allows anonymous acceptance through LLCs, but it does not. Not that I think I'll ever have the problem, but still. Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I live you can form a corporation through an attorney and have a representative claim it. Not that I've put any thought into it, of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would depend on how much I won. But I'm closer to retirement than I am to just starting out, my job provides benefits, and it's challenging and personally satisfying. 

More to the point here: I really, *really* don't want to be publicly rich. I don't want to find out which of my friends and family become insufferable. I don't want to have to worry about unusual security. I don't want to have screen my calls. I don't want to have to worry about my sons' safety. 

I'd rather keep going as I am, with only my Amazon account knowing if I'm spending more than usual. My vacations might perk up but my wife and I are not big spenders. I can go to early retirement, or take a buyout if my job offers one down the line, and enjoy the rest of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said before, if I ever won the lottery or a big inheritance (about equally likely) I would do my very best to make sure that no one knew that I did. My buying habits wouldn't change enough to get notice, I like where I live and I like my job. I'd just have a comfortable retirement, quietly help out family, friends and charities, and leave the rest to my kids.

ETA: And some research shows my state doesn't allow anonymous lottery acceptance, or acceptance by LLC or trust  funds. Damn. I don't play every week anyway, just a ticket every now and then if the Powerball goes really high, so this is very likely not a problem I'd ever have. But I don't think I've really gotten across the horror I feel at the thought of my privacy and life being invaded and turned inside out the way that abrupt, public wealth would do.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The styling and costume are great, but what makes this is the posture, the knowing eyes, and that perfect smile. There is a woman thinking five steps ahead of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! I'd link to some pics tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 17:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found "Strata" in a used bookstore back in the early 80s and bought it because I was a Larry Niven fan and this was a parody of "Ringworld." I found "The Colour of Magic" a few years later, figured it was more of the same, and was blown away by the new silliness. I've read all the rest, in order as they came out, and in America in the 80s and early 90s that meant ordering from overseas bookstores or from in-country places that did a lot of international business. I ordered mine from some fantasy bookstore in California that brought in UK books twice a year.

I was so happy when Discworld books came to the US, and again when they finally started publishing at the same time without the months-long lag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adaptations and official derivations have been OKed by the holders of the copyright. The characters and settings have been licensed. They are unquestionably legal, for that reason. Sometimes, [they win Pulitzers](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/March_\(novel\)). 

Fan fiction is unlicensed, written without official permission (although authors may allow or even encourage it) and is in a gray area, legally.

Otherwise, nope, not really. It's certainly not the quality; there have been truly awful official works out there, and some amazingly good fan fiction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My two go-to bags are either a [ThinkGeek "Bag of Holding"](http://www.thinkgeek.com/product/aaa5/) (lots of pockets, expands as needed) or a little carryon luggage with expandable handle, depending on my needs. I keep business cards and other necessities in both, and just swap out a padded insert and gear from one to the other.

I'm with you, I don't like carrying something that says "I have expensive gear with me." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] What do you think of behind-the-scenes books like "Marvel Comics: The Untold Story" and "Our Hero: Superman on Earth"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 23:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished the Superman one, by Tom Haven (I read the Marvel book last year), and I really love books like this. It's fascinating to me how many creative decisions I enjoyed/hated/wondered about as a kid were due more to finances, lawsuits and editor whim than they were to servicing the story.

There are reasons Superman went from cocky fighter for the underdog to barrel-chested symbol of law and order, why he became a dick for a decade, why his powers waxed and waned, and all of them are due to market forces and the interests of the editor at the time.

Do you like hearing the behind-the-scenes stuff? Does it make it better for you, or is it too much like "never meet your heroes" territory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 23:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been a huge fan of his comic and fiction work, especially the long Hulk run. He's not afraid to make changes and the things his characters do have lasting consequences. I will admit that after decades of reading him, some of his characters do start sounding alike, but that's true of a lot of writers.

My favorite is probably the "Future Imperfect" two-parter he did with George Perez, with their "Sachs and Violens" miniseries a close second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friends are wrong. Ignore 'em. Don't let friends or lovers or Redditors rush you into anything you're not ready for, with a person you're not sure is right for you. 

Not saying wait for commitment. If you decide, soberly and eyes open, to go have a wild night with a safe rando sometime, have at it. Or you can wait till you find someone you can't imagine not being with. However you decide to change that part of your life, it should be your decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop trying? 

Seriously, guys need to get out of the mindset that love is mechanical. "If I just do a, b and c she'll love me." "If I just make this one change, she'll love me." "If I can find just the right combination of things, she'll love me." It's not an engineering problem. 

Statistically, it has to happen sometimes. Billions of people in the world, certainly someone who wasn't getting noticed by the object of their desire suddenly got noticed. But I'll bet it was due more to a change in circumstance than, say, the guy learning how to dance to impress her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't replace it with anything. The conclusions I reached that caused me to leave the church also prevented me from accepting any other.

There is satisfaction in making the world a better place, there is joy in making others happy, there is peace in making others comforted, there is strength in integrity, and there is confidence that comes from never doing anything you would be ashamed to admit to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giggling. 

Breaks for something to drink. 

Falling asleep after. 

People walking in on you that are a) not attractive and b) have no interest or intention in joining you, they just want you to shut the hell up. 

Karaoke break when a good song comes on. 

Snacks.

Those times when you have to stop, still conjoined, because one of you got the lyrics wrong during the karaoke portion of the evening and it needs to be settled now. 

The Hunting for the Lube Ritual.

Towelage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Addams Family Values." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I try to... dammit, hold on...

Back in a sec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't care what they do with the images, no.

If you do care about what they do with the images, yes.

Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torn between Jason Bourne and Terminator.

Look, if the computers were really smart they'd make their unstoppable killing machine look like someone harmless instead of a 6-foot-whatever, 250lb bodybuilder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some background: Mills 50 is an urban neighborhood in Orlando, FL, at the corner of Mills Avenue and Colonial Dr. (SR50). In the area: restaurants, funky shops, art shops, specialty shops, markets, and some of the best Asian food of all varieties you'll find on this continent. 

A few years back they invited local street artists to come decorate the buildings, dumpsters and electrical boxes along the streets of the neighborhood and the result was a riot of color and expression on just about every street. Some wonderful stuff out there, well worth the visit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right there with you, if not quite as extreme. (It took years, but I think my brain has accepted my wife as part of me and doesn't mind her presence.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 15:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more inclined to like it if it didn't start off with the very recognizable baseline from a better song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 15:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the whole area. Fantastic that the city decided to go for this, it really adds some personality to the neighborhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the real secret. Never be embarrassed about anything you do. Rock on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful mural at Snap! on Colonial in Orlando. Artist: Mark Ghmeling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mural at Snap! in Orlando </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 03:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless your prospective (or current) employer goes looking and gets lucky, or your spouse wanders, or your kids decide to figure out what you've been posting your whole life... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. An annoying song that nabbed the opening baseline to aggravate music-lovers for generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to actually stretch the garment. Hold the collar, hold the bottom, pull. Move a few inches over. Repeat. Over and over.

Won't help around armpits and not much from collar to sleeves, and as I said I have no idea if it can do enough to make it wearable for you. 

If there's a design on the shirt you really like, you might consider cutting that out and using it as a patch somewhere else, or framing it as a wall decoration. If it's the shirt itself you want, well, good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HW_Rduet230 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to throw water on this, but there is no anonymity of the Internet. I always assume anything I put online could be made completely public and connected to me. All it takes is a slipup on my part, or someone who knows me deciding to copy and paste, or someone hacking into accounts and releasing things. 

I try hard not to say or admit anything online I wouldn't say in public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the assumption that Reddit contains exactly one dater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen for the extra note that Vanilla Ice claims makes it a totally completely different song. Doo doo doo doo-di-DOO-doo, doo doo doo doo doo-di-DOO-doo.

One of my favorite local bands does a great cover of "Pressure," and I take great delight seeing the people in the audience who clearly thought it was "Ice Ice Baby" looking confused when they hear the actual song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's made from natural fibers, wash it and then, while it's still wet, carefully stretch it in all directions equally. Then let it dry naturally or on low heat.

That said, if it's made mostly of non-natural fibers that won't work. You may stretch it unequally and get odd shapes. It will likely shrink back over time and you'll have to keep doing it. 

This works better for, say, cotton or wool sweaters or cotton t-shirts and polo shirts that used to fit but have shrunk. I haven't tried taking something that was too small for me and stretching it to fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the blog on my iPhone 6.](http://imgur.com/vGYTIG6)

Once you click on a pic to see the gallery, they look fine. But in the blog itself you can't see anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how his supporters react. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were, briefly, but the WikiLeaks haven't been anything major or surprising and O'Keefe has no cred left with anyone who isn't already predisposed to believe him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next may have to be low earth orbit. Amazing stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want to push past this because you want to, or because you think you need to?

If you think you need to, don't. Good stories don't need to be explicit. Intimate stories don't even need to be explicit. You can work at writing good scenes that don't get into detail and as long as the emotional impact is there, off-color words aren't needed.

If you want to, well. Two methods come to mind. First, find some scenes from other writers you like and try retyping them. Can you? Can you type them if you replace some of the terms with milder versions as you go? That might help you pinpoint what the problem is. You just may need repetition, as you suggested. Does it make a difference if you retype a scene that doesn't reflect your particular interests? Some writers have a problem writing sex scenes for fear that readers will read too much into them about the author's own practices (especially for those authors who tend to write the same scenes over and over). If that's you, you'll have to either get past that or write enough of a variety of scenes to make it impossible to tell what you yourself might like.

Second, try writing as steamy a scene as you can. The first time it won't be. Go back and go over it and add more details. You can take breaks and work up to it if you like.  Keep rewriting the scene with more specifics, layering them on until the result is what you want.

You may never be comfortable writing a sex scene. No worries. Everyone is different. If you've tried and tried and it's not your thing than it's not your thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fake news site, fake description.

[There is a Jumper sequel series coming, based on the daughter](http://screencrush.com/jumper-sequel-youtube-red-tv-series/). But no indication that Christensen or Bilson will be there, no mention of their deaths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm expecting that. Just saying that while he's not likely to change his trajectory, there's still a chance that she might. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the moment, you're probably right. But there are three weeks left.

There will be more WikiLeaks. Wouldn't surprise me if they're saving one big leak for the final weeks, possibly even one big lie to capitalize on the minor-but-accurate ones they've been dribbling out.

The DNC could still do something stupid. Nothing like the Democrats to snatch defeat from the jaws of victory.

We could have another terrorist attack. Voters tend to look for (perceived) strength at such times.

I think it likely that Clinton will win. But it ain't over til it's over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much exactly this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Firefly."

(Don't throw things! I don't kneejerk this answer for everything, but even back when "Serenity" was coming out I was asking for an animated "Firefly." Just about all the actors have done voice work before, a western-slash-anime style would be awesome, and it wouldn't need the same size audience to be successful. Way lower budget needed. Also, Tumblr would explode.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing. Like when science fiction authors of the 40s and 50s kept putting future humans in plastic jumpsuits and talking about food pills.

Humans don't change much. The best science fiction, I think, recognizes that and just deals with how we'd react in changing times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to go back and stop you from posting this, but I kept tripping on banana peels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking generally, because many authors tend to write shorthand characters. Couple major personality traits, a goal, a crippling drawback, and they're good. No need for extraneous background.

Also some authors seem to think that humans will have moved past the need for animal companions (or religions, or different musical tastes, etc). The fact that we're not essentially dissimilar to humans 2,000 years ago doesn't seem to dissuade them from thinking we'll all be homogeneous and evolved or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I'm trying had to keep an open mind. It *could* be a great series.

On the plus side, all the discussion here and elsewhere has got me wanting to read em again, so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are five.

"Jumper" and "Reflex" are about Davy and Millie.

"Griffin's Story" is sort of a tie-in to the movie. I liked it better than the movie, but I don't really think of it as part of the series.

"Impulse" and "Exo" follow their daughter. The books start off with kind of a young-adulty vibe, with lower stakes and local consequences, but they ramp up quickly.

There's also a short story between the two sets of books that [you can read here](http://www.tor.com/2008/08/26/shade/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah...

I really may have to mute this and try my best to ignore it till after the first few episodes are out and I can read reviews.

Jumper is one of my favorite books, and Ive loved the series that Gould has written following it. The movie took the basic idea (coming-of-age novel about abused teenager who discovers he can teleport) and shoveled an unnecessary action movie on top of it. There were no secret cults of anti-teleporters out there, no Samuel L. Jackson, no kid teleporter. Gould just took the idea of if I can picture it, I can teleport there and let his character work out everything he could do with that. Turns out, a lot.

And the original story, where the kid starts taking on terrorists, is actually far more relevant to todays news than the slick, FX-heavy crap the movie ladled on.

The only good thing out of it, for me as a fan of the books, was that movie money probably helped Gould write more.

The recent books have followed Davys daughter, and I would in fact love to see a good adaptation done. But the movie was such a massive disappointment to me that I really dont want the same director touching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing. To get embarrassed you have to care what people think about you, and that's too much work.

Also, guys? Cashiers will never mock you for buying feminine hygiene products for someone, especially if you're not trying to hide them. They may even find you more appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. If I'd seen it first, I probably would have enjoyed it more, and no reason anyone has to have the same tastes as me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I went all digital I was using [Midtown Comics](http://www.midtowncomics.com/) because my local shops kept missing books I wanted. Decent delivery, good customer service, everything was packaged well. I haven't used them in awhile, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does Bookmooch compare with Paperbackswap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah...

I really may have to mute this and try my best to ignore it till after the first few episodes are out and I can read reviews.

Jumper is one of my favorite books, and Ive loved the series that Gould has written following it. The movie took the basic idea (coming-of-age novel about abused teenager who discovers he can teleport) and shoveled an unnecessary action movie on top of it. There were no secret cults of anti-teleporters out there, no Samuel L. Jackson, no kid teleporter. Gould just took the idea of if I can picture it, I can teleport there and let his character work out everything he could do with that. Turns out, a lot.

And the original story, where the kid starts taking on terrorists, is actually far more relevant to todays news than the slick, FX-heavy crap the movie ladled on.

The only good thing out of it, for me as a fan of the books, was that movie money probably helped Gould write more.

The recent books have followed Davys daughter, and I would in fact love to see a good adaptation done. But the movie was such a massive disappointment to me that I really dont want the same director touching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I play online games I almost always use a female character. Partly because it's more fun for me to watch a woman kick ass, partly because I'll be looking at her back for long periods of time and I prefer looking at women, and partly because it's fun to annoy the obnoxious guys who try to screw with me. And there are a LOT of obnoxious guys out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, basically. I'm always a little reserved, a little distant to friends and strangers alike, but around my family and maybe two friends I'm completely open.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from just working as a good story (see: your points above), my favorite fanfic does at least one of these, and preferably more:

1. Makes me remember why I love the original source. It captures the fun or the excitement or the drama the same way, with the same feel to it.
2. Helps explain something in the original source. The backstory of a character, or a scene that answers a question, I love those when they're well done. They actually strengthen my appreciation for the original, if that makes sense. My favorite fanfics could easily be canon. 
3. They write the characters *better* than the original source does. I prefer the Clark, Diana and Bruce of unpretty's DC universe much more than the way the actual DC has written those characters in the books for quite some time, and definitely more than the DC movies handle them.

I tend to read fanfic to get more of the original work. I do love some AU stuff but it has to work harder to get my attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just screamed (internally) for 25 seconds watching my M Ms s-l-o-w-l-y drop from the snack machine so I think I understand sports now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's the purchase I haven't made yet. I bought what I could afford and hit that gulf between the pricy consumer stuff and the low-end pro gear, and I'm not ready to make that jump yet. I calmed down, after that... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if the model isn't actively smiling or laughing, I still get a sense of airy, floating, joy. "Playfulness" seemed the best way to describe it :)

I might try something like this, but with the model meditative and serene, just to see how it looks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you're adding the responsibilities of adulthood it doesn't mean you have to give up on your dreams.

I'm middle-aged. I have had jobs that were grinds but I did my best to make them fun or at least pleasurable for me and for any coworkers or customers I came in contact with, and I became competent enough at any position I held so I could largely ignore office politics. My wife and I are happier together now than we've ever been, and we're both still discovering new interests to explore together and separately. 

Work can be fun, and if it can't be fun it can be satisfying, and if it can't be satisfying it can be what pays the bills while you do what thrills you. Building a family can bring accomplishments that your childhood self could never have dreamed of. You can always travel. You can always write, and the older you get the more things you'll have to write about. I've always written, off and on, through my life, and I've recently discovered a love of photography, and I've started writing stories about the scenes I photograph. I never considered that, as a kid, but I'm loving it now.

You're realizing that the adult game of life is harder than the children's game of life. It happens. That just means it's more of a challenge, and the results can be more rewarding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! Beautiful ride, hopefully even after a storm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent post. Colbert-as-Colbert was, I think, brilliant because he kept so many layers moving at the same time. He was never "just" a parody of a blowhard conservative a la Bill Reilly, that would gave gotten boring long before the end of the first season. 

And it was in his interviews that his genius shone through. Even while he was playing an "well intentioned, poorly informed, high status idiot," as he described his character, he still couldn't help arrowing in on weaknesses in a guest's position, even when it was virtually certain that Stephen Colbert himself probably agreed with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me stress I haven't gone through myself, so grain of salt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It helps to post useful or funny comments on other photos. Work on the social part of this social media. And good use of tags can help spread your audience. 

[Check this link for a good tag discussion.](https://www.reddit.com/r/photography/comments/4p6n1j/hashtags_on_instagram_use_them_properly/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with the last part. Papers endorsing candidates gets a little fuzzy, as it isn't as easy to distinguish between the editorial board's decision and the newspaper's reporting they way we're expected to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little confused by this. Very few of the media outlets who have backed Clinton have done so without *major* caveats. The Washington Post endorsement yesterday listed several things about her they found questionable. Very few of them consider her flawless or blameless. Many of them talk about having two poor candidates but list her as the better choice.

What the main media sources are not doing is believing the hyped up, already-debunked conspiracy theories about her. I don't think that counts as having the media in her pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand you can get through, but it's still flooding over the streets at high tide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buffer won't post to Instagram. It just lets you create a reminder that will send a notification to your phone that loads the photo into the app and puts your caption in your phone's clipboard so you can paste it. You still have to set up and post the Instagram pic yourself at that time you want it.

Best they could do, apparently, but still pretty sad.

I can understand, more or less, wanting to keep their app walled off from 3rd party apps, but I simply don't understand the resistance to an iPad native app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Just started following you last night on Instagram after Instagood posted another one in this series. Beautiful, playful work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe every fifth or sixth book I read is one I've loved before and was reminded of, and occasionally I'll get on a run where I want to reread a series (although with Discworld and the Spenser books, that can be a significant chunk of time) (I do it anyway).

One way to relive that moment: find it in a different format. I enjoyed the audiobook of Daniel O'Malley's "The Rook" just as much as I did when I first read it, for different reasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. Again:

 Can a man enjoy seeing his wife with another man without being insecure or sexually ineffective?

I'm just curious if this is possible. Cuckoldry seems to require pathetic men. What's the term/kink for men secure enough to watch their wives take pleasure without being threatened?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as long as you get a woman, it's ok that another man gets yours? Cuz in your comments above you seem scornful of a man getting off on another man with his wife. All I did was add a person. Can a man enjoy seeing his wife with another man without being insecure or sexually ineffective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't answer my question, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you and your wife swap with another couple? Are both guys now cucks? Or is the other guy a cuck but you're somehow even manlier? I'm confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ones I have left are either books I can't find (or afford) in ebook form, books with sentimental value, rare or valuable books, books that work better in print (big photo books, books with fold-out maps, etc), or books that are works of art.

And I still have more books than I have shelves. Or stairs. Or storage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because as groups grow and seek to define themselves by what they are and what they are not, insults for people who are not in the group gain traction quickly. Especially when those insults are used to immediately put any target into an easily-dismissed strawman category which instantly means any argument that person might have is instantly meaningless. And when those terms are sexually-based, fun to say or type, and cast the target as someone inferior by definition.

Me, I fully support the rise of the use of the word cuck (and SJW, libtard, beta male, sheeple, etc), as it saves me all kinds of time by pointing out which people are probably not going to engage in any sort of useful discussion. Not fond of insults against the GOP, either, although liberals don't seem as inventive for coming up with anti-GOP terms. Basically if you regularly use insults to describe your foes as if their inclusion in that group you made up is a foregone conclusion, there's little point in arguing with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I started going with ebooks and trimming back my library, the only books I keep now are ones with some significance. Three come to mind.

A first edition of **Good Omens** signed by both authors, after they both made rare appearances in Florida the same year.

A leather-bound copy of the Sherlock Holmes stories given to me by a friend 35 years ago. 

My old, battered copies of James Blish's **Star Trek** books I found as a kid on a shelf in a North Carolina bookstore in the early 70s: my first awareness that there was a world of Star Trek (and other fandoms) outside the TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how long it will be before the cars are hacked thoroughly enough for some bored Russians to play GTA with real cars. With unwilling, terrified passengers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't argue with Trump supporters.

I have often argued with people who are planning to vote for Trump because they don't like Clinton for various reasons, or don't like the Democratic Party for various reasons, or because they support the Republican party and believe in its ideals and priorities, or because they are tired of the current government and want to see it shaken up. All of that I understand, and I can talk to and argue with people holding those opinions. We may not end up agreeing, but we can always find some common ground.

I haven't been able to argue with anyone actually eager to vote for Trump. I've talked and gotten a lot of bumper stickers and memes and sound bites back, but I wouldn't say there's a lot of interaction there. So I don't try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driverless cars will be awesome, but not until everyone is using them. The in-between stage will be Road Rage Against the Machine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, excellent. I caught the first episode (and love the books) but haven't seen the rest yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not her specifically, but whomever his opponent was he'd be claiming they were there due to a fraudulent voting system.

Well, no, he wouldn't claim that. He would say he thought it was suspicious, or that "people were saying," or that "everyone knows." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 15:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had Bernie won the nomination, he would have sang praise to Clinton. He isn't trying to point out voter fraud, he's trying to undermine his opponent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 16:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The desire to capitalize on it with cheesy reality shows and other cash grabs might die. The desire to put yourself into another time, to design cool things that never existed, to surround yourself with clothing and decoration and devices that make you happy and the desire to get together with like-minded friends, that's going to keep on going.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only happy to see this, I was *relieved*. After all the previews and trailers kept showing the Inceptiony bendy buildings I was getting desperate to see any sign of Ditko-inspired madness.

Now I am reassured, and I think this is the point where I stop watching trailers and reading articles and start blocking it on social media. I already suspect two, possibly three big potential tie-ins to the MCU and I don't want to be spoiled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be me. I prefer fanfiction that could serve as extensions of the original source. Most of my drive to read fanfiction is that there isn't enough of the original, and I'm impatient (looking at you, "Sherlock").

I'm fine with slash if the characters are naturally leaning that way or it's believable in character, but I dislike romances that were forced just because the writer really wants it. 

That said, a good story is a good story and there are several AU works I really like. But mostly I want work that could be canon, or that explains glitches in the original and makes it stronger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most important: It is not about you. Don't make it about you. Don't complain, don't tell long stories, don't force the grieving to interact any more than they're ready. Show support and willingness to lend comfort, and move away so others can do the same and the survivors can get through the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh. Not bad. Not the best. We go every now and then when a friend is playing guitar there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a range of pics from one angle to another. Same side.

http://imgur.com/a/U7rjB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I swung by again this morning and took pics from one angle to another. Same sign, same location, folks. 

http://imgur.com/a/U7rjB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 02:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you hear the winds come sweeping down the plain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, since there seems to be some conspiracy theories popping up, here are some of the pics I took that have not been cropped. 

[Pic from before Hurricane Matthew, taken standing by the corner. ](http://m.imgur.com/gallery/noGq1IH) 

[Pic taken after Hurricane Matthew, through my windshield, farther to the side since they get touchy when you drive into a sidewalk to take pics.](http://m.imgur.com/gallery/apbNITA) The employee had walked back inside by this point. 

Both from my iPhone, shot with Camera+.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not zoomed but cropped to match the first. I was farther away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditors of Volusia, represent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same side of the sign, but the first shot was me standing by the sidewalk looking at it almost head on, and the second was taken from my car in the Winn Dixie parking lot, slightly to the side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freeballing Friday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi neighbor! Glad you came through OK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are from my iPhone, but the first was me standing still in the parking lot and taking my time and the second was me grabbing a quick shot through the windshield. Things were a little hectic, right after :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed when I saw the sign before Hurricane Matthew and snapped the first pic. I laughed a lot harder Saturday morning and had to explain to my wife why I suddenly had to pull over and stick my phone out the window.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a difference a day makes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public storm shelters open Thursday in Volusia, Flagler counties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened, I think, was that they wanted to get closer to how real people talk. And real people just aren't that interesting.

If I'm with a friend, there will be digressions. We could crawl out of a car accident, and we would be making jokes and discussing movies while waiting for the ambulance. But I doubt anyone would pay to hear us.

But TV and movies use shorthand for this to move us forward into the plot with just enough of it to make everything seem "real," and the balance here may have been off. I liked it, myself, although toward the final third the dialogue got a little stiff for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
