<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8496</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 16:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Great American Novel by Philip Roth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 16:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a big fan of all of Isa Chandra Moskowitz's cookbooks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 16:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shared a [music playlist essay](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2009/08/book_notes_jona_4.html) for the book at my website, that might be insightful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 13:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite is Chris Adrian's novel Children's Hospital, the creepiest book I have ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 22:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have several friends that swear by NYU's Summer Publishing Institute. I've been on several panels there and gave always been impressed with the instructors and students. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 13:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great review! [Taiye Selasi wrote a music playlist essay for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/05/book_notes_taiy.html) on my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 17:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am headed there a couple of days this week and will search out the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 14:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, if you have several boxes Housing Works will send a truck to pick up your donation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 13:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The books are well made, gorgeously illustrated and designed, but also sturdy and made to last a very long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 14:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a great fan of book blogs (and collaborative book sites) that are passionate about their subject and offer a different perspective from other print and web media.

Disclaimer: Of course, [having one of my own](http://blog.subject8496.com), I admit to a possible bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 19:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a literary fiction presence online, look to the websites of literary journals and websites like The Millions, The Rumpus, and others. 

I am lucky to live in Brooklyn and be surrounded by writers and people in publishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 13:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ernest Cline also [wrote a playlist essay for the book at my site](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/08/book_notes_erne.html) that makes a nice addendum to the novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 13:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodbye Columbus is my favorite, but The Great American Novel is one of the funniest books I have ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 13:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't read as many literary quarterlies as I used to, but always make time for Tin House and PANK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 13:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Millions](http://themillions.com), [The Rumpus](http://therumpus.net), and [The Airship](http://airshipdaily.com/) are my current favorites (and I have to mention my own, [Largehearted Boy](http://blog.subject8496.com), which covers both books   music and how they intersect). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe [Austin Grossman's playlist essay on my website](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2008/08/book_notes_aust.html) will help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 13:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. If you are ever looking for some free books, let me know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 to donating them to Housing Works, and they will even send a truck to pick them up if you have several boxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 21:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Book Notes: Adrianne Harun -"A Man Came Out of a Door in the Mountain"](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2014/04/book_notes_adri.html)

I have authors create and discuss music playlists that relate to their book in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 13:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent book, the author Daniel Levine [shared a music playlist for it at my site](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2014/04/book_notes_dani_11.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 15:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the shoutout, here is the direct link to the 2013 list of best books lists:

http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/11/online_best_of_13.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 13:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bookish](http://www.bookish.com/home) is the best I have found, though it isn't anywhere near perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 14:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent suggestions from one of my favorite indie presses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 15:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nominated Fiona Maazel's Woke Up Lonely for the [play-in matchup](http://www.themorningnews.org/tob/2014/the-pre-tournament-playoff.php) against Kate Atkinson's Life After Life (chosen by Lev Grossman). Geraldine Brooks was the judge for that round, and chose the Atkinson novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 13:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite novels last year. Marra shared a [music playlist essay for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/06/book_notes_anth_1.html) on my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 23:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hold your books, along with several by Lynda Barry, to be instrumental in fostering creativity, and have added both Steal Like an Artist and Show Your Work to the suggested book list I give out at my talk to MFA programs.

What are one or two books you specifically recommend on creativity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 13:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite novels last year. Hannah Kent shared a [music playlist for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/09/book_notes_hann_2.html) on my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 14:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I don't collect signed books myself, I usually get them for friends   family at signings (I am lucky to live in New York City).

I often recommend to friends to check out their local bookshops, many (at least here in the United States) sell signed copies. Also, check out independent bookstores online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 13:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A book I truly enjoyed, and I read little fantasy. Erin Morgenstern [shared a music playlist for the book on my site](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/09/book_notes_erin_1.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 14:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Years ago Metacritic actually aggregated book reviews, but the traffic paled in comparison to music, film, and games.

I would love to see a site that aggregated both reviews and author interviews/profiles for specific books, it's a niche that hasn't been exploited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might enjoy this [playlist he shared for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2006/09/book_notes_chuc_1.html) years ago on my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 13:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pass some along to friends and family, and give the rest to a local thrift shop. A very small percentage I keep around if I think I will want to reread them at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 13:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often match music from the author's country with the text when I am reading something in translation.

Authors [create and discuss music playlists for their books](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/book_notes_2012/) on my site, there are over 1500 in the series so far, these are the soundtracks I've been recommending lately for specific books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 13:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epileptic by David B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 19:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up to you, stay put. The shoe is on the other foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 15:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nathan Filer shared a [music playlist for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/11/book_notes_nath_2.html) at my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 13:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite book of 2013 was Susan Steinberg's short story collection Spectacle.

2014's is Jesse Ball's novel Silence Once Begun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 20:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barber on Pearl in DUMBO. Great haircut for $17 plus tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 15:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claire Vaye Watkins and Kevin Barry are two of my favorite young short story writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 15:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've had audiobooks for a while, but just launched ebooks. As publishers sign on, the catalog should increase dramatically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 13:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lauren Groff wrote a [music playlist essay for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2012/03/book_notes_laur_12.html) at my site, that might answer a question or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was one of [my favorite novels of 2013](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/12/favorite_novels_6.html). The author (Nicola Griffith) [shared a music playlist for the book on my site](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/11/book_notes_nico_2.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 13:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually an old baseball or hockey card (I keep a couple of stacks around the house and office for that sole purpose). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 13:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woke Up Lonely by Fiona Maazel, from Graywolf Press (which killed it last year). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 13:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, it's a labor of love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 12:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beyond those already mentioned, I'd add:

A Strange Object (Austin small press that has only published one book so far, Kelly Luce;s short fiction collection, but has great promise)

Biblioasis and House of Anansi (Canadian presses)

Bellevue Literary Press

  Other (publishes works in translation)

Restless Books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 23:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that many websites make more revenue from "native advertising," essentially sponsored posts, than banner advertising (including AdSense) these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 00:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrace Books on Prospect Park West (a sister shop to Community Bookstore) is a great used bookstore in Park Slope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 00:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These days the biggest cross section of referrals to my books/music site come from social media (Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, etc.). Be sure to tag the acts you cover when you announce your posts on socia media, then they wil help spread the word about your blog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 13:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loathed "All the Sad Young Literary Men," but found this book smart and enjoyable.

She wrote a [playlist essay for the novel](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/08/book_notes_adel.html) on my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 12:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am collecting [major and interesting year-end music lists](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/12/2013_yearend_on.html) on my website.

In previous years, i tried to include every online list I found (check the archive links for those), but it became too overwhelming.

I also collect [every "best books of 2013" list I find](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/11/online_best_of_13.html).

edited: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 21:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> El Yucateca's hot sauces are mainstays in our kitchen, especially the habanero, chipotle, and jalapeo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 13:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd add Teju Cole's debut novel Open City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorel is an amazing hibiscus liqueur made in Red Hook.

Also from Red Hook, Van Brunt Stillhouse offers a couple of great whiskies, plus rum and grappa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 23:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rumpus and The Millions both have strong followings among the publishing and writing communities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 14:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [EarlyWord](http://www.earlyword.com/2013/11/27/best-books-few-inroads-for-ebooks/) creates spreadsheets of the books mentioned on the major award lists (like the ones you mention) for both adult fiction and nonfiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 23:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything by Geoff Dyer or Michelle Orange impresses me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 12:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Cinnamon and Gunpowder and enjoyed it. The author, Eli Brown, [shared a music playlist for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/06/book_notes_eli.html) on my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 13:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These days bookstores, especially independent boosktores, are a vital part of their community, so having an integrated event space (in NYC often achieved by movable tables and/or shelving) is often considered a must. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 22:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a food blog, but I co-host a monthly food storytelling   reading series, DISH, at Manhattan's Housing Works bookstore in Soho.

This coming Wednesday we are featuring LA chef Roy Choi, DannyMacaroons' Dan Cohen, Brooklyn distillers Van Brunt, and more. There will be whiskey and macaroon samples.

https://www.facebook.com/events/152795731596383/?ref=22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 18:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Penina Roth, who runs the Franklin Park Reading Series, is an inspiration on the neighborhood (Crown Heights), borough (Brooklyn), and city level.

http://franklinparkbrooklyn.com/reading-series/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 14:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, their e-books are all DRM free and the Tor.com blog is one of the best book sites online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 22:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of Brooklyn's independent bookstores host book clubs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 15:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't listen to them, I'd much rather read the physical book or teh words on an e-reader. For me, the narrator's voice recontextualizes the text, something I would rather do for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 15:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rachel Kushner's novel The Flamethrowers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 14:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have a [series on my website where authors create and discuss playlists for their books](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/book_notes_2012/). So far over 1500 authors have participated, including Bret Easton Ellis, George Pelecanos, Karen Russell, and many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TWC is having routing issues in NY. I contacted live chat support two hours ago and they confirmed the problem, said engineers were working on it, but didn't have an ETA for resolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 16:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brooklyn, about half the internet unreachable for me as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 16:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having the same issues in Brooklyn with TWC internet. Online chat said it's a known issue, and that engineers are working on the problem. No ETA for resolving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 16:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for pointing out this site, just bookmarked it for future TWC troubles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 18:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd check into the Housing Works bookstore in Soho on Crosby St. as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 15:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The New York Times critics' lists as well as the PEN literary awards are the ones I most look forward to.

I actually collect the [online year-end book lists](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2012/11/online_best_of_11.html) at my website every year, and should start aggregating them for 2013 in mid-November. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 14:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the book. [Daniel Kraus created and discussed a music playlist for it on my website](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/04/book_notes_dani_4.html), you might find that interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 15:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Edelweiss](http://edelweiss.abovethetreeline.com/) lists book releases, you can sort them by release date. The interface is a bit unwieldy, but usable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 14:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Night Circus, too. Check out the [music playlist essay](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/09/book_notes_erin_1.html) she wrote for the book on my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 14:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine go to a thrift store whose proceeds go to a charity I support and a middle school and high school library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 14:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lev Grossman discussed the music he listened to while writing [The Magician Kings](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/08/book_notes_lev_1.html) and [The Magicians](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2009/08/book_notes_lev.html) on my website, that might help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 14:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great book, Kevin Brockmeier shared [a music playlist essay for it on my site](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2006/02/book_notes_kevi.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 14:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Godfather series. The first two movies are classic, the Mario Puzo books pulp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 13:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Five Chapters](http://fivechapters.com) serializes a new, literary short story by every week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 11:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I host a monthly reading and music series there, Largehearted Lit, but only have one more scheduled this year (October 16th with Cari Luna and Mitchell S. Jackson). Hope fully you can stop by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 00:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WORD is one of my favorite NYC indie bookstores, cozy with a knowledgable and friendly staff and great events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 02:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it part of my routine to post daily, right after my morning run or do walk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My blog is [Largehearted Boy](http://blog.subject8496.com), a book   music blog that explores where the two overlap, especially with the Book Notes feature where authors create and discuss a music playlist for their books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tor](http://Tor.com)	is my favorite science fiction blog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just subscribed! I've been blogging over 11 years, and might have something to add. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 23:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jami Attenberg's novel The Kept Man is the quintessential Brooklyn novel for me, especially it's depiction of Williamsburg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 14:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geoff Dyer, Wayne Koestenbaum, Camille Paglia, Michelle Orange. All have relatively new essay collections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 00:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a couple of blocks from me, I was wondering about the hovering helicopters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 02:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I love Housing Works both for buying books and literary events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 14:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. He did a reading as part of my Largehearted Lit series for the book, and we had MC Chris play. It was fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 13:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was one of the best fantasy books I have ever read. Lev Grossman [shared a music playlist for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2009/08/book_notes_lev.html) on my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 12:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jenni Fagan wrote a [music playlist essay](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/08/book_notes_jenn_13.html) for the book at my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 13:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am halfway through the new Tartt novel and enjoying it. I am also especially anticipating the new Jhumpa Lahiri and Hilton Als books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 13:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ernest Cline shared a [music playlist](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/08/book_notes_erne.html) for the book on my website that you can stream on Spotify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 13:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always seen the need for something like this, for no other reason than to aggregate reviews (and links to them).

Years ago Metacritic did this for books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 13:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claire Vaye Watkins short story collection Battleborn (published last year and just issued in paperback) is the finest first book I have read in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 13:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karen Russell wrote a [music playlist essay for Swamplandia](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/08/book_notes_kare.html) for my website, you might find that interesting.

I picked up the novel because I had read and enjoyed several of her short stories. I especially liked the one that was the origin of Swamplandia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [coworking wiki](http://wiki.coworking.com/w/page/16583629/CoworkingNewYorkCity) lists many of NYC's coworking spots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 12:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Adrian's novel The Children's Hospital is the creepiest fiction I have ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh My Rockness](http://ohmyrockness.com) is my go-to music show calendar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 12:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These days my reading is predicated by [my blog](http://blog.subject8496.com), I read the books I am featuring (usually the next week). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 17:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always use the term for a publisher who is not art of the "big 5" (now that Random House and Penguin have merged). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 13:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm streaming more on Spotify and Rdio these days than buying new releases, and discovering new music through sites like [NoiseTrade](http://noisetrade.com) (to feature as free   legal music downloads on [my blog](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/daily_downloads/)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 13:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David B.'s Epileptic, a harrowing account of his brother's illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 13:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zazen by Vanessa Veselka, Battleborn by Claire Vaye Watkins, Building Stories by Chris Ware, and Malarky by Anakana Schofield </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 12:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like insightful reviews and features that are original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 12:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michelle Tea just published the first novel in a YA trilogy, The Mermaid of Chelsea Creek.

She wrote a [music playlist essay for the book at my website](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/07/book_notes_mich_23.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 13:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big fan here of both PoetryGenius and RapGenius. You should do an IAma interview on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 14:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed this book. [Andrew Davidson created and discusses a music playlist for The Gargoyle](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2008/08/book_notes_andr_3.html) on my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 13:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Birmingham, Alabama, and took them to the local salvation Army Thrift.

Here in NYC, I take books to Housing Works Bookstore in Manhattan:

[http://www.housingworks.org/bookstore/donations/](http://www.housingworks.org/bookstore/donations/)

If you have a big enough donation, they may send their truck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 13:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you finish the book, [stream (and read about) the music playlist he put together for the book at my blog](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2011/08/book_notes_erne.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 13:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a similar feature on my website, Largehearted Boy, called [Book Notes](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/book_notes_2012/), where authors create and discuss a music playlist that is relevant to their book. Some build a soundtrack, others discuss music that influenced the book. Even others create playlists from their characters' perspectives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 02:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We kept our car for about a year after moving to Brooklyn, but rarely used it, and alternate side parking on our street in South Slope was a hassle. It is easier just to rent a car when we need to get somewhere not covered by public transportation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 15:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Community Bookstore is in Park Slope and is an excellent indie:

[http://communitybookstore.net](http://communitybookstore.net)

I'd also recommend Greenlight in Fort Greene and BookCourt in Cobble Hill (both not too far) and WORD in Greenpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 13:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tin House](http://www.tinhouse.com/) and [Conjunctions](http://conjunctions.com/) are my two favorite quarterlies that feature short fiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 12:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally listen to film soundtracks, classical music (Arvo Part recently), noise (Merzbow), and instrumental indie rock (Explosions in the Sky) while I am writing.

I have a [Book Notes feature on my website](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/book_notes_2012/) where I ask authors to create a music playlist for their book. Many discuss the music they listened to while writing, but just as many start their piece off by saying "I don't/can't listen to music when I write." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 13:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leonard Cohen, Patti Smith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 13:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best nonfiction titles I have read in the past 10 years, along with Dave Cullen's Columbine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 13:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Bell's fabulist fable of a novel In the House upon the Dirt between the Lake and the Woods. He wrote an accompanying [music playlist for it on my website](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/06/book_notes_matt_21.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 13:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Among the Thugs, by Bill Buford, which examines English soccer hooligans as well as the sport itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 02:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Adventures of Augie March, by Saul Bellow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 13:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite novels of the year. Marjorie Celona [shared a music playlist essay](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/01/book_notes_marj.html) for the book on my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 14:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My blog is about both books   music (and where they intersect): [Largehearted Boy](http://blog.subject8496.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 14:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old school represent! (I started my blog in 2002) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 12:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked Lara Santoro's novel, The Boy. She wrote a [playlist essay for the book](http://www.subject8496.com/blog/archive/2013/01/book_notes_lara.html) at my website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 12:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also recommend Bronsky's novel The Hottest Dishes of the Tartar Cuisine. Fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Largeheartedboy is the name of my website, it comes from the Guided By Voices song, "Unleashed! The Large Hearted Boy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 12:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree totally with the previous comments. Before moving to Brooklyn a couple of years ago I cut my own library by about 90%.

First I triaged what I wanted to keep (books signed by friends, valuable books, ones I haven't read, and those I would read again). Then I contacted a local thrift store to pick up the rest, they sent a truck and loaded all the boxes.

I recently helped a friend clear out his late grandfather's book collection. We used an app called [BookScouter](http://bookscouter.com/) to maximize the financial return for the books. It was extra work, but we ended up getting 40x the amount offered by a used bookstore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 14:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Bell's novel In the House Upon the Dirt Between the Lake and the Woods, followed closely by Rachel Kushner's novel The Flamethrowers and Fiona Maazel's novel Woke Up Lonely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 14:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate your diligence (I moderate the booklists Reddit). I was appreciative that someone posted something from my blog on one of my favorite sites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 03:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for linking to my site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 13:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Tin House is publishing the best short fiction these days, and is always exceptionally well designed.

[Five Chapters](http://fivechapters.com) is a website that serializes a new short story every week, and features both exciting new and established authors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
