<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject713</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahha that's what I get for not proofreading. 

We certainly did, and it was a humbling moment for me because I did not think America was that racist. Though the more I thought and discussed with friends and colleagues I'm trending more towards people were fed up with the establishment (motivations are unknown to me) and looked past the racism/bigotry/etc... to get someone ultra anti-establishment. I understand Bernie was out of the establishment but the strong anti-democrat sentiment seemed to be more prevalent than strong anti-republican until the election.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe "they" is too broad. It only takes 1 student. I don't have imperial evidence but have being a recent graduate I would estimate that a majority of the student body disagrees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, people definitely are attending the event. There is definitely a sub-culture of conservatives in College Station that sympathize with this. However, the university and organizations within the student body are hosting programs at the same time of the event so students can peacefully protest. Several thousands students participating in events occurring at the same time is a great way of protesting the ideas and rhetoric of Mr. Spencer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this surprise anyone? Our textbooks are just as bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's depressing is he picked Texas A M for a reason. It wasn't random selection. Thankfully, the university and the student body openly rejected the false assumption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who chew really fucking loud and don't care that the rest of the known universe can hear it. Then they start to breath really heavy like their life depends on it. Eat that fucking hostess in 5 bites, not two you asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of bullets that can be fired without reloading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ain't gon need fish oil for bout 2 weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnny Manziel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Challenge Accepted" -Elon Musk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 04:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Texas and I did not ride my horse to class, stop asking. Though yes, I know someone who did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/gallery/i2vWZ

Just waiting for him to come out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
