<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9743</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 20:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, for the most part. Depending on where OP lives and what schedule his school follows (if he is a high school student) this could be very true. Although, when I was in high school we saved dissecting pigs and cats for much later in the year. If he lives in the US, that doesn't seem to add up because most high schools are on summer break or just starting back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 10:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously didn't read the tweets. 
Michael Broadhurst @iLoveThemBroads
Lame ass Japs! If they had beat us i would have recreated the Hiroshima incident

Alyssa Koenigsberg @lyskoenigsberg
@JustgotCapled: Suck it Japs! Haven't felt this good about beating Japan since Hiroshima. #Gold #USA

David Russell @davidrussell65
i havent seen that many japs cry since hiroshima #merica

Kyle Senchak @Maychak_Music
This soccer game will end the same way WWII did. With Hiroshima and Nagasaki burnt to the ground. #USAwillprevail

Wesley Alan Poe @Iwrestle_Utweet
USA went Godzilla on them japs. Hiroshima beat down. Quit soccer and build me a Honda. #USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 10:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, Hiroshima and Nagasaki should not have even been brought into the conversation. A lot of the tweets said "that was for Pearl Harbor!" which in reality is pretty harmless. If you feel that the lives of your people are equal to winning one soccer game, I'm not going to stop you from thinking that. I'll tell you you're wrong, but I can't stop you. The tweets that offended me were the ones that said something along the lines of "I haven't seen Japs cry like that since Hiroshima." If the situation were reversed, and a whole bunch of Japanese teens tweeted "Haven't seen whites cry like that since Pearl Harbor" there would be an outrage. Much bigger than the one we have on our hands here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 08:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you're coming from completely. Although I don't think I'm "buying into" anything, per se. I don't believe there should be a score board, but people see it that way. It's just the truth that Americans resent the Japanese because of something that happened 70 years ago. If something I've said can possibly influence them to be a little bit nicer or think about what they say before they've said it (and make an ass out of themselves) then I've done something to be proud of. I know I can't change everybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 08:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good wow or bad wow? 
**Edit:** Now that I look at it, probably bad. I'll admit that I was not alive for the bombings, but by "pain" I meant physical pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 07:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2,390 US citizens   soliders died and 1,178 were wounded on December 7th 1941. 64 Japanese soliders were killed and 5 were wounded. 

In early August of 1945, Hiroshima had an estimated population of 255,000 and Nagasaki had an estimated population of 195,000. After the bombings, Hiroshima had at least 66,000 dead (although there are estimates that go up to as much as 140,000 deaths) and 69,000 injured (not to mention future injuries due to radiation) while Nagasaki had at least 39,000 dead and 25,000 injured. 
To understand the suffering that the Japanese felt, think of this. If you were between 0-1000 ft of where the bomb was dropped, you would have a 93% mortality rate. 60% of the deaths in Hiroshima were caused by radiation burns, but in Nagasaki 95% of the deaths were caused by radiation burns. 

By looking at the bare minimum of the dead and wounded in both these events, 102,615 more Japanese died and 92,886 more Japanese were injured. It's a shame that all these human deaths are no more than notches on a score board, but that is the way the US seems to look at it - and we won. There is no questioning who went through more pain. Even today, almost 70 years later the Japanese have health problems due to lingering radiation. I can't even begin to understand how many deaths due to cancer or other things were caused by the bombings. 

It's disgusting that people in the US can be so rude and inconsiderate about something that they likely weren't even alive for. I know WWII veterans and they would never go on twitter and say "LOL THATZ 4 MY BUDDY ON THE ARIZONA. #wantsomewaterforthatburn" - even if they knew how to work twitter. It adds insult to injury when people do something so unnecessary. Good for you, your country killed hundreds of thousands of civilians and then beat their grand children in a soccer game. Feel good?

/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 05:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the US is no longer a "melting pot" it's more like a mold. KPOP has a thing for pushing the envelope, trying new things, and making it their own. Music in the US uses the same tactic to get a hit single every time. I can honestly admit that I *am* being biased, I have no objections to that. If it becomes a little bit more popular then I have no problems with that, but if I wake up every morning to see the thing I've been so passionate about for so long, I'm bound to start to hate it. It's similar to setting your favorite song as your alarm clock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 05:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care who enjoys it, I care about it being ruined. You've got to admit, the US has a talent for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 05:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, mainly. Also I'm sort of upset after learning today that most Kpop fans are apparently jerks like you. By that I mean, I thought that the KPOP community was tight-knit and we all found something in common to bond over. I figured even though there were band rivalries, a lot of the fans would stick together. 

That's the thing I don't want to see shattered. I've never been in a "fandom" or anything else like this before, and it was something special to me. The US media has a habit of taking things that are amazing, wringing them out like a towel, and moving on to the next thing. I would never want that to happen to KPOP.

Although, after today, with people like you I am somewhat surprised. Apparently the KPOP fandom is not really all that nice. Still, with the friends I've made from KPOP it is something I just don't want to see ruined. Maybe somebody like you couldn't understand that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 00:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dog and [my dog](http://imgur.com/0YoUe) look the same. But mine is 7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 23:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be overreacting but today I've gotten 5 texts, two telling me that a local radio station is using a "Fantastic Baby" soundclip, and a couple others telling me that Psy is playing on repeat in a store. It's just a little overwhelming for me. On one hand, I want the artists to be successful but on the other hand, I really don't want to see them on TV or see the terrible US media rip them to shreds like they do to American artists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 13:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently once a photo is posted on reddit, it can no longer be posted anywhere else. Who knew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 18:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "you all are stuid"

*Spoken like a true scholar.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 14:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this Dakota Fanning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 19:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One phrase that really bugs me is "where are you going?" The customers are either complete assholes due to their fear, or absolute idiots. By asking them where they are going you're going to run into one of two problems. First off, they can be rude and say something along the lines of, "I'm going where I'm supposed to, where do you think I'm going?" That causes unneeded confrontation and should probably be avoided. Second, they can become confused and begin to think they are actually going the wrong way. That can lead customers to take a wrong turn through a character door or an emergency exit which is annoying for the actors and ruins the mood for the customers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 15:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may sound like a hipster, but it would be really bitter-sweet for K-Pop to become a hit in the US. On one hand, I would love for my favorite artists to become as successful as they can, but on the other I kind of want them to be my dirty little secret that I share with other true fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 09:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She keeps falling for it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought things like this only existed on the internet - until I witnessed this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 08:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 22:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the game you're playing!

I just finished Majora's Mask for the first time in a while, and I was so annoyed at how often Tatl would go "DING!" I'm sure if you took a shot every time she did that you'd die. That goes for the guides for any of the console games, (Navi, Tatl, Midna, Fi, ect.)

Other possibilities could be:

Down a bottle when you die

Take a sip when you roll because you think rolling makes you go faster

Finish your drink when you're about to enter a boss chamber

Find an important item? (heart piece, whole heart, map, compass, weapon) take a shot!

If you're playing Skyward Sword, take a shot every time you jump off Skyloft and don't summon your Loftwing

Take a sip every time you make Epona run out of carrots

Sidequest? SHOTS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunter Thompson had a big adventure after a storm and only ended up with torn pads! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 22:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see your cardboard Deku Shield and raise you my hand carved Deku Shield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 15:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, he is. I am calling the vet to get the number as we speak. I'm not too sure how the chips work, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 15:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father and I just got back from the pound in Cheshire, they have had no calls or sign of him but hopefully they will as the day goes on. This information is really helpful as it ties in with all the other leads we've gotten. Thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 05:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had it for that long. Also:

Name: Hunter

Age: 7

Breed: Australian Shepard

Coat: Copper with a white chest   paws

Weight: 80lbs

He is neutered and does not have a collar!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 03:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You beat me to it, Shenan. Please get Hunter home! Also, who downvotes this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-19 03:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was me lolololol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed way more at the expression of the pig on the right. Looks like that slot is not just for coins - if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 13:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get out of my cityyyyyyy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 06:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god your dog would eat me! When he hears loud noises, he thinks he's a lap dog. Sometimes when he's too scared to be touched he'll hide under my bed. If you're really desperate, give your dog some meds. Idk what the proper dosage would be for a dog that big, just call your vet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 06:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog is a 90 lb baby. He freaks out over fireworks, thunder, even rain. The vet suggested giving him antianxiety pills, but they ended up giving him the shits. I came home from a party after a huge thunderstorm to find my mother cleaning up a shit pancake. Needless to say, the pills didn't work. Since I live in a place where thunderstorms are common, he has to go through this a lot. I've learned that sitting with him on my lap (which is uncomfortable for me) and petting him softly while talking to him calms him down. About 10 minutes after the thunder storm or fireworks are over he returns to his normal self. You just have to be there for your dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, have you ever wanted to do/learn something but you think you've passed the age to do so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 06:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently sparked up the urge to become a dancer. I'm only 19, but I feel like I'm way too old to learn how. That has caused me to become ashamed to look for classes in fear that people might look down on me for being really bad at my age. Has anybody else wanted to do something so badly but feel you've missed the chance to do so? If so, what? Did you end up doing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 11:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was so beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Young Link and Young Zelda cosplay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 11:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 10:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My username is relevant! I just started a new game a couple days ago and I'm on the Zora Temple. I haven't played since I was a kid, but does anybody else think that Mikau (Zora Link) is the father to LuLu's babies? In her diary, LuLu writes that she is scared to tell Mikau that her eggs have been taken, but reluctantly tells him so he can help find them. [But then he dies anyway...](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 09:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just commenting because I'm mad at you for painting over the nails with drylok in your scene last year. I tore up 2 bits trying to take them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 10:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you post a status about God and race, you're gonna have a bad time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 09:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 08:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this has already been asked, but why is Shirley the most prominent child of Fred? She seems to be the one always on TV and on the radio, much more than any of your other siblings. Do you think she'll take over the church when your father passes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently rescued this mother cat and her kitten. Found them a loving home last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 06:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's building season at the haunted attraction I work at, and these little guys wanted to help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 06:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad part is, everybody who posted on this status is 19 or older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister has an iPhone, I have a Droid x2. They both get the job done. It usually comes down to personal taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 23:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couples therapy. Men don't like to listen when their significant other says something is wrong. They believe it will blow over. If you feel that you are no longer happy, try therapy with him and see if he can change. If not, you don't deserve to be in an emotionally abusive and controlling relationship. Whatever you do, do not stay in a negative relationship for the sake of  your child. Children who grow up in a household filled with fighting parents turn out a lot less stable than children raised by divorced families. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
