<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4555</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 01:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha he doesn't look too tough, unlike the face in the wall... 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 17:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're close. Schizophrenia is a form of psychosis, just like psychotic depression is. Symptoms are shared since they are both psychosis. The anti-psychotics I'm taking are the same as what schizophrenics take.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 13:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is different because it manifests itself through auditory or visual hallucinations as well as having paranoid thoughts/feelings that I'm being watched or people are judging me. The sociopathic tendencies stem from my interaction with people. It's not that I have moments, but the fact that I just use people, manipulate and lie. Watching others suffer makes me feel good in some ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 13:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, ask as many as you want. Getting out more regardless of how crappy I feel. It always helps to push myself out, but not to be pushed out. If you have a friend you're worried about give them opportunities to do things invite them places and don't get upset if they say no. I don't want to generalize because there are different kinds of depression, and mine is very different from normal depression which it seems like you're aiming towards. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 12:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm good questions they seem scripted... I'm open about my depression not so much the psychosis. Whenever I tell people I'm depressed I hate when they ask why, and I try to tell them, but then they start hounding me with life stories so they can try to empathize. It doesn't seem empathizing it just makes me feel like they don't care/want to talk about themselves. So don't do that, just listen to what they have to say. 

This question is cyclical. If I knew the thoughts that I had then I would have the thoughts that I have, so meeting me I wouldn't want to help me because it is someone else. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 12:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that I'm still here amazes me sometimes, I tried to ignore or power through the things in my head almost my whole life up until a few months ago. When I started seeing help things got a little better, just opening up to someone was a huge deal.

For the second question I'm not sure if you mean in general or for some cases where it gets bad. So I'll answer both. 

In general just keeping my head off of bad thoughts. I have to constantly be aware of my thoughts and whenever I get negative thoughts I try to change the subject. 

For really bad days where hallucinations or voices are acting up, and just trying to ignore them not let them get to me. Reddit helps a lot for keeping my mind off of that when I'm alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
