<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 01:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes she is listed on there. Glad to hear I can stick with the nipple creams and gel pads, because they're the only things keeping me sane at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 01:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I actually looked at my insurance policy again and saw how to get it covered. It wasn't clear the first time around when I read it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rant: Saw a lactation consultant today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 06:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You caused your baby to lose all his nursing instincts." 

Saw an LC today with my 2 week old. I wanted someone to evaluate my technique and help me out with his painful latch, as well as hopefully get a good pep talk. Lack of sleep from new baby, combined with some possible PPD, and marathon cluster feelings has made formula look oh so tempting as of late.

She asked me to get him on the breast, and I used the technique that was taught to me by a different LC at the hospital: football hold, and using free hand to feed the nipple to his wide open mouth. LO was more than happy to go to town on the boob juice. She immediately wanted me to unlatch him and use the cradle hold to try and get him to self latch. Baby was upset about the interrupted feeding and didn't know quite what to do. He wasn't feeling around for my breast or bobbing his head up and down to try and latch. That's when she said it. "You caused your baby to lose all his nursing instinct." She also told me I'm doing baby a disservice by using nipple cream and my medela gel pads. She said I need to stop using them immediately to get my nipples desensitized to baby's feeding. Anyone else been told this? 

I'm sorry! Had I known what to do I wouldn't have booked a lactation consultant! Last thing I needed was to be made to feel inadequate. Ugh! Just needed to rant about this visit. Worst of all, baby still has an uncomfortable latch, and I'm out $100 for this consultation because insurance won't cover it. Need some motivation to keep going here, because in seriously starting to burn out! 

Edit: Thanks everyone for the comments and support! Before LO was born, I was able to easily express a few table spoons of colostrum no problem so I had the false confidence that BFing would come naturally. However, after he was born via emergency c-section, my colostrum supply dried up after the first 3 feedings and I was forced into supplementing with formula (By SO and Mom, at the suggestion of our pediatrician after baby lost nearly 15% of his initial birth weight) before leaving the hospital. Milk took 5 days to come in which added even more stress. Once the leche started flowing, we had a good few days before I started blistering and bleeding. It got to the point where I dreaded feeding time which is why I went to go see a consultant. Happy to have confirmation that the particular one I saw was probably just an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 22:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 40+3. That, or "take a nice long walk".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought I would! (At 40+2). Saw OB today and I'm still only 1cm and 67% effaced. (Been sitting at 1cm for the last three weeks). BP has been in normal range, but inching up, and I got trace proteins in my urine today for the first time. US and NST scheduled for Monday, and possible induction after that if nothing happens over the weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 15:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For bringing on labor? Probably not, since I'm still here 16 hours later now at 40+2 with no signs of progress. Definitely worth it for some R R though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
