<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7770</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 20:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I agree,  they are making us do much more work in market. They give us more work load and expect us to finish faster. I do like working at target, I'm just a little overwhelmed with the work load  currently . I recently saw a documentary on how evil Walmart is and that's why I asked some of these questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questionable work ethics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 23:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey target redditors!  I just wanted to ask a few questions? 
Does the target you work encourage or discourage over time? 
Is the health plan worth getting? ( I'm 18 about it hit my 90 days, have diagnosed depression and adhd. Not other medical issues!) 
Has the target you worked for done anything morally wrong to any of its workers? 
Do you like working at target lol? 
FYI I work in the market section of target, any feedback would be appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First post, do you like ties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 19:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 08:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Stat track ch mw Bayonet and ft hydroponic?  2:1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 07:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Stat track case hardens Bayonet, and a hydroponic ak 47 for your fade c: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so I figured out the lag in my messages,  you have do delete all your messages and the lag will disappear... As for power saving I really haven't noticed a drastic change on my phone!  But Goodluck hope you can find something  that will allow you to reduce your battery usage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
