<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7030</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teleporter/replicator are based on the same basic tech just implemented for different purposes. Transporter limit is generally 40,000 kilometers. I think the limit would be on the energy side and practicality. Why not have a 1000 industrial replicators and a 1000 teleporters working in unison. Replicate the part, then teleport it in place. Rinse and repeat until the ship is built. Since replicators can pre-determine temperature why not replicate a beam with "hot ends" that when teleported to the assembly in orbit automatically welds into place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I know one thing, if a transformer suddenly comes to life and realizes it's just a lever...It would probably be quite pissed.](http://i.imgur.com/mz4NoJO.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the heat emitted by the LED have the same effect as the light? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am one of the bottom left corner clicks. My reasoning was "I'm not going to be a sheep and click where you tell me to." So I clicked as far away as the suggested spot that I could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confidence level when pronouncing someone dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a good deal. Just make sure you wear a cup. If it is a craigslist thief they like to donkey punch these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dream is an i5? That is like if MLK had just settled and said "Meh, ok well just take Mississippi."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brut?...OK we need to have a talk one PCMR to another. Unless this is a very specific situation where you are dating a daddy's girl and you found out her dad uses Brut and you are using it to smell like her dad to get in her pants, UNLESS it is this very rare of situations you need to upgrade your deodorant like you did your GPU's. Next time skip the K-Mart special and shell out a couple extra bucks for something that doesn't smell like a WWII sailors uniform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work in shipping (software integration side) this basically means FedEx either lost, or destroyed your package. You are not the shipper, the company you purchased it from is (AKA you can't do shit). They are responsible for filing a claim with FedEx. Get your refund from company you got the stuff from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the Fedora? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that really your dick in the Hangover the Vegas one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started my career that way as well! At like 4 or 5. Are you my older sister Rebecca? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a store thief. Poor-ish family. Used to steal Lego kits from stores. I'd say about 80% of my Lego's were stolen. I used to yell "Mama" and run through the checkout lane sneak grab a bag. I was misdirecting before I even knew what it meant. Then go to the toys section load it up and just walk out with it. I also stole Uberraschung Eier by the shit ton (I mean we literally would dump a full tray of them in a bag and walk out). Looking for those mini monster truck windup cars and the Metal Medieval figures. Stole so may of those I actually started to throw the chocolate away (got sooo sick of it). Eventually my racket came crashing down when my parents got suspicious of all the new toys I had and a friend of mines father came into the store and caught us in the act. In the end I probably stole $1K of Lego's, a couple hundred of misc toys, and about $400 of Kinder Uberraschung Eier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming in late on this, as an Ascendant(? one whom has ascended) I rarely meddle in the dealings of console peasants. Is Sony using the Burger King method of marketing? Where more stacks are more better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously the Inception theme. Freak the shit out of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elementary school in the 90's. This kid named Ben was always doing crazy shit. He crushed up a bunch of smarties in the library and started randomly snorting them with a $1 bill. Librarian caught him and the Principal nearly called the cops until they found out he was snorting candy. For 8th grade graduation Ben shaved his eyebrows, dyed his hair orange, and wore a burnt orange suit. Good times. Last I heard (a year or two ago) he was in prison for slinging dope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I'm still stuck on the fact that a dragon that lays eggs produces milk...I thoroughly checked the Wyvern's and I see no tits.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 14:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you don't play ARK so move on. There are a TON of issues that have needed fixing for months. Dino drift on server restarts, tamed dino's falling through the floors, eggs falling through the floors, structure snapping, death from stuck character vibrating (don't even know how to explain this one), lighting issues, holes in the map, dino pathing AI, tamed dino following mode pathing, can't breed water dinos,  the list goes on and on and on. Instead of fixing the base game issues, they release a fucking DLC?? Yeah I guess I'm a "mad gamer". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 06:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There will be no DLC or in game transactions" Wildcard on ARK... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live cam feed of Hurricane Hermine rolling into Cedar Key, FL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 06:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 09:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yeah this is where I quick scope newbs from across the map, oh and my Shuttlecock trophy, no big deal." Gettin the ladies wet since 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dayz Comes in. 220 sq/km map. Drops mic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awe snap. The UN better send them a stern written letter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah! With the external antenna connector. Made my first yagi from my Orinoco Gold with a Pringles can.  Good days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These images are actually of the first effects shots for Star Wars. When George saw them he was appalled at the poor quality and cheesy look that he reshot all of them. He said if he left them in they would have ruined the movie. He scrapped all of the effects shots and started from the ground up supervising the entire process. This eventually lead to the development of ILM. 

edit: adding this link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FSuDjjlIPak  at the end you can see the shots of the fottage that was actually used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The AMP says Masterrace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A: That is not real cream. (It looks gelatinous aka the cream you can freeze) B: That looks like a factory crust if I have ever seen one. C: [It looks like this crap.](https://i5.walmartimages.com/asr/2c12f1b7-8f12-4851-bfe3-7d3b6c5d9900_1.645942ed817d0dbac72b17571863e22a.jpeg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 05:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All hail Klugen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As close as they are, Ryan had ample chance to slip Michael a little muscle relaxant. MUhaha MUAHHAA MUAHAHAHAHAH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 05:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice timelapse. (look at boat masts) Not a single lightning strike. It's 3 or 4 lightning strike images stacked on top of each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That tree never stopped playing catch with you. As the ages past, it watched you grow into the man you are today. Best Dad anyone could ever have. RIP tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 16:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So instead of being called a "faaaag" by a 12 year old you will now be called a "crippled faaaag". I'm sure this will end well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah had a "like" moment as well. The only people I have on Facebook are my family that I like, and high school friends to keep in touch. No coworkers no friends (due to the fact if I saw their emoticon spammed FB posts we would probably no longer be friends). One day Facebook suggests my fucking landlord. Who's last name I didn't even know. She popped right up in my suggestions. I was genuinely creeped out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs more points. Would watch on Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a fancy bar first time in years with a gloomed out friend who's relationship just feel apart. Didn't want to be there. Did it out of pity. I'm a solid 3/10 got the cheapest draft beer they had at the bar, turn and immediately soak the most gorgeous 11/10 girl I have ever seen. I'm freaking out and without even thinking I dab her chest with a napkin apologizing profusely. Then I freak out and start apologizing even more realizing I had basically just groped her. She was so sweet about it. Didn't think anything of it. Here I am a lowly 3/10 in a place I don't belong speaking to the most beautiful woman I have ever meet and we are totally hitting it off. And then, just like in the movies, her boyfriend Chad comes up and that's it. What did you actually think the nerd gets the girl? get the fuck out of here. That shit doesn't even happen in the movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yeah good try, unless it looks like a Viking siege ship you're doing it wrong.](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uU4gesNsDDI/maxresdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 22:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call this the Smiling Asshole. 
First off the person making your sandwich is hard of hearing and possible doesn't speak English. It does not matter if the artist was born in Wisconsin and enunciates the English language perfectly at a proper volume, to you they are deaf and foreign. Therefor you must speak loudly and repeat everything twice with emphasis. 

Flat bread, make sure to mention your intolerance for gluten, Pepperoni, South West Sauce, no Cheese (the treatment of cows in the dairy industry is atrocious be sure to mention this loudly and look around to make sure everyone heard you). Add as many jalapenos that is legally allowed to be placed on a flatbread. Lettuce, and then insist on having it toasted. You like hot welted lettuce.

Then ask for another piece of flatbread on top, look them square in the eyes, and say now make it smile with sriracha. Ask them to draw a smiley face on it. Never break eye contact. Never look at the sandwich. When they ask "Is this enough?" you say "More...MOOOREEE." Never break eye contact. This is war. There can be only one winner. Push that sauce to the limit. You want that flatbread to look like Sansa's wedding night sheets. When it's all set and done proclaim, "I guess you really are an artist." Pay with change if you are a guy, or slightly moist dollar bills pulled from your bra if you're a woman. 

Edit: Oh forgot to add. After you are done paying tell them you that you know that you can be a pain. Pull a $20 bill out of your pocket, look like you are about to put it into the tip jar. Then use your thumb to slide a penny out from behind the bill and let it drop into the tip jar. Pocket the twenty and walk away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Cherry MX Switches cost on average $2.50 and have an average life span of 35 Million key strokes. I was just looking to save $.00000057. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The heist leader in my story is named Opie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 19:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a splash of light and a dance of sparks the three would be robbers materialized precisely 24 hours before they had left. "Alright boys." Remarked the leader Opie. "Looks like this plan of ours is going to...plan." All of them Chuckled. Opie than repeated the entirety of the plan just to make sure everyone was on the same page. Out of the corner of the dimly lit ally a voice suddenly called from what looked like a pile of garbage. The robbers turned to see a homeless man groggily lying in a heap of cardboard. Opie asked him "What did you just say?" The homeless man replied "If you really had a time-machine why didn't you just get the lottery numbers?...dumb asses." The homeless man then turned back around in an attempt to catch a few more winks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 23:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once Google goes nationwide...Xfinity is fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is how they could have saved the show. They should have all been in prosthetic and makeup to look like Jeremy (played by the Ginger guy), James (the German woman), and Richard (the guy from Friends). The should have lip synced to recordings of their voices from old shows (all things the BBC can do since they own the rights) and do terrible impressions of their voices. Totally pretend like this is what they are going to do from here on out. Kinda like Chef from South Park. Do the news like this, and a little something else (don't let the crowd in on it, let them stay in the shock they would have been in). Then do some kind of reveal like "Ok guys, this isn't going to work" and tear off the makeup and prosthetics "its way too hot in all this crap. Can't we just do a show about all the ridiculous sports cars we are all passionate about?" Then just walk it off like it was a bad idea. And go on with the show a new. Skip all this shit about "reliving" past episodes with the laser crap and the Reliant Robins. That is British comedy. That would have been amazing to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people on Reddit do this? Is it funny? Just honestly trying to understand. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a far more realistic rendering of what a post nuclear apocalypse landscape would look like if there was no nuclear winter to kill all the plants off. Look at Chernobyl; it's an overgrown forest of plant life. And Bears. Radioactive Bears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of bomb is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah agree with you. It doesn't compare to the MOD. And I should have said "all the pain of the MOD and then some" in regards to Standalone. The MOD is a million times better, but the random door is still 70% more lethal than the average player you might run into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time in almost 2 years this weekend. Quite a few things pissed me off right off the bat. Asking "Hey how do I get this to work?" the answer usually is "Oh that's been broken for a while now, no joy compare." Example being Range Finder, nope don't work. Spending 4 hours getting burlap strips just to find out the Net Spawns are bugged (1 spawn per server that randomly jumps around every 15min...) Getting a vehicle running and not even 30sec later it's glitched. Spinning wheels...get a friend to reset it. Then a couple minutes in going to get fuel boom battle-eye DC...YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME...dead of course. So yeah it's all the pain of the MOD with none of the cool shit like helicopters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 22:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> De-cap the Die. Go on eBay get some used microscope lenses. Buy a kaleidoscope and dump all the dumb plastic shit out of it and hot-glue that new lens in there. Place CPU die in kaleidoscope for sick ass cpu die kaleidoscope action. Kaleidoscope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
