<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6292</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 02:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spurned my advances because she "wanted to save herself for marriage."

One week later sleeps with some random douche and boasts about it to everyone.

Just realized she was was a scumbag stacy, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cartoon network has kinda gone to hell since I was a kid, but the one show that stands out as truly terrible is Uncle Grandpa. Seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 17:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was supposed to watch the house for a week while my family and i were away. We came back, she was gone, 7 large ashtrays have been left in the house filled with thousands of used cigarettes, dozens of trays of half eaten moldy food (not to mention the dishes) left on virtually every flat surface, and as for what was stolen? XBox, Gamecube, PS2, Dreamcast, VCR, DVD player, at least 50 games from a variety of platforms, half my mom's jewelry collection, two TVs (CRTs, no less), half of our movie collection (at least 100 vhs/dvds) and my dad's car. 

All taken and sold for drug money, except the car. That was found on the side of the road 50 miles away two weeks later.

TL/DR: Sister stole almost every last gen game console, lots of high end electronics, dad's car, the house's hygeine, and our family's sense of security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 03:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw post, 777 karma. Didn't want to change it, so I came here to comment my approval. On this page, and it's up to 1018 karma. So, eff it. Upvote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 05:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok... how did you get partial percentages? Did the goody bags drop more than one item each?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 06:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She knows everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 01:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you can smell it on anyone who's even touched the bar within the last 12 hours. From thirty feet away. It overrides any other scent. It's terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 20:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irish Spring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 16:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that would definitely explain it. I've tried Dos Equis, Sam Adams, Guinness, Blue Moon (certainly the least offensive on taste), Killians (i think, anyway), and at least three sips of Bud before I just threw the cup away. So at least I gave it a fair shot.

I'm not one to persist in blindly trying things that prove simply unpleasant. Point me toward one you know to be good, though, and I'll certainly give it a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 03:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beer. Just, in general. They all taste about like pee smells.

Let the outrage flow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 01:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just throwing this out there, mold on your cheese doesn't mean the whole block has gone bad. Cut off the mold, what's beneath is still good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 00:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instant upvote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 01:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 04:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's another turtle on it's belly. Turtle on turtle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 13:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 23:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overworld, then. Give me something new to look for underground, the surface is fine as is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 18:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, seriously? Stop messing with the world generation, add some new things to MINE, give us new things to CRAFT. Please?

Am I the only one?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 17:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally! Microsoft has caught up with what Sony's had going since day 1 of the PSN store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 06:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I should know better than to post when tired. What I meant to say is that if anyone ever comes up with some new information, it will likely show up on here less than a picosecond later, given the fanbase and the dearth of knowledge we have right now. You won't miss anything if you watch closely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 05:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes, lesson learned. Don't post when tired, it sounds angry. Sorry, gents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 03:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The release was barely a month ago. 2 people are working on it. They are notorious for not telling people things.

Calm. Down. And. WAIT.

Like the rest of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 04:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My rule of thumb: If the weapon is better than the one I have now, equip it and improve it even more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 03:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, not gonna lie... at first, I thought this was a screencap from Skyrim.
Then I saw the tent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 03:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you never know. Still, lots of positive reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 15:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Try this.](http://www.kumbaso.com/borderlands-2-season-pass-pc-download-steam/?setCurrencyId=2) Game   season pass for $23.
Worth a shot. Never used the site myself, but it seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 01:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Speak of the devil...](http://www.amazon.com/My-Little-Pony-Rainbow-Sweatshirt/dp/B00ATG54LK/ref=pd_sbs_hg_36) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 03:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 years and counting.
I've seen dozens succumb to curiosity. Don't do it. Just... don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, have never experienced anything remotely like what you're describing here. I keep my bread in random places around my kitchen, but usually on top of the fridge. My bread often lasts upwards of three weeks a loaf, and it never molds for me. I only ever toss the heels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 03:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just think, that's only how long you have to wait until it'll let you play it. It'll still be downloading for a while after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 03:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually had this happen to me! Ran a dungeon in late evening, killed the boss off at 12:56 game time and leveled up. As I was allocating the skill points, suddenly I'm attacked by an ogre and 3 collies! I dodged out of the menu, back into the boss room, where the guy I JUST KILLED is waiting for me! Managed to survive, but I had to fight my way back out of the dungeon too!
Fortunately, I got two more levels from the whole ordeal.

Tl/dr: had to fight a boss twice with no recovery, Wollay plz fix! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 08:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you middle click/drag on the map, it'll fill in all the places you've been 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 13:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess? A less-than-deserving title that will release closer to the time it gets decided.
It'll be fresher in their minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 02:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent entirely too long trying to understand the size difference between the two soldiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 23:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can! Vamps need blood to survive, Zoms eat flesh. They are getting SOME of the necessary sustenance from their feedings, but not enough to keep them from decomposing. So, they continually regenerate just enough of themselves to keep moving, while rotting off the bits that can't be sustained on their diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has actually been my zombie theory for years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-30 17:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 15:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having just completed it on "normal" difficulty, I can tell you that it's not very difficult if you can manage stealth. The game has a very shallow learning curve, so even if you're not used to stealth based games, you should be able to pick it up pretty quick. 
It's also not your standard survival horror game. It's more an adventure game, with zombies. You can, if you want to, kill every enemy you encounter, it will just be very difficult in the earlier stages.
If you give this one a shot, I imagine you'll have a good time, given the games you listed as interesting to you. Try it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 18:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of looks like a yellow Captain Qwark (Ratchet and Clank). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 18:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only things that will win me back:
1) Turn off the goddam Orwellian camera
2) Lift the mandatory 24 hour server sync, or delay it out a week/month
3) Implement low-cost used title license transfer fee for used games, instead of the one and done bullsh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 06:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been informed that more than five exclamation marks on any one sentence is a sign of an unbalanced mind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was waiting for someone to post this. All the upvotes, sir, for time-traveling truth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 00:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Soulsh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 00:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be lovely if people would post video links instead of images. You know, for those of us who have to work and don't see it live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 08:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously thought this was a Borderlands post when I clicked. Severe double-take confusion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 08:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been WAITING SO LONG for this day! *tears of joy* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 08:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you handle your bill paying online, no calls have to happen. Took me all of twenty minutes to hit up all of my billers and update. Could be worth it in this case, especially if you don't have/want to make a paypal account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 07:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another easy method: Call your credit/debit card issuer and report your card missing. It will be cancelled, a new one sent to you within a week, and Microsoft won't be able to pull payments from it anymore. You might get emails about it from Microsoft, but then you can just sit back and laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 07:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be the only person who remembers this, but... It's Happy Bunny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 05:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, no. You are insane. Quite around the bend, in fact. But I'll tell you another thing: All the best people are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 13:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlikely.

Problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 00:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE read the first four words and suddenly have Secret Agent Man pop into their heads? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xbox One
X-one
Xone.

Xbox One. In the Xone.

Completely irrelevant, but your post made me think of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 13:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairly certain this is the only flow chart brought forth on Reddit that I will ever have an actual use for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 19:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't like being the only one who sees creepy eyed people in the background of photos plotting world domination, is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 18:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I wasn't the only one to notice this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 03:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be the bearer of bad news, but it appears that your towel rack is not level. Or perhaps the rest of the room is slanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 03:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nifty sculpture, but... honestly, I was just too freaked out by the goat dog. Gog. Doat? Thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 21:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came close here last year, but only for a couple weeks. Enjoy your molten bragging rights! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 18:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're willing to tiptoe quietly outside your established comfort zone...

Lost Odyssey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 18:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 98 degrees Fahrenheit is an "oh god why?" Just you wait 'til you hit triple digits, friend.

Oklahoma: above 113, most days after June. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seriously looks like he's using DDR moves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 13:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You, sir, get an upvote.
Not for the cat. For the poster. Classic Turtles FTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 03:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do it. Seriously. Make it happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one in this subreddit who doesn't know what the hell these "teenager skins" are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 11:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd been wondering when someone would make this connection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 12:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to witness it. Just walk on by. Go gather flowers on the other side of town. Pretend that everything's okay, knowing that just out of earshot Roggvir is taking his last breath. It'll be okay as long as you can't hear it... right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 12:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me, or does anyone else see the word Jesabel instead of Iesabel? (youtube trailer, http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wp9NYs2o2u8 )

That said, looks absolutely fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 17:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me a couple looks to figure out what I was seeing. At first I thought it was a huge mutated alien, um... thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 17:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it was an unintended glitch to start with, but Notch didn't do anything about it when it was discovered. Still there even with Jeb in charge, so I'm starting to think they'll never remove it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 16:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunate, yet, somehow... intriguing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 16:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A creative person would find some lava and water near each other and use the redstone exploit (link: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BWSOuBbMjKU ) to create a nether portal and gather glowstone. Glowstone!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 05:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EXPERIENCED driver in the U.S., I also wonder why people do this. Especially when I am in the right hand lane on a three lane highway with no other traffic around whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 12:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kingdom Hearts. Not too difficult controls, hack   slash style gameplay, and best of all it's primarily disney movies and characters. Square Enix teams up with Disney to bring us a wonderful little RPG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 13:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this game to death, but have never beaten it, or made it past the third disc, and probably never will. 
I made it to the same point three times, halfway through disc three, and something would always happen so that I could not finish the game. 
First, my memory card malfunctioned - it was one of those with the multiple slots that you select with a button. The buttons stopped working, and my save was lost shortly after starting the third disc.
Second time, the save data corrupted on me for no discernable reason - again on the third disc.
Third time, made it to disc three, no problem - suddenly, farther than I'd ever gotten before by only an hour's gameplay - third disc freakin' cracked in half when I put it into the PS2. 
I'm afraid to download it to my PS3; it'd probably brick the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 02:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the marketplace: Psychonauts and Beyond Good   Evil. Two awesome single player puzzle/platformer games that don't get enough love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 06:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic rap, or C-rap. Let's just save time and call it what it is. Crap.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 05:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moriarty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 01:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heavily reminiscent of Chrono Trigger. Lucca mods Robo into a scooter. Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 15:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone gone into the Workshop and made a test chamber to check this out yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 14:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's all I needed.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KmGsTbBSyF0)

And if that's not enough... watch [this](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1IO5JDrAYJU feature=relmfu), [this (claptrap wub wub)](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VW7qO_wpfvk feature=related), and, if you actually want to see how it plays, [this.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZcoNXQio7fE feature=relmfu) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 22:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [relevant to title](http://lesliebloom.files.wordpress.com/2011/09/77556815f34bcc51e97fce55f87d07ae_5.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 14:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I have to contribute here is that Borderlands doesn't work with the regular wired controller, you have to use a generic one for some reason (Logitech works for me). Even then, when I try to use the gamepad, the forward/backward movement controls are inverted. I'm sure there's a fix out there, but I just found it easier (read: more responsive and accurate) to just get used to the keyboard and mouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 00:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "wwwwhheeeeEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE-*bzzrtt*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 14:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by all rights, I should still be on my first 360. Sold it to my brother for money to move in with my now ex-wife. He's still got it, and it still works like a beaut from what I hear, purchased in 2006.
Now I'm on my 5th, all others sold because of the same horrible woman. Not one of them ever broke on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 14:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here you go!](http://yaoihaven.wetpaint.com/page/Furry+Animations) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 15:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you expect to get rid of racism? -Mike Wallace, 60 Minutes

Stop talking about it.
[-Morgan Freeman](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2d2SzRZvsQ)

Seriously, guys. They're just really stupid looking shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 17:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Chrome, click the Wrench icon, go to Tools, Extensions, then find RES in the list and uncheck the Enable button.

Not sure about Firefox or other browsers, but it's most likely in the addon manager for the given platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn internet, delaying my reply long enough for it to be worthless, lol. Hope this doesn't last long, without my Never Ending Reddit, I might actually have to go outside! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 00:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turned RES back on to confirm, problems are back. Weed, bacon, minecraft character models, random unrelated images. RES is busted, or at least for me that's the issue. Did you try refreshing Reddit after turning off RES? That reset the links for me, and now they work just fine
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 00:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was having the same problem, then I noticed that these things tended to appear halfway through the second page of Never Ending Reddit. So, I turned off the Reddit Enhancement Suite. Now everything looks fine, not sure what's going on.

Another odd thing, my comment history showed old posts with strange links to unrelated images as well, that's fixed by turning off RES as well. Someone broke RES!

EDIT: Turned RES back on to confirm, problems are back. Weed, bacon, minecraft character models, random unrelated images. RES is busted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 00:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was having the same problem, then I noticed that these things tended to appear halfway through the second page of Never Ending Reddit. So, I turned off the Reddit Enhancement Suite. Now everything looks fine, not sure what's going on.

Another odd thing, my comment history showed old posts with strange links to unrelated images as well, that's fixed by turning off RES as well. Someone broke RES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
