<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4846</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...makes other cars feel cluncky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 23:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only warm up period I see is the 0.5 seconds between putting my foot on the brake and seeing all the icons turn off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 16:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ive noticed my commuting... chi has drastically improved since going EV. in the gas car: gas brake clutch brake gas gas gas...  over and over in traffic probably raised my blood pressure or something. when i got my 500e i noticed i was much more relaxed, since the motor regen took care of 65% of the braking tasks and the rest were just a slight rest the foot on the peddle maneuver. the S is a totally transcendent experience in traffic. standard regen basically eliminated my need to foot shuffle and now autopilot... everyone at work wonders why im so happy in the morning now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 16:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are very few things that i still enjoyed about my gas miata that were characteristics of the ICE power plant. most of my joy came from the weight and the suspension setup...   one thing im surprised i do not miss is the noise. my miata had a sweet track header and muffler that... though cool sounding at full bore, was super annoying almost any other time. now that ive been EV driving for several years anytime i hear WHHHAHAAAA, wwwhahahaaAAHAHAHH,  waaaaahhhaHAHAHAHAHH... i just shake my head and say... all that noise for nothing. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 20:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> miata. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing, the SC's likely have no more information to give.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 10:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats entertainment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this guy rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spaceX next mission: mine asteroids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 03:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yah... thats pretty dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0.21, next car in line is a tatra. not bad company to be with i say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 01:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> given Chrysler looooong legacy of financial disarray, i sincerely hope not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 20:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just wait till you use it, i felt the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 16:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, how about helping the company exist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 01:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interior room. 3 looks a little cramped by comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> half, because a black bit of vinyl would be just about as useful as a fake grille </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> first rule of reservation number is dont share your reservation number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> order it and then buy some black vinyl if you want a big black nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 18:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats pretty good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 08:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 08:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i did but i dont think it changed anything. all the field entries were the same.    firefox mytesla login first, chrome just model3 page, both had the same fields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 07:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure, but demolition man is a WAY better movie. 3 sea shells and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 07:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/FlpPR_GgwEc?t=52 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 07:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a man has got to charge... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 07:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> double click opens the trunk, which is required to get the charge adapter out. if im too fast the trunk stops mid open... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sooooo much question dodging. i love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ok, now that the reveal happened... can i complain about the charge port opening feature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mirrors not folding all the time, whatever...   all doors opening when set to just driver..  i can live with. what the heck is up with using the key fob to open the charge port? 5 second press, hear some internal noises, then another press for a few seconds to open...   yourgh!!!


and yes i have used the screen option to open, but by the time im ready with the j1772 adapter and cable the car has autolocked and the port is closed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah... # does something VERY different on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #teslakiller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check out the photos post. looks like the p car has carbon fiber wheels.   = super light an very strong. good for range and performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damnit... too busy putting in cc info to take the car in. wife yelled, "lets order it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> woah. cf wheels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ap and supercharger standard, thats a pritty big deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> model3.tesla.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha... well ive been watching the same videos over and over for the last 35 min, my 16oz are already gone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah. this is awesome.

might need to add the extension https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-cast/boadgeojelhgndaghljhdicfkmllpafd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is also true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got a p90d because its fast as you know what, the environmental aspect is just one of the many perks. the biggest one is not standing around like a mouth breather at the fuel station... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well the cotomer stories videos are not bad...    just need like 25 more of them because im tired already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 04:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like you, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 04:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> speaking of that, i see no connection between mytesla and the model3 page...   hopefully they know me by name only? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 04:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the site is grrriiiiiinnnndddeding to a halt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awww... but all I have is beer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> horrible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you guys should send someone down the street to get some breakfast ajarski! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> nature approves: two teslas and a rainbow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 05:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> knowing how much my tires cost, i have yet to push the p90d hard into a corner. everyone says it handles great...   maybe one day ill say, "aww screw it!"

i should do a comparison of my experiences driving the 500e again for the first time in a month! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool thing about heavy machinery is they can rip up pretty much anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watch the videos on teslamotors.com and it will only take as long as signing, setting up profiles or bluetooth. 45 min. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing on my feb 2016...   lazy burbank service center.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 15:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> last car I bought was a 2011 mazda miata for $20,000. after that was 2 leased evs each for $200 a month.

the model s is new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 23:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your on a roll today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 15:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 01:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go full on and test the p90d, just because they will let you. you can understand how the 70 and 90 feel and still get the wallop that is L mode. might as well right? i mean... it is there.    sounds more like what would Lucifer do but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 23:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell, 3 of my long time friends want to drive my p90d and dont even want to let them. i 100% trust them in most areas and i know from going to the racetrack with them that they can handle cars.

still does not want to make me let them take it for a spin. good luck... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plastic, the car hauler...   really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> becauseCUSTOM!!!!111 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 04:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh good, I was gona say "aww gyp!" would kinda suck to pay 30k over a car that is just a software change. ludicrous mode at 10k is probably a software switch but somehow im ok with that...       wife also calls me a chump for going p90dL... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 04:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> while considering the p90d vs p90dL I imagined that this would be an option. got to say im glad I went full in from the beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 04:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im surprised you fixed it! interesting location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 00:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could be brighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> credit card for sure, possibly cashiers check, maybe wire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> high five! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> per facebook:
"Racing an Alfa 4C against an Alfa 4C ...being pulled by a Tesla Model X.

Jonny, driving the red 4C, was convinced I would die. No luck, my friend, not today." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 18:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unfortunately i dont have my HOV tags yet so i cannot comment on the car pool lanes specifically. after driving for several weeks with ap on i have noticed the only parts the car makes my more alert is the sections of curving, dipping, concrete expansion joint sections.

for instance this section of the 5 north:
https://www.google.com/maps/@34.1745477,-118.3067847,19z/data=!3m1!1e3

and the 210 east:
https://www.google.com/maps/@34.1508515,-118.1533087,18z/data=!3m1!1e3

i dont know what it is about these sections. but every day the car waits until the last possible moment to start turning. unsettling if there are other cars on either side.

might be the concrete pavement does not work as well as asphalt? 

everywhere else it works fantastically. im not even bothered by the fact i dont have HOV tags yet, as if there is any traffic the autopilot just does its thing and i just gaze out the window. stress free the way to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 05:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...show up at a store?
or wait till the next day and place it online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 01:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh i know, i took my miata there in 2013 for the yearly leguna seca miata track weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmmm, i did want to take the 500e last year but the drive up from los angeles would have been terrible.

...do i want to track a $100,000 car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but... they covered up the autopilot camera. manually driving to the track is so 20th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least that one is not an ICE conversion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 00:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just keep picturing the sport bikes i have seen with awesomely wide track tires on the rear...    with a huge flat wear mark down the center from never leaning into a corner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> op needs to check out http://www.plasmaboyracing.com/whitezombie.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly. part of the deal is crazy acceleration without the need for a stripped out interior and no air conditioning!

...which is exactly what my previous fastest car offered me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> since so many enjoyed my photo on TMC and /teslamotors, i figured i would share it here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> chocobo, because asian wife... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 03:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> premium interior adds some cool lights around the cabit, fog lights, maybe the turning lights and best of all the auto open close trunk. non of this is necessary but all nice to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 19:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also its just a crappy rebel t1i, so its inherently blurry. the photo was uploaded near the cameras max resolution so no matter what the edges show up soft. this photo was focused smack on the car and still looks "blurry" https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1575/24662772204_64a7a7b6e6_o.jpg  just a bad sensor.    just enjoy the damn photo will yah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 19:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope, was not on auto. i just have shaky hands.

also... im not a photographer so, whatevers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 16:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uh...  what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats right, no red brakes either. thought about badge delete...   but I said screw it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 hours in, and i have totally fallen for it. truly a fabulous means of transportation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 19:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% worth it. autopilot is a godsend and ludicrous mode is stupidly fast. such a nice car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 19:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i did pick up in burbank. features or television animation? i work under the burbank television animation offices :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 16:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahah! i had the car in my possession for 20 min before i dropped it off for xpel front wrap. the car was in their shop for most of the day so i figured i would go to work while waiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 06:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really digging the complexity of it. different times of day it shows a different depth. very pleased with this car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 00:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha, yah... vfx can be a pretty boring job. Thanks though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> took delivery today, made a sketch when i got to work... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 22:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 06:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> turnaround may be quick, but information updating is definitely not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 06:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good luck and godspeed, i can only imagine your torment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 06:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good luck and godspeed.     i can only imagine your torment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 06:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i test drove the P90DL, the pasadena store asked what was my timeframe. i said oh ill order by the end of the year. they wanted to give me a CPO car that day. i really though...   maybe i should! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 05:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats awesome! though, im pretty sure the car will be delivery ready before the status changes. its just been that way the whole order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 05:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha i forgot you browse here!     dude, i am so freaking excited. probably wont share anything about it on facebook though. your in a special group! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, just really really late. ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> excellent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it will, and it just gets worse. hahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as much as im excited about it, i really dont think its worth me standing in a que all day. i can wait for online the next day and im not on the verge of death do be one of the first cars built. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 19:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well i ordered at the worst time, immediately at the end of Q4, which means my wait was the longest possible to build. shipping would have been worse if i was east coast though...

its a p90dL, pano roof, autopilot, air, tan leather, black headliner, premium interior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 19:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> order placed 12/25 confirm 01/01 production began 2/11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> just pre-apologizing in case i break the mytesla page with my constant refreshing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 16:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 02:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ill be joining you soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> los angeles, it should have been here 72 hours ago, ha! lazy truck drivers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 15:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. mines been done since Thursday and today marks the first date in the estimated delivery range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 03:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn... none of those are my car. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 15:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well I would totally get a lotus 7 if it were a full ev that can carry 5 plus a shit ton of stuff, protect me from the rain [in style], and go damn near 300 mile on one charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 05:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its ok, we get faster deliveries. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
