<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 00:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aragorn is a numenorean, specifically the royal heir and therefore has the strongest blood.  The lives thrice as long as men, stand slightly taller, and have a affinity for the magic of the land (making magic from herbs and nature).  The closest fantasy trope would be a half elf.  A big theme in Tolkien's writings were power being passed through blood, so while all numenoreans had elven blood, Aragorn's elven lineage was very strong.  As was his Distant Maiar lineage.  Fun fact, Elrond is Aragorn's great^16ish uncle.  Elrond's brother was the progenitor of the numenorean royal line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 17:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point, though I would say Elrond would be able to master the ring easier than Galadrial due to his maiar lineage.  Aragorn I could see being a maybe, given time.  He is much more humble than his forebears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 14:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make much since regarding the final battle at the black gate.  The whole strategy hinged on Sauron believing Aragorn had taken and became master of the ring (just like he did with the palantir).  Granted, Aragorn is no man, but he is only distantly related to elves and VERY distantly related to a maiar.  Could someone like Boromir or Samwise control the ring?  No, not at all.  But Aragorn, Elrond, galadrial, and probably even legolas could over power Sauron's will for control of the ring (Sauron is in a very weakened state during Tlotr) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 05:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually makes a lot of sense.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mhmm, mhmm.  I know some of those words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well DBZ abridged actually added a fourth metric of power levels.  In DBZ there's ki, martial power, and magic; abridged introduces toon force.  Everyone is pretty similar their counterpart with the exception of some genre saviness besides Goku, Krillan, and Nappa.  The thing about toon force is that it grows strong stronger off of the other person's seriousness.  For Nappa, abridged Nappa would dominate in a hilarious way because it would be funny.  Abridged Goku would take it 6/10 for the same reason as Nappa.  Abridged Killan would actually lose pretty handily because funny and he seems generally less capable and confident.  

Honorable mention for abridged Yamcha,  he loses all fights always.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With no help or prep for either side, Spike takes this in hand to hand or gunplay.  Lupin is no push over when it comes to fighting but Spike's whole job is to be a killer and he's damn good at it.  Spike 9/10

With any sort of prep Lupin gets a huge advantage.  Even with just 30 minutes of prep I could see this swinging 7/10 for Lupin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 06:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god I'm Arthur Dent.  I die extremely quickly but not before making a dry witty quip about how absurd this scenario is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 08:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we compare them to Tulkas and Manwe then fingolfin wins without prep, faenor with prep.  Fingolfin already proved he is a force of nature in a fight, but Faenor would somehow get ahold of something to boost his power or outright decimate Fingolfin with a bit of time to prepare.  The fight would have a lot of implication though, fingolfin hates faenor but not enough to kill him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King's science fiction is, imo, so much better than his supernatural.  I've read dozens of kings books but Tommyknockers remains my favorite by him. The incesteus girl on girl pelvic tentacle face rape doesn't hurt either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think of Hyperbole and a Half's depression comic when this topic comes up, particularly the dead fish metaphor.

My fish are dead.
"Have you tried feeding it?"
"You used to have so many fish, what happened?"
"Do you like bees?"
"I will help you find your fish"
"Why not just make them be alive again?"

The solutions you are giving are to a different problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 15:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political marriage, fam.  Yes she would be roughly the same age as Varian but it's supposed to feel weird and unnatural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 12:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true and I considered this in my post.  At full power, Eru calls Melkor the mightiest of the Valar after they sing the song of creation so this statement includes all Valar, the ones who went to Arda and the ones that didn't.  Tulkas is the only one who could hope to beat Melkor in combat at full strength but Melkor is most likely too clever/capable to fight Tulkas on even footing.  At his peak, it took all of the Ainur to defeat Melkor and his minions (which are an extension of his power.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 05:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingolfin was stated to be "strongest, the most steadfast, and the most valiant."  This seems to contradict your statement with Faenor but I don't think Tolkien was talking about Faenor's combat abilities.  While strong in combat, faenor was never a warrior but a crafter.  Fingolfin was the warrior out of the sons of Finwe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 03:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably.  But you chose poor representatives for their respect race.  Boromir is one of the mightiest humans Arda.  In the hobbit Gandalf says that he chooses a thief, bilbo, because a hero is not available to slay smaug.  In the trilogy he calls boromir a hero of his kingdom.  What little feats he has are ridiculous.  Strength wise he was able to keep up with Aragorn, someone above peak human, at shoveling snow banks taller than them with their bare hands.  In Moria he cleaves straight through a mountain troll's (the giant ones) arm in one stroke of his sword.  He uses a one handed sword.  

Legolas is an elf and he's no push over, being a prince (Tolkien was a big fan of power running naturally in royals/nobles) but he's just a strong elf.  Sure he can carry a hobbit and throw a goblin, but he's speed to Boromir's strength.  

Tl;dr.  Elves are, on average, stronger than humans physically.  But Boromir is likely the physically strongest humanoid on middle earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 03:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonsense, Fingolfin is directly states to be the mightiest elf in physical combat that ever lived.  He did what most Ainur couldn't do; hold their own in combat against Morgoth.  Tulkas can defeat him, Manwe can match him, and the others flee.  Fingolfin, son of  Finwe The First, King of The Elves, is beyond any mortal who ever graced Arda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 02:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have loved for her to be politically married to Anduin to further solidify Stormwind's claim as THE human kingdom.  Then, when Varian dies and Anduin is thrust into running THE human kingdom he suddenly has Celia, Jaina, and Genn breathing down his neck for horde blood.  This would be a great way to make the rising tension between the Horse and Alliance feel natural as well as make a great chapter in Anduin's character arc as he grows to become a king in his own right with the struggle of his adviser's bloodlust.

But instead we got Celia the token priest with less dialog than a shout out to Southpark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 15:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I remember this.  I remember my BT geared rogue getting chosen for OT kara over a pleading paladin who insisted he could OT as a paladin.  Poor BC paladin tanks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hard because Sargeras doesn't have a lot of feats to compare him to.  We know he is much stronger than anyone in the burning legion by a significant magnitude and his two lieutenants are mid-tier reality warpers and continent busters with their magic.  Sargeras was also able to beat each race collectively into submission if he could not tempt them, so demons like Pit Lords who can destroy whole cities by themselves are a trifle.  Also Sargeras cut a planet in half, so there's that. I would put him near Odin in power.  Maybe even slightly above but we just have never seen him struggle with anything so we don't have a ceiling for his powers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 18:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with elfs and elves.  But when you're an already renowned professor at Oxford who goes on to make one of the most iconic pieces of fantasy every written, you can kind of do whatever the hell you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 16:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And give Goldshire a wide birth unless you like trolls and ERPers in the hundreds.  A lot of RP can be found throughout Stormwind but mainly in the Cathedral and Mage districts and the several inns throughout the city but you can find RP pretty much anywhere.

Some advice for finding someone to RP with: make an outgoing character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 07:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grim dark capeshit done right.  It's also about as long as the Harry potter series and will leave you in a mental haze when/if you finish it.

Don't like anyone because they all disappoint you or die or both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 15:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it would depend on the power and how safe it was.  Tonks, Hagrid, and Fluer had powers similar to mutants, shape shifting, half giant, and hypnotizing respectively, and they attended their schools.  But if the power was like cyclops or Jean's then I imagine two men like Xavier and Dumbledore would have no problems sitting down and working something out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All reality warping used against Sargeras is easily canceled by his own reality warping.  He might not be as strong at warping reality as some ES gods but he'll be doing it defensively and his combat feats make up his offense.  He cut an earth sized planet in half in one pissed off swing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 07:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't C'hun.  Or at least not all of him.  It's more like, he stuck the tip of his finger into our world and we managed to poke it back in.  He's still there and he is much larger and much much more powerful than what we faced.  It took the combined might of the Titans to defeat one old god.  The creator and designers of our world.  Old gods in their true form are raid bosses to the titans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 19:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siege of Undercity and the rest of the Wrath expansion was a war on two fronts.  The Alliance and Horse were in such open hostilities than Tirion was barely able to keep them in check when under his banner.  The lich King was still the main focus but many quests in Northrend revolve around attacking the other faction.  A lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 13:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While scary, it will kill you pretty quickly unless your a school girl.

2/10 normally.  Pretty freaky but over quickly.
10/10 if school girl.  Shits about to go down (and up, and in, and all the way through) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 13:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very little hoops.  Being a multimillionaire opens up a lot of doors, unsurprisingly.  Canada wants your sweet sweet capital gains taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was on NPR the other night.  The interview was great and his sense of humor seems pretty close to Bob's in Bob's Burgers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of the old God being dead off the coast of darkshore perhaps the smaller well at Hyjal and the even smaller wells in teldrassil are managing to keep that one prison powered and keeping the others on stand by mode.  If we keep with the theory that the old gods are responsible for Sarg'a corruption and the whole burning legion, it makes sense that the target, time and time again, are the different wells of eternity.  It could be the old god's willing the burning legion to attack Azeroth and destroy the wells.  And let's not forget Staghelm tried to corrupt Teldrassil after the war of shifting sands, spending decades very close to an old God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leg.  He hit his leg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be a case of convergent evolution.

"In evolutionary biology, convergent evolution is the process whereby organisms not closely related (not monophyletic), independently evolve similar traits as a result of having to adapt to similar environments or ecological niches."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My engine gets hot enough to cook some mean burgers, why not slap a griddle on top?  There's just really no need or reason and the ability to speak wouldn't be used often enough and would take up unneeded room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 06:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pine trees.  You think, "those aren't leaves, those are tiny little green needles" and then you step inside one and the sky disappears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a whole department for shipping large freight.  They contract large freight shippers to deliver your bed/tv/swing set.  Like all large freight shippers they pre arrange a time to be there but usually Amazon acts as a liaison between the the of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 08:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not just the main story but the whole just drove home how bleak and hard these people's lives are.  I still get chills thinking about finding the groom's grave outside Armadillo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 04:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it.  It also ties in well with the two in the high-ground scene staring at each other and, without any effort, Obi-wan can tell what Anny is about to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 14:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard has a couple deep dark stories per expansion.  Wrathian genecids his whole flight and Alex's rape baby army in Cata.  Loken killing his brother's wife and breaking his spirit and, of course, everything Arthas did, especially the quests in Icecrown.  The exploration of orcish subjugation of the Draenei in BC; I remember a short story from Maraad's pov about a draenai woman being (implied) raped by a gang of blood lusted orcs and then chucked from Aldor Rise. As for vanilla, Darrowshire and the Borov family come to mind.  And I haven't even touched the old gods and all the horrible things they've done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 14:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the Orc host making their home in Mordor didn't just disappear.  A lot of them will die from infighting while the next dark lord is decided.  And there will be a LOT of infighting.  The witch King, second in command, is dead; the other 8 ringwraiths lost what little physical form they had with the destruction of their rings; even the mouth of Sauron, another likely leader, was killed at the black gate.  The group of orcs left will likely not have the numbers or coordination to do anything besides raid small settlements close by and attack travelers that stray too close, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 15:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we've even seen some.  But remember that not all Maia are suited for battle.  Sauron, for instance, is a Maia of Aule the Craftsman.  He has a direct hand in making the rings of power and was capable of crafting feats none but most likely Aule himself could replicate.  But he was simple as strong as a strong elf in combat.  I mean, some of the old elves like Fingolfin held their own against Melkor in single combat, a feat some Ainur couldn't do.  Then you have Gandalf, a powerful Maia of Manwe who could inspire the hearts and minds of man and elf, but was only able to match an average Maia of Melkor in single combat.  Maiar are sort of pigeon-holed into the supernatural abilities they have.  If their specific task involves combat, like oerome or the Balrog General, then their forms are truly terrifying to face on the battlefield.  But if their domain is protecting the forest, like Melion and her barrier capable of keeping all enemies out or seeking out all forms of knowledge like saruman, then their magic would be less effective.  I mean,  Saruman was stabbed to death by wormtongue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 15:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of good answers in this thread already but I'd like to touch on the Haradrim since no one else has.  During the second, third, and even fourth age (after the war of the ring) Gondor was constantly either having minor skirmishes to all out wars with the southern country of Harad.  Gondor usually has the upper hand but that didn't keep the wars from being costly.  This constant expenditure kept Gondor from expanding its territory without fighting for every inch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 06:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've seen, the Disney castle isn't an actual castle as much as it is a palace.  The difference being one is sturdy and defendable while the other is ornate and showy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 06:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a seasoned Amazon warrior, not Wonder Woman's daughter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 13:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In places like India and Russia people even give them huge tips when they're nice enough to not give you a false speeding ticket or needlessly detain you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 19:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea.  The ring has some form of sentience but perhaps it just never thought to?  Or maybe it was unable to shrink that small.  Who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 16:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of questions, I'll try to answer then all.  The first one, the West Gate, requires a history lesson.  During the second age the Nolder, the elves who refused Manwe's request to travel to the undying lands to live and opted to stay in middle earth, lived close to the dwarves and became close allies.  These elves helped the dwarves to build the West gate that the fellowship enter.  As for having the password on the door, you have to understand how secret the elven languages were.  Gandalf knew elven, of course, Aragorn did as well, and Frodo knee a little.  Before you can learn a word of elven you have to be declared Elf-friend which is no small feat.  It's not mentioned in the movies, but Frodo walked often with the elves in the forests around the shire and it took him over a decade to become an Elf-friend.  So the chances of anyone being able to read the language who wouldn't be welcome are extremely slim.  Like, a few people in middle earth slim.  

As for how Gollum got in, I don't think it's ever stated, more implies he's able to scuttle through and air shaft or run-off hole.

The orcs did know about the mithril.  However, since the dwarves had hundreds of thousands of mithril arms and armor, and the remaining mithril was very very deep down in Moria, they were probably contented to work with what they had.  Keep in mind the city had much more steel arms and armor than mithril, enough to field multiple armies.  All superior to orcish iron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 14:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's a few problems with your idea.  As others have already mentioned, the ring has more of an aura of corruption than grows stronger the closer you are to it.  Also, though it's never touched on in the movies, the ring can change sizes at will, able to fit the hand of Sauron and Frodo/Bilbo.  In fact, when making the journey up the side of mount doom the ring kept changing sizes hoping to be dropped to buy itself time for the ringwraiths to arrive.   So there's a good chance it would just grow to unplug itself or to bust out of any container. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 04:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other books.  The main source for all of this is the silmarillion.  It reads like the bible in the sense that it is very dense in the information presented and skips over hundreds of years to talk about specific events for awhile.  There is also Unfinished Tales which is a collection of finished and unfinished short stories by tolkien.  Lastly, Tolkien wrote extensively about The lotr world in essays and letters throughout his life, clarifying this, expanding on that.  Still no answer for Tom Bombadil though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To expand more on where Elrond got the power to do this, Elrond is not wholly elven.  He has the blood of the Maiar ( what Gandalf is) and the blood of man in his lineage.  In fact, the maiar Melian is his great grand mother and whose most memorable feat includes protecting her entire kingdom with a magical barrier known as The Girdle of Melion, so you could say protecting his kingdom with magic is in his blood, not to mention he had a ring of power increasing his already substantial magic.  

Also his grandfather is a human, Beren, and his brother, Elros, is Aragorn's great(to the 16th) grandfather.  Aragorn married his cousin.  It's complicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 01:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe for WoW 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna answer as if you asked who was the least important END boss of an raid.  In that case, I'd say Lady Vashj.  To me, she always seemed like they were originally going to send Aszhera but decided not to so they made up Lady Vashj on the spot to send to Illidan's side to be cannon fodder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 22:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an answer, but you might like A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court.  It's by Twaine and, in short, a smart guy is sent back in time and uses his advanced knowledge to become the court wizard and other odd adventures, more than one involving gun powder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The forgotten realms elven language has never been codified to the best of my knowledge.  However, since FR elves are based off Tolkien's elves in many, many ways, I can assume that they share a language. 

The elvish word for love is Mela when used alone and -mael- when combined with another word as in A'maelamin which means 'my beloved'

So to answer your question about language similarities, elvish is more of a Germanic language in how it handles syntax and the combining of words.  It sounds a lot softer, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 14:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My paladin is a combat medic that focuses on multiple ways of healing.  His first go-to option is the light, obviously.  This is easy enough to manifest because the light is all around and inside of us.  Whenever he is mending someone injured the light visibly emanates from himself and the other person as we are the conduit always, he is just drawing more light from you than normal.  

As for the more inherently evil beings  he has to heal, he has learned very very basic nature magic (enough to stop the bleeding and stabilize only) and is learned in the art of rune crafting (inscription).  This was thought up back when herbalism have you a HoT and I just kept it in anyway.  With his arcane ruins he can increase the body's natural regeneration after stabilizing the evil being who he is trying to save.  The nature magic came from the earth, vines literally sprouting from the ground and burrowing into the dying person and sacrificing their own health.  The ruins pull magic from the near-by lay-lines like any other arcane spell.  It just sort of pops into existence.

Worst case scenario, he has even temporarily turned someone to stone and brought them to Archerus to be healed by their fellow death Knights.  This was done via a potion that reacted with a human body alchemically (despite being dead).

The point I make is that there are many ways to manifest magic depending on the source, many of them cannon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 13:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy pretty much hits the nail on the head.  I've also heard the head cannon that only species with the same amount of fingers can make hybrids; poor gnomes.  I wish I could conically make a half-vrykul but I don't want to RP as an 11 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 04:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you may have gotten an ASMR reflex.  ASMR can be a good bandaid, like masturbation, in my experience.  Try this video.  Just sit in a quiet dark room, preferably with headphones, and try it.  

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=f_Bl8KJel7Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 16:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like most brands have a significant chance of blowing up.  But, you know, /r/hailcorporate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 22:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the lawyer up part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 06:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say this like Obi was unfazed.  He was fighting his lifelong friend and brother to the death, post child slaughter.  Obi even used the dark technique of mutilating your opponent (same one he used on Maul) he was so overcome with emotion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 16:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes to everything.  Sting isn't one of those radar things from Alien, it's just a magical elven dagger.  The glow depends on: number of goblins/orcs, and nearness of goblins/orcs.  Interesting enough, Gabdalf's sword, Glamdring(known to the goblins as beater) and Thorin's sword, Foehammer (known to the goblins as biter and also not a hammer) glowed just like sting did in the books, and they also made goblins run at the sight of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 16:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingolfin is arguably the strongest being who was not an ainur on middle earth as far as combat went.  He was easily the strongest elf, the strongest son of Finwe ( one of the first elves, father of Faenor creator of the silmarils.)  so it really wasn't just a rank and file elf challenging Morgoth to a duel, it was Fingolfin, High King of the Noldier challenging Morgoth.  And Morgoth was also weakened at the time, ungolioth's bite having forced him to stay in his physical form (ainur and maiar are not inherently physical beings). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 15:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> numenoreans weren't the first humans as much as they were kind of half elves (humans who's ancestors were elves but chose the template of human in iru's plan, it's complicated).  Fun fact, Aragon marries his great great great great great great great cousin as it was Elros, Elrond's brother, who chose the kinship of men and who's line became the Kings of numenor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 18:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're about to have our second and I getting snipped soon after she's born.  It's not a matter of trying more, at least not for our situation.  It was just communicating better about what we both needed/wanted in a partner.  Our situation is still the same, we just know what's going through the other persons head now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 17:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I was/am in a similar situation as you, except in the husband.  Deadbedroom since the birth of our son.  I acted, physically, how your husband acts to my wife after the deadbedroom got to be too much.  It may be different for him, but I acted out this way for a few reasons.  The big one is the pent up sex drive, when sex dreams about your wife surpass actual sex with your wife in frequency, hypersexualizing my wife is how I coped.  But it is unfair to treat someone as a sex symbol day in and day out and expect them to reciprocate, let alone enjoy it.  I've winced changed my habits, showing my affection by putting my hand on her hip or giving her lower back a rub--something physical but much less sexualizing.  The butt slaps and boob grabs still happen but a lot less frequently.  And instead of undressing randomly, I step to help before her shower or when changing outfits.  So far only one zipper incident...

The insults... I'm not proud of this but I did manage to keep the feelings internal, mostly.  Again, now sure how he feels, but I saw my wife's rejection of my middleschool like attempts at affection as just that, rejection.  It got to the point that looking at my wife's body in a sexual way (which, remember, I did constantly) would make me angry.  I was angry that someone I married, someone who used to have sex with my several times a week, seemed so against the idea of physical intimacy with me.  Was age making me unattractive?  Did she just pretend to like sex to make me happy?  Was she just using me for kids, income, and a father figure?  Again, not proud.  We had a long, long sit down talk.  We needed it.  If you feel like he isn't able then put a counselor between to the of you to mediate.  I've realized that my wife's attraction is mental more than physical.  I really had no idea before that.  I've stopped internalizing and villainizing her in this and come to terms with how we both need to work on our bedroom.

Good luck to the both of you.  After making all these changes in my life, nothing about my wife's sex drive has changed.  But she has agreed to see a doctor about her hormonal levels after she gives birth and finishes breastfeeding ( sex the first time in 3 months and she gets pregnant.  No sex for 2 months after.  Boy did I feel used at the time.). So don't give up hope! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 03:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy has it right.  It wasn't going well for Goku before he went SSJ, but he was still holding on.  During the underworld tournament, king Kai mentions SSJ increases goku's power my seven times.  A fist full of senzu beans wouldn't have helped Frieza the moment Goku went super. 

Edit:  I've been corrected.  It's 50 times.  Goku could have taken on 10 Friezas after his transformation.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 13:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, Jessica jones just isn't a great role model his early into her character arc; she's okay, but not great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 13:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted this list a couple times now.  This is from my experience as Amazon customer service tier 3.  The list for shipper quality goes:


UPS

FedEx

Your single uncle who let you drink at 13

All other shippers but lasership and USPS

Any random person off the street

Lasership

A homeless heroine addict

Someone who straight up tells you they will not deliver your package and throws it in a trash can right in front of you.

USPS.


Your post master may vary (but probably won't) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 05:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but with so little demand you'd be sitting in it for a while.  Most transmogs I throw up sell within a week.  Including the 1k+ ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 01:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little things.  Farming transmog gear is one of the better ways to make some gold.  The 50ish green plate set Glorious(item slot) can go for thousands of gold a piece.  You'll also find amazing transmogs you didn't even know existed.  Goldshire and silvermoon are retched hives of cum and villainy.  You'll learn a lot about lore.  People even do lore runs of old content to pass the time.

And, of course, there's the role players themselves.  It can be off putting when someone is literally touting nazi-esque doctrine to you but they're really just a scarlet ambassador.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 16:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff doesn't read those, but it is a good place to go for things like this.  Executive customer relations reads and responds to those.  For all intents and purposes they're floor managers in what they can do,  so they can usually get things done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 16:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is, within 7 days.  You may have just gotten an asshole on the phone who didn't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 16:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you need to ask for a member of management whenever you call.  You need a ticket filed for your account and related accounts, which most first tier CSAs can't or don't know how to do.  Keep in mind you need to ask for a member of management twice or thrice depending on the location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 07:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Doom is ruthless, but not evil.  Everything he does is for the good of someone.  Do his ends always justify his means?  Maybe not.  Maybe you're just on the wrong side at the wrong time.  Then you have to realize that Doom is really prideful and unfortunately second best.  Second best scientist next to Richards, second best engineer to stark, second best peak human next to cap, second best magician next to Strange.  The list goes on and, as you can imagine, the guy is a one man wrecking crew.  

When he was passed over for the title Sorcerer Supreme of Earth, he received a boon as compensation for coming in second.  He used this boon, instead of for any sort of revenge, to travel with Strange to hell and save his mothers soul.  The only way to do this was to have his mother forever think of him as a monster but she would have these thoughts in a higher plane.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 15:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guessing she had her implants placed through belly button, which is a real thing and just as weird to watch as you think it would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how old she is, but like most 30 year olds in Hollywood, she doesn't look it.  Appearing younger as an actor is good for almost every role.  This isn't one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 14:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like it should me Wonder Woman's younger sister, or even daughter, rather than Wonder Woman.  Never have I thought Wonder Woman looked like she was in her early twenties like she does in this picture.

I think this is how most of the "too skinny" crowd feels but doesn't know how to express.  Gal's skinny frame and young face are just too young looking to play a wise leader in my eyes.  Especially with an older bats and supes on the screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 17:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question seems like it would belong on /r/asksciencefiction a similar and equally satisfying sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't have to be natural selection at work.  I think my professor described genetic mutations as 90% harmful, 9% useless, and 1% useful.  We can just say that the pointy ears are in the 9% useless like enlarged breasts when not lactating and having no hair grow on our elbows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say the opposite of the evil dragon would be the good alicorn or Pegasus.  Pegasus was half God and half monster and was a servant to Zues, bringing him thunder and lightening when he asked.

Outside of Greek mythology, the Pegasus has been a symbol of wisdom and bravery all the way through the European medieval period where it was seen as the wisest and most noble creature, to the renaissance where it represented art and beauty, all the way up to WWII where it was the UK's paratrooper's logo.

Honestly, the dragon kind of stole the Pegasus's shtick in modern times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't, his hp just stops at 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 16:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the old spam latency spiking abilities outside encampment until the server just says fuck it and drops your game.  My hurricane Druid was handy for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 21:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world tree in hyjal was blessed by three of the five aspects, alexstrasza, ysera, and nozdormu.   The other two aspects were off being crazy and homicidal.  This gave night elves good health, the ability to enter the dream, and timelessness respectively.  After the end of the third war, when the new world tree was made, only alexstrasza and ysera blessed the new world tree, keeping the night elves good health and ability to enter the dream.  Nozdormu was lost in time at the time and unable to give his blessing.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 14:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't... I don't think you did it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 07:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, not really.  Free shipping works by being free; or as close to free for everyone.  They'll wait several days for an unoccupied space on as truck that would be empty and put your box there.  If no space presents itself then they'll send it standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 21:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh huh, uh huh.  I know some of these words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 08:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heptodrenolininumenose.

Hep**a**to - liver

Dreno - Adrenal gland
lin - linear

In**d**iu - A heavy metal isotope used in white blood cell tests

Menose - close enough to vagina blood.

So the word you made means that adrenal hormones are affecting the kidney and causing blood to flow uncontrollable from the vagina.  A White Blood cell test has been ordered using the Indium isotope.

Next time just say Anemia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 00:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, okay.  Where to start...

I think your both hurt.  Going from the OP and this comment, I think he has a lot of anxiety and frustration about himself that is bleeding into his desire to have sex with you and that, coupled with point one and two, is most likely his main issue.

As for comments like you saying you thought of his best friend, never is that okay.  You're not only hurting him when you say that but you're also confirming his delusions of inferiority.  

You may not like porn or "fucking" but he does.  There is another post on here that read something to the affect of: we don't do things our SO does because we suddenly enjoy them, we do things they enjoy because their joy brings us joy.  And this invites them to do something for we choose and share in our joy.  You say you don't want to end this relationship despite friends, family, and experts telling you to do so.  Well it's going to take sacrifice, experimentation, patience, and a truly monumental effort on both of your parts because it sounds like you two are in a really bad spot.  

So he's ducking you, emulating the porn stars.  Duck him back, still follow my advice despite you not wanting to act like a porn star.  This will build his confidence back up because if the testosterone isn't helping then it isn't physical, his problem is mental.

Yes you will work harder than him.
Yes you will put more of yourself out there
You will leave your comfort zone

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 22:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned changing diapers earlier, do you happen to be a new mom?  A lot of men have this weird thing where they can stop seeing their wife as a woman but as a mother.  You might want to bring it up at your next counseling session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you let him know, when things were originally getting serious, that sex is something you don't see yourself doing in a few years?  Did he know about your disdain for sex when he proposed?  When you got married? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are three major things going on here, that I see.

First, I think he has a porn addiction.  It might not seem like an addiction if it's only every other day, but he most likely still is LL and that is just his sex drive; he is quelling his sex drive the moment it builds up.

Another thing which may have caused the first is that porn is a fantasy.  If you explore the niche corners of porn, you'll find things that are very extremely, things that should impossible, and things that are so out there that they can only be portrayed through drawings.  Your husband most likely showed you the tamest porn he likes so as not to weird you out.  You can show him weird things you're into and he could do the same when he knows you won't run away screaming, but my wife hasn't looked at me the same since I showed her /r/hucow so be aware of what you're getting into there

Lastly, sex and masturbation are not the same thing.  Sex is a loving, intimate union between two people.  Masturbation is more like me and my penis going on an amusement park fun ride that is over before you know it.  Yeah, he a sex drive for both but that's where it ends.  It's no substitute for sex and more like a band aid for a missing limb.  This is a HL with a LL saying this, so trust me.

Now for what you can do to; incorporate the porn.  Join in on his masturbation, offer to give him a blow job or a hand job instead of him using his hand.( possible rejection point 1) Forewarning, most men have a mastery of their genitalia so it may take a bit to make him cum like he can with himself.  Try this a few times and after each time tell him you're going to go finish yourself off.  After a few times  tell him it's his turn. (Possible rejection point 2).  This could be foreplay if he's ready to go after your turn.

If you're rejected at point 1 then he needs counseling for his addiction.  If you're rejected at point two then he needs counseling for being a selfish prick.  If he refused counseling then... I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The original Nightmare Before Christmas poem by Tim Burton, read by Christopher Lee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 19:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 16:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Algalon so much, he was the perfect icing on what many consider to be the best raid tier WoW has ever had.

Up against all odds, fighting despite the futility, and it's just you, the player.  Ronin or Bran don't help, there's no other big names NPC, it's just you fighting to save the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not rare, just uncommon.  However, for proper Mountain King rp abilities, you'll want to go prot for the free thunderclap, get the storm hammer to throw, and get heroism, all of which are lifted directly from the mountain king's abilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mathias Shaw.  Leader of SI:7 and we hardly know a thing about him. What makes him one of the best rogues in the world?  How good is he, really?  How much clout does he even have?

I've wanted Mathias to get more story since vanilla. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 17:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think shamanism is what he's familiar with and therefore calls all spell casters shaman.  For instance, fireball, immolate, and holy fire could just be the way other races do fireshock.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 16:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resto Druids have always wobbled back and forth between extremely strong and several tiers ahead of every one else in pvp since vanilla.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone change her eyes to that of Leela's from Futurama? Additional Futurama-esque changes are cool too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 05:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 07:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S-class Leet.  Anything he makes is better than the previous iteration.  Let your imagination run wild with that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
