<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject516</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 06:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio State.  I can tell she's standing in line at the Thompson Library's cafe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 23:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, but there will never be a candidate who represents your views 100%.  I mean, even looking at your example, one candidate will go directly against what you want to create *more* unnecessary wars and the other will work with what the previous presidency left for him. 

Once again, I'm not telling people to vote only Democrat or Republican; you're allowed to vote for whoever you want.  I just thought I'd point out that I disagree with the mentality of "every vote is meaningless so fuck it."  Vote green if you want.  Abstain from voting if you don't think you align with any of the candidates.  Either way, you're making an informed decision based on the views of the candidates and how they resinate with you which is a lot better than saying "every vote is meaningless." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 23:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it, I knew I forgot to pay something this month... BRB gotta call TWC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 23:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great and all, but you're missing the forest for the trees.  Sure, statistically speaking, one vote means nothing but you originally said "each vote is meaningless."  Telling 500 people in Florida "that since one vote is useless, you should take voting lightly" could drastically alter the course of history.  The point is, if we're looking at this as 1/300,000,000 people, then yes it's meaningless.  If you live in a swing state and it's an extremely close race, then 1/500 *does* make a real difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 23:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pooooor Ohio, too.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 22:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it difficult to see that if 500 more people voted that day or if 500 people who voted for Nader voted for Gore, then the election would've gone an entirely different way?  500 people basically decided the election in 2001; is that not enough proof that your vote counts?  If 25% of the upvotes on this one post in /r/AdviceAnimals were votes for Gore in FL, then everything would be different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  I can't believe people actually think the two candidates are "the same."  Sure, it's a broken system, but it's very apparent (if you stop thinking with a tinfoil hat) that both candidates would lead very different Americas.  One is against abortion and said he'd elect a Supreme Court Justice who would ensure it's made illegal.  C'mon people, real issues are in play despite you thinking politicians are puppets and "crony capitalists." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 21:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an idiotic and incorrect viewpoint.  According to [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida_election_recount),  Gore officially lost by ~500 votes but some studies say he actually won by 100-200 votes.   I'm not saying you should only vote Republican or Democrat, but saying your vote is meaningless is misleading and wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 05:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pack of Sharbaos came all dried out.  Shargles are the best, IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 15:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care either way, but she could've possibly meant "most of [the random strangers on the internet looking for NSA sex] probably have AIDS," which is a pretty reasonable worry.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 06:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, I would *love* a real world example of this.  At 326 pixels per inch, two rows of pixels is barely noticeable, if at all.  If this were way back when the iPhone had a screen with 320x480 resolution, I might've agreed with you.  Though, at 640x1136, two rows is nothing.  C'mon, just realize that this isn't a big deal in any way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 06:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm, no, no it's not.  I'm a developer, I know what it's like to develop for multiple devices and supporting a 15.98:9 device is the exact same as a 16:9 device.  Values aren't hard coded so it shouldn't matter the display size and if images were formatted in 16:9, the OS would most likely clip 1 pixel row off the end or "letter box" it by a pixel or so, which would be unnoticeable.  Though, if these images were 16:9, they would look pretty meh on a 3:2 screen, so 15.98:9 is actually much better in that situation.  Once again, for all intents and purposes, 15.98:9 = 16:9. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate the message, I am just dumbfounded by the messenger.  You're basically saying "That 4.999 Mb file can't be called 5 Mb because it's missing the 0.1 Kb!"  They "met" the industry standard just fine, you just don't want to agree with it.  One missing pixel on a super dense screen will make zero difference when playing movies/videos.  Honestly, if that's your complaint about the screen, then you're basically saying nothing's wrong with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's a stretch.  You literally just said apple gave us a screen missing 1.78 pixels on the end of it.  They REALLY fucked us over big time, huh?  Le sigh.

Math:
1. 640 / 9 = 71.11111111

2. 71.11111111 * 16 = 1137.77777776 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sqrt(.25^2 + 1^2) = 1.03077641.  So it's ~1.03" larger diagonally, which sounds about right for 3.5" to 4.3". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 14:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, this image is a pretty bad  effect of a great feature.  In cities without 3D buildings, the terrain is topographically accurate so you at least get an idea of how the area actually looks vs. looking at a flat map.  The terrain must be really hilly in OP's area and the large amount of highways must have gotten visibly distorted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 14:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Almost.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 06:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dad sounds like Calvin's dad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 22:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem!  What're ya going to school for in cbus?  I imagine you're going to CCAD because you're downtown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 22:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing how I'm a burger connoisseur, I can confidently say Thurman's, The Press Grill, The Gahanna Grill, Graffiti Burger, and Club 185 all have great burgers! :)  Welcome to Columbus, we're pretty cool here, I guess.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 13:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true about fashion and style in general.  Dressing up should be fun, not some strict way to wear clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 06:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbus-based 30 Rock fan checking in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 18:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ONLY 3!? :O

Someone has some Community to rewatch.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 14:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does everyone leap to defend that band so aggressively?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 13:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent my summer interning in OR.  I can easily say that it's the prettiest part of America! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, #11 is really a powerful photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 20:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shh... shh... let the circle jerk continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 15:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here it is running on a 2011 MacBook Pro.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6gqtOQJBCwc)

Remember that Macs are the same as Windows computers at the hardware level and Apple hips laptops that have i7 processors, 8 GB DDR3 RAM, and nice GPUs.  Basically, they're fast machines.  Are they cheap?  No.

EDIT:  Maybe you're talking about OSX availability?  Rebooting to Windows 8 from OSX takes all of 25 seconds.  It's really a non-issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 07:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, they can play any game a Windows laptop can and their recent GPUs, processor updates, and RAM options allow for them to be a good gaming laptop.  Sure, it's not a 10 lb beast with a desktop CPU in it, but I like that about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 07:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It just shouldn't cost $100 for an extra 16gb of flash memory

The Nexus 7 is basically sold at cost and the 8 gb to 16 gb jump is $50.  I can only imagine the 16 gb to 32 gb is more expensive.  Obviously there's a mark up, but it's not to the point that it's price gouging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 20:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but not much of a point when Cydia and other jailbreak apps have to be updated :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 05:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A woman after my own ~~heart~~ wedding gift.

FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 02:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PJayy is Batman now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 02:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it possible that this isn't a fluidly repeating gif?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 14:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, how is OP's favorite Britta moment the time where she breaks down in front of the group?  Off the top of my head, one of my personal favorites is [this scene.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SnKgveE0Odg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 00:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried so hard to get into Newsroom and I just couldn't.  It's way too "inyourfaceliberal" for a show that's trying to be "level-headed."  It's not that I don't mind liberal views or social commentary but it just repeatedly shoves it in your face with long-winded rants and perfect 20/20 vision of the past.  :\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 23:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm, no I didn't.  It's in there below Boardwalk Empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 23:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're in the episode, so I think they're there to be cannon.  Also, we're missing the random assortment of cats walking around the forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 21:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He has Advanced Aging Disorder and he got you pregnant!?  That's immoral and disgusting! ....pfft I'm just kidding...  Have any names picked out yet?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 20:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but it's also an extremely high rated show.

From [Wikipedia:](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Girls_\(TV_series\))
 Critics lauded the show for its raw nature, humor, and refreshing tone.  According to Metacritic, which assigns a normalized rating out of 100 to reviews from mainstream critics, the series holds an average score of 87 based on 28 reviews, indicating "Universal acclaim". The website also lists the show as the highest-rated fictional debut series of 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 20:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last season technically ended during last year's TV schedule, and seeing as this year's has yet to start, I figured it was a valid entry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 20:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I've never watched DA, I just keep hearing it's great.  I thought about adding The Wire, but it's no longer running.  If I were to do that, I could also add 24, Lost, and a lot of other shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 19:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people seem to think that America's TV is full of crap because of shows like The Jersey Shore, but we actually have very good TV.

* Mad Men
* Community
* Dexter
* The Walking Dead
* Archer
* Always Sunny
* Louie
* American Horror Story
* 30 Rock
* The Office (well, the older seasons, at least)
* Girls
* Veep
* Parks   Recreation
* Curb Your Enthusiasm
* Modern Family
* Boardwalk Empire
* Breaking Bad
* ~~Downton Abbey~~ Sorry about that, I haven't watched DA, so I didn't know it was British.
* Game of Thrones
* HIMYM
* Children's Hospital

And a lot more.

EDIT:  Seeing as everyone seems to have read over the "and a lot more," here is a list of shows other people have noted:

* Workaholics
* Homeland
* Sons of Anarchy
* Suits

Please try and remember this list is for shows that are currently running or just ended.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 16:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, this is me saying goodbye to the next 45 min. of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 20:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hurts my heart. :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 20:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, well I originally thought the article would be enough motivation for those going through a similar situation to do something about it.  I noticed that this subreddit has turned into a "working out subreddit," which is why I tried to introduce motivation for another problem.  If this isn't a good submission, then beyond pictures of skinny people and tumblr-esque images of quotes, what should one submit?

(Serious question, not some douchey response, I swear!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 08:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, that is science right there.  Gonna have to go with you on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 04:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1535 loadcycles
38 Months
68%

...can you tell I use my computer a lot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 18:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm, confidence != cockiness.  

Welcome to the trap many guys fall into when they think they're confident.  Confidence means you believe in your actions and who you are and don't care about what others think about it.  Confidence is the ability to go on a dance floor and move your hips without having the fear that someone, somewhere will think you're a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 18:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, congrats Derferman and all involved!  I've been following the progress of the game since the beginning and have had my doubts for awhile, but you've seriously quelled all of them!  As a developer, I take my hat off to you and respect you and other developers for getting through many difficult things many other developers would've given up on.  These include creating your own levels/maps, having to redo sprite sheets multiple times, implementing systems for new characters, etc.  Sure, a lot of it comes down to creativity and being able to accurately predict how Community would've done it, but you've done a fantastic job so far!  I look forward to every bit of progress! :)

Good luck guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 18:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense.  I have a friend who's going to school for homeopathic medicine, and I have a hard time grasping the concept (I'm an engineer).  It's interesting to me, but I've never once thought to use one of the alternative forms of "medicine" when I could just go to a doctor.  Though, it's crazy to think that there's an entire field of medicine that could actually be useful in some way but the majority of people turn away from it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 17:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered this, but is homeopathic medicine really just the placebo effect or does anyone know of any instances where it's actually real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 03:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's absolutely no way to read that in my head without the jingle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 00:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a senior who's going through semester transition hell, I want to grab them and tell them how lucky they are to be starting now.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 21:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look great, man.  I clicked the image and I immediately said "self-esteem" when it opened.  I'm a gay guy so trust me; you look great, man!  :)  

(Not hitting on you, just saying that you're attractive and I'm someone who's actually in a real position to think so :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 21:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srsly.  Everyone should be trying to make sense of their life and get their health in order, but that should happen by finding their passion.  Joining the army because it will make you thinner won't make you happier if you don't really want to join the Army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 21:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think it's a little unfair to call masturbating myself to bed every night a "love life," but sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 09:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I come from the midwest and moved to Oregon in June.  Two weeks after being here, I stepped on a brown recluse by accident.  I was barefoot.  I smashed it.  

Nature never tried to kill me in the MW.  Not like this, at least. O_o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 09:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Asian father... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 22:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a very large difference between having an opinion and unnecessarily hating a group of people.  If you can't see that one's prejudice and discrimination and the other is blindly favoring your opinion, then there's something wrong with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 18:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She hasn't responded to you, I hope she's alright! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 08:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 10.5, any idea if they run a bit large? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm lovin' it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 02:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 03:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question, is that what makes the BBC impartial?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 16:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If yeh cud chaynge yuh fayt, wood ya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 16:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Better.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H4hvZkBpUJs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 16:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OhthankGod.  It's been *forever* since I've heard that new Katy Perry song! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 17:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  had dagger nails

For some reason, the imagery of this is hilarious :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 08:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it, I'm out of the running.  Stupid homosexuality ruining all of my fun :(

/me is a redditor in a cold sweat, with pale skin, cat hair on his lap, a neckbeard, and a love of ~~boobs~~ penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 17:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something Lord's work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 09:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was like, "this is a secret?  Everyone does this at my school!"  Then I read OSU.  So yes, it seems that everyone does it at my school haha.

Gooooo Bucks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 09:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell if being sarcastic

...or just an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 18:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure this is too late, but I'm going to pm you my email address in hopes that I can buy cheap shirts :)

Either way, thanks for doing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 10:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut your whore mouth, Teekoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 10:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the word?

*I must know.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 10:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When this post is one hour old, then reddit has my permission to go down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 10:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish that we could talk about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 22:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Britta will be in school much longer than anyone else.  She declared a Psych major at the beginning of her Junior year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 21:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.  I thought they would tone down the in-jokes and wackiness once they got off hiatus to help ease in new audience members.  NOPE.  I mean, it was fun for older members, but I can't imagine *hearing* about Community, tuning in, and watching the Asian guy from The Hangover ordering child soldiers into a riot... against students who were mad about losing a Bio credit... at a funeral for a character named Starburns... who happened to be a meth dealer... etc, etc.

That's not how you win over potential fans, IMO.  Though, what do I know?  I might just be streets behind :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 06:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, I imagine "Britannia" to be a preppy blonde girl rather than Ye Olde Great Britain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 06:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this deserves a Dora The Explorer "Veeerryyy good!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-02 01:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, it's not.  Though, actors are the ones who actually pull in an audience which is what funds the entire show for all involved.  In workplaces, people with such leverage and pull are allowed to act any way they want to (bosses, actors, even consumers in certain situations).  They're not any more special than anyone else, but without Chevy Chase, they would've lost a very large name attached to the show which undoubtedly brought in viewers.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 16:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  I love Harmon's work, but the guy is a child.  You're a show runner, not a performer.  He should've stayed in the background and tried to make the actors feel as welcome as possible.  Instead, we had a childish fight between him and Chevy which was ridiculous; everyone knows Chevy's an asshole, why risk your job and the show to publicly point it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 15:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You remind me of a [young Liz Lemon](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gMkzLHwe4-c).  Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 04:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought these!  They're coming in the mail soon and I can't f'in wait!! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 16:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You deserve a medal or something.  Seriously, keep doing your thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 09:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to admit, he really dropped the bomb on us out of nowhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 03:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't BB also have a life-time warranty on their clothes?  That, in and of itself, makes it worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 06:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A.  You're fifteen; don't mention your genitalia on the internet.  
B.  Sorry, bro, but you're average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 05:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if I buy these boots, what's a good way of preserving them?  I plan on wearing these frequently to class/out, so should I buy water proof spray or something of the sort?  

You're absolutely right, though.  I should try and save money on more of a trendy piece of clothing or shoe, because those are meant to last a year or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 04:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I'd reply to you with what I ended up doing.  I looked at my Chase Rewards account, noticed I had over 10,000 points and cashed in for a $100 Nordstrom gift card.  Now, the boots are going to be $60! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 01:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know, but $160 on boots is a bit much for a student.  I know, that's super cheap for Red Wings, but there's not much I can do in the way of paying sub-$200 for shoes :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 09:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I went (a month or two ago), I found Penguin's The Earl polos for $23, which is almost 1/3 their retail price.  I picked up 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 07:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really never went out of style.  Sure, it's not exactly stylish, but it's not a "fashion don't."

http://dappered.com/2011/11/the-glory-of-the-style-guilty-pleasure/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 22:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't they all be bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 21:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!  I have nothing to add beyond it's subreddits like these with commenters like you that make reddit an amazing place :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 20:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't actually dead, it was writhing around randomly, so I put it out of its misery.  Sorry about the blurry pictures, but it's the best I could grab on my camera and without getting *too* close to it.  Thanks in advance if you guys could help and I can try to provide more information if need be! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 04:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are the Hivemind; you will be assimilated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 02:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's actually starting to work, baby."

"***I don't take notes from you!***" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 02:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the reason I stopped watching Modern Family was because I was tired of Cam and Mitch.  I'm gay and I found it enfuriating that they fought every. single. episode.  My roommates say that every other family does, too, but the difference is that Cam and Mitch never resolve their issues; they sweep them under the rug at the end of each episode.  So then the writers decided they should get a *second* kid, which made no sense to me because all they ever did was fight and introducing another child would only make it worse.

/vent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 10:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the years since the riots occurred, the death of gay icon Judy Garland earlier in the week on June 22, 1969 has been attributed as a significant factor in the riots, but no participants in Saturday morning's demonstrations recall Garland's name being discussed. No print accounts of the riots by reliable sources cite Garland as a reason for the riot, although one sarcastic account by a heterosexual publication suggested it. (Carter, p. 260.) Although Sylvia Rivera recalls she was saddened and amazed by the turnout at Garland's funeral on Friday, June 27, she said that she did not feel like going out much but changed her mind later. (Duberman, p. 190191.) Bob Kohler used to talk to the homeless youth in Sheridan Square, and said, "When people talk about Judy Garland's death having anything much to do with the riot, that makes me crazy. The street kids faced death every day. They had nothing to lose. And they couldn't have cared less about Judy. We're talking about kids who were fourteen, fifteen, sixteen. Judy Garland was the middle-aged darling of the middle-class gays. I get upset about this because it trivializes the whole thing." 

Wikipedia seems to disagree with you.  I'm not personally saying you're wrong, just that this note was there.  Though, thanks for educating me on the Stonewall Riots!  Now I know why Pride is in June! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 07:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris.  Mutha' Fuckin'.  Pratt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
