<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 17:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was literally my mother and i so many times. This hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NativeOne Becomes First Native-Owned Broker-Dealer Member of the NYSE to Participate in Public Securities Offering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 22:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 16:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what cough syrup then? and how much should we take each? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did the edits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tripple C's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 16:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started birth control yesterday, and my friend and I have been planning on doing tripple c's. Can I mix these? Im only taking five.

edit: I'm taking Generess Fe.
edit: We're taking the Purple box of Coricidin   I'm taking five pills, my friends taking 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 00:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can vouch for this article, I have MDD and have been having more intense and negative dreams ever since the first symptoms started showing. In fact, last night I had one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 11:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've heard of queens town from something I read in Powder once... but anyway, I will if I'm ever there, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 11:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 11:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horseback riding, skiing, longboarding, adventuring, reading, obsessing over cute things, trees, and spending too much time on the internet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 10:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Holidays :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 10:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 09:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence my username. I have MDD. Life get's better after meds come in the picture, take it from someone just like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 08:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember much of elementary school as far as my emotional status. Middle school comes, and by that time there is a lot of fighting going on at home. One temperamental father + one emotionless alcoholic mother + one rebellious older sister = an overwhelmed me. There was a lot of crying, a lot of anger. I didn't know how to handle the anger; not to say I was violent, but I lashed out at people verbally when it wasn't my complete intention. 
Mind you, I'm a shy kid, so showing anything besides my normal self is difficult enough.
High school comes, and then I hit that being bullied part of my life, which now that I look back, triggered a lot of depressive symptoms. Frequent crying, anger, isolation, irritability, dropped grades, no motivation, gained weight. Any symptoms after I did better at a new school after one year of torture stopped for the most part until college, but I still carried around of unresolved bitterness.
College comes, and I'm doing all the right things; making friends, going out, doing my homework. I had a broken hand, so that restricted from me doing anything physical. Then I got mono, which went away about mid october. The lines between where everything went bad are faded between a lot of time being stressed about grades, being away from my home (I live at a best friends house at home currently), and being sick maybe 90% of this semester. 
These are the symptoms I can come up with now, and they're pretty spot on for what I was going through before medication.
Extreme fatigue, feelings of guilt/worthlessness/extreme pessimism, insomnia, waking up from sleep often, sleeping through alarms, irritability, isolation from people, no appetite, no motivation to do school/physical work, physical aches, horrible memory, bad focus, constant state of sadness, suicidal thoughts. I've dropped ten pounds since september. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 08:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Emotional bullying, it was my freshman year of high school at an all girls school. All the girls spread rumors about me, nobody ever included me, and they were from a rich town while I wasn't. I did no harm to anyone and was just a shy girl when people would actually talk to me. I didn't "cope," I kind of pushed myself through everyday and came home in tears no matter how the day went. I tried to get help from teachers and my parents, telling people how mean the girls would be to me, but nobody did anything, especially my parents who didn't want to jeopardize my place at a very highly regarded school. I did retaliate a few times and confronted a few snobby girls, but they ran off the second I asked if they had anything to say to my face. I'm happy with how I handled it that one time, but it never stopped. After a year of that turmoil (I transferred sophomore year), it left a huge footprint on who I am today. There are a lot of issues with me making friends and trusting people now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 08:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Symptoms from a few months ago or earlier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 07:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 07:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you darling, you as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 07:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A school psychiatrist diagnosed me. I've only seen him twice in the past weeks though, even though I was supposed to see him weekly. It's not seasonal. And no?

edit* My plan is to see one when I go home for breaks then switch off with an off campus therapist during school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 07:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's reassuring that some others understand. It really takes a toll on you before you notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 05:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People, public, crowds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 04:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true. I reached the point this semester where I couldn't ignore/live with it for any longer. I was surprised to see how much it escalated from perfect happiness to a wreck in a matter of weeks. The worst part is I realized I was showing symptoms since middle school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 03:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something that you could call a series of unfortunate events. I have sad roots, and lived an okay life, but you can't really get away from where you came from, can you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 02:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teaching yourself Swedish? Why Swedish? Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 02:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually over thinking about negative things. Or, you know, actual negative events. A lot of the time it's kind of letting myself drown in negativity that brings me down more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 02:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple things, like kittens, sunshine, chocolate milk, and snow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poland Spring. Pumpkin. If you haven't tried pumpkin ice cream, you're missing something big in your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats. Ninjas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 22:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. There is still stigma for it with kids my age, but a lot less, I would say. A good majority of kids these days in the US have been diagnosed with some kind of illness or disorder. It depends if I'm talking to close friends; if they're not close, yeah, it does make me feel uncomfortable and invaded. I get choosy about who I tell, so lucky you, Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 22:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are a lot of other young adults, sadly. I don't know much about those two. I'm on 150mg of Venlafaxine daily, but the dosage is subject to change. I don't have a lot of side effects besides being leveled out emotionally... as long as I take my medication. Otherwise, one missed dose and so begins the anxiety, mood swings, heart racing, bad headaches, isolation, and an overall really bad mindset. I fear not being able to live without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 21:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that means a lot. Today's a happy day indeed. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 21:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because of the medication, but not completely. I don't think I ever will be "better." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 17:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the same thing to a broken bowl when the main bowl part snapped off. Still works like a charm. Good luck to you and your friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 22:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Bourbon for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sissue" I should use that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 09:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pronounced "Mora" in most cultures, but a lot of spanish natives will pronounce it "Maw-rah," which seems strange but sounds nicer with the accent and the way the r rolls off the tongue as an l. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does Reddit think of this uncommon name for a girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 09:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a young woman in the 21st century with the name Maura, it's not every day I cross paths with someone sharing the same name (Maura's language of origin is Latin. It is predominantly used in German, Irish, Italian, and Spanish, and can be translated to meaning dark, dark-skinned, star of the sea, bitter, and great.) I am already rather confident with the name I was given. However, I don't hear much feedback about it, other than it is rare. What do you guys think of it-strange, ugly, nice etc.?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
