<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7383</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 05:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are all really cool! Such an interesting idea.

Have you ever discussed using these to advertise for chemistry majors? I'm an undergrad and if I'd seen stuff like this I probably would've become a chem major sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 03:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw, it did, thanks!

It looks kinda like granite, is it? I'm only in the 5.10 range so there'll probably be plenty to keep me busy. Is the bouldering natural rock too?

As long as there's somewhere to change; do you know if there are showers? I'll probably be going back to work after and don't want to look like a coke addict.

An unrelated question, do Ithaca's (outdoor) stores usually have sales on winter clothes in the summer? I may be coming back to Cornell for grad school and will probably be biking year-round so lots of exposure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 02:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local gym has a test that's really basic (i.e. tie a figure 8) and they give training if you can't do that, is that how it works there?

Is there a store/outfitter on campus that sells loose/brick chalk? I have a chalk sock. I'm in Florida so I'm used to heavy hand sweat; is it like that year round or does it dry out when summer ends?

I've seen it called natural rock, but the site shows cinder blocks; what's actually going on? That's pretty cool how the routes work, though; what range of grades are usually kept taped?

Also, is there a locker room there? I'm working in Baker and can't wear shorts there so I'd be bringing a change of clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 02:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys sell the climbing card there? I only found semesterly climbing access paired with a full gym membership, but I don't even lift.

Also, how does the belay test work? Is it just tying the knots and calling commands or is it more involved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 02:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the responses everyone!

I'm being given a student card and I got a NetID, so I guess I'm effectively a student so that shouldn't be a problem. I've been climbing off and on for about 2 years but I'm not great (V4-   5.9/5.10, haven't climbed since January) and only in it for the fun, but I'd still be up for pms for pairups (my belay skills are on point; I could pull rope on a 5.15 as long as you're top-roping). I mainly boulder so I'd probably be hang dogging on anything over 5.9.

I'm there with a program so if I were to snake away for a weekend I think it might have to be open to 13 other people with likely 0 climbing experience and no transportation (so I'll look into the outing club). My shoes smell horrible (yay, Evolv!) so I'll put them in a plastic bag or use this opportunity to buy new ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions About the Lindseth Climbing Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 03:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm coming to Cornell for the summer and I'm a climber; how does the Lindseth wall operate?

* Are the people there friendly enough that you can get a belayer by just showing up?
* Is everyone skilled enough to not drop you while belaying?
* Is the atmosphere "get good at climbing" or "have a good time climbing?"
* Is there a long wait for routes to open up during the summer?


~~Is it a BYOG kind of place or do they provide/rent out equipment?
Most importantly, do they provide shoes? I do **not** want to put mine in my luggage.~~I googled.

Bonus question: how long is the drive to the Gunks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 17:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now who's saying incriminating things? Haha.

I suppose it's somewhat common in the US, at least within the realm of chemistry classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 17:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OTC just means over the counter; we just stated that to show how cool it is that a simple mirror plane separates something you can buy at a grocery store and a [schedule II] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Convention_on_Psychotropic_Substances#Schedule_II) drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 17:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't data from a real reaction and there's no defined SM; we made it up for proof of concept linked to (what we thought was) a fun compound. As for the energy differences, we attribute those to sterics; compound B is the Z isomer, whereas compound A is E. 

As for the actual concept of thermo vs. kinetic, the kinetic product is whatever forms fastest (i.e. has the lowest transition state (TS) energy: smallest G) and the thermodynamic product is whichever has the most stable end product (i.e. biggest change in G: largest |G|).

[Here's an arbitrarily chosen graph showing the TS energy and final product.] (http://imgur.com/iKVG3dJ)

So in our made up reaction, there are two pathways the compound can go through ([see original exam question] (http://imgur.com/BTUldyx)). One pathway has a lower TS, but a smaller |G|, so it happens quicker due to its lower energy barrier (the TS); the other has a higher TS, and requires more energy, but results in a more stable product (largest |G|), and is therefore the thermodynamic product (as determined by the |G|).

Hope that helped! (Though you probably already understood everything past the first 2 sentences, that was a knee-jerk response to try to explain everything I guess.)

Edit: Added [links.] (http://images.wikia.com/zelda/images/e/e9/Link_%28Four_Swords%29.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (sorta) helped make that exam, so [I can.] (http://imgur.com/a/plrZV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 15:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["A metal-free organicinorganic aqueous flow battery"] (http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v505/n7482/full/nature12909.html)

This is the Harvard paper about the batteries using quinones, you might've heard of it called a rhubarb battery.

[Here's Harvard's news release on it.] (http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2014/01/renewable-energy-breakthrough/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinions on a Masters/Minor in Education and (Science) Education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Educators of /r/AskAcademia, what are your opinions on studying education while(graduate minor)/after(M.S.) getting your Ph.D.? If you did, do you think it helps your students learn or was it just by virtue of working with many students over time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doing an REU and Going to That School for a Ph.D. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 18:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was accepted to an REU program for this summer and would really like to do my Ph.D. with them. The nature of the application I listed groups I wanted to work with and I was picked for my #1 choice; could this be seen as them willing to accept me for graduate studies? It seems like a 3 month funded program vs. a 4-5 year Ph.D. is a bit of a jump.

Has anyone here done an REU and been accepted/denied by that school for their Ph.D.? What was your experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 03:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I found her surfboard;] (http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/213ebc/he_found_this_washed_up_shoreyup_that_is_two_bite/) the design really bites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 19:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP, but I'm coming to Cornell for a summer research program too; I saw something about community bikes happening at Cornell, is that still going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 23:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely this.

Email the graduate students of groups you are interested in for graduate study and ask them what they think of the group. If you've already been accepted and are going on visitations, seek out the disgruntled students that they aren't putting on display and ask them their opinions.

Also, don't bad mouth your program when at other universities, it's unprofessional and won't be well received, not to mention you may be insulting someone who is friends with people in whatever program you're hoping to get into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 20:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a business man, but back in high school my algebra teacher told me I was stupid and would never answer any questions I had, this lead to me struggling later in precalculus since I'd never properly learned algebra and subsequently avoided calculus since I was "too stupid for it." I was scared as hell to take it in college.

I'm in my 3rd year of college now and I'm minoring in mathematics and have a 3.9 GPA in it; everything is easy, the calculus sequence, diffEQ, and linear algebra were all a breeze.

I think this applies to everything, not just science; it's all about perspective and perseverance, just because you can't do something in high school doesn't mean you're not smart enough. There is more than one way to do/think about things and some ways work better than others, but early experiences may try to force one way or another on you. On some level it may just be buckling down and actually doing the work, but it might be that things aren't being though of in the right way.

It may also be worth noting I got a B- in general chemistry, and now I'm going to be spending my summer doing research at Cornell; don't give up on something if it interests you! Give it your best and that's all you can ask of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 20:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basic math.

I'm a chemistry student minoring in math and physics, most laymen seem to think that this means I can rattle off obscure multiplications and do basic algebra in my head rapidly; I still count on my fingers for the elementary level stuff and have to sit down and write out precalculus problems.

Just because you're bad at high school math doesn't mean you're not smart or can't do real mathematics! There are so many more ways to think about things than what they force-feed you in compulsory school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 16:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning Dr. Omberg,

I have a more general question about what it's like doing research in a national lab as compared to within a university. I've heard places like Sandia and Oak Ridge can get bogged down with bureaucratic nonsense and the scientists can sometimes go *days* without anything new to do; what has your experience been like? Is not having to jockey for funding worth the red tape?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 06:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Ultra 12.0.2.1076. It might be because it's ultra, but I'm sure it's not exactly computationally intensive to apply a naming algorithm.

I have a friend who uses 13 on his mac and windows computers and he's also able to name, it might be under a different section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 04:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Select your compound, right click and go to analysis and select name.

It even updates as you change the structure, it's really cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 02:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there are *torrents* of other ways to get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! I loved OChem (obviously) so much that I'm TA'ing it.

Just a few tips, since everyone seems so terrified of it:

* learn to see the patterns; trying to memorize only makes it harder than it needs to be.

* carbon is not pentavalent.

* get a modeling kit if you can't/until you're able to think in 3D.

* get ChemDraw to name things for you. IUPAC is the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 22:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's [5,6-dioxo-1,4,5,6-tetrahydropyrazine-2,3-dicarbonitrile](http://www.chemspider.com/Chemical-Structure.517636.html).

I scraped the carpet out from inside my RBF and it was right underneath! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Synthesized a Hardwood Floor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 21:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's free, but you should contact the professor prior.

Graduate courses usually cost much more than an undergrad class if you want them on your transcript. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 17:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like graduate courses are much more reading and independent work than an undergrad course. This is pretty ubiquitous among the science departments here and isn't limited to chemistry.

My university offers a few courses that are split between grad and undergrad; I'm in the biochem class right now and it's totally manageable. We also have a 2 credit polymer course which I've heard very good things about, the students learn a lot and it doesn't feel like a burden at all.

You may want to try *auditing* it to give it a test run; I've done that with all my grad classes (they make us pay 3x the price for them, and they don't accept ramen noodles as payment) and it's saved me from committing myself to some courses that turned out to be quite boring review of what I already knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 19:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are the views? Some of our windows here literally face brick walls.

I actually put down the Dichtel group as my 2nd choice; does he seem like he'd be open to a visiting undergrad poking around his lab (supervised, of course)? I'm most interested in Dr. Abrua for my grad P.I. but I wanted to see some other labs while I'm there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 07:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was invited to Dr. Abrua's group; do you know him? I actually made a thread here asking about Cornell's chem department a couple days ago after I found out. What's the Baker Lab complex like?

Definitely stay if you can, summer research was so much more involved without the distraction of classes. There are probably internal scholarships that will fund it too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 06:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! The Cornell program is a MRSEC too; I actually applied to Northwestern's but Cornell only gave me 3 days to respond so I committed to them since I'm really interested in their entire school.

They've got some really cool stuff going on there, you should definitely accept! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely go for the REU! I'm a 3rd year undergrad and I spent this past summer in my own lab and will be spending this summer at Cornell with an REU program instead of staying here again, my PI actually encouraged it.

It's a great way to network and see where you'd like to go for graduate school; an undergrad from my lab a few years back ended up doing his PhD in a lab at Berkeley that he REU'd at over a summer, they invited him to apply.

Also, it isn't the MRSEC REU, is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 23:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and he seems fairly prominent in the field (though it seems like it's a requirement that no Cornell professor can have their website updated past 2011); I've been looking into his work with Dichtel, it's nice to see all the communication among the chemistry department there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Cornellians Care to Comment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 06:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got accepted to an REU program at Cornell for this summer; needless to say I'm really excited!

I figure some of you guys are/were likely students there and I was wondering if I could get your opinions/experiences/juicy gossip about the university's chemistry department and the campus/town in general.

I've been invited to Dr. Abrua's group so if anyone has any experience working with him or his students please weigh in! (Please confirm my suspicion that he's as affable as his page makes him seem).

PMs are welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 16:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see something from my home institution!

I'll have to look into auditing the class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 20:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember in freshman chemistry doing some report on the lattices of graphite and diamond, my conclusion was that graphite was more stable and you should buy a woman a lead pencil (instead of a diamond ring) to show her your love was forever. Either the TA didn't read it or I just wasn't funny.

I also remember doing a proof for a physics problem and halfway through I gave up and wrote "A solution exists, finding it is left as an exercise to the grader." Full credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 18:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really gorgeous!

I may be moving to Evanston soon; would you mind sharing some of your favorite places in the greater Chicagoland area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
