<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8068</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My colleagues were throwing likes onto fb posts thanking Trump for the millennial tears. It was glorious to see so many hidden centipedes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He jacked up my folks' costs for healthcare, so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never dreamed a dream

Where our memes became more than memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F

f

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ho lee fuk

Hillary = Babidi

Kaine = Majin Buu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't floated mana since Psychatog...

*Saving Private Tog flashback* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being that elves have their roots as nature spirits, it kinda makes sense that they would eventually see industrialization as the next big step in nature's evolution. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dragonborn fight elementals, wound them and shed their scales into the wounds. One of the scales will mature into a Dragonborn egg that gets nutrition from the elemental's carcass. Then the Dragonborn hatches and eats the dead elemental to finish the development of its magic system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. That + clothing + history lectures are my big turnoffs as a fantasy reader, so I keep them barebones in my own work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of them bother me. Just don't go all Captain Save-a-Hoe and you're fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Darigaaz, the Igniter]]

[[Tarmogoyf]] - Ryan Barger

[[Sarkhan Vol]]

[[Psychic Venom]]

[[Fire and Brimstone]]

[[Carnivorous Plant]]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you didn't grow up in a backwater where everyone either got trapped in the small town life, got wrangled into running drugs, or ended up with dead-end careers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats chode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you will. The Ifrits are, well, Ifrits from the Moslem mythology. Aesthetically similar, but slightly different. I've justified their humanlike hierarchy as their recognition that we humans are the uber cockroaches of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that meant she was looking to get me out of there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your fellow player's cell #'s. No reason you lot can't go hang on the weekends or w/e. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind games are part of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rig of Entropy -

A sprawling construction of igneous rock in the jungle-shrouded heart of my world's equatorial continent. Embedded in the Rig's base are fossils from the world's foundling races, which catalyzed the study of the Rig by the major monasteries and covens. 

The jungles surrounding the Rig are haunted. The ghosts of Engineers, Progenitors, and Shedders work to keep the Foreshi from mucking around with the Rig. Last time the Foreshi got access to the Rig's magical energy, it set off a big bang that accelerated evolution, turning the Foreshi into the Primevals and simultaneously giving rise to the Primordials. The ghosts remember and seek to prevent that from happening again.

The Foreshi initially fooled around with the Rig because they needed a new energy source. Their old ones had been co-opted by the Engineers and Shedders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. She just kept asking me things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe.

The Primevals (dragons) and Primordials (elementals) lived in outer space; the setting is the debris from their territorial spats collected into a world.

Does that make them aliens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They started out as opportunistic fauna in the Primordials and Primevals. At some point, they began adapting to the world around them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farseer - I felt like there was a very good 200 page book buried in the first volume. About the same for the subsequent ones, except a good 300 pager within the 800ish pages of the followups.

Book of the New Sun - if you like Tolkienesque language, you'll like this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Broken Empire* or *The Red Queen's War* are my recommendations. They move along at a good pace and have a nice sword-and-sorcery feel to them that I haven't gotten from many recent series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer Whelan, Swanland, and of course Frazetta styled covers. Stuff like the single crown/blade/weapon/armor are a turnoff. The exception being the UK cover for Morgan's *The Dark Defiles* with the cool dragon skull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who were the Chyurda again? Not the Mountainfolk like Ketricken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cards = something wrong

potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you do. Same time I did this, she pointed at a jokey diagram of the male brain with three lobes labeled "sex." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scourge is interesting. I can see the uses vs Paths and your own Relics though. Surprised he didn't go 3-2 on Koth to Chandra. Congrats Kevin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> son of a bitch
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it feels like they're trying to hypnotize you? As in, they're throwing you the serious eye contact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell her you wanna show her something in a book/on your phone. I did that, girl I was flirting with leaned right into me. There's your kino. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Become an expert at whatever it is you're studying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes OP. Same shit, different year.

Hey you fookin droobs stop downvoting me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 22:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, its the DnD creature that got big in 4th edition, except mine don't have tits or humanlike proportions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "whopper of a wikileaks"

Sounds like a fucking gerri. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a link to my book - its a hard copy and about 200 miles south of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Yuan-Ti think the Dragonborn are vicious idiots.

The Dragonborn think the Yuan-Ti are spineless bitches.

The Vaku think that the Yuan-Ti and Dragonborn are extreme ends of the world's biorhythm and hire themselves out as mercenaries to both the Yuan-Ti and Dragonborn with the intent of maintaining that biorhythm.

The Yuan-Ti and Dragonborn both think the Vaku are the inbred hicks of the world.

The Ifrit believe that the Dragonborn are misguided, that the Yuan-Ti would make excellent tools, and that the Vaku are the real menace.

Humans, it depends by continent/country/culture.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Primeval Dragons and Primordials existed in a cosmic void after the big bang. 

Prior to the big bang, there's evidence for four Foundling species: the simian Progenitors, the amphibious Foreshi, the reptilian Shedders, and the synapsid Engineers. It is believed that the Shedders and Progenitors ganged up on the Foreshi while the Engineers attempted to remain neutral in the conflict. From this, a few esoteric religions believe, came the big bang that gave rise to the Primevals and Primordials. Similarities between the Foreshi and Primevals indicate that the Primevals arose from the Foreshi. The Primordials seem to be an amalgam of the Progenitors and Shedders achieved by the Engineers' skills in manipulating their primeval world's elements.

As the Primevals and Primordials slugged it out over territory and energy sources, the debris from their fights came together to form the actual world for my setting, Flamedroi where remnants of the Foundlings looked on at the great cosmic wars between the Primordials and Primevals.

From the Primevals came scales, shed, that gave rise to the Regents (a lesser race of dragons) with the intent that the Regents would keep watch over the surviving Foundlings. Cany Primevals feared that the Foundlings would find a way to help the Primordials put an end to them. 

A select few Primevals attempted to make peace with the Foundlings. Unfortunately, the vicious Foreshi tricked the peaceful Primevals into believing that they would need to brainwash the violence out of the warlike Primevals. This triggered further infighting among the surviving Foundlings. In the end, an Engineer stepped up to construct a massive rig that would harness the chaotic energy thrown off by the fighting between Primeval and Primordial. Into this rig the peaceful Primevals began casting their kin; from it emerged wingless Pit-Dragons (yet another race of dragons just beneath Regents) cursed with vicious, bestial temperaments. 

The Shedders, seeing themselves reflected in the Pit-Dragons, turned on the peaceful Primevals and began studying elementalism with the intent on beating the Primevals at their own game. A newly emerged race, the Yuan-Ti - terrified of the Primevals, convinced the peacelike Primevals to casting their warmaking kindred into the same rig as had birthed the Pit-Dragons. This didn't go as planned - from the rig came a viciously stupid five-headed draconic monstrosity known as Tiamat. A Shedder skilled in elementalism emerged to fight against Tiamat - this Shedder is known as Bahamut. So Tiamat and Bahamut fought and the world began developing its own magical defense mechanisms against the two factions.

In the end the Primevals were hunted to extinction by the Foreshi and the Yuan-Ti. During this time mankind's ancestors emerged as well from the Progenitor lineage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works like an inflammatory response -

Magic to summon aggressive elements

Magic to promote growth

Magic to burn out the thread

Magic to trigger healing

Magic to remove the leftover debris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 09:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Yuan-Ti suffer from PTSD induced by the fighting between the Primevals and Primordials. It was made worse when the Yuan-Ti attempted to end the fighting, inadvertently created Tiamat, and kicked off a war between Tiamat and Bahamut. They've since sought isolation and would rather act in impish defiance of the Primeval Dragons, blaming them for their state of existence.

The various underworld elements are driven be a desire to not go back to the impoverished existence from which they came...or they despise the underhanded dealings of the industrial heights from which they fell and believe their mobster work is more honest.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 09:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read ADWD and connect their dream sequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seen a lot of friends coming out for Trump on my facebook. Feels good brahs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would need to be a blue/black deck to run Psychatog you scrub.

edit

Y u salty brahs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Simic Skyswallower]] you potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut yer gabber. Graffdigger is the new Lightning Bolt ya droob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that shit boyo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find new gods. Go to Innistrad and make more gods like [[The Gitrog Monster]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this thing's first run in Standard. Psychatog was a backup win, I think. or some builds included it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere in ADWD. The chapter were he dreams that he's armored in black ice with a red sword. It reads like he's leading the wildlings in an attack on the Wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there something wrong with the audio? She sounds awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on your preference in terms of foreshadowing. I'm not a fan of foreshadowing with all the subtlety of a brick to the head. The books have given us evidence that Jon is a dragon/Targaryen. We have Dany Targaryen. Two dragons, with a prior event called the "Dance of Dragons." That's my kind of foreshadowing - its there, but without too much in the way of flashing neon lights telling you in all-caps what's going to happen.

I could be entirely wrong - we'll know when we have the book in our hands. I imagine Aegon will butt heads with Dany or Euron depending on how well he has consolidated his powerbase by the time these two become bigger threats. There's far more moving pieces in play that we must needs consider before writing off any of our theories as definitively wrong. Especially when these theories are taken from textual evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a couple of dreams in ADWD, one where Dany's fighting the Usurper's dogs at the Trident...except they're made of ice...and one where Jon dreams of beheading Rob, usurping him as Lord of Winterfell.

That's where I got the idea. Thematically speaking, I think it makes sense for Aegon to step up and clean up the debris from the Jon v Dany Dance of Dragons. Aegon, likely Faegon, is a bastard of no notable birth or heritage, yet could be the one to unite commoner and lord alike against a greater threat.

I feel that Dany vs Aegon is too blunt for GRRM. Too telegraphed, if you will, given the historical basis for the Dance of Dragons. Euron is the wild card, but then he may also ultimately end up on team Ice given the TWOW sample chapter "The Forsaken." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon vs Dany

If GRRM cuts the chaff, he can do it in seven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUARK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tried to please everyone and got divine hypertrophy, which resulted in them ultimately failing - increased workload of prayers/devotions/sacrifices (they let the individual cultures do whatever they want) made them work harder, turning them into giant, polymorphous monstrosities.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Jund"

"Tier 3"

OP my modern instincts don't amount to more than kicking in other planeswalkers' teeth until a better one comes after me, but I think I know more about the format than you.

edit - 6 potatoes got beat by Jund...probably the build from last year with [[Thundermaw Hellkite]]. Turn in your Modern cards boyos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny thread

provocative pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shit's getting cray cray. I'm waiting for Moloch to show up and disavow Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flamedin (From Moorcock's *The Dragon in the Sword*) + Le Casse Roi Russe (from King's *The Dark Tower*) = Flamedroi, my world's name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does magic stimulating growth count as healing magic? It can't mend wounds, and is intended to augment magics meant for a more offensive use. Now, these offensive magics aren't meant to cause harm - they are the world's defense against extraplanar stressors, injury etc.

This growth magic could be redirected to anything in the environment - jags of metal, thorns, etc to augment the object's size and durability. There you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one likes to lose, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 03:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A foil Tarmogoyf from MM2. Beautiful Ryan Barger art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the big bang, it began appearing as a defense mechanism against the Primeval Dragons and Primordials.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you fall for that, you deserve to fall for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fam

I thought MIA = Missing In Action = Hillary

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marit Lage is Eldrazi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone Gregor's size busting out a sudden burst of speed would probably catch even the best off guard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yeah, she'd mentioned she'd been drinking some wine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nemesis was once a human. Prior to the events of the first game, the events of the first movie took place. So Nemesis is that Matt guy that got clawed by the Licker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yuan-Ti, long ago, made it a tradition to remove their fireglands in defiance of the Primeval Dragons with whom they share a lineage. In place of these they developed psionic venom glands that amplify their prey's feelings of anxiety and guilt, rendering their prey a blubbering sack of bones and blood. 

Dragonborn, seeking to adapt to the shifting climates, developed a technique that allowed them to conceal themselves in loose folds of skin magicked to give them a humanlike appearance. It hid them from their natural predators, the Yuan-Ti. In general, dragonborn magic is more focused around seizing power through subtler means ie persuasion than their Primeval ancestors that used might alone.

Navajko, the ancestors of mankind, focused their magic around the natural world ie taking on the bestial characteristics of the furred dragons of the northern frontiers to survive the ice age. Along with this transformative skinshifting magic came an affinity for the natural world - not the ability to conjure elementals, but rather than ability to conjure beasts in the likeness of various mythical houndlike creatures.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figure out what you want your nonhumans to stand for. Mine tend toward reptilian and prehistoric because I'm playing with a subtheme of letting go of the past, rather than allowing it to rule the present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She puts them through the wringer, I guess, but I had a hard time connecting with them. But the aesthetics of Robb have clearly informed Martin's work - he sort of expands on her themes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever hold an interesting job? I dropped a reference to an unusually high-stress job I held for a few years. From there she's firing off a game of 20 questions about the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malik!

How has Barack changed since he got into office?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, no up and down mang. Just a straight stare throughout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Rain Wild give me a better look into how life under dragons works in this setting? Got some nice teases in Fool's Fate about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next: Rain Wild Chronicles or Fool's Assassin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have finished Fool's Fate.

Should I stop and read Rain Wild Chronicles or go on to Fool's Assassin? I managed the Tawny Man books without the Liveship Traders Trilogy if that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insectlike mites you'd find between a dragon's scales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself. I got [[Eldrazi Mimic]] duplicates in a fatpack and that helped me move them quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized they were Star Wars like at the end of Eldest. Not my choice of gateway book. I would suggest Harry Potter instead, or even Anne McAffery's Pern of LeGuin's Earthsea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're gonna have to start pinning important shit to Goku's gi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crossing the gulf of time and space to fight is a real bitch, so they've never fought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

Its when a realm called the Green Inferno passes through the lands of the living. This is the realm from which the beastfolk - fearsome, apelike beings that can shift into bestial dragonlike demons - came. They stalk the lands, demanding tribute from their lands-of-the-living-bound descendants. In turn the beastfolk carry out whatever acts of vengeance their scattered devotees demand of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4:

Progenitors

Foreshi

Engineers

Shedders

Before those, there was a Big Bang. After those 4 came the Primevals and Primordials. After Primevals and Primordials came lesser elementals, lesser dragons, and mankind's earliest ancestors. The angels and demons were initially forged as armor and weapons (respectively) for the Primevals' hellhound offspring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MAGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is coming from the campaign that told us to imagine "President Donald. J. Trump."

Their ad campaign isn't out of character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its show Stannis, shit would be on fire yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I preferred Arya's to Brienne's because we got to see the Brotherhood. Brienne gave us a well-rounded look at the role of the Sparrows, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 18:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Standard still dancing to the tune of loot-scoot-boogie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to Northos/Northeros and recruit sellswords acclimated to fighting in wintery conditions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the full panoramas of the Jund lands from Champions of Kamigawa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If poetry is your strength as a writer, then showcase it! I would say I've never been into poetry, but then I never realized stuff like "It Wasn't Me" and "Holidae Inn" were poetry. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you miss Tiam? It seemed fairly badass from what I remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly, I preferred the movie's take on the Urgals and Razac. Barbarians and weird elementals were better than the novel's derivatives, but of course neither of the two (novel or movie) is all that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 18:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malazan style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they ask you questions? Like about your favorite food? Sports? Anything like that? It seems like they do fine keeping up the conversation, or at least giving you stuff to work with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 08:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potential triggering:

Went to a chinese buffet with a lovely asian and her african american friend. Dude and his girl that looked like your textbook SJW had the booth near ours. We heard a noise from the kitchen that sounded like power tools.  Asian says she's kinda worried - and the aa chick says yeah, you know what they say about asian places. Both laughed.

SJW dude bertstared me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body Language in the Apartment (not IOIs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 06:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not IOIs. I don't think a lady would invite you into her apartment if she weren't interested on some level. Anywho, I ended up there to borrow something since she'd put that out a while back. She invites me in, chats me up a bit and is pretty open the whole time, keeps the convo going. Whole time it feels like she's eyeing me up and down. Its kind of awkward tbh.

Sedditors that've been in something similar - how did you proceed in your interactions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep - Sundered Worlds was the first title; it was retitled later. Same happened with Phoenix in Obsidian - that one got reprinted later as "The Silver Warriors." I preferred PiO myself...if you want to continue with those edition, you'll want the Von Bek omnibus. The third novel in that one is TDITS. However, Titan Books has been reprinting most of Moorcock's Eternal Champion novels in the US. Del Rey did the Elric series for the US.

Cameron's Avatar kind of reminded me of The Eternal Champion, so you've got that at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 01:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Political leader tries to secure a region for a magic-line; other nations throw their lot into the war

*Their greed conjures a dragon that darkens the skies over the region, feeding on their greed

*Wandering hero turns into an angel and slays the dragon

*Dragon's burnt flesh crashes to the earth in hundreds of fiery chunks like a meteor storm

*Everyone's shit gets fucked up; everyone gets even madder
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a waste of time, but its easy enough to write about if my lit texts are anything to go by. I couldn't help but notice there's interesting themes about class ie the educated class vs the uneducated that sandbag superstition to make up for their shortcomings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood Red Game is the one you skipped, I think. Its not important to the Erekose series at all. Its more where Moorcock starts developing ideas for his Multiverse concept. It is a pretty weak novel, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't think anyone is saying that exactly. My point is, what's happened has happened. I'm certain no one is carrying those elements from Lovecraft into their works in this day and age. So continually belaboring the series' flavor of the day racism seems like an exercise in pointlessness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Dragon in the Sword* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the Japanese version of RE1 feature the god complex Wesker had in RE5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 07:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she look kinda like Jeb! on purpose....or is it just me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
