<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4819</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 22:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and then there's that ending... the way the sun comes up and Dracula just dusts himself off as if going "welp, my work here is done" and Alucard is just standing there...

You know what would have made the ending better? That shoulder-to-shoulder walk presented in popular movies, like say Casablanca's ending with Rick and the chief of police?

I actually would have liked to see that with Dracula and Alucard, all like "come on, son" "alright dad" and doing a sort of walk-and-hug thing side by side as the credits roll.

I mean then at least I could have appreciated the already absurdly silly story by laughing at such a hilarious scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's discuss Castlevania: Lords of Shadow 2. (Series SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checking posts around the internet and the series seems to be disliked immensely, especially the second one. While I love the gba and ds castlevania games based on sotn, a classic, I also found myself growing to like the first LoS, even though I dismissed it back in 2010. But I played it a few years ago and thought it was pretty ok for the most part, gameplay wise at least. Then there was the mirrors of fate game (ps3 version) which was as close to the IGA castlevania games as you could get, so I liked it too.
Finally we have LoS 2.
It's funny, I don't think I've ever played a game where the story was absolutely abysmal but the voice acting was top notch. I mean how does that even happen, the voice acting was fantastic. Robert Carlyle is amazing as Dracula, his voice is just oodles of goodness, I love listening to it. And then there's the rest of the cast like Patrick Stewart, Jason Isaacs, Madden who voice Alucard, they're all great, I love listening to them, but Robert Carlyle most of all. I can't help praising it a lot.
Anyway, it's true there are things in LoS 2 that deserve criticism, like fact that even after you regain your Dracula powers you still have to sneak around those armored enemies with laser canons and can't actually fight them, which seems like a questionable and hilarious design choice. Or just how underwhelming Dracula in modern day happens to be, an interesting premise that's wasted. But despite that I still enjoyed the game, I don't know I just did. As far as 3d beat em ups go in the vein of god of war, this was pretty much as enjoyable as it gets. Dashing with Dracula feels amazing as heck, the powers are fun, changing between blood whip and ice sword that heals you and fire fists that break enemy defenses is enjoyable, and I like that you can level up these just like in other series.
I liked the castle portions because as similarly silly to the main story as they are, I enjoyed going through the castle and actually appreciated the developers painting a history of Dracula/Gabriel, with stuff like his son as the innocent, his wife as his virtue, trying to make him seem all "tragic" and stuff, etc etc. I mean at least they did something, and I kind of liked the idea behind what they went for, especially when the white wolf appears each time.
The ending was absurdly abrupt that left me with a most bemused expression especially when the credits just started rolling but even then, I enjoyed the game so much that I actually got the Alucard dlc and heck enjoyed that too, complaints notwithstanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why in the heck does the Waitress not have any friends? Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In who pooped the bed when Dee is trying to get a sex and the city going, she tells the Waitress that since she doesn't have any friends she may as well hang out with Dee. But why the heck wouldn't the Waitress have any friends....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you even talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 17:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this movie so damn much you don't even know. This movie should have won 2011's Oscar for best animated feature instead of... *Rango* :/

Shame it didn't but nevertheless remains as one of the best movies (especially since the academy awards have never been a guarantee of quality) and one of the ways in which a sequel does things right, by expanding on the foundation that the movie built before it instead of doing retcons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god lol. I guess that's the thing with not being American or living in America. There are so many references you might miss out on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 12:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to admit this but I've always wondered what that line meant. Is it a reference to how she likes eating meats and wants to find the actual food, like a deli platter?

Or in this context does she mean beef as in trouble as in "where's the trouble?"

Or is it the third meaning. So many double and triple meanings...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 12:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it's not necessarily ALL female villains. Nevertheless it's still an existing, old-as-thyme trope. 

Plus considering Maleficent is the only great thing about Sleeping Beauty (which is really more of a story about the 3 fairies vs Maleficent, which is why I like the fairies so much and the story focuses on them more so than the prince and princess), she's more "awesome cool" villain a la Jafar, rather than "terrifying, gave me nightmares as a kid" villain like Ursula did back in the 90s with the little mermaid. 

On that note, the stepmother from Cinderella IS old, is evil terrifying, and can send chills down your spine with simply her cold gaze and icy eyes. The kicker? *She and Maleficent have the same voice actress.*

How's about that for convincing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female villains have always been more terrifying than male ones, especially from the animated Disney movies. *Possible spoilers here and there* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 11:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Madam Medusa. Ursula. Mother Gothel. Madam Mim.

What do they all have in common? Either fat and/or old women that are absolutely terrifying, use deception, two facedness, and absolute ruthlessness.

I mean yeah sure, Scar, Frollo and Jafar might kill me or torture me and keep me locked away in a dungeon, but that's nothing. With these terrifying female villains, you never know **what** they might do, and that scared me A LOT more as a kid than a guy villain, who I was quite okay with. Mostly because deception and pretending to be someone they're not until "the true form is revealed" always scared the crap out of me and gave me nightmares, which a LOT of these female villains do, like Ursula to look like a human palette swap Ariel, or Mother Gothel to look young, etc etc.

Disney tends to have a trend for this. For example their very first theatrical animated movie, Snow White, had the evil queen who turns herself into an old hag, presumably because there's this rumor that Disney couldn't have an attractive/younger looking woman commit an evil deed like killing, but I don't know if that rumor is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy cow Margot Robbie looks so much hotter as Harley in jester uniform in Suicide Squad! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 11:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good GOD Lemon are you wearing a cup???!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I forgot only guys get hurt there ***scoffs sarcastically*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah maybe. Plus who knows how old Keith really is because he does look kind of grown up and may not necessarily be exactly 25. Especially since I knew him from a soap opera called Passions that I used to actually watch and like, and he was a grown man there. 

Also just checked and in terms of real life he's actually older than elliot so there's that too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 10:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did people here really not like it? I can't quite place the vibe of this forum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It used to be so bizarre to me that Carla is like, 5 to 6 years older than Turk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 10:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time of learning it back then I had come from a place where traditionally it's older men that marry younger women, and the opposite is completely unheard of. 

I mean it's perhaps not that uncommon worldwide but I finally felt the uncomfortable feeling Carla felt when she realized she was like turk's mom, and that angle coupled with just how much older she is than turk made the whole den mother thing she has make a lot more sense in a literal manner, since she really is that much older than him. 

It's not a big deal since love can blossom from anywhere but I have to admit at the time of putting together this factoid I was very stunned, because it's definitely not common for an older woman to be with a younger man, certainly not 5 to 6 years younger. 

Kinda makes me wonder if she wanted elliot to marry Keith so she wouldn't be the only woman in her circle of friends to marry a younger man hehe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still can't believe The Grinder got canceled. Doesn't Fred Savage have enough clout in television by now to prevent such a thing from happening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe no one watched this show, it is beyond hilarious. I crack up at almost every single scene, the humor this show has is totally in tune with my own. 

 

It's such a fantastic show that's unlike anything on TV right now, and for Fox to cancel it... just a damn shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 11:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually made a topic on the tv subreddit about how the shows house and grey's anatomy completely ripped off scrubs in many ways, like the summing up an episode thing and having an arrogant ego driven doctor and doing the "conveniently solve a case through something that happens in their personal life" thing. 

Even though I was right, the users there were adamant about disagreeing with me. Hell, even house's infamous "everybody lies" line was said by Dr Kelso first, and yet the quote is attributed to house. I do sometimes get annoyed at the fact that those 2 shows became insanely successful (hell grey's anatomy is still ongoing) while scrubs was constantly in danger of being canceled. Just one of those little injustices in television.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goodness you guys thank you. Some of these posts have been **AMAZING** solutions and some really enjoyable reads, both entertaining and hilarious, not to mention informative. I really appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my gosh I too have thought of the "if only my ceiling had a tv embedded into it, I could drift off to sleep without having to move a musle" thing! Hehe. 

Don't really care for earphones or headphones though, my ears are already super sensitive and I definitely don't like wearing something if I'm going to bed and want to feel unrestrained, unfettered, before sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's GOT to be a comfortable way to watch asmr videos on your phone while sleeping on your back. [Discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, without having your arms tiredly holding your phone up in the air and potentially dropping your phone on your face in case you accidentally nod off. 

Since sleeping on your back is the best position for sleep, but your arms weren't meant to be holding something in midair like that... oh if only we had telekinesis powers, we could have our phone hover right above our face as we watch a video and gently drift off to sleep... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The split screen thing that Scrubs does is one of my favorite things about the show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When multiple characters have  a problem (usually 3) and the screen splits into 3 panels to show each of them come to a decision. 

I wouldn't mind more shows copying that if they can do it well, but Scrubs really is amazing with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kfc double down thing a few years ago was funnier because that one even had news site saying that 30 Rock "did it first" or at least "predicted the double down." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the actor portraying him since I grew up watching Angel, so back in 2007 when I saw the pilot I was completely psyched to see Connor again. And I think he's great, I love how sleazy the character is and how the show makes you hate him at times for all his sleaze and yet also makes you just as sympathetic towards him. It's hard to describe how but the show pulls it off perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an interesting point on desperation, because it's those moments where he becomes a complete idiot. Hank even calls him out on it as such, saying that he was so greedy about his money that he didn't even notice the dirt around the barrels  was much different than the desert dirt that he actually store the barrels in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It *is* a very bizarre moral compass isn't it... he'd poison a kid, but doesn't want his brother in law Hank to be killed. He'd let Jessica Jones choke on her own vomit to death, but doesn't want Jesse finally taken care of and out of the way, despite seemingly dragging him down, especially as seen in the eyes of Gus initially.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AH thanks that makes sense. I do remember Vegeta finding the poses ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... a question about the androids during the time line the show follows. (SERIES SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't the androids seem as evil as they were during the timeline of future Trunks where they destroy everything, kill everyone, and apparently rip off Gohan's arm. In the show's timeline when they steal a car I don't think they even killed anyone during it did they? 

Would they have started killing after fulfilling their mission to kill Goku I wonder?

Also, what about Android 16. Where was he during the future trunks timeline. In fact, what exactly changed about future trunks going back in time to make it so that Android 19 and 20 existed when there was no mention of them in future trunks timeline? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but do you understand what the question in the original message is asking? It's why **wouldn't** Walt want to give up Jesse to Gus (with the implication being that Gus is of course, going to kill Jesse) considering he seemed to be happy with his new less hectic drug arrangement in comparison to Crazy 8 and Tuco.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else like what if scenarios that the video games had like dbz supersonic warriors on the gba? *Spoilers for all DBZ* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, I don't know, Cell absorbing Majin buu or majin buu eating perfect cell, or what would have happened if such character didn't beat that character. 

It's been over a decade since I played Supersonic Warriors so I don't remember it much, but I do remember being entertained by the dialogue for the what if scenarios. Can anyone recount any other what if scenarios from different games? Like maybe fusions between a Namekian and a Saiyan or anything plot wise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Concerning fusions with Goku and Vegeta. *Entire series and movie spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 12:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Gogeta was only ever in the movie, he never an appearance in the Buu saga, only Vegito did due to the potarra earrings.

My question is, how come Goku never lowered his power level to fusion with Vegeta to become Gogeta during the Buu saga whenever the potarra earrings weren't available?


And if fusions are still relevant, would it be good for goku and vegeta to do so now to take care of the bad guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 12:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this concerning though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wondering something about Walt's relationship with Jesse *Series Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 12:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walt and Gus were bonding in season 3, Walt seems to be enjoying what seems to be an amicable relationship with the big drug dealer this time, and even enjoys cooking with Gale.

So my question is, why wouldn't he want to give up Jesse when Gus wanted him to, why was he so insistent on protecting Jesse, especially considering how evil Walt becomes by the end and even just as recently as poisoning a kid, to be so attached to Jesse. In spite of their constantly strained and rather dysfunctional relationship. 

His strange fascination with wanting Jesse always confused me; instead off him heading for greener pastures with more competent people that have a more evolved vocabulary than just "bitch" he chooses to remain with his old buddy from the beginning of his bad breaking days of cooking meth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've always found a hilarious juxtaposition between all the debauchery this show has and... *safety spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 11:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pete using terms like "swell" and other old school 'wholesome' type vocabulary.  Meanwhile he's cheating on his gorgeous wife Alison Brie (who even does that) while she's carrying his child, and of course afterwards as well. 

It's a juxtaposition I've always found interesting, because underneath all the ideallic settings of quaint neighborhoods and how-do-you-dos, there's a whole world of... I mean for god's sake, Sally witnessed Roger getting oral sex at a party, that's just awful. 

I always thought the show did that juxtaposition painfully well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 10:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up with this joke it was my childhood, how is everyone not giving thumbs up arrows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Dracula went to the blood bank, he said: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Do you deliver?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right one of the earlier ones. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 21:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you even know how rare it is to find uncensored hentai where the character goes "I love you I'm going to marry you!" during sex? You have to take what you can get wherever you get it, even a weird h-manga that gets weirder by the panel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't the porn actors actually communicate with each other while they're having the sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like descriptive porn like "your vagina is amazing, I never knew that different women had different... textures, it feels great" or the girl telling him "okay like that, just keep going... yeah let me get on top and rub my clitoris on you... yeah just stay there... you like it, you like the why I grind on your shaft" and just really descriptive instead of silent breathing or worse going "oh fuck oh yeah oh fuck oh god" (that's not sexy, it's just annoying)

Like, actual communication between the two partners is so much hotter than watching 2 professional porn actors have dispassionately sterile sex. Homemade porn however is usually so silent, with just moaning and groaning, but never actual communication which surprises me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes you wonder what he saw in her in the first place then if that's the way it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if the riley reids or dakota skyes or mia lina types did one, those are more my type than the other girls mentioned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But would spending time with Bruce have changed her, softened her, or even made her a relatively decent human being? That's the question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I really like vanilla or true love stories, does anyone know of any? For example Pretty Cool, I love that one. I even like Peace Hame, weird at it is. Oh also being uncensored is very much preferable, there's rarely a story good enough for me to sit through pixelated genitals or black bars.

My favorite thing about Pretty Cool is how in the heat of the moment he says he's going to get her pregnant and they're going to spend the rest of their lives together, I love stuff like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I laughed. At him of course, not with him. But laughed neverthefew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I laughed. At him of course, not with him. But laughed neverthefew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which episode WAS the (supposedly) mormon girl? I always forget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hmm... do they make any more "professional porn girl fucks a virgin/inexperienced fan" type videos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know brittney skye fucks a virgin once, and on the opposite end I know that james deen has sex with a female fan of his. The validity of those 2 claims are as always suspect, but I'm generally just curious if there exists any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The movie Sideways doesn't have the song Sideways. smh missed opportunity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do ants eat our boogers? What about the nails, and hair we throw away every single day? How do those decompose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 13:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her come hither/dilated eyes look that she gives is just... orgasmic. And that little she smile she does... I just can't, it's too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 13:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. Her come hither/dilated eyes look that she gives is just... orgasmic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 10:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't diddle kids, it's not cool to diddle kids. Can't be small, gotta be big. Something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Bruce Mathis HAD raised Dennis and Dee? Would they have turned out better? *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 09:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, most of the blame seems to be centered on Frank, but their mother seems like a pretty horrible woman in her own right, would she have made them bad like they are now too. 

Or would Barbara have been a nice woman if she had stayed with bruce all this time? I guess it's debatable whether she was always like that or frank brings out the worst in her. 

Still, it makes me wonder about an alternate reality where bruce had been dennis and dee's father all this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 10:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ironic that most people who consider something to be snobby always end up being or saying something snobby themselves hehe xp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I so hate time skips in tv shows (or really any kind of media) especially of an ongoing story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 08:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of my most disliked tropes ever. Maybe it's because almost every show that's done the "5 years later" type time skip always ends up worse than when it started out.

They may do it for any number of reasons like they want to be able to update the tv show world with current technology so anachronisms don't appear, like an iphone in 2004.

And I tend to dislike it for a number of reasons, such as the fact that the time they skipped is actually one we the viewers would have loved to see.

Off the top of my head, I can recall simultaneous ABC shows Lost and Desperate Housewives doing a time skip in season 5, and that's when I hated Lost, and that's when I outright dropped watching Desperate Housewives (which I actually used to watch unironically; I actually enjoyed it as far as female centric shows go. It was much better to me than say, sex in the city) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH my god yes yes a thousand times yes. Young mila kunis was such a 10/10.

I like elisha too, although I was weirded out when someone first pointed out to me that she and maria ozawa look like each other a little. I couldn't unsee it after that comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 14:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe. I can't watch the video yet so I won't be able to confirm on her quality until I do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 12:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bunch of innocent photos and then bam, nudes. I'm like damn that escalated quickly. 

She really is quite gorgeous isn't she. Wouldn't kill her to smile more though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> oh xkcd... 10 years later and still so accurate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I totally get that, god I loved Desmond... those were some fun days during the golden age of Lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 comments but only 2 visible ones? Dammit I hate when this stupid website shadowbans someone! That person who posted who's now shadowbanned might have just given us the answer and we'd never know! My god reddit is such weird website with this feature... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me find this girlsdoporn video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/lJsD8F0.png

I think it might be the Behind the scenes video of the girl from Episode 319, but I can't confirm and for the life of me can't find the video anywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese porn videos that are 2, 3, or even 4 hours long... I admire the dedication but holy fuck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 15:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, that length is insane isn't it?

And kinda made worse by the fact that it's usually all that censored pixelated genitals nonsense, so it's like, what a waste of 4 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is that Josh Holloway (Sawyer from Lost) show "Intelligence" basically just Chuck? Without any of the humor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 11:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or entertainment factor?

I mean... his power, it's basically the intersect from Chuck which is a very specific detail to copy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Concerning Dennis and his sextapes with all the preamble. *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 11:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a reference to pornography videos that have so much preamble before the actual sex gets under way? Like an hour long video having 30 minutes of just straight jibber jabber?

Just wondering if the show is meant to reference that or just be something specific to Dennis's character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for hentai where the girl says "my hips are moving on their own. You're making me feel good inside." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manga is not unwelcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girlsdoporn episode number with a black girl? She says she's studying to be a nurse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video in question had condoms. Can't recall the episode number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowgirl position where the girl is grinding back and forth instead of up and down on the cock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer when she's grinding back and forth on the guy's cock, especially with lots of hip gyrations, instead of just boringly bouncing up and down bouncy ball style which does nothing for me. 

I'll try to find an example of my own to post to get the ball rolling. 

https://gfycat.com/ExaltedSecondaryBlobfish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elliot... you're my dream girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 05:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyonce singing "fever" in The Fighting Temptations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember when Cuba Gooding Jr won an Oscar for Jerry Maguire and then went on to do... Snow Dogs and Daddy Day Care 2? And such? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol... that was so weird, it was like, wtf Cuba?

I mean, he didn't do it immediately of course, he still had this movie with robert de niro that I  really liked, called Men of Honor, and personally I really liked the comedy movie Rat Race, don't know what the general consensus of it is, but I have good memories watching it with some friends back in the day. 

Still, it's hilariously weird isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies with unreliable narrators bother me a lot more than they used to, like The Usual Suspect and Gone Girl. (Can you recount any other movies like that?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 19:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We never know what actually happened, because we only see the narrative from certain character's point of view. It makes rewatching and analyzing the movie difficult because we don't *know* what actually happened in order to support our thoughts on why so and so did this and that. 

I dunno, can you think of any other movies with the unreliable narrator trope? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized that Elizabeth Banks spent a lot of time on television being knocked up by two different JD's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 19:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrubs - John Dorian

30 Rock - Jack Donaghy

???

Who will be next? Not only that, but both are NBC shows (or maybe because of that? I mean it could almost be considered the weirdest typecast of all time if someone went for the hattrick) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Gallagher as Schmidt's father was a great casting choice this season. *safety spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I always liked Peter Gallagher even before the days of watching the first season of The OC, and seeing him here just puts a smile to my face.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the guy can't even get hard while he's fucking a beautiful woman, and his penis is all floppy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get so angry, I'm like "move  out of the way you stupid ass, if you can't even get hard when fucking the most gorgeous girl of all time yvette yukiko... I get hard just thinking about her"

I'm always like man I'll show those girls what it's like to be disappointed with my rock hard barely 5 inches penis. I'll disappoint her sure but damn if I won't stay hard for her lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The convulsions are a nice touch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 06:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gfycat.com/EnlightenedTornBlackbird

Even if, like most porn girls, it's completely fake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr Cox calling Jordan Godzilla is a favorite of mine, but does anyone have the clip of when he calls her Attila? That might actually be my favorite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 21:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is it about Elliot that makes her look so different in season 1 compared to later seasons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, by season 5 she had long hair again just like she did in Season 1, and yet she looks so remarkably different but in a way I just cannot describe, a certain je ne sais quoi  I can't quite put my finger on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Videos of girls actually sweating and looking flushed when having sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 13:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/AK1Rb8Z.gifv

That's so much hotter than the typical sterile American porn look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... is this photoshopped or real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 06:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/qxqBP

And if so who is she.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for casting couch type video, girl's name is katrina. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 04:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video states she's Latina, she has one of those combination hair colors of black and blonde. 

Near the end when he creampies her they start kissing and I damn near came at the how she was holding him while kissing even though his face is blurred, which is annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albus Severus [safety spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 10:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *criiiiiiiiiiiinnge*

Every time I get to the epilogue. Every time. 

There was nothing in Harry's character that would make him name his own son after snape instead of oh say, just build a memorial in his honor or have his portrait in the headmaster's office. I mean if he loves snape so much why doesn't he bring him back with the resurrection stone during that pivotal scene in book 7. 

I don't know. I was always bothered by the last book for several reasons. Don't know if it's a common opinion with long time hp fans, especially ones who were as obsessed with the series as I was during middle school and high school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oohjoy asmr is one of the best asmrtists ever and yet has had so little exposure in the community [intentional] [whispering] [various accents] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 10:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a cute little hidden gem of an asmr video [intentional] [tapping] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 05:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone knows about peaches, but so few know about nectarines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 09:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lol, XKCD made the red herring joke of Ex Machina like 7 years before the movie came out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If they were going to do a spinoff season, why didn't they use the interns from season 8? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 14:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my main question. 

They spent an inordinate amount of time in season 8 attempting to build up those characters, especially in the beginning of the season. 

Yeah I guess they did bring Denise back (better known as Jane from happy endings, an infinitely better and more likable character) but I thought they were setting up katey to be mini elliot and that one glasses dude to be a more dopey looking (but surprisingly sharper) the todd and Sonny to be a... well actually I dunno, maybe jd? I just liked her because she was cute and sweet, which was refreshing in comparison to the snarky sarcastic riff-raff. 

But most importantly of all, they brought back the famous Jett Jackson! I loved watching that show as a kid, and to see the actor again playing Derek is just perfect. Can't believe we never see him again, instead they replace him with who, the ever annoying Franco brother of James? Or the white dude who looks like the drug addict that tried to scam elliot out of meds. That always bothered me since I thought we were going to see him again if they were doing a spinoff on the interns. 

And all this is IF they were going to do a spinoff at all, since in general the interns are usually better in small bursts, like Lonnie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt is basically 30 Rock with Jack Donaghy (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 11:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show is *ok*, but... it lacks a strong male presence, someone for the male audience essentially. 

Plus, a lot of the jokes and supporting characters do fall flat and get kinda grating at times. 

I dunno, liz lemon hit it out of the park with 30 rock and how frustrating (but in a funny way) working with the actors behind a sketch comedy show (or any show really) can be, and tracy + jenna were hilarious. But here the characters waver between the annoying and humorous line way too much, more often than not landing on the annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never did get why American porn girls like riley reid and lexi belle do everything EXCEPT creampie videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 05:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, why the holdout? It just doesn't make any sense. 

After all they still run the risk of pregnancy with every porn shoot, if that's what they're worried about (though I'm sure they must already take birth control) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized that Elizabeth Banks spent a lot of time on television being knocked up by two different JD's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrubs - John Dorian

30 Rock - Jack Donaghy

??? 

Who will be next? Not only that, but both are NBC shows (or maybe because of that? I mean it could almost be considered the weirdest typecast of all time if someone went for the hattrick) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to say, it always bothered me that JD was a jerk to Danny (prime Tara Reid) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://coolspotters.com/files/photos/3491/zach-braff-and-scrubs-gallery.jpg

I was madly infatuated with Tara Reid as a teenager so seeing her on Scrubs was always a plus, but it drove me absolutely crazy how awful JD was to Danny.

It's probably the only time I've ever truly disliked him, because obsessing over Elliot is well and good but you've got an absolutely gorgeous, stunning young woman right there who wants to be with you. I mean... cripes. Rewatching season 3 always awakens this opinion for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's interesting that the therapist didn't say anything when they were salting Gail the Snail. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Frank intervention episode. Lol she just sat there quietly watching the events unfold as Charlie salted the snail out of the bar. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feel like ranting a little, my Wii stopped being able to read discs and refuses to be a gamecube player. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 11:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wag The Dog and Midnight Run; 2 Robert De Niro comedies that you may not have seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 20:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These 2 movies are simply amazing, and have a great supporting cast. While I know RDN comedy wise from king of comedy, and most people know of him in his 21st work with stuff like meet the parents, but the 2 movies in the title are absolutely fantastic and should be watched by all no matter what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a video of a girl giving a guy a blowjob on a high ledge and she spits the cum out on the street below. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 12:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's disgusting and an awful thing to do. But... I couldn't help being turned on by it __ . Specifically, I think I was attracted to the danger of being literally 20+ stories up and on a precarious ledge where one wrong move and you could fall, so the adrenaline of such a feat is kind of a turn on. 

She's a porn girl so it's not amateur, but I don't remember her name, only that she had... reddish hair, I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So DBZ in a nutshell (courtesy of lilformers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 21:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever seen someone that looked exactly like how you pictured a character as described in the book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 21:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when I was quite young and was reading this book series, anyway in school there was a student a number of grades above me, and they looked exactly like what I had envisioned the character in this book I was reading to look like.

Same thing happened a few years back when I was reading this detective novel, from the "... *In Death*" series. The detective is described as a blond haired woman with hazel nut eyes and whatnot, but I remember seeing an episode of Cold Case and the detective of that show looked *exactly* how I imagined the character to look while reading the books.

It's a weird phenomenon, I don't know how best to explain it but when it does happen, it is noticeable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It always bothered me that House and Grey's Anatomy copied a lot of Scrubs and yet they ended up being more successful than that amazing show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 11:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House at one point was the most watched tv show in America, and ditto for Grey's Anatomy, a show that's actually still going on if you can believe it, according to Wikipedia. 

Both of these copied Scrubs in terms of having voice overs at the beginning and end of every episode, or having an arrogant jerk of a doctor who is still around the hospital because he's just that good and also has a bit of a god complex, I mean Dr Cox was basically House before that show even aired, complete with an addiction to alcohol as opposed to painkillers for House.

While these 2 shows were pulling great ratings, Scrubs was in danger of being canceled on NBC nearly every season, to the point where at the end it really did end its run on NBC and ABC picked up the show instead, giving fans proper closure to the series as opposed to the terrifying way that season 7 ended. Honestly, just thinking about such injustice keeps me up in the afternoon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys, androids! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 02:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy shit I think Ai Uehara is the only Japanese woman that smiles in porn, I think I'm in love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 18:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gfycat.com/JoyousAnguishedAnaconda

It's just missing uncensored, and she would be the perfect girl making perfect porn, uncensored happy Japanese porn. Anyone can help out?

https://gfycat.com/ElderlyTightIberianlynx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need even more reprimanding asmr or sarcastic to the viewer asmr [request] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 09:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fred asmr is pretty good with his rude English gentleman series, I got so many tingles from his rude librarian video. 

I'd like for one of the girls to do one as I'm sick of the fake sweetness and pretending to care videos that they all do, some that are especially saccharine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was eating jelly/gelatin dessert part of anyone else's post Iftar snack during Ramadan times? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember there were so many flavors of Royal gelatin dessert that simply don't exist  anymore in any markets, despite it tasting very good, so many  memories as well of sitting with extended family during gatherings and having some. And some families even put little fruit pieces like sliced peaches into the dessert.

I also think it may have been good in terms of keeping your body relatively hydrated so you feel better for the next fasting day. At least, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Um... the picture that accompanies "foreshadowing" to the right of this subreddit... I don't get it? Could someone explain it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 21:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one that depicts a scene from empire strikes back. 

But I recall no such scene of a half broken and smoking Vader mask with what appears to be Luke's face on it so..?

Just hoping to be reminded of context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plothole in mean girls: how come no one acknowledged that gretchen wieners was clearly the hottest one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else miss the Trix cereal fruit shapes of the 90s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 22:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We went from this:

https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/9/9b/Old_Trix_Box.jpg

To this:

http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_0LtfnmicScs/SnTVtLpQ_qI/AAAAAAAAGFY/wGL9utOEMWc/s400/trix-swirls.jpg

To now this:

http://img.huffingtonpost.com/asset/scalefit_630_noupscale/5627c4391200002e007e5a85.jpeg

I mean... it's literally heartbreaking. We've reverted back to what Trix used to look in like, the 50s or whatever. 

I'd give anything for them to release the fruit shapes as a special edition, just one last time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirates 5 not having Keira Knightley is gonna bother me so much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 22:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if they are bringing Orlando Bloom back, why not Keira?

I don't even get what's up with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the guy who keeps posting manga sex comics, could you release Shady Dealings and School Regulation Violation #34? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 15:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought they were available on Fakku but fakku seems to not allow you to view their comics anymore. In any case I was just curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> School Rumble related: I can finally see Tenma-chan's value now. *SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 14:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's the heart of the group. She's the one who brings Mikoto, Eri, and Akira together. Without her, these 3 wouldn't be as close friends, with there being a clear rivalry between Miko and Eri, both being attractive, successful girls with one being more athletic and into sports while the other being more "princessy" as they say. Which can (and has) lead to friction.

She's I guess the innocent, or the sweet one that everyone likes to protect and take care of. She may not be smart, strong, or have any type of skillset whatsoever, but without her the group can't or doesn't come together. She's essentially the heart and soul of the group.

Now why Harima wants her when he's way out of her league I don't know, but I guess that same kindness she has is what Harima likes. Although it's clear that he idolizes her, and a smarter show that isn't just a huge tease would eventually have an arc making him realize or distinguish the difference between idolizing someone, and actually liking or loving something, and have it be mutual, which is much different than just one way idolizing a person.

Anyway just rewatching the show for the umpteenth time and thought about her role in the series overall, since I used to call her the weakest link, while Harima is (easily) the greatest anime character of all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video where a guy and girl are looking deeply into each other's eyes and say I love you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 02:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if it exists. Especially if that's the moment where he finishes inside her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LilCandy was this porn girl who was thin and then later became really fat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/9qksYq0.png

I don't know why but that makes her seem oddly endearing, that they have problems just like everyone else and since she's from Kentucky, it makes sense that obesity would hit her as well, as she just kept getting fatter. I can relate lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just love when they use the opening of the nutcracker soundtrack in certain scenes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 12:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like in Mac's Banging the Waitress, I love that because it's both hilarious and nostalgic for me since I grew up watching the nutcracker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I always thought it was odd that they chose a Japanesey lyricd song for Crisis Core's ending. *SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 11:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Futurama is so unrealistic. Stephen Hawking in a pizzeria? Preposterous! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 00:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing isn't even worth the gold it's made of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys should seriously watch Another Period, it's really funny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always love when they juxtaposition costume drama sets with modern comedic moments that poke fun at the timeline back then, and this one is really good, Natasha Leggerop and Riki Lindhome are great in it. Also the rest of the cast are amazing too, for example Christina Hendricks of Mad Men fame is in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The movie Room with Brie Larson really depressed me, was it emotionally taxing on anyone else? *Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 15:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really powerful movie. 

I could barely stomach the first half hour, with it dawning on me what the situation was, her being kidnapped, raped, even beaten, which makes me a combination of sickened and angry beyond belief. 

Then I was literally shaking restlessly in my seat when the son was in the pickup truck and I was like "please please let him find help oh god please please I can't watch please let him escape"

Even though it was just a movie, I was so invested by the situation and it really resonated with me, the feeling of being trapped against one's will, but at the same time absolutely horrified me, and made me so upset. 

It's just a really emotionally draining movie. Especially since the journey doesn't end after they got out. There's still so much to think about. How is she going to live the rest of her life? Will the fact that she was kidnapped and held prisoner for 7 years define her and the rest of her life? Can therapy and support really be enough to live a satisfactory high quality of life? I don't know. 

And the kid. What about him. First off, The child actor in this movie was fantastic, I can't believe the academy didn't give him any sort of recognition. Anyway, as strong as he is, what will it be like when he becomes a teenager, an adult? What about the stigma surrounding his birth? What about the unfortunate implications of what causes someone to be a horrible rapist who traps humans, is it something genetic, will the kid be something like that?

I don't know. The movie just sort of ends but I was left with all these questions, because the situation really got to me. 

What did you think about the movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any news on an emerald green Vita color? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar to the green psp that came bundled with peace walker? I leapt on that color immediately. Was gorgeous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The longer intro they had in the beginning of Season 2 actually wasn't half bad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 01:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original intro will always be a classic, but I remember reading on Wikipedia that the reason it was changed back because of the overwhelming complaints at the new intro. But I mean, I've never disliked it myself. After all it's still the same song and motif. Plus "I'm No Superman" is just a great song no matter what.

An old timey link for the curious:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bhh7qzurMZY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember in the beginning when they tried to make Jordan the villain or an antagonist of sorts? Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially with the "truth bombs" she dropped during the first season's finale and the aftermath of that hurricane. 

It's rather funny when you see an episode of season 4 where she becomes incredibly goofy like the rest of the cast (while still being abrasive in her own way) to how mean and sharp tongued she was when Perry and her were squabbling in any situation during season 1. 

I'd say it's the turning blonde that really mellowed her out. If you'll notice after she becomes blond she becomes incredibly kooky, and a lot less guarded with mean retorts like she was earlier.

Always thought the disparity between the two was interesting, especially as someone who grow up watching The Drew Carey Show and knowing her character from that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've always thought it was weird that Namco decided to release Tales of Symphonia on the ps3, but STILL KEEP Tales of Vesperia on 360 only, at least in America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the fact that they actually released a lot more Tales games since 2008, and yet still never did Tales of Vesperia for ps3 in North America. It's like... why not? So strange. They released both Tales of Symphonia *and* its sequel, which were both previously on gamecube and Wii, although Symphonia did get a Japanese only ps2 release. 

It's kind of disheartening, since I fully expected them to release the updated Japanese Tales of Vesperia that they did for ps3 in North America at some point. 

Especially since it felt that way since they ported Eternal Sonata, which was on 360, and I always got the vibe that this was like a fun appetizer to the main course, Tales of Vesperia. 

But it never came. 8 years later and a gen that's now passed, and they never brought it. Despite them releasing other Tales games, hence my confusion. It's just strange, all things considered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a shame no one watched this show, it was really good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A certain population of internet women known for complaining about female empowerment all the time, and yet didn't even bother to watch this great amazing show with a fantastic performance by Hayley Atwell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate vegemite. Too good to be true </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I forget iZombie is a CW show from how good it is. (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 13:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would have thought that such an off-putting title actually housed one of the best shows currently airing? I actually waited 4 months after being recommended it to bother watching it because I couldn't get past the name and the network it came from, but then I did... and I ended up with an unfamiliar feeling that I now identify as "like" which soon turned to "absolutely enamored by"

See what happened was a fellow Veronica Mars fan recommended it to me, so I watched because of the Rob Thomas name attachment, but I stayed for the absolutely adorable Liv and her lovable personalities. Then afterwards the plot started getting crazy good, which brings us to what we see today, a really amazing show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I always wondered about Rowdy/Steven. (Spoilers?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they have the Rowdy being lost just as a storyline or did the production team actually lose the dog Rowdy at some point and decided to make a storyline around it with the whole Steven thing, and then later they found the dog Rowdy and had Turk and JD have two dogs now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me identify who the slightly Asian looking girl is in this video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.playvids.com/v/82A4uGkxyea

It's from a series of videos called "Student Sex parties" and this one is creamy birthday bash

I just want to know if she's an actress that's been in other porn videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celebrity sextapes are usually so boring where the woman just lies there... except for one from some Russian celebrity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 13:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember the details, or if she's Russian even/some general Eastern European state, basically it was part of or close to the infamous 2014 leaked hacks thingie, and she's grinding away on her lover and really moving those hips and it's incredibly passionate, and I just thought that was amazing. Just curious to get a name since it was 2 years ago so I can't remember more details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized they had both Harold AND Kumar in season 5. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno thought that was funny. A shame that they didn't keep Harold around though, he was just in the jury duty episode and they seemed to build him up but guess not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hell happened to Pete Holmes channel on Youtube? Did it get taken down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This girl being fucked, does anyone know what she's currently been up to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/WAsjV4m.jpg

I've seen a couple of her videos from public agent, czech streets, woodman casting, fucked or fired, and more, all around 2012/2013. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to play guitar (well enough to get you laid) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you kidding me, how could this show be cancelled???!! Doesn't Fred Savage have enough clout by now to prevent such a thing from happening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 17:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is tearing me up inside, it's such a fantastic show that's unlike anything on TV right now, and for Fox to cancel it... just a damn shame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Von Karma is such a dick (courtesy of Hiimdaisy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I absolutely love Hiimdaisy, she's one of the greatest webcomic artists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about internet speeds, computer power and how "it" all works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example let's say I have a gallery of 800 videos on a page, all with thumbnails, all showing on a single page. I have a slowish 3mbps speed, and after a while the site mostly gives up on showing all the thumbnail images, it just simply gives up, no matter how long I have the page up.
Why does it give up? What does it take for it to not give up loading all the thumbnails?
Same thing with an imgur gallery featuring entire comics, like more than 50 panels. After a while it needs to reload, and not all the images immediately show up.
Does this have to do with internet speed, the hardware capabilities of the actual computer, or both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys, 50/50 with JGL is such a good movie. *Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a young otherwise healthy dude who finds out he has cancer. Anna Kendrick is in this and she's adorable. Seth Rogen is in this and he's not hateable. It was an amazing movie.

Bryce Dallas Howard once again plays a kind of bitchy role or role where you tend to dislike her, she's really good at those (The Help and maybe Jurassic World. Among others)

It was a weird quirk that JGL's character doesn't know how to drive, that seems odd. But otherwise, very emotional and heartwarming the whole way through, you really feel for JGL's character. I remember seeing the trailer for this movie and knowing immediately that this movie would resonate with me very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Quick question about internet speeds, computer power and how "it" all works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 10:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I finally finished playing the Xenosaga trilogy. I feel they were overly ambitious storywise, but unfortunately fell way short. [SPOILERS, for both it and Xenogears] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 12:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame, because there were a lot of good ideas here. Gameplay wise I found all of them fine, not without their problems but overall not bad at all, even 2 which had the tedious stocking/casting elemental sword/airing/boosting method of winning battles. 

But I remember when I first played Episode 1, they had a pretty interesting setup with: 

- the gnosis phenomenon

- Shion's character and her traumatic history as well as emotional baggage from Kevin leading into her connection with Kosmos

- Kosmos herself, and all the mysteries surrounding her architecture

- Realians and their rights, as well as prejudice against them as seen by Lieutenant Virgil, which I thought was going to be a larger part of the story since they focused so heavily on it at the beginning (but ultimately... was not)

- Jr (one of my favorite if not favorite character, and a very interesting backstory with URTVs, U-DO, genetic mutation and tampering, etc etc)

- Ziggy's backstory

- Momo and the connection to Joachim Mizrahi

- The subcommittee which I felt had some parallels with those red and blue floating orb heads in Xenogears that were monitoring Fei and co, although the subcommittee's role ended up being extremely small and restricted to show only Juli Mizrahi, and I feel they made her a lot less... cold than she was in Episode 1, which weirdly enough I actually didn't like because her character seemed completely different (ironically the reverse happened with Shion, but ultimately both had a similar negative impression on me)

- Albedo, who is still one of JRPG's and general video game's best villain of all time, gruesomely psychotic and you love every minute of it, not to mention the splendid voice actor that gives it his all for the role

- Chaos and the mystery surrounding him

- Vector's president and the identities of the people in the hoods, 2 new colors (black and white) that are shown in Episode 2, and then all revealed in Episode 3.


While some of these were handled as best as they could in Episode 3 as they were rushing to conclude the trilogy, I still feel overall that they didn't explain somethings well at all, like U-DO. I don't even understand what happened there with the young Fei and Juriev who was possessing Gaignum's body and what that all about was, and I just went... huh?

Same with the gnosis phenomenon, which was the central point driving the entire series, and then we get a shorthand explanation by Wilhelm at the end saying that gnosis are "people who are happy and don't want to live in this universe anymore" and that's it? How... utterly underwhelming, this couldn't have possibly been what they intended for the gnosis to be way back in Episode 1 when Jr showed Shion and the Elsa crew the Betty half human/half gnosis and the research they were doing on the phenomenon. 

On that note, what was the deal with wanting to go back to "Lost Jerusalem" or earth as it were? Even Wilhelm addresses this point when he tells Margulis "what were you even planning on doing once you got there?"

The series ends with them trying to search for Earth, with regular space travel and no more UMN, but... why? The world these games presented to us seem to be a utopia with medicine, nanonmachines, technology, realians, no troubles anywhere, or rather lots of tools to deal with them, so what exactly is so important about going back to earth, besides an archaeological interest in humans' past history and homeland? 

I don't know, all this is actually just a summation of things that I felt were lacking in what were some interesting games that I liked, but however felt could have been **more**, you know what I mean? 


Oh and another thing, for being jrpgs and linear ones at that, I feel like they were way too short, at only 20 hours per playthrough (2 is way shorter) which is half the length of most jrpgs. When Episode 1 ended as soon as they reached Miltia, I was like... wait what? We just started this game. Any other RPG, this would have been the introduction. Other series like Tales of from Namco or Star Ocean 3 which is also set in space, were way longer and I feel that negatively impacts the story of the Xenosaga games since they could have fit the entire story in one game if they wanted to. 

Especially considering there aren't that many sidequests (with 3 boasting absolutely none besides the 2 optional bosses) so with this it seems to imply a greater focus on the story, and yet... the story itself is rather lacking. So many subplots were not covered or not explained as properly as one would think, and in my opinion considering the game's length, they shouldn't have focused on making an episodic jrpg but rather made one whole full game first, *then* looked at making sequels to it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need more reprimanding asmr or sarcastic to the viewer asmr [request] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 02:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly the same thing as something dominatrixy, although that's acceptable. 

I'm just tired of the caring friend type roleplay or when a video is overly positive, I want more reprimanding the viewer while still being tingly, or maybe 2 people in the video where one is being a grumpy gus to the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABC cancelled Better Off Ted, Happy Endings, Suburgatory... so many great shows before their time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I do love Modern Family a lot but I can't believe how many great comedies ABC has canceled. I can't believe no one watched these great shows, I know ABC gave Happy Endings and Suburgatory a fair chance, having them go on for 3 seasons, so I can't hate them for that. 

But it's just a darn shame.

OH, and then there's the short lived "Don't Trust the Bitch in Apartment 23" which I also found was kinda nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a sitcoms or such show any kind of cooking or food preparing, I always wonder if those vegetables are real or not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 14:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've got these huge gigantic carrots, large bell peppers and delicious looking purple cabbage, but it all looks a little too good, a little too shiny at times, and I wonder if it's real or fake like those plastic fruit that some people for some reason consider good decor for their home.

I dunno, just wonder about that on any tv show that has segments of the characters making a sandwich or salad or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does one even get porn videos that were filmed in the early 2000s and even have an imdb page? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 12:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.imdb.com/name/nm1283219/

Say I was interested in Ann Harlow's filmography and want to see her videos/scenes, where can I even get them? I mean... I doubt an adult video store has them. I know a lot of her scenes are on the porn tubes but I don't know which belongs to which "movie" or anything like that. 

I'm just overall curious how one would even acquire these since there's so much other porn it's doubtful there's any place for them. Even an official website for them or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still don't understand this "getting to level 50" exploit in Xenoblade on the Wii. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 10:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bxmoqMXA3Hw

Courtesy of this guy

https://www.reddit.com/r/Xenoblade_Chronicles/comments/3714cu/you_can_get_level_50_before_you_even_get_the/

His voice gets really indistinct at the most crucial moment of explaining the video, and I have no idea what he just did during the battle (or before) to be constantly getting level ups. 

Just curious. I know you don't level AP or SP so it's nearly 50 levels of wasted opportunity to get them, but still interested in trying this method out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm always thrown off when I see the Pogo episode in season 2 is actually titled Pepperwood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 07:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the alias Nick uses for the Jess and adult school writer storyline. 

The Pogo subplot is easily the better of the two, being both hilarious and providing development for the characters as well. I crack up every time they tell Nick what his pogo is, "We don't laugh about your Pogo Nick. We're worried about you."

Such a classic episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any news on new Nintendo 3ds colors? Perhaps an emerald green one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 18:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Days of Future Past is ok... but Futurama did it first. *spoilers, for both* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odette Annable... is like an attractive looking Megan Fox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When porn companies do the "behind the balls" shot, the terrorists win. They realize that right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 22:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do they keep doing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a kid did you ever wonder what Popplers tasted like/wanted to try them? (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd always drool when Bender would describe their deliciousness, and I imagine they taste not unlike shrimp, which is my favorite food of all time. 

The episode always makes me hungry, still does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For practicing Muslims, especially Arab Muslims on this forum, you ever wonder about Ramadan times in places like Alaska? Northern Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 12:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Places where the sun never sets, or sets at 11:00 pm, and rises at 2:00 am, what if one was a Muslim there?

Alternately, since the Islamic hijry calendar is a lunar calendar and is always changing, what about places where the sun never comes up or only comes up for half an hour to an hour per day? If a Muslim lives there, can it really count as fasting? 

Because Islam was born in the Arab world, which has relatively consistent hours and sun times year round, it always makes me wonder about stuff like this, especially during the Prophet days with the spreading of Islam, if they thought about how the different timezones and locations on the earth impacted things like Ramadan fasting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never know how to respond to people that ask me "isn't it unhealthy to deprive yourself of food and water for so long for an entire month?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 16:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually shrug and go oh well, but even some non muslim doctors (and/or practicing physicians) who I've met on my travels during Ramadan have said this to me before, and that it's bad for the body. 

I've never asked any Islamic scholars at the mosque or such this question, because living in the Arab World you really don't want to rock the boat, especially not all by your lonesome. 

But it still makes me wonder, if there's a passage in the Quran or one of the Prophet ahadiths that addresses this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why would mutants be treated any differently than aliens? (Series Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially since it's so pivotal to a character's origin. I love that theme in Futurama but it's also something I wonder about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently some guy "knew" Riley Reid (or whatever her real name is) years ago and had pictures to boot: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 15:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that I know a lot of creampie videos are fake where they just put a weird colored viscous liquid in the women's vagina, how can I trust anything ever again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 13:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Riley Reid did a series of creampie videos which was great (except for the fact that they were incest themed which is just pure facepalm) but it turns out they were fake, so now how I can trust any video with the tag creampie?

*ponders deep in thought* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Men 2 is still the best one. I don't know why Bryan Singer is sucking with the recent X-Mens. They should have brought back Matthew Vaughn. X-Men Franchise SPOILERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I recommend you guys watch Infinite Polar Bear, simply amazing movie with great performances. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's both heartbreaking and heartwarming of a movie, with engrossing performances by both Mark Ruffalo and Zoe Saldana, not to mention acclaim reserved for the child actors who were really good in this too, it's really an enjoyable movie to see all around, and no one saw it this summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh no no this is forever, this is what we do now. This is who we are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what exactly IS a "baby boomer santa" ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to ask that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... my utorrent keeps crashing? Is this a common problem? I don't know what happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of a sudden one day I switched on the computer and opened utorrent, and bam the program crashes with an error report. Don't know if it's something virus related or what's going on, as the rest of my computer seems fine. 

I have qbittorrent as a backup, haven't liked its layout so far. Just wondering if there's something to be concerned about regarding utorrent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which season 2 paintball episode did you like more, cowboy themed or "star wars" themed? *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered what the consensus on that was by fans. For example I much prefer the cowboy theme as I love those movies and the homages to them. Not a fan of the star wars/scifi stuff. 

Always wondered which season 2 paintball episode was people's favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've always wondered something particular about the count of Monte cristo. *SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 10:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't Edmond go through with the original plan of digging out to escape the prison? After his friend died he became heartbroken, then seemingly gave up on the original plan they concocted, then at the last second used the now iconic hiding in the bodybag to escape plan. 

Always wondered this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argo was an extremely tense movie, really good too. *safety spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Affleck really did get a second wind in the 2010s, although the amazing Gone Baby Gone was actually in 2007, but still close the second decade of the 21st century.

Movies like this really make you think though, about the problems in the world and how simple geographic locations, or customs, language and culture, can make literally the exact same species, enemies of each other. It's depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So. What if airplane seats were first come first serve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 13:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a small scene in Gone Girl that always irked me... *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Gone Girl's playing minigolf with the 2 rednecks and her pouch of money falls to the floor, I immediately thought that was supposed to be intentional, but then later it turns out it was not and it kicks off the entire change of plans in which she calls Desi and subsequently kills him, returning to Affleck. 

What I kind of find strange is, for being such an insanely meticulous, methodical person, to have her pouch of money just clumsily fall to the floor like that is... well, it just really surprised me. I could have sworn it was an intentional move considering she doesn't seem like the type to make mistakes like that. I mean hell, nearly everyone with that amount of money tied to them would be extremely careful and make sure not to have a slip-up like that, especially in front of people that could easily rob you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a shame Squaresoft never put their backing into Xenogears, both as a franchise and simply just a single game. *Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could have been a pretty damn good series had it been completed, a third pillar to complement the Final Fantasy and Dragon Quest juggernauts at the time.

Having played Xenogears, I saw a lot of good ideas and good elements for story telling that, had the game not been rushed but rather fully realized, could have made it a strong contender for a supporting pillar to the Square brand to accompany the already strong Final Fantasy series back in the day. The end of the game features the title "End of Episode 5" implying it was meant to be a whole series.

Been reading opinions around the internet, and it's got varied opinions with some liking the game and some disliking it. For my part, even after disc 2, I just find myself more fondly remembering the enjoyability of disc 1. I thought the on-foot combat system was especially fun, featuring a sort of fighter battle system like Tales/Star Ocean but actually still being turn-based.

The robot battles were fine and inoffensive, I would have been fine either way but getting an ether doubler and giving it to Elly for her aerods attack does make the robot fights much much better at 9999 damage per turn, and that's just her turn.

Though I can't imaginehad there been more episodesthat they would all feature Gears since a lot of people speculate that the different timelines and past Fei lives and incarnations were ideas for other episodes, of which Xenogears is the 5th one. So I would be fine with games that just featured on-foot combat. Either way, it deserved the full 6 episodes, or at least a fully completed game instead of what happened in Disc 2. 


Overall, it's just a shame the game wasn't as fully realized as it was, and never got the 6 or so episodes that whoever was in charge of was planning. There was so much more that could have been covered with various characters like Emeralda; I mean there's an entire sidequest for her in disc 2 that I would never have even known about without a FAQ, and it's just a shame the game just ends after so there's no point to it. Same with getting Citan's sword, which was only for his on-foot character and not gear.

I dunno, just lamenting what could have been, now that I've finally played and enjoyed the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been playing the Xenosaga trilogy, and I feel it was kinda presumptuous of Monolith to want to make 6 games when the 3 games we got were already so short. *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 10:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I absolutely love how far and improved asmr equipment has become within the last few years. [Discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 08:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in 2011 and 2012, most  asmrtists tended to have really poor sound quality and almost all of them had that static, that white noise that completely ruins the asmr experience for me because it's really distracting. 

I remember back in the days of whispercrystal and when asmr maria was first starting out, they were one of the few that had pretty good videos. But the other asmrtists had that white noise and it wasn't helpful. 

However... now as of 2016, most of those asmrtists all updated their equipment, and I just find it amazing and really appreciate how much sound quality has improved. New tinglers are incredibly lucky to experience extreme asmr tingles since the experience is both still new to them so it's more powerful, and they have amazing sound quality to enjoy as well, so you can really hear all the skk skkks and the whispers and such without interference, with a crystal clear sound. 

Just thought it was something that I personally really appreciate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, back in season 1 episode 18 Basic Genealogy, "coffee" really WAS code for sex, despite Jeff and the girl saying no. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to know the names of the first girl, 4th girl, and 5th girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gfycat.com/LonelyScratchyHarrierhawk

Anyone know the name so I can see if they do other vids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This girl being fucked, does anyone know a place for me to get ALL her videos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 11:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/WAsjV4m.jpg

I've seen a couple of her videos from public agent, czech streets, woodman casting, fucked or fired, and more, but I've been looking at her database and she has more videos and I'm just wondering, how does one even find porn videos that are not readily available on Xvideos or etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of curiosity was that Affleck's dick or was he wearing a prosthetic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 09:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of actors wear prosthetics on top of their penis or in a woman's case pubes bush. 

Was just curious if it was his actual penis in gone girl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... I've always wondered. Why did Futurama have those short animation sequences during the intro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shots of classic cartoons that we used to watch, I always wondered what the meaning behind that was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is that picture to the right of the subreddit from, out of curiosity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 11:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlie looking forlornly out the window reminds me of something but I can't recall what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're into movies, I recommend a little cult classic known as Soapdish. It's hilarious and a really likable movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never understood the average rottentomatoes score myself. Even if you're not a fan of soap opera type tv shows, or have never even seen one, you'll still appreciate how hilarious this movie is, with a lovably over the top performance by Kevin Kline, an irresistibly delightful Sally Fields, and a young RDJ that will make you feel nostalgic. 

Also includes other performances like Elizabeth Shu and smaller roles from Terry Hatcher, of Lois and Clark/Desperate Housewives fame, as well as that dude from one tree hill, the father dude, the one who's a bit of an ass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FINALLY saw The Descendants. I cried a little V__V . *SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 16:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheating makes me so mad... but like George Clooney at the end of the movie I have to learn to let go of the hate and the pain, and just forgive, and focus on the love that one can improve, like George Clooney with his 2 daughters, I love the final image of them just sitting on the couch watching morgan freeman in what I *assume* is march of the penguins. What a nice note to end the movie on, very sweet after me spending an entire movie angry and yelling at the screen "just confront the guy already goddamnit, so I can get some catharsis here!"

I can't help but feel that his decision not to sell wasn't at least **a little** motivated by him not wanting to see Brian Speer make any fucking money of his land though, at the end there. 

I can't believe this movie wanted me to hate Shaggy, couldn't they have picked another actor for me to despise?  I like Mathew Lilard : (  ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw an absolutely bizarre movie called Barton Fink. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know what to make of it. Has anyone else seen that movie? What were your thoughts on it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just watched a movie called Ordinary People. It was amazing. I cried a little. *Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 20:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... I'm really not liking season 5. Is that weird/wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I wasn't going to hold it against the show when coach left, and sure I cried and had my tears at last year's finale (christ that was a 10/10 season wasn't it)  but I was still excited at what kind of dynamic the Schmidt/Cece engagement will offer now that the will they/won't they part of *their* relationship is over (1 down, 1 to go). 

But... I dunno. Something about this season, if I'm not outright hating it, I'm bored by it. Something seems missing (this is the part where Winston would say "or someone" lol :p ) and I have to say I really don't like the fact that Megan plastic face Fox took up nearly half the season, and more so than that they kept calling her beautiful. Isn't the New Girl creator a staunch feminist or something? I thought she would ostracize women like fox with their endless plastic surgery and looking like an uncanny valley robot human. They couldn't have gotten literally any other female actress in hollywood right now? 

But I digress, it's been 17 episodes in and this season has been... weird. It has no real identity, and the things it does do, seem to fly completely in the face of previous seasons (like Winston falling for Aly? **WHAT**. What happened to "damn girl you conceited ain't nobody wanna have yo babies" and them actually being good friends instead of a stereotypical fall in love storyline?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know what's ironic? It's Always Sunny is a show about "assholes" and yet the show itself, is not mean-spirited. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not like say, a garbage cbs comedy (like literally all of them)

For example, any other show, if they were going to bring up the now infamous sixth sense and its twist, would spoil the  "twist this whole time" instantly. 

But what does Sunny do? A hilarious alteration that in turn also doesn't spoil the twist for people regardless of whether "they should have seen it by now" or not. The episode from season 5 mac and charlie write a movie. When Charlie goes "that dude in the hairpiece, that's Bruce Willis the whole movie" and then his face after he quizzically asks the gang "that wasn't the twist?" just makes me bowl over from laughter. 

I just find that to be one of the sweetest things about the show. They incorporated the joke into the character of charlie and the rest of the gang like mac telling him he'll explain it to him later and just to move past it, that's one of my favorite things about this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadpool was amazing. I enjoyed it so much. *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 12:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea if I would, but I liked it every element of it. 

Really makes you daydream about the endless possibilities with comic book movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched 2009's An Education. I adore Carey Mulligan. Safety Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we all agree that Jake calling Holt dad is the best cold open of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 13:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's simultaneously funny, cute, sweet, and provides insight into the characters all in one go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gang spies like US is such a weird episode... (spoilers?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 11:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody refers to creampies anymore unless they're talking about the sex act (if they ever did in the first place), hell I didn't even know it was actually a pastry, since most people just say pie, no need to add the cream part. 

The fact that dennis and mac make an overly elaborate plan to get Dee out of the apartment for masturbation instead of say, actually having sex with a woman and wanting some privacy, is rather bizarre knowing what we know about these characters. 

Most of the jokes kinda fall flat because of that...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of people didn't like Dr Miller from season 3 (the "female Dr Cox" boss of Turk) and considered her "an unlikable shrew" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least according to her tvtropes page. But oddly enough as I go through what must be my 10th+ rewatch of the show I find her oddly likable from how abrasive she is even though at first she was just a mouthpiece for "feminism character, grr hate women acting feminine, means weakness!" which I role my eyes at as it is in itself, sexist to assume acting "girly" (whatever that means) equals weak.

I don't know what more of a direction they could have taken with her character in the show especially since she never interacts with JD, but I am kinda interested in her abrasiveness and what it might bring to the table now that I've rewatched the show so many times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a gif of the Dean rubbing Jeff's stomach in Investigative Journalism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 17:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he offers him the chief editor of the school newspaper position. For some reason throughout all the scenes Greendale and Community has ever had, this one has stuck with me the most and is my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting an R4 to put Ace Attorney Investigations 2 fan translation on it and play on my DS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 10:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time I've ever done anything like this, and I'd like to know how? I have a laptop with the desmume application that has ace attorney investigations 2 on it, and I'd like to be able to transfer that to an R4 and play it on a DS as if it were a real ds game. 

Once I get the R4 what will be my next step? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
