<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject998</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. You think Blizzard made this game to... I dunno, feel good about themselves?
2. Money measures success because you need to pay to play. The millions that they have made indicates that many, many, many, _many_ people disagree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Mind* **fucking** ***BLOWN*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you there. A bit of empathy would go a long way towards solving a lot of social issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, even a Roadhog main admits that Roadhog is overpowered.

Oh my glob. You're telling me a person who only plays one hero thinks that hero is strong?? This is amazing! I thought all one-tricks try to main weak heroes.

/s

 He is NOT squishy, as he has the second-highest effective health in the game- that is, 900 to Winston's 1000 when ulting.

This is a highly disingenuous comparison. Winston has 1499 effective health, if he waits to 1 HP to ult. Roadhog has 900 effective health if he heals, **but his heal takes a long time, during which you can shoot the crap out of him**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you start in 3 days, there's not much you can do. If you can see some of their products online, I would suggest you check them out to get the best idea you can of what kind of stuff they do.

Don't stress. They will teach you. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  SuperData Research estimated that Overwatch brought in [...] over $565M in sales on personal computers by the end of 2016, making it the highest revenue-generating non-free-to-play game for personal computers in the year.

So what you're telling me is you know more about how to make a successful game than Blizzard does?

Wake up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying it's possible that they didn't, not that they definitely didn't. 

This is absolutely emergent gameplay. You take a simple set of rules and leave it to players to find uses for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Another intent from Bliz that the community overlooked.

I'd caution against this sort of statement. Using Mei wall to split enemies up is an example of emergent gameplay - it naturally results from experimenting with the ability. Unless of course Blizzard outright said this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not Jar-Jar. He is not the only Gungan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife is a learning designer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how this works. You have dev experience. You don't have to "step down" to the level of a student to get a job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose you also think poor people are poor because they don't really want wealth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you already have a Bachelor's, that's enough. You don't need a postgraduate-level understanding of maths or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not going to get good work without a portfolio. Will Master's help you build a portfolio?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then it's too early to decide which particular flavour of game programming you want to do. Realistically, you won't get to decide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Souls. No, it's not hard, despite what marketing hype would have you believe. But it is an antidote to the bullshit of modern games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. GMK stuff is probably not worth the money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do we have consensus on the most cost-effective system for unlocking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In ME3, I believe someone did the math and figured out that the second-cheapest crates were the most cost-effective way to unlock everything (though I could be misremembering).

Do we have any data on what the "rule" is for ME:A? My wife has been buying the 20k crates but I don't think they're worth it - I've only played a tiny bit but it feels to me like 5k crates are by far the fastest way to get the common stuff "out of the way". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lambhorn -- Cascade [prog / math / instrumental] (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting very high latency on PS4 - any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we're in South Africa. Normally for online games we use European servers - I get ~180ms on League   Overwatch that way. But ME:A seems to be courting the 300ms range, and I can see my wife getting a little frustrated.

Are there any clever tricks we can use to improve the situation? Is it possible to connect only to players below a certain latency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] ME:A Super Deluxe PS4 preorder: who gets the loot boxes if we share the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I will both be playing one copy of ME:A on our PS4. Who gets the weekly loot boxes?

* The account that owns the game?
* The first person to play the game?
* The first person to play multiplayer each week?
* All players who play the same copy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ME:A Super Deluxe PS4 preorder: who gets the loot boxes if we share the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [buying] Weird listing on Taobao - need help from a Chinese speaker/experienced buyer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://world.taobao.com/item/43429852858.htm?fromSite=main

Using Google Translate, it seems if I select "no carved key cap 5" the price comes to 10 CNY (1.45 USD).

Is that correct? What will I get if I order this - a 6x8 with blanks?

What's the catch? Can it ship to South Africa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any ideas for a carrying solution for my office RFID tag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a little passive RFID tag that unlocks the front door at the office. (I'll describe it as I don't want an image link to be interpreted as breaking rule 1 lol.) It's rectangular, about 2cm by 4.5cm, maybe 5mm at its thickest. It has a small oval hole (maybe 2mm by 3mm) on the one end.

I despise carrying small things like this loose in my pockets (I already dislike carrying small change), and I don't want to stick the tag in my backpack because I need it to be easily accessible.

My current EDC is just my phone, apartment keys (disgusting big thing with an ugly-ass gate remote, but what can you do), and a quickdraw-style wallet. The tag is too thick to go in the wallet. I don't want to tie the tag to the keys because I have a separate system for carrying my keys.

What clever solutions can you come up with for carrying this thing around?

My best idea so far is to put a loop of string or whatever through it, and tuck the string into the wallet so it sort of hangs off the wallet. V informal though. My wallet isn't the kind with a band, so I can't tie it to there.

I could do something lame like carry it on a carabiner on a belt loop, but I am not a late 80s dad.

EDIT: Unintentional German

EDIT: I suppose my issues can be summarised as: it's a small, loose item in my pocket, which makes it hard to locate and easy to lose; it also increases the number of items I have to remember to shove in my pockets by 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When, if ever, is it worth it to sacrifice yourself to get a single kill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On occasion, I have made plays that result in getting a kill at the cost of my life (any Rein who has ever charged off the edge of the map knows). 

I've been wondering about this: under what circumstances can I consider my team to have the advantage when this happens? 

To be clear, this is not a play-making question, but rather a shotcalling one: when should I tell my team to press forward after a one-for-one trade? 

Example: KOTH, and the enemy team holds the point. I Rein charge off the map and take their Rein with me. Perhaps my team can now push onto the point given that the enemy team is clustered with no barrier?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the cutoff date for Andromeda preorders on PS4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never preordered before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Convince me to use Clojure over Elixir. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a client-server project that I want to write in a functional style (as a learning exercise, and because I think functional is the future). It will require high concurrency and reliability.

In short, Clojure and Elixir both fit the brief.

I have never worked with either language. I've read part of Clojure for the Brave and True and experimented lightly in the REPL; my Elixir experience is similar. I have some Java experience but no Erlang experience.

Here are some reasons I would choose Elixir:

* Ruby-like syntax is more familiar to me, having never used a Lisp before.
* Pattern matching seems like an incredibly powerful construct.
* BEAM's fault tolerance ("let it crash") is second to none.
* The Actor model seems very easy to grok, from my limited contact with it. I like that there is a canon model for concurrency.
* Concurrency is essentially free.
* Elixir only infrequently lets the Erlang layer poke through.

Convince me that Clojure is a better fit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What rate of SR gained per hour represents real improvement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently climbing roughly 100-150 SR (currently at 1497) per roughly 6 hours of competitive. Am I climbing because I'm genuinely better than my SR, or is it just normal growth due to incremental improvement?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is an interesting concept from your field of expertise? Name   describe it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [news] PSA: If you signed up for the second Shortcut.gg questionnaire, it should be in your mailbox now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 09:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all

PS numpads are evil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RMA shipping from South Africa to Denmark is impractical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have ZAR 6000 (approximately USD 420) in a savings account and the Ergodox EZ exists. Talk me down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 420 blaze it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dividing by zero is literally a high voltage desiring oneness with the universe (or something, idk) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Currently dual-boot Win10   Ubuntu. Want to replace Ubuntu with Elementary. pls halp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old-ass PC (2nd-gen i5 desktop machine) is currently running Win10   Ubuntu. I set this up quite some time ago so I can't quite remember everything I had to do to get it going.

I have however realised I don't really like Ubuntu and would like to try out some other distros.

How can I replace Ubuntu in-place without repartitioning drives etc, and without breaking grub, and with minimal risk of bricking my PC?

If it matters, some distros I am considering include Elementary, Mint, and anything /r/unixporn thinks is cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it good that Rails, Node, etc rely on libraries hosted off-site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 15:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Rails, for example, we manage dependencies in a Gemfile which will at build time retrieve all the various libs from wherever they are hosted.

Why is this a good thing? Why do we not like checking our libraries into version control?

Arguments for:

* We can allow the system to pull the most recent version (or e.g. the most recent minor version), thereby ensuring availability of bugfixes.

Arguments against:

* npmgate. If the library ever gets taken offline, our application will break at build time.
* We can't easily tweak the library locally. (Ruby for example solves this by making monkey patching a thing, though it's still hard to inspect the library source.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Giveaway] TIS-100 (Steam/PC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I already own this game and got a dupe key from the latest Humble Bundle, I'm giving it away.

TIS-100 is perhaps better described as "Literally Assembler Programming: The Game". If the thought of poring over a shitty PDF scan of a printed manual in order to decipher instructions for an obscure computer gets your juices going, this might be the game for you!

While this game is fun in its own right, I'd prefer to give this to someone who can benefit from it on a deeper level. To that end, **enter by telling me why you want to learn to program**. Or if you are already a programmer, tell me a hilarious story of a bug you had to fix or something.

I'll leave this giveaway up for 24 hours or so.

**EDIT:** Received another key to give away, courtesy of /u/mehmenmike.

**EDIT 2: EDIT HARDER** Since I'm lazy, the comp will stay open until tonight (~6 hrs).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Struggling to put words to one of my favourite game design tropes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a feature (or mechanic or trope) that appears in many of my favourite games. It is something so powerful to me that I want to find the words to discuss, interrogate, and analyse it, but I'm drawing a complete blank.

Games which feature this trope:

* Soulsborne games
* Hoplite (Android puzzle roguelite)
* Hyper Light Drifter
* League of Legends

The basic idea is that your character only has access to a limited set of tools or moves at any point (the sweet spot seems to be 3-8). Each of these tools has a simple set of rules that defines it. Crucially, those tools can be combined in incredibly expressive ways.

Think of all the ridiculous combos Lee Sin can pull off in League with only his Q, W, R, and a trinket. Or all the clever attacks you can mount in Dark Souls with a sword and a shield.

Is there even a name for this? Am I being stupid? Is what I'm talking about just "good design"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I nicked my trackball  wat do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the world leave trackballs behind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.

They have the precision   speed/"dynamic range" of a mouse (because you're moving a massive object), but they can scroll infinitely in either direction. The lift-and-replace gesture is much faster than with a mouse because you're moving your finger(s) ~2 cm instead of moving your whole arm and the mouse ~20 cm. They are not limited by the size of your desk. They play well with acceleration and multiple monitors. And they're so comfortable to use.

Did we all just collectively go insane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First impressions after ~2 hours of using a trackball for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 09:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyoo

Before I left work for a week to go get married (woohoo), I ordered a Logitech Trackman Marble as I found a local seller selling them for dirt cheap. This morning I was able to plug it in for the first time and do a little work.

Thoughts so far:

* The ball doesn't move as smoothly as I'd hoped. I suppose what I imagined was a very heavy ball with loads of inertia, that could spin for several seconds if given the initial push. In practice it does have inertia but it comes to a stop quite quickly. I imagine that high-end trackballs like the CSTs behave more like I expect.
* It's incredibly comfortable. The weird alien shape is just so nice to rest my hand on.
* My wrist feels so much better. It's early still, but I suspect this will remain true.
* The big side buttons are really comfy to use. The little ones not so much, but they're not exactly horrid. I found the side buttons on my Sensei Raw to be similarly lame at first, and I got used to them just fine.
* macOS doesn't recognise the back/forward button functionality out of the box.
* The lack of scrolling was a problem. My solution (which I'm very happy with) was to install Logitech Control Center to bind the left small button to middle mouse click, and then use Smart Scroll to interpret the middle mouse click as a scroll action. At first I tried the vector scroll mode (as seen in Firefox), figuring it would be nice to hit the button and then release it until I'm ready to stop scrolling; however, I soon realised I scroll quite a lot, so I changed to grab scroll mode, where you hold down the middle mouse button in order to scroll. Smart Scroll is set to completely consume the middle mouse click - otherwise various apps interpret it as a click still, which is super annoying. Scrolling in this fashion is very, very nice! I kind of wish I had a trackball in my audio days... (EDIT: https://github.com/Seelge/TrackballScroll is a nice alternative for Windows.)
* Small movements are tricky. It takes quite a bit of force to get the ball to start moving from rest.
* The Logitech Control Center software is great for setting the sensitivity - I could leave my OS-level mouse sensitivity where it was, and just use the LCC multiplier to get the trackball sensitivity up to a decent point. My system mouse sensitivity is about 40% of maximum, and LCC is set to a 3x multiplier. Works pretty okay so far.
* I'm wondering whether I need more acceleration. Hard to tell.

Verdict: fuckin stoked I dropped R200 on this bad boi

UPDATE: I've dropped the sensitivity modifier to 2x and it feels way better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspiciously low price... anyone see anything wrong with this listing? (R135 == $9.74, but when you factor in import costs it works out to more like $4.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 10:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there such a thing as a "trackball simulator" (for macOS)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 14:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the trackpads on Macs as of a couple years ago have inertial scrolling: if you start scrolling and release the trackpad during the movement, the page keeps scrolling as if the input device has inertia.

I'm looking for a utility that will allow me to get this behaviour on normal mouse movement as well. As seen here, Windows can achieve this: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UQE3GWSZvKU

Anyone know of such a utility? I post this here because basically what I want is a "trackball simulator" for my trackpad. This is partially an attempt to discover whether trackball-style movement suits me, before dropping the cash on one (I live in South Africa - gadgets are pricier here).

From what I understand, the Steam Controller has such a mode for its trackpad(s) and it's explicitly called a "trackball mode" in the settings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [keyboard_spotting] SSG CuVee with what looks like an 1800-style board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [news] KBParadise announcing "Black Queen" 60% with Cherry Speed   Silent options! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 12:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a non-chiclet keyboard with customisable display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 09:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My co-worker is a pretty big fan of the Logitech G510 and its customisable display. He's looking for a new keyboard at home (RIP old keyboard), and I was wondering what other keyboards on the market have such displays? No chiclet-style keys please - long travel, whether it's rubber dome or mechanical.

I know of the Infinity Ergodox, but that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Combining two unfunny things predictably has an even less funny result </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Music] [IIL] Linkin Park, Evanescence, [WEWIL?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 12:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of an odd request. I really like stuff like Deftones, Tool, etc - the "thinking man's alt metal". But I don't always want really clever, twisting, unique riffs. Sometimes I want the saccharine radio-metal riffs of Linkin Park or Evanescence. I'm also quite partial to the somewhat industrial flavour these bands have.

1. What music would I like that has those kinds of straightforward, fun riffs?
2. As above, but with the added clause that my hipster friends won't disown me completely.

Thanks kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [help] How do I fix this broken switch? KBP V60 Matias </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 09:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My KBP V60's X keyswitch broke. The taller of the two electrical contacts snapped off near the top. 

I've managed to open up the keyboard to the point of removing the plate-PCB assembly from the case. 

I assumed initially that I'd be able to desolder only the broken switch and pop it out of the top of the plate. However, it seems now that the switch housing locks into the plate from both directions - a set of flanges hold it in place from the bottom, and then a latch holds it in place from the top. 

This makes me believe that the only way to remove the whole switch is to desolder EVERY switch. Is this correct? 

If so, I'm a little worried about attempting this. My soldering skills are not the best, and I'm worried that desoldering 60-odd switches runs a big risk of damaging the circuit somewhere (damaging traces, burning out the controller, etc).

I did have another idea: it seems like the switch contacts just poke through the bottom of the switch housing to become the switch pins. Could I desolder only the broken contact's pin, pull the contact out through the top of the plate, and then open up a spare switch, steal its contact, and solder it into the switch from the top?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mapt - online learning platform for developers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm the worst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 11:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explain a nuance about your favourite champion that players are often unaware of. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll start:

Most people know that Karma's R-W is a self heal. What they may not know is that it is a % missing HP heal. This means it heals drastically more when Karma is low on health. If you are duelling a Karma and you realise she's holding on to her ult and W, she's trying to bait you - she will heal at the last possible second, getting back ~40% of her max HP. (Do you have vision of her jungler...?) This ability is a big part of what makes tank Karma so goddamn tanky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Taihao Sunshine owners who use Swiftkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 13:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roccat Sova couch keyboard (75%) with integrated mousepad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is an interesting term or concept from your field of expertise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 19:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is an interesting term or concept from your field of expertise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2003 VW Polo vibrating at idle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 09:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 2003 VW Polo (manual) started acting up on Tuesday morning. I'd gotten a flat tyre over the weekend, so on Monday morning I had it fixed and put back on.

On Tuesday morning, when I started my car, I felt it vibrating. This is not a high-frequency vibration like you expect - this is low frequency, more like *shaking*.

I find I have to rev the car more than usual for a given gear, else it feels like the engine is about to cut out. Acceleration is also much poorer than it normally is.

If I rev up a lot, the vibration gets a little less noticeable. (EDIT: Vibration persists during driving if revs are low.)

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for recommendations for a non-MOBA F2P competitive PC game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't really play League any more due to my living situation, so I'm looking for something to plug the gap.

Requirements:

* It can't control like League/Diablo. In other words, no spamming right click every few milliseconds. This probably means WASD + mouse.
* My machine is a bit of a potato. Can play Mass Effect 3 on full settings and get 60 fps.
* I want an official, in-client ranked ladder to climb.

Preferences:

* I don't have the basic skillset for FPS games, nor do I care much for games that are won by mechanics. I prefer decision-making (hence why I love League).
* I love games that look beautiful. I can appreciate different aesthetics though.
* I LOVE LOVE LOVE games that have a huge roster of colourful characters. (So that I can main the weird one no-one likes.)

Things I've sort of looked at:

* Smite is probably good but the game is so ugly. :(
* TF2 doesn't really grab me with its limited scope for customising your loadout/character. I did kind of enjoy the Overwatch open beta though so maybe?
* Paragon looks fucking baller but I doubt I can run it. (Radeon HD 6570 is much lower in terms of 3D Mark than the lowest graphics card they currently support.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [news] KBParadise announcing new full-sized board V100K2 w/ double shot TaiHao ABS/PBT (Miami!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is Karma going to handle the MYMU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in top lane tank Karma in particular. It's my current freelo build/role, but I worry that the added CDR on Abyssal is going to break my normal build of RoA, FH, SV, Lucidity. It's going to be especially hard to get enough MR *and* enough CDR vs teams that have significant damage in both AD and AP... Not to mention that many of those items are getting nerfed. 

Anyway, thoughts? Feel free to discuss other lanes and builds as well. 

EDIT: One idea that could probably work is to go SV into Lucidity for 20% CDR, then grab a different HP+AP item in lieu of RoA (e.g. Liandry's), and then get FH/IBG for the CDR cap... Or something. Mana might struggle. 

EDIT 2: New RoA into SV is broken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are trackballs better than trackpads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 00:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of articles ascribe benefits to trackballs that actually also apply to trackpads. What actually sets a trackball apart from a trackpad? 

I'm toying with the thought of getting a trackball for work (and possibly home?) to get closer to ergonomic nirvana, now that I have my beloved 60% keyboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a ~60cm wide soft mouse mat with stitched edges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a Sensei RAW and a KBP V60. I'd like a mouse mat that will work well with my mouse (low DPI, mostly League and Warframe) and that can quiet my keyboard a little (I have very quiet keyswitches but I do tend to bottom out on e.g. Spacebar and that impact transferred into my desk causes more noise than I'd like).

I want something I can roll up (as I will carry it to work as well), and I want something with stitched edges (my QCK Mini is already plenty frayed after ~18 months). I don't want something wider than 70cm or narrower than, say, 55cm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I use literally any Omron D2F-series switch as a drop-in replacement for my Sensei RAW Arctic White? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. I live in South Africa and the local RS Electronics doesn't have the D2FC-F-7N(10M) that the Sensei ships with, but they do have D2F-01F-T which I believe is the same, but sorted in Japan or something? Anyway, electrically speaking, are they functionally identical?

Context: I'm planning to mod my mouse for a softer clicking sound (so as not to drive my fiancee up the walls of our small apartment), and I'd like to have a backup and/or practice switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Search term too long </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 09:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [photos] Artsy Matias </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 15:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dystopian sci-fi with designer drug and people believing they see God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 14:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for the title of a science fiction slash dystopian book I saw in a bookstore in South Africa within the years 2010-2013. It was a new release at the time, and possibly the debut novel by its author.

The cover was pink and grey. The blurb described a situation very similar to that of Nine Inch Nails's Year Zero concept album: surveillance state, new designer drug taking the world by storm, people across the globe having weird, possibly religious visions (possibly including hearing the Voice of God).

I looked up the author at the time. There was very little info on him, but I did find his LinkedIn page, which stated that his previous writing work was predominantly in video games (not extremely popular ones though). Pretty sure the author was English, though I suppose he could be American or Canadian. I think his first name is some variation on Christopher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [photos] I have finally ascended. KBParadise V60 Matias Quiet Click </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 09:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Furi | Gameplay trailer | PS4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 08:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooler Master is #hip with the #memes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 17:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ANC (Nelson Mandela's old political party) is really #hip with the #youth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 09:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ANC (Nelson Mandela's old political party) is really #hip with the #youth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 08:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP.GG's logo for the day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 09:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shop bug: Poppy shows under "assassins" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 08:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poppy is no longer an assassin, but if you visit the champion shop and select "assassins" under the dropdown, she shows up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The defeners are winning: old music is outselling new music for the first time in history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 15:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An acquaintance wishes to pursue a career relating to the environment, but is not academically strong enough for law/science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 14:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend told me about a service worker at her office who has a daughter who is trying to figure out what to study. We are talking about a low-income South African family here - the girl has had a poor school education, and they probably don't have a lot of cash to send her to whatever university.

The girl is passionate about the environment. The fields that immediately jump out at me are science and law, but both of those fields require a strong academic background to even get in, never mind pass.

What other career options exist for someone who wishes to work in environmental fields? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First-time phalaenopsis owner, really confused about liquid orchid food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we grabbed an orchid from Woolworths today, along with this: http://www.woolworths.co.za/store/prod/Food/Flowers-Plants/Accessories-Bulbs-Seeds/Orchid-Concentrate-Plant-Food-250ml/_/A-6001009959034

The orchid came with a tag recommending you water it by placing a few ice cubes at the base of the plant (1x/wk in summer, 1x/2wk in winter). It also said to "feed" every two weeks.

The orchid food bottle says to dilute it 5ml to 1l of water, and to feed every two weeks.

So you can see how this is confusing. One thing says "give it like no water at all", the other says "oh it's fine just submerge the whole goddamn thing".

What am I supposed to do here?

On a related note: every article about "beginner orchid care" etc (including the one linked in the sidebar) fails to explain how to feed the plant, so some advice here is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am away from my PC all weekend. FML </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In-depth mastery discussion w.r.t. Varus ADC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 14:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking over the mastery trees and trying to decide on a good setup for Varus. One of the things that's jumping out at me about masteries in their current state is that so many of them are just point dumps; no matter which champion I play, I find about half of the masteries are only there because I need them to reach a higher tier.

So I want to take an objective look at each and every mastery and see if we can decide on which ones actually *matter*, so I can decide which tiers in which trees are worth keeping.

# Ferocity

## Tier 1

* Fury: great
* Sorcery(?): average (though better than for most ADCs, given Varus's high ability damage)

## Tier 2

* Double Edged Sword: bad (in my opinion - ADCs are squishy enough without you debuffing yourself)
* Feast: good (boost for laning)

## Tier 3

* Vampirism: excellent (free sustain! What's not to love?)
* Natural Talent: garbage (less than 1 AD   AP per level? Seriously? If this gave a tangible quantity, it could be good on Varus given W   R)

## Tier 4

* Bounty Hunter: average (good damage, but risky)
* Oppressor: great (most supports bring CC, and Varus has his E   R)

## Tier 5

* Battering Blows: great
* Piercing Thoughts: garbage

## Tier 6

* Warlord's Bloodlust: bad (given how much of Varus's damage is loaded into his spells)
* Fervor of Battle: average/good/great (haven't tested the changes yet. With Q and E, Varus can build fast stacks, but because much of his damage is in his spells, the benefits aren't huge)
* Deathfire Touch: bad (zero synergy)

# Cunning

## Tier 1

* Wanderer: garbage
* Savagery: great (easier last hitting)

## Tier 2

* Runic Affinity: average (no guarantee that you can routinely secure buffs)
* Secret Stash: good (requires you to buy pots, which have become expensive)

## Tier 3

* Merciless: great (general damage buff, good for cleanup)
* Meditation: average/good (Varus is mana-hungry, after all)

## Tier 4

* Bandit: bad (get less than half of the benefit due to being ranged   farming)
* Dangerous Game: great

## Tier 5

* Precision: great
* Intelligence: great

## Tier 6

* Stormraider's Surge: average/good/great (**if** you can trigger it, the MS is a huge boon to kiting)
* Thunderlord's Decree: excellent (suits Varus's trading pattern)
* Windspeaker's Blessing: garbage

# Resolve

## Tier 1

* Recovery: average/good (free sustain!)
* Unyielding: garbage

## Tier 2

* Explorer: garbage
* Tough Skin: good/great (Varus likes to trade)

## Tier 3

* Runic Armor: great (benefits not only lifesteal/vamp which Varus will build, but any shields   heals from supports, including Relic proc)
* Veteran's Scars: good

## Tier 4

* Insight: good (having Flash and Heal/Ghost more frequently is a huge boon for an aggressive Varus)
* Perseverance: good (free sustain!)

## Tier 5

* Swiftness: good (kite like a god)
* Legendary Guardian: good (flat armour/MR means a lot when you have almost none)

## Tier 6

* Grasp of the Undying: garbage (due to low health pool   being ranged)
* Strength of the Ages: bad
* Bond of Stone: hahahaha

That's my thoughts. Now hit me with your opinions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 2012 was the best generation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 09:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alter a movie title so it's about a League champ. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 13:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll start:

#There Will Be Tentacles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Helicopter - Deerhunter (Sakawa Boys) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 09:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> League's newest champ is a big lady bruiser and she looks sick af </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For what price should I sell an antique guitar in need of restoration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 13:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a ~1952 Gibson L-48 with a P90 sitting untouched at my parents' house. It's in bad shape: it spent most of the last five decades sitting in a closet in the Kalahari desert. The finish is cracked and worn, the frets are all worn down, the tuner knobs are crumbling, metal is rusty, etc.

I'm in desperate need of cash, so I want to sell this on to someone who can actually (1) restore it and (2) play it.

What I'm not sure about is how much to ask for it. I see these guitars go for around $3k restored, so what's a fair percentage of that to ask for unrestored? I'm sure the restoration would be expensive so I want to arrive at a price that's fair to both myself and the buyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you want Black Mirror? Because this is how you get Black Mirror. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 08:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All about desian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 15:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What, in concrete terms, is "tempo"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 12:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I followed most of Worlds, watched perhaps half of the games, as well as the EU Summer Split before it. A buzzword I've heard the casters (Krepo, among others) use a lot lately is "tempo".

Now, I can sort of guess for myself what it means generally, but they keep using it in such seemingly specific situations that I think there's a nuance I'm missing.

So: what exactly is "tempo", and how do we manipulate it to serve us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurt Elling -- The Waking [jazz] (2007) vocal + bass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 08:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refreshing stats doesn't work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 14:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm subject998 on EUW. I'm trying to refresh my stats to show some recent Jinx games I played, but it constantly times out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Intro] Well hello there! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 13:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Henr. I'm at work. I'm a software engineer. I'm a gamer. I'm no longer a musician. I'm South African. I'm 27.

How's everybody doing today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Dressing/grooming "for yourself" is a nonsensical and impossible concept. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 09:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a fairly common statement I've seen made around these parts:

 I dress/groom myself for myself.

People (usually heterosexual women) who say this mean that they do not dress up, paint their nails, etc for the benefit of potential partners, but do so simply to feel good about their bodies.

I hold that this is an impossible statement. (I will use "clothing" from here on out, but all of this applies just as much to grooming, makeup, etc.) Clothing is inherently social. Fashion is subject to the whims of people. I think we can agree that trends are not just about utility - we often revisit clothing from eras gone by, implying that our clothes don't get objectively better with passage of time. If I dressed simply "for myself", I would find the clothes I like the most, and the chances of my tastes constantly aligning with changing trends would be fairly small - after all, I'm not concerned with how others view me, and clothing is not about utility, so it's not like I would be "using dated tech" if I didn't keep up with trends.

These people who claim to dress "for themselves" usually dress just like people who do so in order to please potential partners, which further undermines the idea to me that this is a thing that exists in a vacuum.

I can see no other way than that, fundamentally, dressing up *is* for the benefit of others. Even if it's not directly intended for actual men to see (e.g. a few women having a dinner party), there is the implicit male gaze factor: I'm dressing up to communicate to you, and by extension people (men) you will have contact with later, what sort of person I am (including describing my sexual availability).

I understand this is a fundamentally feminist concept, and I have no beef with that (I consider myself a feminist in training). I also understand that I'm probably missing a lot of detail. I want to better understand how this principle can be supported by logic. Please, CMV.

EDIT: Should have made this more clear:

 I'm talking about people who "dress up" (i.e. dress in a way that attempts to look as good as possible), and who don't simply dress in a utilitarian fashion (i.e. wear pants so you don't get cold).

EDIT 2: Thanks for the great discussion, everybody. /u/riggorous did a great job of explaining some key points [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/comments/3ntac6/cmv_dressinggrooming_for_yourself_is_a/cvr548m), if you want to read it.

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real classy recruitment "joke" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][book] Dystopian sci-fi with designer drug and people believing they see God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 14:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for the title of a science fiction slash dystopian book I saw in a bookstore in South Africa within the years 2010-2013. It was a new release at the time, and possibly the debut novel by its author.

The cover was pink and grey. The blurb described a situation very similar to that of Nine Inch Nails's Year Zero concept album: surveillance state, new designer drug taking the world by storm, people across the globe having weird, possibly religious visions (possibly including hearing the Voice of God).

I looked up the author at the time. There was very little info on him, but I did find his LinkedIn page, which stated that his previous writing work was predominantly in video games (not extremely popular ones though). Pretty sure the author was English, though I suppose he could be American or Canadian. I think his first name is some variation on Christopher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is AP Teemo better than AP Varus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 22:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm playing around with AP Varus. I'm somewhat aware of his problems (pulling off the 3x AA - Q/E combo requires that he gets in close range, where he's very vulnerable), but I want to acquire a deeper understanding. 

Why does Teemo, as an AP-based autoattacker, succeed where Varus fails? 

Similarly, why is Varus's need to get in close considered such a huge weakness, when that is the case for virtually every ADC?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I learn Sublime's Vi mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 12:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick background on me:

* Started working as a developer a little over a year ago. 
* Working for a startup with only one other developer (the CTO). 
* Our product is a Rails app, so that encompasses Rails, Javascript, Sass, Haml. We're moving to Ember soon. I have to work on all of the above. 

I'm starting to get a better handle on the terminal. I enjoy using stuff like `grep` and the like. 

The CTO uses Sublime. He's a very "get shit done" kind of guy - I don't think he'd ever have the patience to learn something arcane like Vim. 

I'm a huge Sublime fan. I think it's a perfect mix of familiarity (its basic feature set mirrors your typical text editor, be it Notepad or a text field in a browser), capability (syntax highlighting, regex search), and extensibility (God I love plugins). It's also visually attractive - the fact that it's not limited to using monospace characters for the GUI means it's capable of more than Vim, graphically speaking. 

My terminal explorations have given me a Vim itch. However, I've done a lot of reading this weekend, and it's done nothing but convinced me that Vim *as a platform* is a horrible idea. 

What I'm not convinced about is the merits of Vim-style modal editing. I could see there being some point to it. (After all, in other aspects of computer use I pursue ergonomics and efficiency.)

So I'm wondering: should I try to learn vintage mode? Is it likely to be beneficial? I like the idea of being able to gradually transition instead of having to switch between apps when I get tired. It's also nice to know another person could use my setup without being completely lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DE: The biggest thing putting me off Warframe... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 16:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I enable auto-attack in the game options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 13:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never played with the auto-attack option on. However, recently, I've been thinking it might be good to keep it on for certain scenarios:

* Immediately attacking wards when they're dropped next to me.
* At least sort of fighting back if I get caught while I'm looking at the other side of the map.
* At least sort of trying to CS if there are minions near me and I'm not paying attention.

Of course, the drawback here is that I could attack when I don't mean to, including:

* When under an enemy turret.
* When hiding in a bush and waiting for an opportune moment.

So, convince me /r/summonerschool! Do any of you play with auto-attack enabled? Are there any pros/cons I didn't think of? Should I try it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humble gentlesir pays exorbitant rent for 100-year-old apartment, mounts fedora   sword on wall to make the space work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 16:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the optimal strategy for sweepstakes where inviting friends gives you more entries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Effective system for keeping track of DB migrations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 13:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this past week or two I've been having some headaches with respect to git branches and DB versions.

The short version:

* I started work on a feature branch that requires DB migrations.
* I keep having to switch between the feature branch and master in order to do hotfixes.
* My feature branch is somewhat behind master wrt DB migrations - there are one or two migrations on master that don't yet exist on my feature branch.

I know many might simply say "just merge master into feature", but that doesn't really work for my workflow - I'll merge it when I'm good and ready, haha.

What I'm looking for is a way to easily keep tabs of what version my DB is at on different branches.

I started using `tmux` yesterday (thanks to a post on reddit), which I'm finding quite enjoyable. I'm wondering if there isn't some sort of terminal-based script I could run in a `tmux` panel that could, for instance, show me the tail of `rake db:migrate:status` for various branches or something?

I don't mind having to do a little work to set this up either, I just don't really know how to go about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Spoiler tags aren't always enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 14:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In reference to this post: https://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/3hail2/spoiler_my_god_am_i_hyped_for_next_sunday/

Between the title and the flair, it's patently obvious which team won that game.

What could be done about this? Disable flairs on spoiler-tagged posts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's 3:40 PM on a Friday and I am trying to unfuck my dev DB. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 15:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I dream of a day when Ardent Censer is good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 16:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone managed to find any success with Ardent Censer on Karma?

My recent build (which is sitting on a 70% winrate in ranked, potato Elo) looks like this:

* 9/0/21
* AP quints, scaling AP glyphs, HP seals, Mpen marks
* Spellthief  Sightstone  Morellonomicon   Boots  Zeke's  Sorceror's Shoes   Liandry's  ~~Spellthief~~ Deathcap

Then I started looking to see if I could get Ardent Censer to fit in there. The obvious candidate for replacement is Morellonomicon, for a few reasons:

* Both give mana, and +200% mana regen would be overkill
* Ardent Censer's on-hit damage is stronger in the early game

But the biggest problem with this is it would leave me at 30% CDR, which simply will not do. So I reconfigured, and tried out this build for a couple of games:

* 9/0/21, with AS in the offense tree instead of CDR
* AP quints, scaling AP glyphs, HP seals, Mpen marks
* Spellthief  Sightstone  Ardent Censer   Boots  Zeke's  Lucidity   Liandry's  ~~Spellthief~~ Deathcap

This effectively means I'm trading 15 Mpen, 40 AP, and Grievous Wounds for a small amount of AS, 200 gold, MS, and the Censer passive. I figured it would work pretty well.

It really doesn't, though. I've played it in five games and won two. IIRC, the first one had the enemy Lucian AFK after Pickaxe, so it hardly counts, and in another we got carried pretty hard by Riven and Yi.

I feel like, with the latter loadout, my harass simply isn't anywhere close to as strong as it usually is. Qs feel like they do nothing. Es feel like they absorb nothing. My entire laning phase feels less impactful - which is *bizarre*, because with Ardent Censer coming in 200 gold sooner, my ADC should be making up for my lower contribution with the Censer passive.

I also don't want to go the utility route. The item would work well enough if I went Locket etc (I think, anyway), but that's not what I'm about - I want to be an AP support.

Anyone have any advice? Did I just have bad luck in those games I lost? What can I do to this build to fix the issues while maintaining the spirit of the build? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> subject998's IGS Rep Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you feel about Ardent Censer getting +10% CDR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 10:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Ardent Censer right now is in an awkward place. It's not a bad item, but it's a little hard to fit into a build due to an awkward combination of stats.

The item grants the same level of mana regenaration as Morellonomicon or Athene's (ignoring the unique passives on the latter), two items which AP supports build fairly often. If Ardent Censer offered 20% CDR, it would also have the same CDR as those two items. This would mean you could choose Morellonomicon, Athene's, or Ardent Censer based solely on the AP and utility each item offers.

**Morellonomicon** would be the best choice for raw AP, good for Lulus or Sorakas who want to maximise damage, shields, or healing.

**Athene's** would offer more mana, which would aid supports with extreme mana costs (Lux?), as well as offering some MR versus heavy magic damage comps.

**Ardent Censer** would offer the least AP, while giving a strong passive for the early game - great for Karmas and Sorakas supporting ADCs like Lucian or Sivir.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the actual differences between HP and armour/MR runes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of discussion around runes that relies on subjective, anecdotal "evidence", my favourite example being "[rune type] is just better". 

What are the **provable** differences between taking HP seals and taking armour/MR seals/glyphs?

Here are some of my thoughts. 

* If you have a shield that scales with HP, HP might be better. If you have a shield that doesn't scale with HP, resistances are better. If you have a shield that scales with AP, HP seals + AP glyphs might be better than resistances. 
* If you have healing (of any kind - lifesteal etc) that is not a percentage of max HP, resistances multiply its value, whereas HP does not. 
* There's an optimal curve of HP vs resistances, and it would be wise to pick runes that approach that curve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How has the existence of the null pointer caused "a billion dollars of pain and damage"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 12:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I call it my billion-dollar mistake. It was the invention of the null reference in 1965. At that time, I was designing the first comprehensive type system for references in an object oriented language (ALGOL W). My goal was to ensure that all use of references should be absolutely safe, with checking performed automatically by the compiler. But I couldn't resist the temptation to put in a null reference, simply because it was so easy to implement. This has led to innumerable errors, vulnerabilities, and system crashes, which have probably caused a billion dollars of pain and damage in the last forty years.

- [C. A. R. Hoare](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Null_pointer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some advice on how to make the most of a small space (pics inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I are moving around November into [this flat](http://imgur.com/tK4HY1y) or something very similar (renders   photo from Gumtree). We're trying to figure out how we can make the most of such a small space. [render 1](http://imgur.com/FB9YMM4) | [render 2](http://imgur.com/cv8HOA8) | [render 3](http://imgur.com/WfzmPTR)

The biggest question for us: **how can we have an entertainment area as well as a second workspace**? She uses a laptop but strongly prefers sitting at a desk for the most part. I use a Mac Mini (for now, anyway) so I can't really work on a couch. We have a 32" HD TV which I feel is a strong candidate for dual use as a TV and a computer monitor, but I'm not clear on how to mount it so that it can serve both purposes. The renders I attached will show there's very little space between the kitchen wall and the opposite wall; even so, I was thinking to put a couch (about 1.6m by 0.8m) with its back to the kitchen counter, and mount the TV on the wall.

But that doesn't leave a whole lot of space between the couch and the TV, which is a problem because **we have a lot of stuff** (particularly clothes   books). Another question I have is how we can effectively **separate the "bedroom" from the "lounge"**. I think we'd both struggle to live in a space where you're constantly "in the same space", as opposed to having different areas dedicated to different purposes and delineated from each other. We figured we could kill two birds with one stone here and place a bookshelf in between the bed and the lounge area - is this a good idea?

Finally, any good tips on **how to keep neat** in general are highly appreciated.

First post in this sub - I tried to follow the rules in the sidebar.

EDIT: Added more pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> really dumb question forgive me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 14:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the original game, the activated items that counted towards Guppy did not need to be carried, only picked up once and then dropped. Is this still the case in Rebirth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BSOD: IRQL_NOT_LESS_OR_EQUAL and DRIVER_CORRUPTED_EXPOOL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 21:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks. I'm getting some annoying BSODs. At first I thought this was League of Legends's fault, but earlier today I experienced a BSOD without the game running in any form so there's that theory out the window.

[System info](http://gyazo.com/7036e87ec40ca7a7d8e0ec507fb78552)

(As I type this, DxDiag is giving me a worrying message about not being able to access the system data before?)

I tried enabling Driver Verifier, but it just sent my PC into a reboot loop. However, unlike other cases that I read about online, it didn't actually BSOD before rebooting - it would just silently fail a couple of frames into the Windows "spinny stuff" startup animation. I've included an ntbtlog.txt that was generated while Driver Verifier was activated.

[DxDiag   ntbtlog.txt](https://gist.github.com/subject998/3d9aeb34531915eb2e40)

[BlueScreenView](http://gyazo.com/3d47c8c699a61e982cca20a0ca1c9f8d)

I experienced at least two BSODs earlier while playing League, and one after while not playing League. The only applications I had open in both cases were Chrome (43.0.2357.132) and iTunes (11.0.2.26).

EDIT: Oh! And I ran memtest twice this weekend, passed both times. I did last week update my video drivers, but the BSODs persisted across the update.

EDIT 2: If you're going to downvote my question, at least tell me why.

EDIT 3: For anyone who finds this: it seems the problem might have been Catalyst Control Center's hotkeys. Since deactivating those and restarting I haven't seen another BSOD.

EDIT 4: Disregard. I did BSOD again. The problem was Networx. I have since uninstalled and not had a BSOD in months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M'id laner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 13:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can't play as a female character in Triforce Heroes because women can't be heroes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 09:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice lady in Cape Town offering free room and board... on one condition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does everyone think Luden's Echo is a good item for supports? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Former   current drug users (besides alcohol/tobacco/weed) of Reddit: what made you want to start using? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 22:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No judgement intended, I'm just curious. I've never used anything beyond alcohol, and considering the ridiculously harmful effects of hard drugs, it absolutely astounds me why a person would ever go, "hmm, let's try some heroin." Enlighten me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> campusjob.com reaching out to youth #likeaboss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 09:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help with recording gameplay! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 12:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to start putting some of my #bigplays on YouTube, but I'm not sure how to go about it. Raptr has proven to be pretty great for recording stuff on the fly, but the problem is it records my music as well, which I understand is going to get my videos pulled pronto.

Does anyone know of a good setup whereby I can listen to music as well as in-game sound but not record the music into my videos? I'm tech-savvy and a former sound engineer so I'm not afraid to tinker with this stuff, I just don't know of any software that can achieve what I'm trying to do.

EDIT: I was mostly thinking along the lines of doing clever routing with JACK or something that keeps game audio and iTunes separate before the recording and then mixes them down to stereo, but I don't really think that's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help me get back to Silver! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started playing on the 31st of July last year. It's safe to say I've gotten pretty addicted since! I started playing ranked the moment I hit 30, hoping to get that sweet Morgana skin. No dice, though - I landed in Silver 2, and dropped to Silver 4 by the end of the season.

When season 5 started, I immediately played my placements, got into Bronze 3, then fell to Bronze 4 and have been fluctuating between those two tiers ever since.

I'm super annoyed because I feel like I definitely haven't gotten *worse* at the game. I'd really like to get back up to Silver so I can start wishing I could get up to Gold, lol.

The facts:

* I'm essentially a support main, but I've started playing mid more. I feel like any old solo queue support is likely to do things like provide vision and objective control, but mids tend not to, so by playing mid I'm ensuring that our team probably has two people looking after those things, instead of probably just the one.
* I really like mages. My favourite supports are Morgana and Karma, though I play the former more often in ranked due to her sheer power. (Super hyped for the incoming Karma buffs though!) Mid I like playing Karma and Lux, and have recently picked up Akali (who is quite similar to but more forgiving than my old flame Diana).
* I've started practicing CSing before games. I load into a 1v3 bot match and play only the first five minutes, aiming to get to 1k gold by the end. I'm getting better at it.
* As a support, I always rush Sightstone and make sure to have a ward or two in river against ganks. I will also always have a pink on the map somewhere, usually a defensive one, and I will replace it as it gets destroyed (which almost never happens, yay Bronze). When we get a kill or two and the opportunity presents itself, I'll drop deeper wards to get some vision of the enemy jungle.
* I'll hold on to survival tools like Flash, Barrier, Zhonya's too long, and get burst down before I can activate them.
* Related, I hold on to summoner spells too long. When I play support, I almost never use Exhaust until it's way too late (I think this is related to me not being able to spot when an engage is happening vs when the enemy is just harassing). When I play jungle with Stalker's Blade, I forget to Smite champs.
* I just make shitty mechanical mistakes. I use my skills in the wrong order. I don't take enough care when clicking targets and end up autoing a minion instead of the enemy champ.
* I often underestimate how far I am from safety, especially when we're pushed up in bottom lane. I'll see an enemy coming down the river to gank, and will walk back at a leisurely pace only to get deleted before I'm even in my turret's range.

I'm sure there's loads more issues that replays will uncover. [Here is my op.gg page.](http://euw.op.gg/summoner/matches/userName=subject998)

Appreciate any help, summoners! ^(rip lore) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> League's Lux gets girly af new Star Guardian skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 10:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How not to approach a girl you don't know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LET IT BEGIN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 21:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enemy team has Nidalee and Ahri. We have Annie and Lissandra. Who goes where? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few weeks ago I had a game where the enemy team had a Nidalee top and Ahri mid. On our side, there was an Annie and a Lissandra. Neither of our solo laners took Teleport (they both had Ignite), so we had some flexibility in terms of who goes where.

How would you have assigned the solo laners, purely in terms of "countering"? Of course things like general familiarity with playing vs the enemy laner are also important, but assuming Annie and Liss were equally skilled   equally comfortable playing vs Nida and Ahri, and vice versa, who should have taken which lane?

I was trying to figure it out for myself in terms of CC. Both Annie and Liss have some nice CC on their side, and both Nida and Ahri have to stay mobile to stay alive. Given that Ahri's recent changes have moved her away from assassination, I'm inclined to think Liss should go vs Nida as she is safer, being able to ult herself if caught by a spear. But Ahri is annoyingly mobile, and Lissandra's CC and mobility would be really useful to lock her down (naturally, Annie can stun Ahri, but if Ahri manages to survive the burst, there's almost zero chance she'll die unless both her Flash and her ult are on CD).

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the "Juggerkog" composition so popular in pro play at the moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the basic gist of it: you have an extremely vulnerable hypercarry with huge range, which you abuse by running what amounts to 4 supports to keep him safe. 

But why do I see this comp played so often the last few weeks? Do pro teams believe it's an instant win? Why? What changed to enable this comp?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this weird projectile I'm firing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 00:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
