<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8864</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The flu and recovery tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate my weak body.  After the stress of finals, I suddenly got sick, and lingering flu is sapping the energy out of my body.  I feel slightly better now, but I don't know when I should get back to the gym?  I feel I have to start all over with getting to good condition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard, but I'll keep reminding myself that boxing is just for myself, and that I'm here to improve my body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it's just physical pain.  I'm just not used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mostly muscle pain.  I must admit there is a spring to my step.  But then again I've never really pushed myself in training like an athlete in my life before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting to feel afraid of going to the gym because of the pain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That moment after a hard workout feels great, but during the workout I feel lots of exhaustion and pain.  I don't know why I fear it.  I feel my weakness when the pain grows, and a feel the struggle.  Some people are motivated by this, and I desperately want to fight through the pain, but I feel the fear and aversion to pain too.  Do you guys feel that way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 20:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a beginner myself.  Can't say any of my advice would be useful.  I heard from other's around here that you could develop bad habits without another person.  I'd say keep your body in shape, and do HIIT exercises to mimic stress in a boxing match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 20:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with biggerthangod.  I identify myself the same way.  But curling up in bed and hoping things would be better made me fatter and unhappy.  I realize getting beat up and trying to improve is better than feeling sorry for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, the audience wants flashiness, while Mayweather plays strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 20:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I identify myself as bisexual, asian.  I've been through a bout of minor depression, and most of this is to find mental focus.  There's an inner rage within myself to fight more myself and be proud of myself.  Something I need to work on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 20:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fun imagining you're beating up someone without the consequences, I like doing that shadowboxing too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mental Training/Visualization/Meditation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 06:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how you guys mentally prepare yourselves for training?  Or if it's necessary at all?  Does meditation work?

I found this link about mental visualization in boxing, what do you think?

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jNyecdfzluE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What motivates you to box? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 19:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I've been a bookish, nerdy guy.  I was picked on a few times too.  I feel like my physical presence doesn't makes everyone look down on me.  But I have a really strong urge to fight and beat up someone, just to see how it feels like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should your knuckles hurt after doing mitt work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should your knuckles hurt after doing mitt work?  My trainer said it strengthens your knuckles, but my knuckles have been aching for a week now?  Should I work through the pain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your commute time to the gym? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there weren't traffic, I could easily go to many boxing gyms, but most of the gyms around me are a half an hour drive each way.  How long does it take for you guys?  What's reasonable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 03:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine does 10 per training session.  150 registration one time and 50 a month to use facility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 08:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, then again, intellectual bookish types aren't as athletic in comparison to everyone else.  Then again, I'm American, and people just don't move that much in general.  At least there isn't much cardio happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you juggle work and boxing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling better, before and after boxing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has boxing changed you mentally and physically, before and after?  Did you get the body you desired?  Did you feel more alert? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
