<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4830</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is like a Kindergarten kid who wants to take his toys and go home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he hasn't read it by now, what's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where would this new party stand on abortion and gun rights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer [this version](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mWjorK8Gv3A). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there enough votes for such a party? It could be difficult creating a party that appears to religious conservatives on social issues while also appealing to progressives on financial issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what you mean by fiscally liberal. There is an argument to be made that this is what the mainstream GOP is. They play it pretty loose on fiscal policy. Big task cuts, big borrowing, big debt increases. They talk about curbing entitlements by rarely do much about it.

I suppose you are asking a more serious question, about a party or candidate who truly embraces "fiscally liberal but socially conservative". As someone who grew up Catholic, I think you are on to something here. Most socially conservative Catholics I know vote Republican. This is primarily due to the abortion issue. Most of these same people are eager and active in helping the poor. I do find them to be a little uncomfortable with the idea of paying more in taxes to have that money go to social programs. They seem more comfortable with the Catholic Church and its various charities playing that role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Christie's political career wasn't already over, then it is now. He has said he is done with politics and will go into the private sector once his term is complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has that covered. He is going to build special doors that are only to be used by animals during migration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like NeverTrump will get their wish. Trump isn't likely to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NeverTrump movement is facing a nightmare scenario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her husband would be more likely to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Trump really is trying to piss off as many voters as possible before he goes on a tirade about the election being rigged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gunfire leaves one man dead, another hurt in San Jose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melania Trump Accused of Plagiarism Again, This Time From Marla Maples </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the part that gets left out of 2nd Amendment fantasies. A person would need to be a George Zimmerman level asshole to not care about taking someone's life, no matter how justified you thought to were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised he is at zero. I guess polls don't allow for negative percentages.

Damn rigged polls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Trump will be spending a lot of nights on the couch if he wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melania Trump says people are 'too mean' on the Internet. The Internet reacts, obviously. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun owner who shot and killed intruders says he is 'devastated' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF!? Louisiana Supreme Court: Priests Dont Have To Report Child Abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bizarre leaked Pentagon video is a science fiction story about the future of cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orlando Gunmans Wife Breaks Silence: I Was Unaware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Nevada desert, Bundy family warns of another standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amy Grants new Christmas album reignites the old Whats Christian enough? question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Ag Commissioner Sid Miller calls Hillary Clinton C-word on Twitter, blames staffer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not so Happy Meal - Shooting outside McDonalds in San Francisco leaves 1 injured </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Today: A New Target of Gun Control Advocates - Bullets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! That would be scary to experience in person. I've felt some 3-4 level quakes, but they are nothing like the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the small sampling of conservative Catholics, I'm friends with on Facebook, they keep posting stuff about Mike Pense. Stuff they see as positives. Anti-abortion, and the general social conservative stuff he represents. Maybe that's how they can stomach swallowing the bitter Trump pill, while ignoring the Catholic VP on the Democratic ticket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why anyone would do work for Trump without getting paid up front, is a mystery to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump surrogate hopes Hillary Clinton and Huma Abedin go down like Thelma and Louise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma fugitive Michael Vance killed in shootout with police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's one way to ensure a taco truck on every corner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but, will the NY Times release the rest of his tax returns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Husbands With Guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like that store is getting a late start. The War on Christmas usually gets started in early October. I expect it to move all the way back to the day after Labor Day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 more Richmond cops to be fired in sexual misconduct scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murdered womans sons aided in suit against gun dealers by killers mother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump supporter charged with voting twice in Iowa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 06:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya'll Qaeda is on the lose again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Trump victory aint gonna happen says Nancy Pelosi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hard is it to prove a conspiracy. They were actively calling for 3% folks to come and support their effort in taking over the BLM land. Isn't it enough to be a conspiracy to say "Hey, let's get our guns, head to a remote part of Oregon, and steal land from the BLM that we think should belong to the locals?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the government lost its case against the Oregon occupiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 01:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CLM = Cowboy Lives Matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The verdict for those armed militants who took over a federal building is white privilege in action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outcry Over Oregon Standoff Verdict: White Militants Acquitted While Native Protestors Maced, Beaten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are making sure people who aren't planning to vote for Trump don't get to vote. If you are not an angry white guy wearing an NRA T-shirt, you are immediately suspected of being disloyal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Cerrito resident comes home to gun attacker, dies on front porch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 08:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with that. Let's cancel the election and give it to Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 08:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You have to proved that they conspired *with the intent* of impeding officers

Is that hard in this case? A bunch of good ol' boys showed up heavily armed and talking about taking land from the Feds? If I were an employee of BLM stationed in that area, I wouldn't have wanted to go to work. Does someone need to get shot before it's considered impeding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 07:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's quite the metaphor for the Trump campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 06:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the Feds screw this up so badly? Is anyone guilty of anything? They were [charged with a number of crimes](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Occupation_of_the_Malheur_National_Wildlife_Refuge#Trials)

 A total of 27 people involved in the occupation were charged under federal law; of those, 26 have been indicted for a single federal felony count of conspiracy to impede officers of the U.S. from discharging their official duties through the use of force, intimidation, or threats. A number of those under indictment on the conspiracy charge are also charged with a variety of other counts, some of which incur sentences up to life imprisonment, including possession of firearms and dangerous weapons in federal facilities, use and carry of firearms in relation to a crime of violence, depredation of government property (relating to damaging the site "by means of excavation and the use of heavy equipment"), and theft of government property. In addition, several of those under indictment in Oregon have also been indicted separately for their roles in the 2014 Bundy standoff in Nevada.

Hopefully, the government lawyers for the trial in Nevada can learn from the mistakes in Oregon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 03:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some colorful details from [Oregon Public Broadcasting](http://www.opb.org/news/series/burns-oregon-standoff-bundy-militia-news-updates/ammon-bundy-verdict-oregon-standoff-malheur-court/)

 After the verdict was read, Ammon Bundys attorney Marcus Mumford was tackled to the ground by five U.S. Marshals. He insisted his client was free to go. Ammon Bundy faces a US Marshall hold and is supposed to be transferred to Nevada where he faces charges for the Bunkerville standoff.

 Theres a hold for Ammon Bundy and Ryan Bundy out of the district of Nevada, said Matt Schindler attorney for Kenneth Medenbach.

 Theres nothing Judge Brown can do about that. So acquitting him here, all it does is effectively release him to that hold, to be transported to Nevada. And the court that has anything authority to deal with that, is the court in Nevada. Marcus let the emotion of the moment, I think, overtake his better judgement.

 During the incident, Judge Brown ordered everyone out of the courthouse. Mumford was later detained.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF!? Bundy Brothers Acquitted in Takeover of Oregon Wildlife Refuge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 03:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since both say #ImWithHer, I'm good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will fit right in on Trump's new TV network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Nugent keeps it class, says Hillary Clinton is a devilbitch who hates everything good about America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Militia group calls on members to patrol polls on Election Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as Trump doesn't get elected, I'm good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to the Halloween bonanza I have quickly finished 5 of my last 6 pokemon. The last one is an Aerodactyl, so that's going to be tough, especially since I don't currently have any 10k eggs. It's a little bittersweet getting so close to 142.

I will keep at it, stocking up on candy to evolve the next round of pokemon, whenever they become available. Also, powering up my best fighters to max, and upgrading a few to better IV versions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So what exactly constitutes a revolution and other than a some Twitter posts, why does the author think that there's one in progress?

Trump not getting many votes from the ladies, that's gotta count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's true, no one has more respect for women than Donald J. Trump. Look at what he has done for feminism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump awakened a feminist revolution in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've started walking my one Dragonite in the hopes of getting enough candy to evolve my IV 91 Dratini. Those suckers are hard to find in the wild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This ad is so weird](http://www.youtube.com/embed/1PG2V0YnokM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump speaks Hindi in unusual new campaign ad aimed at Indian-American voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lou Dobbs targets Evan McMullin with ugly Mormon mafia smear, while Jason Chaffetz flip-flops on Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On November 8th, Im voting for Trump. On November 9th, if Trump loses, Im grabbing my musket. You in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Trump's big problem. I can't stand listening to him going off script and going full on conspiratard. Trump might have the occasional good idea but those moments get buried under a tremendous pile of bullshit. There is no vast media and left wing conspiracy. Trump is just a fucking moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi groom asks Snapchatting wife for divorce 2 hours after wedding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you not familiar with the Dilbert cartoon? If so, that is a lot of fun to read, especially if you work in IT or a corporate office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dilbert creator Scott Adams: No terrorist attack before Election Day means ISIS prefers Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mob Boss' Wife Says She'd Have Cut Husband's Throat If He Talked Like Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oakland artist creates Trump coloring book, donates proceeds to immigration nonprofit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps campaign has spent more on hats than on polling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michelle Obama really, really doesnt like Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps latest excuse for losing doesnt quite add up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress may flip -- but dysfunction is here to stay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 17:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clarence Thomass Twenty-Five Years Without Footprints </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton Has Finally Achieved Obama-Level Support Among Young Voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's tallest church being eroded by peeing, vomiting vandals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBA TV host Kristen Ledlow says she was robbed at gunpoint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Trump poses for a photo with woman wearing a 'Latina against Trump' shirt, has no idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On freedom of the press, Donald Trump wants to make America like England again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Jake Tapper, Kellyanne Conway spar over Donald Trumps Gettysburg list of grievances: He delivers his own speeches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man gunned down in front of hotel near SFO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 07:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reports: 3 men with 'creepy clown' masks, gun found by security at SF's Westfield mall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 07:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 wounded in East Oakland shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Yorker Endorses Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 07:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pornstar Jessica Drake: Trump Offered Me $10,000 for Sex (Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 06:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cubs beat Dodgers 5-0 to reach 1st World Series since 1945 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off his message again: Trump vows to sue all female accusers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's why Donald Trump's skin is so orange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Murray crashes White House press briefing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore to Trump Voters: 'You're Legal Terrorists' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian warships pass through English Channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck. Fuck Fuck. Fuck Fuck Fuck. Fuck Fuck Fuck Fuck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 2016 election is depressing, but at least we get a Weird Al video out of it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps new justification for attacking the Clintons: Michelle Obama started it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 19 Charged With Gun Trafficking, Bank Larceny In Brooklyn, Officials Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This November, marijuana activists are pushing pot over pills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Donald Trump Reject the Election Results? Yes. Would It Do Any Good? Nope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks threatens Tim Kaine, DNC Chairwoman Donna Brazile: We have a surprise in store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A massive cyberattack caused major websites to go down across the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Donald Trump Accuser Says He Touched Her Breast, Asked Dont You Know Who I Am? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump praises Hillary Clinton as a great senator and wife in newly discovered video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's Mormon PR problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 00:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's advice in 2007 book: 'Accept blame' for 'painful defeats' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's super basic mistake about the economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump keeps falling for Vladimir Putins praise and propaganda, and its finally hurting his campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's 2016 and Kansas approvingly cited Dred Scott in an abortion case. It was not a good idea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans, time to prepare for a scorched-earth Clinton presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump: I will 'totally accept' results of the presidential election 'if I win' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps meaningless pledge to accept a clear election result </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Attempt To Refocus Campaign Gets Obscured By One Blinding Final Debate Moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump just put Hill Republicans in a no-win situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is asking America to hire him for the worlds most important job. Heres his resume. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Donald Trumps campaign manager given up on him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton chides Trump as her plane prepares to leave Vegas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's Contempt for Democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet reacts to final presidential debate with hilarious memes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative not happy with Trump's debate abortion answer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney general leads criminal probe of Wells Fargo bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump and Roger Ailes No Longer on Speaking Terms (Report) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative Legal Scholars Decide Trump Isn't Worth It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslims for Trump ad pictures Sikh man leading group to distinguish Muslims and Sikhs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's campaign manager: 'No, I do not believe' there will be widespread voter fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hacking, leaking, undercover election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Springsteen: Donald Trump is a flagrant, toxic narcissist who wont go quietly when he loses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 07:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Semitic Posts, Many From Trump Supporters, Surge on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is bringing Obama's estranged half-brother to the final presidential debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second victim dies in shooting over weed deal in Sonoma County </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Jr.s joke about Aurora theater shooting sparks anger in Colorado. Trump Jr. on day of Aurora theater shooting: Overall I give the movie two thumbs up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore secretly made a movie about Donald Trump, and now he's premiering it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco police hunt for shooter near schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Election a Morality Play or Just Reality TV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melania Trump takes a page from Hillary Clintons playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian air defense raises stakes of U.S. confrontation in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: teenager shot in Bayview, suspect at large </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Stop whining,' Obama tells Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Donald Trump is doing to discredit the media is very, very dangerous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, 1.8 million dead people arent going to vote in November </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The triumph of Chuck Berry: At 90, the rock pioneer has a new album on the horizon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump says the election is rigged. Heres what his supporters think that means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump proposes five-year ban on executive branch officials and lawmakers who want to become lobbyists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer is focusing on the big prize: Senate majority leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 01:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Guns don't kill people, toddlers do': The shocking new gun-control PSA focused on children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative originalists letter calls Trump indifferent or hostile to the Constitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melania Trump to Address Sexual Assault Allegations on 'Anderson Cooper' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle school principal accused of paying hitman to kill pregnant girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Protesters Defying Donald Trump: His Customers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps latest tweetstorm: Joe Biden can be creepy, so why cant I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black voters remain key ingredient Louisiana political gumbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Bill Clinton strategy is going very poorly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps claim that a Clinton-backed Haiti factory amounted to a massive sweatshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 09:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials responding to reports of shooting in Vallejo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 07:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New York Times should do its homework: NAACP wants a moratorium on new charter schools  and for good reason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 07:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dangers of Trump's 'rigged election' talk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rudy Giuliani: Dead People Generally Vote for Democrats (Update) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence rebukes Donald Trump: The election isnt rigged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Intensifies His Claim That Campaign Is Rigged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop reading national polls, the state numbers are where it's at </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-shirt depicting Kaepernick in gun sight sold outside Bills stadium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giuliani: Alleged Trump groping couldnt possibly have happened because it was in first class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been waiting for 7 years for Obama to take my gun and all I got was a job, marriage equality and Cuban cigars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the Russians really preparing for war? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Campaign on Latest Accusers Claim of Lewd Behavior: Media Has Gone Too Far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 00:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Should Take a Drug Test Before Debate, Donald Trump Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 dead, 12 wounded in gunfire at Los Angeles restaurant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Donald Trump reacted when his teleprompters broke down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neo-Nazis tell Michelle Obama: Dont wax feminist if youve been to a Jay Z concert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extremely unattractive': How Donald Trump tries to discredit women based on their looks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump, Jr.'s advice to women who can't take workplace sexual harassment: Teach kindergarten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cosmo once asked Donald Trump to do a nude shoot. Really. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Carsons Morning Joe interview was jaw-droppingly bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to Americas Mayor? How Rudy Giuliani became Trumps attack dog. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence gave an odd answer to a young girl's question about self image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling Burned by Media, Trump Turns Up Heat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosie ODonnell Details Depression Caused by Presidential Debate Insult in Ivanka Trump Poem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 7 dumbest arguments in defense of Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In surprise San Francisco appearance, Clinton addresses Trump comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Here come the rape police': Rush Limbaugh reacts to Trump's 'sex-talk scandal' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres the advice Donald Trump gave Bill Cosby about sexual assault accusations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump cancels "Hannity" interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump's Going Ballistic Over Assault Allegations Against Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican newspaper not super excited about Dylan Nobel win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest: First lady says she's 'shaken' by Trump remarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Getting Into Serious Electoral Trouble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump chases skirts, then hides behind them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is This Republican NY Senate Candidate More Unhinged Than Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NY senate candidate promises Harlem residents 'Kool Aid, KFC and watermelons' at campaign event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Ship Fires Missiles at Yemeni Rebel Sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the GOPs Big Tent turned into a house of horrors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Gets Ready to Be a Bad Loser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She wore a message to a Trump rally: Grab my p-. I dare you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 02:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Women Say Donald Trump Touched Them Inappropriately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giuliani wrongly accuses Clinton of lying about 9/11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As protesters accuse her husband of rape, Clinton blasts Trumps scorched earth tactics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump will protect you: Some fear he is running to be a dictator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm one of the Central Park Five. Donald Trump won't leave me alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
