<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> W1D1: What advice do you wish you'd gotten before you first started? What do you wish you'd known once you made it to the end? All advice welcome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Kulyustan's in Manhattan (also has a wider range of spices). Or if you're willing to venture into Brooklyn, Sahadi's. A bunch of the places nearby make good shawarmas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Albuquerque Journal ran an obituary for Walter White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] My favourite thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the show did a really good job of showing how a lot of the issues that Hannah, and the rest of the characters, were dealing with were very systemic. Like yes, Hannah was slut shamed and objectified, but Jessica and Skye feel the effects of that too. Even Justin, Alex, and Tyler were affected. Especially when it comes to Bryce and his actions. Justin feels indebted, and Alex wants to fit in. While Tyler is also being bullied or picked on by his other classmates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the show needs to keep up the "reasons" conceit since we're already invested in these characters. But one way to do that, and still kind of feature Hannah is to explore Alex's suicide and what led to that. Because he was depressed after he and Jessica broke up, and what happened with Hannah was the last straw, but maybe there was something happening in his home life that first started the whole thing? He clearly does have some issues with his dad and his dad's job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hannah originally survived in the book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
