<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80 proof?  what's the name of that shot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, that's definitely potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd better add a couple zeros since you're considering the surgery/disease </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 17:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, never heard of spinners.  Cool! Also thanks for the recipe.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c16SND1GsJo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like you to braise two lamb shanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A way to a man's heart is through his stomach.  I guess it's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 02:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks excellent. Any chance for OP to post a recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the hammer/handles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auxilliary?  Like to drive a pto for the dump bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how do you think that relates to "the rest of us" providing free healthcare to food service workers? (such as ballot proposal in Colorado or Romneycare in MA) Also, I think you mean no one 'declares it though', meaning they aren't paying their fair share of income tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really reminds me of my first table when I was a waiter at a semi-fancy restaurant. Somehow it happened to be prom night, and my first table ever was an 6 top. I had actually had a bit of training, here's the computer, here's how you enter stuff to get a bill, here's the salads, here's the dressings, here's the desserts you're going to serve, here's the tall pepper grinders that you can offer during the salad, here's the fountain for drink re-fills, napkins, I don't know there was a lot of stuff. Like after your shift you have to make sure to do the carpet, and dust this and that. Important things like this is where the food comes from and this is where you turn your order in. Anyway, my first table I go out and bring the menus, receive and deliver the drinks, and then take the order. Well this is where IFU. I guess I was excited and I totally their appetizers. I must have run to the line and turned in their dinner orders and started hustling their drinks and salads and totally forgot the apps and all of that delay. I think I might have realized that when I presented the bill and apologized or mentioned that I didn't charge them and it all worked out. I think I worked there for a number of more months. oops, sorry prom dinner party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He,,,,,Could,,,go,,all,the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, seems like it would require more frequent maintenance than a tapered bearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool, thanks for the reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, very rigorous maritime engineering standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of our '99 F250 super duty has the 5.4l correct engine label on the left and 7.3l on the right from factory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at the wiki, I can't see an AWD GM maybe it's from a Volvo. Otherwise it would be a 4T65, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, could you say "that the front fell off"? gosh I love that video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The computer game I-76 was fun for a while when it came out. I'm sure this guy was just trying to re-live the fun in Texas/New Mexico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I had to think about this for a while. There's supposed to be a temp sensor on that side of the oil pan? Have an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you call those split rims? or Are those split rims? Looks like 16 bolts holding the two halves together. IDK aviation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting wheel bearing. I've never heard of one that uses ball bearings like the commenter on imgur states. Also, the race is smaller than the bearing which I guess is the way ball bearings work. I had to google the name, maybe Chevy should come out with those again instead of the Caprice. I really wanted to blame Fiat-Chrysler for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was from the Volvo in the computer wallpaper and it had a very large brick on top forcing the front suspension and the roof rack to bottom out. Anyway, why did the speaker cause the roof-rack to fail?
EDIT: whole question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used lkq a few times with success. Twice specifically for a Ford 8.8 rear end on two '98 f150s. I guess my local shop couldn't repair it if the bearings spun in the housing. IDK, they tell me stuff's fubar get another, but in this case we did try to send it for repair. IMO those rear ends suck, we have a pretty good maintenance program and our f150s aren't high mileage or off road use.
EDIT: 2 f150s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done the 2nd option.  Get a little color on the stuffed chop in a fry pan, transfer to oven to finish about 1/2 hour.  I just use a jarred gravy from Heinz.  Tasty.  I guess if you had already cooked the stuffing though you could try to keep the chop juicier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ooh, where is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might check with your base/local librarian.  There's some things like measurements that might be easier to learn from a book. Or just grab the measuring cups and spoon set (teaspoon, tablespoon, etc) and check them out. Use them while helping your wife, etc. 3 tablespoons to 1/4 cup, 4 cups to a quart, 4 quarts to a gallon, 8 ounces to a cup, stuff like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got hit in the face with a ground ball during infield practice. Broke the front tooth. Unbelievable pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that banana flavoured stuff from bad dentist visits previously.  Nice TIFU! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't play cops" yeah, that and lose your Cop buddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shortly after 9/11 attacks I traveled by air.  I had a mini-leatherman in my toiletry kit.  I mean this thing is like 2 inches square by 1/2 inch when folded.  It was deep inside my carry-on inside a separate toiletry bag.  They went straight to it.  They said I could mail it to my home or wherever I was going at the post office upstairs.  I said f-it, just keep it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our vehicle maintenance still has a 1986 F250 w/300 six on the road, licensed.  The oldest is probably the 1976 John Deere tractor the has to run once every year, lol.  They didn't buy a backhoe for the newer one.  It's crazy, we're spending over $4m/year fixing this old crap. I mean if you include wages, healthcare, uniforms parts and shop supplies it's probably a whole lot more than that.  We got capital money for 5 snowmobiles or something this year. Talk about job security, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would cost me $2000 to go to San Francisco from Fraser, CO in style on Amtrak. It would take 4 days.  I could fly from Denver in 2.5 hours or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way back when I was riding with a friend in an AMC Eagle.  It was fancy, I think 5 speeds.  The shifter came off in his hand.  It had a plastic ball on the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That first screw on the right side looks like it goes through the lighting bracket.  That's not normal at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that he was banned/timed out because of self promotion.  The time out has ended though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but does it have catsup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they de-shell it and then stir-fry?  looking great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things pregnant women order for $200 Bob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, you got me by 400' but at least we have pastrami in Colorado.  Anyway, yours looks very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 01:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Evinrude is part of Bombardier now.  Toro's website is great though, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Permatex Hi-tack?  You can fix the soles of your boots with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh, first thing I said "ooh, those wheels, oh that dog"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, that's a great point.  My shop goes through a whole lot of (mostly Cu) crush washers on really expensive stuff like splitter boxes and torque hubs.  Now I know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, there's a lot of stuff here.  I don't like the oval thing on the front, or the pipes in the bed.  It's a good thing that there's a fire extinguisher either side, lol.  The wood in the bed and the trunk are pretty cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, wow that looks great.  You're killing me today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's on the two slices of bread in the middle, duxelles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks very tasty.  Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if I spit on the leftovers will they let me take them home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, 51258?  Is that a Cat engine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I see the evidence, what's the cause and resolution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a bad tread to have on a trailer depending on application. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that usually happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex and I got another rescue after we had to put her dog down due to cancer.  Almost the first thing this dog did was run away.  She was pretty sweet and already trained a bit.  It was pretty scary when she ran across the interstate highway, I remember she hid in the middle, no injuries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 05:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but what are you going to eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 04:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should always stack with the soft stuff on the bottom so that whatever falls doesn't break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, this post is how I wound up in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can use them to measure stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canning is done at harvest time in order to survive the hell that is winter in Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it goes bad quickly in the fridge.  Freezer is the way to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your sirloin looks like a rib eye to me. IAnotabutcherthough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked once and they didn't seem bad at all compared to another box lunch.  They're like $2 here when they're on sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you can find store brand frozen chicken kiev, brocolli cheese, or cordon bleu for $1.00 each.  Those are a really awesome deal.  The Barber brand ones are great too, but way more expensive.  Frozen ravioli is good.  I keep wanting to like frozen chicken wings, but they suck.  So far as meals go, I think the Stouffer's and Marie Calendar's are the best.  Boston Market ones have gone seriously downhill of late.  The Stouffer's mexican lasagna and regular lasagna are tasty. Almost all the frozen fish from Van de Camp and Gorton's suck except the grilled filets with no breading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, this one has two cheese stuffed sausages and 'penos on the side! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that your photo shows a creamy sauce.  And especially no black burnt spots on the noodles.  I like mine creamy.  IMHO, you should be able to order your Mac and Cheese (or shells and cheese) to a specific doneness.  Like your steak.  And also a certain hotness regarding spice level.  You did the doneness like I would like it OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, do not GIS "tub girl" please.  Anyway, u/wowthisguyoverhere you could try Cheetos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about roasted Hatch green chilis.  Think about them in a cheese sauce, they're probably tasty and hot, and now they are in a shell.  Think about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, how about buying a box of shells.  comes w/9mm and 2 clips
http://i.imgur.com/QhU2vIY.jpg?fb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's the way we did it last time both at once.  We just used a regular floor jack and a hoist with strap through the window opening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 03:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is an excessive drain on the battery a user can check that easily by removing the negative battery terminal.  If there is a visually noticeable spark as the terminal is removed that is a good indication of an excessive drain on the battery when in shut down condition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pull the new bushings in.. using a socket to allow the bushing to come all the way thru the bracket.

thanks for the reply and suggestions.  when you do it, do you do both hinge pins at once or one first and then the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like some sort of cheese on top of the tomatos and herbs you see in the linked photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2000 CHEVY BLAZER LF door hinge kit dorman 924-106 924-107 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've had my Blazer since 2003 or so and replaced the LF door hinge pins and bushings once back about 6-7 years ago.  The hinges were badly wallered out, and of course the new bushings didn't hold up.  Now it's time to either do the same again or I noticed that Dorman has come out with replacement hinges for just this application.  #924-106 and 924-107.  http://www.dormanproducts.com/gsearch.aspx?type=parttype year=2000 make=Chevrolet model=Blazer parttype=Door%2520Hinge%2520Assembly origin=YMM

Wondering if anyone has experience with this whole hinge repair.  The problem is the current hinges are spot welded into place, and it may be required to remove the whole dash or something to get at the back side of the upper hinge to install the new hinge and backing plate.  Wat do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 2k Blazer and had the transmission replaced in 2004/5 on a road trip. Somehow the transfer case ran for about 10k miles without any oil at all. Still going good today, and I have no idea why it was drained in the first place, but hey free oil change kind of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's a laptop. I guarantee they shut the lid and walk away.

And order parts we have to return later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have been a link to /r/trees/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you're going over 90mph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, where do you cook your lunch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The radiators on the car are only for oil and charge air (turbo 1.6l V-8 in this case). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think OP's protein to protein to protein to protein to salad ratio is looking great!@ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd enjoy eating this. If only chili, it should be a squish thicker but served this way the rice will be better. It's like a reverse of what the US has been doing, and taking a US staple and adding an Asian element. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know Owen, but I like him already! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, confirmation. Also, I need to work a dry rub into it even if it's only salt and pepper (I'll do better than that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, me also.  MyPi is/was my deep dish pizza inoculation so there I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, subby needs to call it Sausage, Lamb and Beef Ragu next time. +1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a biologist, but I stayed near a Holiday in last night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one looks like it might hold together for the long haul.  I lurv mac and cheese and also with catsup, so that's cool. Good looking tomato and also a bit of cream cheese and lettuce. Bun looking solid. Missing red jelly/sauce on the right side bottom. I like it a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it has a squirt of jizz on the side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, this looks great of course.  And one more upvote.  I've only been to HI twice and both times I got poke at a "grocery", once Costco and 2nd Food Lion.  I was very happy to eat it as it was sold.  Do you have any generic/specific instructions on ramping it up like I think you did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it comes out of a butt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, It brings back memories of my father who worked @ Hormel in Mankato for a while.  Anyway, I've just started reading the books of James Lee Burke and in all of them so far he has mentioned a sandwich of ham with raw onions.  No mention of condiments so far.  Could be fried ham and toasted bread, but raw onion.  The books are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 03:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks slightly soupy in the photo also, however I like that because the crust will soak up the liquid easy!  Looks awesome subby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, they look really great.  Did you put the Memphis wet sauce on right away without any rub? EDIT: A lot of times when I make wet ones I'll cook them a couple hours wrapped in foil and then drain grease b4 applying wet sauce.  That's why I ask... Apartment dwelling rib eating machine here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 2nd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 03:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think it's mostly in the bones.  And the blood should be easy to buy as it mostly goes down the drain, right?  Plus it's liquid so maybe easier to harvest than marrow or something.  Liver probably has a lot also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's in the blood not the steaks.  No idea how much blood in a cow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it would be HP brown sauce in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking different food is photoshopped onto the table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like we don't understand the depth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't groceries do smoked stuff?  You can get an automatic smoker from Alto-Shaam.  Get one and hook it up, put some chicken and ribs. Actually, get two or 6 of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
