<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9885</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first house I remember living in with my family was a rented 1 bed room back to back flat in a shitty neighbourhood where we all slept in 1 room and got burgled on a semi-regular basis. At this time my dad ran his business out of a garage, had no employees and my mum had to work nights to make ends meet. By the time I was 12 they owned a 4 bed semi detached house in a desirable location, and my dads business had relocated to a large showroom and workshop space and had 5 permanent members of staff. Really quite impressive when I think about it, makes me grateful to have seen both sides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cotton headed ninny muggins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well yeah can't say I've tried that, but I can highly recommend adding a few squares of high cocoa content squares of chocolate to a regular chilli!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was expecting to hate it! But I find it makes the chilli more rich, deeper in flavour without really tasting too much of chocolate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the theme coming out in a lot of these comments, of a kind of rebelliousness that the customer will probably not notice, but allows the server to feel they've got a little one up on them without doing anything that could risk their job - reminds me of studying Scott in anthropology, acts of everyday resistance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eating super unhealthy food with zero guilt, and being loud as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's not considered strange everywhere, but I was pretty sceptical of chocolate in a sauce with meat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a great time taking a morning to visit a stable in ryogoku district, watching the sumo wrestlers training is really something else! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
