<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1258</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 06:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lawn mow your hair. please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 06:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shave that shit up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 18:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is scary because my roommate was in Argentina and Chile for a weeks just now and her mom's dog's name is Bear and he looks exactly like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 02:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg this is my life. I thought I was the only one out there :'(

Kinda stupid but not gonna lie, i'm terrified of switching my birth control...and a little embarrassed about talking to my doctor about the fact that i'm dry as the dessert in summer time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure how to do this type of problem with percentage yield. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 04:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I know how to find a percentage yield when I have a certain amount of grams, with an excess of another,  and an actual yield given to me.

This problem has no excess but grams of 2 compounds and an actual yield...i'm not sure what to do with the second compound...
Here is the equation:

15.0 g methane and 10.0 g carbon monoxide were placed in a vessel. What is the theoretical yield of acetic acid if actual yield is 19.1? What is the percentage yield? 

CH3OH (l) + CO (g) -- HC2H3O2     (already balanced)

So if it was just 15.0 g of methan with excess CO, i would know what to do, but with two compounds, I don't know. Any help would be appreciated. thanks!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 07:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avid lurker here! Please keep me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 04:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dearest OP,
I currently am going through some tough times right now as well. While they aren't over, maybe it'll make you feel better to know you aren't alone. After being at the top of my class, in the honors program, and class president, I got discriminated by a teacher verbally and emotionally over and over again. Just brought my self confidence to an all time low. I developed panic disorder, lost my position on council, got kicked out of the program as senior in college, and now I have to start all over in another major when I thought I was going to graduate this year at the top of my grade.

Though I can't get over it,  learned to COPE. I talked to friends, I started to take life day by day and stopped planning into the future unless i really needed to. I tell myself I'm beautiful everyday, I tell myself I'm not worthless - even thought sometimes I don't believe it, but you know - sometimes I do. 
I don't know what kind of advice to give you, but you aren't alone in tough times :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 02:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also def belongs in /r/firstworldproblems  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 23:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just tell your mom. This is a couple's fight.
Yes, he's your dad. But the one who he will be cheating on is your mom. She's the one who should be the one to confront  him and whip him back into shape and tell him what's up. You're mom is not a scared little girl who needs to be protected. She can fight for what's right and what is hers with the  right information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 22:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved how they body autonomy to organ donation. Well put and I'm going to steal this phrasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 22:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also shed a tear of satisfaction reading that. The vindication I felt was like it was my own bike.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Net Ionic Equations. HAAALP. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 23:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in general, I understand the concept of a net ionic equation, as well as, how to do them. I understand that you do not break up a solid, liquid, or gas.  What am i confused about, is that when trying to figure out if it's S, L, G, or Aq - I have no clue how. 
If all the reactants and products are Aqueous how am i supposed to know what breaks up and what doesn't to create your equation. 
Yes I can use a solubility chart, but I feel like i'm missing something.
1 examples
NaClO(aq) + HBr(aq) NaBr(aq) + HClO(aq)

These are all aqueous. What breaks apart on the product side.
I know the first side is Would NaBr stay as NaBr? Or would it be Na2+ and Br2- or would it be HClO- or H+ Cl+ O+ 

fjfkda; HAALP.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 02:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL. 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what is the title? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 20:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read this manga before and it's fairly short. Here is a clip from it.
http://www.mangahere.com/manga/joousama_no_tamago/v01/c001/51.html
It's about a girl who is a shinigami ( a lower class shinigami) and she is paired up with a top A+ shinigami guy. She doesn't like killing people but she wants to be one of the best. It's shoujo. Anyone know the name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 04:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no such button even when logged in :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 03:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never needed to poop? 
I call that bullshit.
That crap is a lie
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 20:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I think that'll help!

Well, my parents want me to get someone I don't know from India ( i live in the US) by the time I'm 26. Btw, I'm 22 right now (and so is my boyfriend.)  I'm not very happy with the idea, but they said that is IF i CAN'T find someone in the US who they approve of. My boyfriend and I are currently in a long-term relationship Looking to stay together. As for marriage, I honestly don't know and couldn't say because we're at the end of our college lives and that brings about soo many changes.
All I know is, I REALLY don't want to be in an arranged marriage. I'll fight it tooth and nail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indian girl here who grew up in the US. Listen, my parents want me to get an arranged marriage too. I don't know how I feel about that. I know where you are coming from.

ANYWAY, I entered my first relationship this year, and it embarrassed me a LOT that I didn't know the first thing about relationships and my BF had been in so many relationships before.
You know what changed me from being an insecure pathetic creature?
When my BF told me it's not a one way street. 

Basically, your happiness matters too. Yes, you want to make him happy, but STOP THINKING ABOUT HIM FOR A SECOND. If you can't be happy, how can you make someone else happy? 
Also, learn to accept a compliment, it makes life a lot easier. Trust me, I've been there. 

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and then when you say you can't they go, "oh yea,  my hair gets frizzy too." 
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 02:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to say this, Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 21:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigander here. YES. THIS. THIS is exactly how it feels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 05:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about your brother? Was he ok with you moving out? How did you take it? Are you making sure to still stay in contact with him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 05:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was TOTALLY going to suggest this piece as well. It is FANTASTIC. And quite light hearted but gets the point across!
I was not a feminist- and refused to be called one- until I read this. 
Now, that word pretty much defines me. 
Seriously, if you're confused - this piece is the way to go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 05:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't abnormal at all! It can take a lot more time than just 4 to loosen up. As everyone has said previously, a water-based lube really helps (it was a gift from the gods for me.) And just go slow, I found it pretty painful almost always and have to really slow at first, but after the first initial 5 minutes, I'm good! Also, if the problem is with how tight you are at first, try (or have your partner) finger you a lot. It can really help!
Remember,  your body is yours and unique. No one else can tell you exactly what will help, but I hope everyone's comments to give a good direction to go into! Good luck! Happy sex life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 02:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.  I don't know what it is. Since i'm not a doctor and I've never met you- no one on reddit could accurately diagnose you, but i will say that Schizophrenia can come i many different forms, including being as "mild" as just a voice. Don't freak out though, it really  may just be stress. On another note, if you generally do not think these voices are yours, have you ever tried ignoring Flynn? Pretending he isn't there? What happens? 

2. Don't ever think you are crazy. Having a mental health problem never makes you crazy. Just like a physical illness doesn't make anyone a freak. Take care of your mental health, it's just as much a part of you as your physical body is. Ok? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 22:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First things first. If you don't have a support network, find one.
Your friends at school are a great one - if you have some good ones, I'm sure they'd be more than happy to help you cope and help around the house with things you don't know. Maybe they just don't know how to approach you right now. Ask and find them.

Second - relatives, they may be farther and harder to get a hold of, but can your grandparents, aunts, uncles, cousins - anyone who you'd typically have over for chistmas -can they help you? Can you move in with someone? Can they  move in with you for a bit and help you get back on your feet?

Another point-  Did your parents have a lawyer? See what they left you? Life insurance?  Wills? etc. Did they leave any information on what to do as a landlord etc in case they ever passed?

fourth - what about school? I know this may not be the right time to think about it when you are grieving, but if you were in school, take a break but don't forget about it. It's important for your future. Don't get held down my these weights that have been forced on you. Keep going to school if you can afford to. 

If you ever need anyone to talk to, please PM me! Sending some more Michigan love to you. Be strong but not too strong. It's ok to ask for help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 20:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed! I absolutely hate bugs and looking at those pictures creeped me out the whole time I was looking, BUT it was such a beautiful and tender story I just had to keep going. /r/AwwwWTF  is definitely the right place for this post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How is it that when it blizzards, the normal roads are horrible, but the highways are pretty much spotless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 22:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 04:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10032 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **oopsies I was so angry i spelled "buy" wrong i the title. my bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS. THIS is the most unjust, backwards, and insulting law Michigan has ever made. This is clear that the war against women is still strong in Michigan. I am ashamed to be a resident of this state.
Rape Insurance. This law sends the message that I should be anticipating rape. We are not being taught that rape is bad, we are now taught that we should anticipate it.
This will only bring about illegal abortions and harm to woman who can't afford them. 59 government officials and over 300,000 people voted for this to pass. I'd like to know how many of those people read the whole document and didn't just jump at the word "anti-abortion." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michigan now requires woman to by Rape-Insurance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 18:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 04:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two things to say: 

1. I am definitely squealing over this post. It's just too cute and I'm rooting for you!
2. I am incredibly jealous that you are able to talk to your mother about this. You are SO lucky. If only my mom would come to terms with the fact that I'm 22 and old enough to date, that would be a major load of my shoulders. You are SO SO LUCKY. YOUR MOM IS THE COOLEST.

Good luck! Can't wait for the update! AHHH ~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 23:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIM HORTONS, obvi.  they aren't the greatest, but i always  enjoy them. Fairly cheap too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 22:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  who is your insurer? I'm on Lo Loestrin Fe as well but mine always come out to $0 under blue cross blue shield. That's one of the  more well known ones that insurance companies usually will pay for. You should also definitely talk to your doctor about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 05:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly in my heart of hearts, I  think it would be fair and wonderful and humane and I want everyone to be happy and have enough money.

In my brain of  brains as a poor college student, I say this is ridiculous and unfair. Why should people who haven't even been educated get paid more than  some people who have taken the time to educate themselves. I mean a lot of entry level after college jobs don't 't even pay that much. You know what I'm saying? If they got paid that much without going to college, I feel like I'd start to think, why did i just waste all that money when I'm getting that kind of pay?

Selfish, I know :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 05:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geo-cashing!! Maybe when it's a little warmer out though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 08:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not gonna lie, I totally checked my email after I read this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 00:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm SO sorry. If I was anywhere in the vicinity, I would have grabbed some blankets, made popcorn and watched whatever movie you wanted on your couch. Also I would bring you cake. Everyone needs a little chocolate on their birthday..
FYI - i'm 22 and female and this was in  no way meant to be creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 20:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, i just want to give you a hug man.  THANK YOU for vaccinating your child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 04:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a couple newer ones that are pretty dancey:

*Hush - Miss A

*Number Nine - T-ara

*Lonely- HyorinU   I - Ailee

*Heaven- Ailee

*Give it to me  - Sistar

*Wedding Dress - Tohoshinki

*Wedding Dress  - Taeyang

*All Day I think of you -   2 PM

*Poison - Secret

*1,2,3,4 -- Lee Hi  

*Talk That - Secret

*I got a boy - girls' generation

*Spectrum - S.M. The Performance (Zedd song but in Korean) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 23:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i adored this. I've been in a kpop dead zone for a couple weeks. This revived my ears! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 22:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe i'm an idiot for asking but why is OP spending thanks giving with his ex-wife's family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 07:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "turn off the heat in your house."

Try doing that in below 0 degrees and see whether you can stand it before bailing that one out.  Large Greed. Big Talk. Small Brains. Miniscule feelings of humanity and empathy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 22:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outdoor play really relieves the anxiety. Sunlight is great and fresh air never hurts! 
I also liked board games- only a little anxiety but a good way to take your mind of things.

I DON'T SUGGEST movies. Kids can zone out and we know where that goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 22:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. This gets me SOOO mad. As a sister of a child who has aspergers. I know where you come from and how, for whatever reason, these special little guys are always blamed...always the victim, always asking for it when something happens to them. NOT OK!

my advice? Exactly what the rest of these people have been saying AND get some sleep. You will think a lot better after you slept and be ready to fight the good fight! Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 02:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit, that's all I have to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
