<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6420</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR Your body needs sugar and fats to get energy from. That's why your brain "rewards" you when you're taking in foods rich in sugar and fats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To people just quickly reading this, you HAVE to see the album. It is a hundred times better than the story itself. And that was already pretty good by itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not originally my idea, but putting garlic powder adds quite a nice flavour as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, looks like I've been in the Jokes subreddit long enough. I'm starting to recognise the jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope I'm not too late.
Unless you are at a higher end restaurant, or a franchise like McDonalds (maybe, not sure on that one), you shouldn't get fried food when you are eating out. Chances are the oil has been there for weeks. Depends on your luck really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, if you squint your eyes and try to blur out details the picture starts looking like the colours in the circles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, the event is already on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the Prisoners Dilemma, sort of, if we add cheating and stealing to betraying others. If you cheat others and they don't cheat you, you end up profiting a lot while the other loses. If both of you cheat each other, you'll both end up losing more. If both of you are honest you'll not end up losing much, but you won't win much either.
Of course, reality is much more complicated. You get punished if you get caught cheating. Cheating is discouraged in most societies. Being honest is not encouraged if cheaters abound in your circles. Unlike in the Prisoners Dilemma if two people cheat each other, they might not be that bad off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Currently summer and trying to ignore a moth the size of my thumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuuuuuuuck that screws with my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Slept 6 hours and yesterday and currently in bed trying to go to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are ever in Argentina, try the Morcilla (Blood sausage) in BBQ houses. I don't know what spices and seasoning they add but it is amazing. 
Duck Blood is also quite nice, and it's a signature ingredient in Nanjing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, I really dislike that. It's like biting into one of those anise seeds that you get in curries or Chinese braised pork. I remember I tried a black jelly bean for the first time and almost spat it out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 09:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offals are actually quite delicious, though a lot of westerners are very put off by them. Liver, heart, and tongue are a bit more accepted, but things like kidneys, stomach, intestines, blood, and tendons are part of some of my favourite Chinese dishes but if I told you i was eating that a lot of people would look at me like I'm a savage or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you don't understand the concept of seasoning. If it is bland, then add more flavour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found 85% a bit sour, which put me off. And 90% was almost tasteless for me and didn't taste as smooth. But I love 60-70% dark chocolate. I like it more than milk chocolate, which I now find too sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like coconut flavour but I dislike dessicated coconut with a passion. It's one of the few things that can make me turn down a dessert (or at least consider it). However, I love coconut milk (the Chinese drink, from the juice boxes) and recently discovered that if you toast the dessicated coconut, it gets rid of the awful texture and gives it a very nice nutty flavour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, I miss Argentinian gelato so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
