<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5054</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Simulating the Pineapple Express in the half degree Community Climate System Model, CCSM4](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069476/abstract)

**Abstract**:

Atmospheric rivers are recognized as major contributors to the poleward transport of water vapor. Upon reaching land, these phenomena also play a critical role in extreme precipitation and flooding events. The Pineapple Express (PE) is defined as an atmospheric river extending out of the deep tropics and reaching the west coast of North America. Community Climate System Model (CCSM4) high-resolution ensemble simulations for the twentieth and 21st centuries are diagnosed to identify the PE. Analysis of the twentieth century simulations indicated that the CCSM4 accurately captures the spatial and temporal climatology of the PE. Analysis of the end 21st century simulations indicates a significant increase in storm duration and intensity of precipitation associated with landfall of the PE. Only a modest increase in the number of atmospheric rivers of a few percent is projected for the end of 21st century.
___


Study: [Atmospheric river landfall-latitude changes in future climate simulations](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL070470/abstract)

**Abstract**:

The latitude of landfall for atmospheric rivers (ARs) is examined in the fully coupled half-degree version of the Community Climate System Model, version 4 (CCSM4) for warm future climate simulations. Two regions are examined: U.S. West Coast/North Pacific ARs and United Kingdom/North Atlantic ARs. Changes in AR landfall-latitude reflect changes in the atmospheric steering flow. West Coast U.S. ARs are projected to push equatorward in response to the subtropical jet climate change. UK AR response is dominated by eddy-driven jets and is seasonally dependent. UK simulated AR response is modest in the winter with the largest relative changes occurring in the seasonal transition months. Precipitation associated with ARs is also projected to increase in intensity under global warming. CCSM4 projects a marked shift to higher rainfall rates for Southern California. Small to modest rainfall rates may increase for all UK latitudes, for the Pacific Northwest, and central and northern California. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists investigate how atmospheric rivers may change as climate warms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Life Cycle Greenhouse Gas Emissions from Uranium Mining and Milling in Canada](http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/acs.est.5b06072)
___

**Abstract**:

Life cycle greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions from the production of nuclear power (in g CO2e/kWh) are uncertain due partly to a paucity of data on emissions from individual phases of the nuclear fuel cycle. Here, we present the first comprehensive life cycle assessment of GHG emissions produced from the mining and milling of uranium in Canada. The study includes data from 20062013 for two uranium mine-mill operations in northern Saskatchewan (SK) and data from 19952010 for a third SK mine-mill operation. The mine-mill operations were determined to have GHG emissions intensities of 81, 64, and 34 kg CO2e/kg U3O8 at average ore grades of 0.74%, 1.54%, and 4.53% U3O8, respectively. The production-weighted average GHG emission intensity is 42 kg CO2e/kg U3O8 at an average ore grade of 3.81% U3O8. The production-weighted average GHG emission intensity drops to 24 kg CO2e/kg U3O8 when the local hydroelectric GHG emission factor (7.2 g CO2e/kWh) is substituted for the SK grid-average electricity GHG emission factor (768 g CO2e/kWh). This results in Canadian uranium mining-milling contributing only 1.1 g CO2e/kWh to total life cycle GHG emissions from the nuclear fuel cycle (0.7 g CO2e/kWh using the local hydroelectric emission factor). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite critics claims that mining and milling uranium is a hidden cost in the comparatively clean nuclear fuel cycle, extracting the radioactive material produces only a small fraction of the processs total emissions, according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Life Cycle Greenhouse Gas Emissions from Uranium Mining and Milling in Canada](http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/acs.est.5b06072)
___

**Abstract**:

Life cycle greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions from the production of nuclear power (in g CO2e/kWh) are uncertain due partly to a paucity of data on emissions from individual phases of the nuclear fuel cycle. Here, we present the first comprehensive life cycle assessment of GHG emissions produced from the mining and milling of uranium in Canada. The study includes data from 20062013 for two uranium mine-mill operations in northern Saskatchewan (SK) and data from 19952010 for a third SK mine-mill operation. The mine-mill operations were determined to have GHG emissions intensities of 81, 64, and 34 kg CO2e/kg U3O8 at average ore grades of 0.74%, 1.54%, and 4.53% U3O8, respectively. The production-weighted average GHG emission intensity is 42 kg CO2e/kg U3O8 at an average ore grade of 3.81% U3O8. The production-weighted average GHG emission intensity drops to 24 kg CO2e/kg U3O8 when the local hydroelectric GHG emission factor (7.2 g CO2e/kWh) is substituted for the SK grid-average electricity GHG emission factor (768 g CO2e/kWh). This results in Canadian uranium mining-milling contributing only 1.1 g CO2e/kWh to total life cycle GHG emissions from the nuclear fuel cycle (0.7 g CO2e/kWh using the local hydroelectric emission factor). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite critics claims that mining and milling uranium is a hidden cost in the comparatively clean nuclear fuel cycle, extracting the radioactive material produces only a small fraction of the processs total emissions, according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why We Dont Know If It Will Be Sunny Next Month But We Know Itll Be Hot All Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 09:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Prolonged California aridity linked to climate warming and Pacific sea surface temperature](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep33325)
___

**Abstract**:

California has experienced a dry 21st century capped by severe drought from 2012 through 2015 prompting questions about hydroclimatic sensitivity to anthropogenic climate change and implications for the future. We address these questions using a Holocene lake sediment record of hydrologic change from the Sierra Nevada Mountains coupled with marine sediment records from the Pacific. These data provide evidence of a persistent relationship between past climate warming, Pacific sea surface temperature (SST) shifts and centennial to millennial episodes of California aridity. The link is most evident during the thermal-maximum of the mid-Holocene (~8 to 3ka; ka = 1,000 calendar years before present) and during the Medieval Climate Anomaly (MCA) (~1ka to 0.7ka). In both cases, climate warming corresponded with cooling of the eastern tropical Pacific despite differences in the factors producing increased radiative forcing. The magnitude of prolonged eastern Pacific cooling was modest, similar to observed La Nia excursions of 1o to 2C. Given differences with current radiative forcing it remains uncertain if the Pacific will react in a similar manner in the 21st century, but should it follow apparent past behavior more intense and prolonged aridity in California would result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clues from prehistoric droughts and arid periods in California show that todays increasing greenhouse gas levels could lock the state into drought for centuries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 09:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RTs Thom Hartmann talks climate change with Leonardo DiCaprio and his upcoming documentary Before the Flood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 07:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 07:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **According to literature on 1.5C pathways , such as i.e. Rogelj et al. (2015)^36 ,worldwide CO2 emissions from energy and industry would have to reach zero around 2050 to stay within a 50% chance of returning warming to below 1.5C by 2100.** Assuming an average car lifetime of 15 years, this implies that the last ICE vehicle would have to be sold roughly in 2035. Note that the 2050 timeframe refers to global emissions; realistically speaking, this timeline would have to be shortened for developed countries, to give other regions more time to develop, along with financial support from developed to developing countries.

(1) Good luck with that

(2) Assuming an ECS of ~3C, 1.5C of warming is already locked in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero-emission vehicles need to reach a dominant market share by around 2035 for the world to meet the Paris Agreements lower warming limit of 1.5Cand even that could be too late to avoid the need for significant negative emissions, according to new analysis by the Climate Action Tracker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 07:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Sea-ice indicators of polar bear habitat](http://www.the-cryosphere.net/10/2027/2016/)
___

**Abstract**:

Nineteen subpopulations of polar bears (Ursus maritimus) are found throughout the circumpolar Arctic, and in all regions they depend on sea ice as a platform for traveling, hunting, and breeding. Therefore polar bear phenology  the cycle of biological events  is linked to the timing of sea-ice retreat in spring and advance in fall. We analyzed the dates of sea-ice retreat and advance in all 19 polar bear subpopulation regions from 1979 to 2014, using daily sea-ice concentration data from satellite passive microwave instruments. We define the dates of sea-ice retreat and advance in a region as the dates when the area of sea ice drops below a certain threshold (retreat) on its way to the summer minimum or rises above the threshold (advance) on its way to the winter maximum. The threshold is chosen to be halfway between the historical (19792014) mean September and mean March sea-ice areas. In all 19 regions there is a trend toward earlier sea-ice retreat and later sea-ice advance. Trends generally range from 3 to 9 days decade^1 in spring and from +3 to +9 days decade^1 in fall, with larger trends in the Barents Sea and central Arctic Basin. The trends are not sensitive to the threshold. We also calculated the number of days per year that the sea-ice area exceeded the threshold (termed ice-covered days) and the average sea-ice concentration from 1 June through 31 October. The number of ice-covered days is declining in all regions at the rate of 7 to 19 days decade^1 , with larger trends in the Barents Sea and central Arctic Basin. The JuneOctober sea-ice concentration is declining in all regions at rates ranging from 1 to 9 percent decade^1 . These sea-ice metrics (or indicators of habitat change) were designed to be useful for management agencies and for comparative purposes among subpopulations. We recommend that the National Climate Assessment include the timing of sea-ice retreat and advance in future reports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately access to terrestrial food is not sufficient for polar bear populations^[1](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/09/160913150503.htm) , and though there is debate on when exactly polar bears evolved^[2](http://www.cell.com/cell/abstract/S0092-8674(14\)00488-7) it's quite evident that they have managed to survive through several glacial / interglacial episodes. Perhaps they'll resort to even more food sources including [Arctic Char](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9m_Q9Ojbcmw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first study to examine dates of spring sea ice retreat and fall ice advance across polar bear habitats around the Arctic has found that sea ice decline is hitting all 19 subpopulations of polar bears in the Arctic during the spring and fall, the times of year when they're most vulnerable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 02:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately access to terrestrial food is not sufficient for polar bear populations^[1](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/09/160913150503.htm) , and though there is debate on when exactly polar bears evolved^[2](http://www.cell.com/cell/abstract/S0092-8674(14\)00488-7) it's quite evident that they have managed to survive through several glacial / interglacial episodes. Perhaps they'll resort to even more food sources including [Arctic Char](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9m_Q9Ojbcmw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Sea-ice indicators of polar bear habitat](http://www.the-cryosphere.net/10/2027/2016/)
___

**Abstract**:

Nineteen subpopulations of polar bears (Ursus maritimus) are found throughout the circumpolar Arctic, and in all regions they depend on sea ice as a platform for traveling, hunting, and breeding. Therefore polar bear phenology  the cycle of biological events  is linked to the timing of sea-ice retreat in spring and advance in fall. We analyzed the dates of sea-ice retreat and advance in all 19 polar bear subpopulation regions from 1979 to 2014, using daily sea-ice concentration data from satellite passive microwave instruments. We define the dates of sea-ice retreat and advance in a region as the dates when the area of sea ice drops below a certain threshold (retreat) on its way to the summer minimum or rises above the threshold (advance) on its way to the winter maximum. The threshold is chosen to be halfway between the historical (19792014) mean September and mean March sea-ice areas. In all 19 regions there is a trend toward earlier sea-ice retreat and later sea-ice advance. Trends generally range from 3 to 9 days decade^1 in spring and from +3 to +9 days decade^1 in fall, with larger trends in the Barents Sea and central Arctic Basin. The trends are not sensitive to the threshold. We also calculated the number of days per year that the sea-ice area exceeded the threshold (termed ice-covered days) and the average sea-ice concentration from 1 June through 31 October. The number of ice-covered days is declining in all regions at the rate of 7 to 19 days decade^1 , with larger trends in the Barents Sea and central Arctic Basin. The JuneOctober sea-ice concentration is declining in all regions at rates ranging from 1 to 9 percent decade^1 . These sea-ice metrics (or indicators of habitat change) were designed to be useful for management agencies and for comparative purposes among subpopulations. We recommend that the National Climate Assessment include the timing of sea-ice retreat and advance in future reports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first study to examine dates of spring sea ice retreat and fall ice advance across polar bear habitats around the Arctic has found that sea ice decline is hitting all 19 subpopulations of polar bears in the Arctic during the spring and fall, the times of year when they're most vulnerable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe "stopped reading" and downvoting aren't the best way of putting your message across. 

1) This isn't my message, I simply posted it because other people may find it interesting. I actually *did* stop watching it when he presented that poor attempt at fitting a trend line.

2) 'Stopped reading' was purely hyperbole, I obviously read the comment at length. However, it shows my distaste for ridiculous claims as I've already pointed out. 

3) Whom ever downvoted a) who cares b) it wasn't me, I hardly ever downvote c) downvoting / upvoting is a perfectly legitimate means by which to express approval or disapproval of the comments within a thread

waste disposal is a problem that has not been solved, and pretending that it doesn't matter is silly.

While it is certainly of concern, it's not the be-all and end-all of the nuclear discussion. For one, the amount of nuclear waste is minuscule relative to other energy source, and it doesn't necessarily have to be waste. Let's not forget about the shortage of medical isotopes either.

http://www.world-nuclear.org/information-library/nuclear-fuel-cycle/nuclear-wastes/radioactive-waste-management.aspx

What to do with nuclear waste, while problematic to some degree, should not be a debate that prevents the world from reducing its emissions when it's amongst the top global issues, if not thee most important issue of our time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [A Cold-Wet Mid-Latitude Environment on Mars during the Hesperian-Amazonian Transition: Evidence from Northern Arabia Valleys and Paleolakes](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JE005052/full)
___

**Abstract**

The growing inventory of post-Noachian fluvial valleys may represent a late, widespread episode of aqueous activity on Mars, contrary to the paradigm that fluvial activity largely ceased around the Noachian-Hesperian boundary. Fresh shallow valleys (FSVs) are widespread from ~30-45 in both hemispheres with a high concentration in northern Arabia Terra. Valleys in northern Arabia Terra characteristically start abruptly on steeper slopes and terminate in topographic depressions at elevations corresponding to model-predicted lake levels. Longer valley systems flowed into and out of chains of paleolakes. Minimum discharges based on the dimensions of the incised channel assuming medium to coarse sand-size grains ranges from 10s to 100 s m^3  s^-1 , respectively, consistent with formation via snowmelt from surface or sub-ice flows. Hydrologic calculations indicate the valleys likely formed in hundreds of years or less, and crater statistics constrain the timing of fluvial activity to between the Hesperian and mid Amazonian. Several craters with channels extending radially outward supports evidence for overflow of interior crater lakes possibly fed by groundwater. Most FSVs occur away from young impact craters which makes an association with impact processes improbable. The widespread occurrence of FSVs along with their similar morphology and shared modest state of degradation is consistent with most forming during a global interval of favorable climate, perhaps contemporaneous with alluvial fan formation in equatorial and mid-latitudes. Evidence for a snowmelt based hydrology and considerable depths of water on the landscape in Arabia supports a cold, wet and possibly habitable environment late in Martian history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New findings from NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter supports a cold, wet and possibly habitable environment much later in Martian history than previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonardo DiCaprio, Bernie Sanders, and the 100% Renewable Myth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How global warming stacks up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious why you stopped reading after "not even the Japanese can do safe nuclear plants"?

Because it implies (and I of course may be mistaken) that nuclear plants aren't safe no matter who builds them. This is simply outright false. There are currently [442](https://www.euronuclear.org/info/encyclopedia/n/nuclear-power-plant-world-wide.htm) operating nuclear reactors world wide. During the entire history a total of two have had catastrophic failures of which only chernobyl has attributed deaths directly linked to radiation exposure. If you want to shut down all nuclear reactors because of a catastrophic failure then you're also going to have to shut down every hydroelectric dam. The [Banqiao Dam](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banqiao_Dam) failure resulted in an estimated 171,000 deaths, and 11 million people losing their homes. 

Environmental activism (Greenpeace, etc) fly in the face of greater scientific committees such as the IPCC which supports rapid expansion of nuclear reactors to mitigate global climate change. The fact remains that while the end goal of reaching total renewable energy sources is ideal, the path to achieving net negative emissions cannot be achieved by the fastest path possible without the further development of nuclear energy.

at least from an environmental activism perspective, [Greenpeace, NRDC] have good reputations.

That's called the [echo chamber effect](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Echo_chamber_(media)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Primitive Solar System materials and Earth share a common initial 142Nd abundance](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v537/n7620/full/nature19351.html)
___

**Abstract**:

The early evolution of planetesimals and planets can be constrained using variations in the abundance of neodymium-142 (142Nd), which arise from the initial distribution of 142Nd within the protoplanetary disk and the radioactive decay of the short-lived samarium-146 isotope (146Sm). The apparent offset in 142Nd abundance found previously between chondritic meteorites and Earth has been interpreted either as a possible consequence of nucleosynthetic variations within the protoplanetary disk or as a function of the differentiation of Earth very early in its history. Here we report high-precision Sm and Nd stable and radiogenic isotopic compositions of four calciumaluminium-rich refractory inclusions (CAIs) from three CV-type carbonaceous chondrites, and of three whole-rock samples of unequilibrated enstatite chondrites. The CAIs, which are the first solids formed by condensation from the nebular gas, provide the best constraints for the isotopic evolution of the early Solar System. Using the mineral isochron method for individual CAIs, we find that CAIs without isotopic anomalies in Nd compared to the terrestrial composition share a 146Sm/144Sm142Nd/144Nd isotopic evolution with Earth. The average 142Nd/144Nd composition for pristine enstatite chondrites that we calculate coincides with that of the accessible silicate layers of Earth. This relationship between CAIs, enstatite chondrites and Earth can only be a result of Earth having inherited the same initial abundance of 142Nd and chondritic proportions of Sm and Nd. Consequently, 142Nd isotopic heterogeneities found in other CAIs and among chondrite groups may arise from extrasolar grains that were present in the disk and incorporated in different proportions into these planetary objects. Our finding supports a chondritic Sm/Nd ratio for the bulk silicate Earth and, as a consequence, chondritic abundances for other refractory elements. It also removes the need for a hidden reservoir or for collisional erosion scenarios to explain the 142Nd/144Nd composition of Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have now demonstrated that Earth and other planetary objects that formed in the early years of the Solar System share similar chemical origins  a finding at odds with accepted wisdom held by scientists for decades. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [A Cold-Wet Mid-Latitude Environment on Mars during the Hesperian-Amazonian Transition: Evidence from Northern Arabia Valleys and Paleolakes](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JE005052/full)
___

**Abstract**

The growing inventory of post-Noachian fluvial valleys may represent a late, widespread episode of aqueous activity on Mars, contrary to the paradigm that fluvial activity largely ceased around the Noachian-Hesperian boundary. Fresh shallow valleys (FSVs) are widespread from ~30-45 in both hemispheres with a high concentration in northern Arabia Terra. Valleys in northern Arabia Terra characteristically start abruptly on steeper slopes and terminate in topographic depressions at elevations corresponding to model-predicted lake levels. Longer valley systems flowed into and out of chains of paleolakes. Minimum discharges based on the dimensions of the incised channel assuming medium to coarse sand-size grains ranges from 10s to 100 s m^3  s^-1 , respectively, consistent with formation via snowmelt from surface or sub-ice flows. Hydrologic calculations indicate the valleys likely formed in hundreds of years or less, and crater statistics constrain the timing of fluvial activity to between the Hesperian and mid Amazonian. Several craters with channels extending radially outward supports evidence for overflow of interior crater lakes possibly fed by groundwater. Most FSVs occur away from young impact craters which makes an association with impact processes improbable. The widespread occurrence of FSVs along with their similar morphology and shared modest state of degradation is consistent with most forming during a global interval of favorable climate, perhaps contemporaneous with alluvial fan formation in equatorial and mid-latitudes. Evidence for a snowmelt based hydrology and considerable depths of water on the landscape in Arabia supports a cold, wet and possibly habitable environment late in Martian history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New findings from NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter supports a cold, wet and possibly habitable environment much later in Martian history than previously thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greenpeace... reputable environmental groups...

Almost stopped reading right there

...not even the Japanese can do safe nuclear plants.

Ok, stopped reading.

But if it makes you feel any better I also stopped watching this TED presentation after he presented the following chart: https://i.imgur.com/pMwyy5X.jpg and tried to pass off a flat trend for an increasing trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Substantial role of macroalgae in marine carbon sequestration](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/pdf/ngeo2790.pdf)
___

**Abstract**:

Vegetated coastal habitats have been identified as important carbon sinks. In contrast to angiosperm-based habitats such as seagrass meadows, salt marshes and mangroves, marine macroalgae have largely been excluded from discussions of marine carbon sinks. Macroalgae are the dominant primary producers in the coastal zone, but they typically do not grow in habitats that are considered to accumulate large stocks of organic carbon. However, the presence of macroalgal carbon in the deep sea and sediments, where it is effectively sequestered from the atmosphere, has been reported. A synthesis of these data suggests that macroalgae could represent an important source of the carbon sequestered in marine sediments and the deep ocean. We propose two main modes for the transport of macroalgae to the deep ocean and sediments: macroalgal material drifting through submarine canyons, and the sinking of negatively buoyant macroalgal detritus. A rough estimate suggests that macroalgae could sequester about 173 TgC yr^1 (with a range of 61268 TgC yr^1 ) globally. About 90% of this sequestration occurs through export to the deep sea, and the rest through burial in coastal sediments. This estimate exceeds that for carbon sequestered in angiosperm-based coastal habitats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists urge for greater protection of kelp forests as a new study shows that they remove more carbon from the atmosphere than previously thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking for a Christian perspective I believe you may wish to look at / contact [Katharine Hayhoe](http://www.cbc.ca/radio/tapestry/sharing-truths-1.3442515/how-to-talk-climate-change-with-evangelical-christians-1.3442612) as she does a great deal of work in that area, and may be able to help. 

Best of luck on your paper! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The Political Divide on Climate Change: Partisan Polarization Widens in the U.S.](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/00139157.2016.1208995) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative Media Bias Is Inflating American Climate Denial and Polarization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The Political Divide on Climate Change: Partisan Polarization Widens in the U.S.](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/00139157.2016.1208995) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative Media Bias Is Inflating American Climate Denial and Polarization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From the beginning of this election cycle in 2015 through the first six months of this year, fossil fuel industry political action committees and employees donated $37.2 million to Republicans running for federal office. In contrast, industry giving to Democrats totaled just $3.8 million. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The formation of Charons red poles from seasonally cold-trapped volatiles](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature19340.html)
___

**Abstract**:

A unique feature of Plutos large satellite Charon is its dark red northern polar cap. Similar colours on Plutos surface have been attributed to tholin-like organic macromolecules produced by energetic radiation processing of hydrocarbons. The polar location on Charon implicates the temperature extremes that result from Charons high obliquity and long seasons in the production of this material. The escape of Plutos atmosphere provides a potential feedstock for a complex chemistry. Gas from Pluto that is transiently cold-trapped and processed at Charons winter pole was proposed as an explanation for the dark coloration on the basis of an image of Charons northern hemisphere, but not modelled quantitatively. Here we report images of the southern hemisphere illuminated by Pluto-shine and also images taken during the approach phase that show the northern polar cap over a range of longitudes. We model the surface thermal environment on Charon and the supply and temporary cold-trapping of material escaping from Pluto, as well as the photolytic processing of this material into more complex and less volatile molecules while cold-trapped. The model results are consistent with the proposed mechanism for producing the observed colour pattern on Charon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have learned that Plutos moon Charon captures methane shed by the nearby dwarf planet, creating thin reddish coatings on the moons poles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Shellenberger: How fear of nuclear power is hurting the environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was that climate change? Scientists are getting faster at linking extreme weather to warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nature Geoscience | Editorial: The coming thaw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The future of Hurtigruten is hybrid: We will be able to sail on battery power and cut climate gas emissions, the cruise shipping company says about its new vessels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Mass Loss Rates of Fasting Polar Bears](http://www.journals.uchicago.edu/doi/full/10.1086/687988)
___

**Abstract**

Polar bears (Ursus maritimus) have adapted to an annual cyclic regime of feeding and fasting, which is extreme in seasonal sea ice regions of the Arctic. As a consequence of climate change, sea ice breakup has become earlier and the duration of the open-water period through which polar bears must rely on fat reserves has increased. To date, there is limited empirical data with which to evaluate the potential energetic capacity of polar bears to withstand longer fasts. We measured the incoming and outgoing mass of inactive polar bears (n = 142) that were temporarily detained by Manitoba Conservation and Water Stewardship during the open-water period near the town of Churchill, Manitoba, Canada, in 20092014. Polar bears were given access to water but not food and held for a median length of 17 d. Median mass loss rates were 1.0 kg/d, while median mass-specific loss rates were 0.5%/d, similar to other species with high adiposity and prolonged fasting capacities. Mass loss by unfed captive adult males was identical to that lost by free-ranging individuals, suggesting that terrestrial feeding contributes little to offset mass loss. The inferred metabolic rate was comparable to a basal mammalian rate, suggesting that while on land, polar bears can maintain a depressed metabolic rate to conserve energy. Finally, we estimated time to starvation for subadults and adult males for the on-land period. Results suggest that at 180 d of fasting, 56%63% of subadults and 18%24% of adult males in this study would die of starvation. Results corroborate previous assessments on the limits of polar bear capacity to withstand lengthening ice-free seasons and emphasize the greater sensitivity of subadults to changes in sea ice phenology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Land-based food not nutritionally sufficient for wild polar bears, according to new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nature Climate Change | Editorial: Global reach and engagement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Abstract**

The Arctic plays a fundamental role in the climate system and has shown significant climate change in recent decades, including the Arctic warming and decline of Arctic sea-ice extent and thickness. In contrast to the Arctic warming and reduction of Arctic sea ice, Europe, East Asia and North America have experienced anomalously cold conditions, with record snowfall during recent years. In this paper, we review current understanding of the sea-ice impacts on the Eurasian climate. Paleo, observational and modelling studies are covered to summarize several major themes, including: the variability of Arctic sea ice and its controls; the likely causes and apparent impacts of the Arctic sea-ice decline during the satellite era, as well as past and projected future impacts and trends; the links and feedback mechanisms between the Arctic sea ice and the Arctic Oscillation/North Atlantic Oscillation, the recent Eurasian cooling, winter atmospheric circulation, summer precipitation in East Asia, spring snowfall over Eurasia, East Asian winter monsoon, and midlatitude extreme weather; and the remote climate response (e.g., atmospheric circulation, air temperature) to changes in Arctic sea ice. We conclude with a brief summary and suggestions for future research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Arctic sea ice and Eurasian climate: A review (pdf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Similar estimates of temperature impacts on global wheat yield by three independent methods](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3115.html)
___

**Abstract**:

The potential impact of global temperature change on global crop yield has recently been assessed with different methods. Here we show that grid-based and point-based simulations and statistical regressions (from historic records), without deliberate adaptation or CO2 fertilization effects, produce similar estimates of temperature impact on wheat yields at global and national scales. With a 1C global temperature increase, global wheat yield is projected to decline between 4.1% and 6.4%. Projected relative temperature impacts from different methods were similar for major wheat-producing countries China, India, USA and France, but less so for Russia. Point-based and grid-based simulations, and to some extent the statistical regressions, were consistent in projecting that warmer regions are likely to suffer more yield loss with increasing temperature than cooler regions. By forming a multi-method ensemble, it was possible to quantify method uncertainty in addition to model uncertainty. This significantly improves confidence in estimates of climate impacts on global food security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After comparing multiple studies used to predict the future of global crop production, researchers have found that they all agree on one point: rising temperatures are going to be really bad for wheat production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. The asteroid belt is simply the remnants from the formation of the early solar system that never coalesced, and are unrelated to [Theia](http://science.nasa.gov/science-news/science-at-nasa/2009/09apr_theia/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to clarify, the Nice Model is nothing at all like what /u/amworkinghere babbled on about, and is actually a robust scientific theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same theory. Theia formed roughly in the same vicinity as the Earth, along one of the Sun-Earth Lagrange points^[1](http://science.nasa.gov/science-news/science-at-nasa/2009/09apr_theia/) hence the similar isotopic compositions between the Moon and Earth. Had it formed anywhere else we would see large discrepancies between the two isotopic compositions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 23:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't just the journalist. It was OP too. The study has nothing to do with whether or not it was a Mars sized impactor, but rather [the specifics of the impact itself](http://www.geologypage.com/2016/09/moon-proto-earths-mantle-relocated.html) (ie. head on collision, or glancing blow) and how the debris aggregated.

"Our K isotope result is inconsistent with the low-energy disk equilibration model, but supports the high-energy, high-angular-momentum giant impact model for the origin of the Moon." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | A Hiatus of the Greenhouse Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 23:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new hypothesis might reconcile two opposing theories that have tried to explain Mars's mysterious history for more than 40 years. The new study suggests that Mars flip-flopped between a deep-freeze climate and a habitable one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 22:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazil just ratified the Paris climate agreement. Heres why thats a really big deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 20:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 20:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Atmospheric methane isotopic record favors fossil sources flat in 1980s and 1990s with recent increase](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/09/06/1522923113)
___

**Significance**

There is no scientific consensus on the drivers of the atmospheric methane growth rate over the past three decades. Here, we report carbon and hydrogen isotopic measurements of atmospheric methane in archived air samples collected 19771998, and modeling of these with more contemporary data to infer changes in methane sources over the period 19842009. We present strong evidence that methane emissions from fossil fuel sectors were approximately constant in the 1980s and 1990s but increased significantly between 2000 and 2009. This finding challenges recent conclusions based on atmospheric ethane that fugitive fossil fuel emissions fell during much of this period. Emissions from other anthropogenic sources also increased, but were partially offset by reductions in wetland and fire emissions.

**Abstract**

Observations of atmospheric methane (CH4) since the late 1970s and measurements of CH4 trapped in ice and snow reveal a meteoric rise in concentration during much of the twentieth century. Since 1750, levels of atmospheric CH4 have more than doubled to current globally averaged concentration near 1,800 ppb. During the late 1980s and 1990s, the CH4 growth rate slowed substantially and was near or at zero between 1999 and 2006. There is no scientific consensus on the drivers of this slowdown. Here, we report measurements of the stable isotopic composition of atmospheric CH4 (13C/12C and D/H) from a rare air archive dating from 1977 to 1998. Together with more modern records of isotopic atmospheric CH4, we performed a time-dependent retrieval of methane fluxes spanning 25 y (19842009) using a 3D chemical transport model. This inversion results in a 24 [18, 27] Tg y^1 CH4 increase in fugitive fossil fuel emissions since 1984 with most of this growth occurring after year 2000. This result is consistent with some bottom-up emissions inventories but not with recent estimates based on atmospheric ethane. In fact, when forced with decreasing emissions from fossil fuel sources our inversion estimates unreasonably high emissions in other sources. Further, the inversion estimates a decrease in biomass-burning emissions that could explain falling ethane abundance. A range of sensitivity tests suggests that these results are robust.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fugitive fossil fuel methane emissions have increased since the 1980s by an average of about 24 megatons per year with much of this growth occurring since the year 2000. At the same time, methane emissions from wetlands, rice cultivation and biomass burning have fallen, new study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 20:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Code Red: Unravelling the myth of a "carbon budget" for 1.5C </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 21:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Understanding Sea Level Rise, p4: ice sheet dynamics and (13) melting feedbacks  a background to 21st century SLR acceleration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 21:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 11:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very fair and reasonable assessment by all accounts, and one I don't disagree with entirely. My only disagreement is what exactly Hickel is trying to convey, but even there I remain uncertain, and while I lean slightly in favor of little or no bias I'm certainly open to your position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 11:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a while since I last visited the topic so please forgive me if I don't recall the majority of criticisms towards it. That being said I can recall a couple.

1) Cowspiracy pulls a lot of their information from a 2006 UN FAO study, "Tackling Climate Change Through Livestock: a global assessment of emissions and mitigation opportunities." The film was released in 2014 and given the wide criticisms of the 2006 study the UN actually released a revised revision in 2013. Why they insisted in reporting values from the 2006 report instead of the 2013 revised report when the film was released in 2014 is anyone's guess. Note too that the 2013 report is about reducing GHG emissions through better management, and doesn't suggest people stop eating meat. 

2) They cherry picked their facts, in some instances having questionable sources, in order to custom tailor their message. For example they state the following two 'facts': 

a) Livestock and their byproducts account for at least 32,000 million tons of carbon dioxide (CO2) per year, or 51% of all worldwide greenhouse gas emissions.     

and 

b) US Methane emissions from livestock and natural gas are nearly equal.

(a) uses questionable sources, and is actually incorrect while (b) uses a credible source and is correct (though they purposely leave out that CH4 emissions from industry remain the larger contributor and not agriculture). However, values for CO2 emissions are also available from the source they used for (b)  - the EPA -  which states that industry is the largest emissions source of CO2 globally, and emissions from agriculture, forestry and land use account for [~24%](https://www.epa.gov/ghgemissions/global-greenhouse-gas-emissions-data) of global CO2 emissions, not the 51% they claim. So why did they use the a credible source for claim (b) and opt to not use the same source for claim (a) when the information is so readily available? Cherry picking facts is generally a red flag of an agenda driven bias. Furthermore, with the boom in unconventional shale gas production across much of North America and better estimates of emissions on CH4 relating to the industry it's very likely that agricultural emissions make up far less than initially reported. 

Of course there are other claims as well, and misleading statements, but I don't have the time to do *all* the foot work. Hopefully I've demonstrated why Cowspiracy should not be viewed as unbiased, or entirely trust worthy, and one should refer to more credible sources such as those I've already mentioned such as the IPCC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Severe turbulence, which recently forced the emergency landing of a transatlantic flight, is on the rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 10:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 01:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  have these people not seen the documentary Cowspiracy?

That documentary is highly bias, and as such, I would not recommend it. It uses hyperbole and misleading claims in order to form a persuasive argument. The way to inform people is not by misleading or exaggerating 'facts.' 

The best information available can be found here: https://www.ipcc.ch/report/ar5/

Stopping the consumption of meat is not the answer. Proper land use and feed management, enforcement of regulations, reducing overall consumption, and changing the type (ie. less beef, more fish and chicken or other types) of meat are far more pragmatic approaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, the OP (original poster), did not write this article; however, the author [Jason Hickel](https://www.theguardian.com/profile/jason-hickel) did. 

I'd be just as cautious to write this article off as I would to take it as gospel. 

... dismissing other solutions to carbon sequestration

And rightly so. There are currently no methods of CCS that can be scaled such that they actually have a significant impact on CO2 emissions. At the lower end, Hickel (not OP - ie. me) suggests 3-15% which is well beyond anything developed thus far relating to CSS.

By masquerading as exposition of reliable scientific consensus...

Hickel didn't do that though. He clearly stated that the study was not yet peer reviewed and the title itself does not lean in favor of any scientific certainty using the following, "*might be*." (it's also why I posted it here, and not under /r/science )

There is a reason to be skeptical of silver bullets for complex, multifaceted global issues.

Hickel is not suggesting you drop every possible solution to solving our current scenario, and he does give reason in the article to be skeptical, stating that it's not yet peer-reviewed. On the other hand, his underlying message is correct based purely on the other two studies he links to - that is that better soil management can play a significant role in mitigating anthropogenic global warming. 

In my view, Hickel is simply saying, 'Hey, look at this, it's worth considering and taking a closer look at.' And, to that effect he's absolutely correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists are closely monitoring a key current in the North Atlantic to see if rising sea temperatures and increased freshwater from melting ice are altering the ocean conveyor belt  a vast oceanic stream that plays a major role in the global climate system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our best shot at cooling the planet might be right under our feet: Studies suggest that regenerating soil by turning our backs on industrial farming holds the key to tackling climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 11:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our best shot at cooling the planet might be right under our feet: Studies suggest that regenerating soil by turning our backs on industrial farming holds the key to tackling climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 11:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Social and economic impacts of climate](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6304/aad9837)
___

**BACKGROUND**

For centuries, thinkers have considered whether and how climatic conditions influence the nature of societies and the performance of economies. A multidisciplinary renaissance of quantitative empirical research has begun to illuminate key linkages in the coupling of these complex natural and human systems, uncovering notable effects of climate on health, agriculture, economics, conflict, migration, and demographics. 

**ADVANCES**

Past scholars of climate-society interactions were limited to theorizing on the basis of anecdotal evidence; advances in computing, data availability, and study design now allow researchers to draw generalizable causal inferences tying climatic events to social outcomes. This endeavor has demonstrated that a range of climate factors have substantial influence on societies and economies, both past and present, with important implications for the future.

Temperature, in particular, exerts remarkable influence over human systems at many social scales; heat induces mortality, has lasting impact on fetuses and infants, and incites aggression and violence while lowering human productivity. High temperatures also damage crops, inflate electricity demand, and may trigger population movements within and across national borders. Tropical cyclones cause mortality, damage assets, and reduce economic output for long periods. Precipitation extremes harm economies and populations predominately in agriculturally dependent settings. These effects are often quantitatively substantial; for example, we compute that temperature depresses current U.S. maize yields roughly 48%, warming trends since 1980 elevated conflict risk in Africa by 11%, and future warming may slow global economic growth rates by 0.28 percentage points year^1.

Much research aims to forecast impacts of future climate change, but we point out that society may also benefit from attending to ongoing impacts of climate in the present, because current climatic conditions impose economic and social burdens on populations today that rival in magnitude the projected end-of-century impacts of climate change. For instance, we calculate that current temperature climatologies slow global economic growth roughly 0.25 percentage points year^1 , comparable to the additional slowing of 0.28 percentage points year^1 projected from future warming.

Both current and future losses can theoretically be avoided if populations adapt to fully insulate themselves from the climatewhy this has not already occurred everywhere remains a critical open question. For example, clear patterns of adaptation in health impacts and in response to tropical cyclones contrast strongly with limited adaptation in agricultural and macroeconomic responses to temperature. Although some theories suggest these various levels of adaptation ought to be economically optimal, in the sense that costs of additional adaptive actions should exactly balance the benefits of avoided climate-related losses, there is no evidence that allows us to determine how closely observed adaptation gaps reflect optimal investments or constrained suboptimal adaptation that should be addressed through policy. 

**OUTLOOK**

Recent findings provide insight into the historical evolution of the global economy; they should inform how we respond to modern climatic conditions, and they can guide how we understand the consequences of future climate changes. Although climate is clearly not the only factor that affects social and economic outcomes, new quantitative measurements reveal that it is a major factor, often with first-order consequences. Research over the coming decade will seek to understand the numerous mechanisms that drive these effects, with the hope that policy may interfere with the most damaging pathways of influence.

Both current and future generations will benefit from near-term investigations. Cracking the code on when, where, and why adaptation is or is not successful will generate major social benefits today and in the future. In addition, calculations used to design global climate change policies require as input damage functions that describe how social and economic losses accrue under different climatic conditions, essential elements that now can (and should) be calibrated to real-world relationships. Designing effective, efficient, and fair policies to manage anthropogenic climate change requires that we possess a quantitative grasp of how different investments today may affect economic and social possibilities in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find climate change already playing major roles. For example, they found that temperature depresses current U.S. maize yields by ~48%, warming since 1980 elevated conflict risk in Africa by ~11%, and future warming may slow global economic growth rates by ~0.28 percentage points per year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Social and economic impacts of climate](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6304/aad9837)
___

**BACKGROUND**

For centuries, thinkers have considered whether and how climatic conditions influence the nature of societies and the performance of economies. A multidisciplinary renaissance of quantitative empirical research has begun to illuminate key linkages in the coupling of these complex natural and human systems, uncovering notable effects of climate on health, agriculture, economics, conflict, migration, and demographics. 

**ADVANCES**

Past scholars of climate-society interactions were limited to theorizing on the basis of anecdotal evidence; advances in computing, data availability, and study design now allow researchers to draw generalizable causal inferences tying climatic events to social outcomes. This endeavor has demonstrated that a range of climate factors have substantial influence on societies and economies, both past and present, with important implications for the future.

Temperature, in particular, exerts remarkable influence over human systems at many social scales; heat induces mortality, has lasting impact on fetuses and infants, and incites aggression and violence while lowering human productivity. High temperatures also damage crops, inflate electricity demand, and may trigger population movements within and across national borders. Tropical cyclones cause mortality, damage assets, and reduce economic output for long periods. Precipitation extremes harm economies and populations predominately in agriculturally dependent settings. These effects are often quantitatively substantial; for example, we compute that temperature depresses current U.S. maize yields roughly 48%, warming trends since 1980 elevated conflict risk in Africa by 11%, and future warming may slow global economic growth rates by 0.28 percentage points year^1.

Much research aims to forecast impacts of future climate change, but we point out that society may also benefit from attending to ongoing impacts of climate in the present, because current climatic conditions impose economic and social burdens on populations today that rival in magnitude the projected end-of-century impacts of climate change. For instance, we calculate that current temperature climatologies slow global economic growth roughly 0.25 percentage points year^1 , comparable to the additional slowing of 0.28 percentage points year^1 projected from future warming.

Both current and future losses can theoretically be avoided if populations adapt to fully insulate themselves from the climatewhy this has not already occurred everywhere remains a critical open question. For example, clear patterns of adaptation in health impacts and in response to tropical cyclones contrast strongly with limited adaptation in agricultural and macroeconomic responses to temperature. Although some theories suggest these various levels of adaptation ought to be economically optimal, in the sense that costs of additional adaptive actions should exactly balance the benefits of avoided climate-related losses, there is no evidence that allows us to determine how closely observed adaptation gaps reflect optimal investments or constrained suboptimal adaptation that should be addressed through policy. 

**OUTLOOK**

Recent findings provide insight into the historical evolution of the global economy; they should inform how we respond to modern climatic conditions, and they can guide how we understand the consequences of future climate changes. Although climate is clearly not the only factor that affects social and economic outcomes, new quantitative measurements reveal that it is a major factor, often with first-order consequences. Research over the coming decade will seek to understand the numerous mechanisms that drive these effects, with the hope that policy may interfere with the most damaging pathways of influence.

Both current and future generations will benefit from near-term investigations. Cracking the code on when, where, and why adaptation is or is not successful will generate major social benefits today and in the future. In addition, calculations used to design global climate change policies require as input damage functions that describe how social and economic losses accrue under different climatic conditions, essential elements that now can (and should) be calibrated to real-world relationships. Designing effective, efficient, and fair policies to manage anthropogenic climate change requires that we possess a quantitative grasp of how different investments today may affect economic and social possibilities in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find climate change already playing major roles. For example, they found that temperature depresses current U.S. maize yields by ~48%, warming since 1980 elevated conflict risk in Africa by ~11%, and future warming may slow global economic growth rates by ~0.28 percentage points per year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Sub-lethal effects of dietary neonicotinoid insecticide exposure on honey bee queen fecundity and colony development](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep32108)
___

**Abstract**:

Many factors can negatively affect honey bee (Apis mellifera L.) health including the pervasive use of systemic neonicotinoid insecticides. Through direct consumption of contaminated nectar and pollen from treated plants, neonicotinoids can affect foraging, learning, and memory in worker bees. Less well studied are the potential effects of neonicotinoids on queen bees, which may be exposed indirectly through trophallaxis, or food-sharing. To assess effects on queen productivity, small colonies of different sizes (1500, 3000, and 7000 bees) were fed imidacloprid (0, 10, 20, 50, and 100ppb) in syrup for three weeks. We found adverse effects of imidacloprid on queens (egg-laying and locomotor activity), worker bees (foraging and hygienic activities), and colony development (brood production and pollen stores) in all treated colonies. Some effects were less evident as colony size increased, suggesting that larger colony populations may act as a buffer to pesticide exposure. This study is the first to show adverse effects of imidacloprid on queen bee fecundity and behavior and improves our understanding of how neonicotinoids may impair short-term colony functioning. These data indicate that risk-mitigation efforts should focus on reducing neonicotinoid exposure in the early spring when colonies are smallest and queens are most vulnerable to exposure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has found neonicotinoids, the worlds most commonly used insecticide, cause queen honeybees to lay as much as two-thirds fewer eggs, jeopardizing the health and stability of entire bee colonies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Connecting Climate Model Projections of Global Temperature Change with the Real World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlantic Hurricane Season is Seeing More Major Storms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 September 2016 | ENSO Alert System Status: Not Active | Synopsis: ENSO-Neutral conditions are slightly favored (between 55-60%) during the upcoming Northern Hemisphere fall and winter 2016-17. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 11:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonsense. We *know* that conditions could range from [RCP2.6 to RCP8.5](https://andthentheresphysics.files.wordpress.com/2015/07/rcps.jpg). These concentration pathways were evaluated:

One clear finding from the data is that increased levels of CO2 did not increase grass production. Instead, the amount of grass grown at sites with elevated CO2 remained flat, even at CO2 levels almost twice the present atmospheric concentration^[1](http://phys.org/news/2016-09-warmer-wetter-climate-impair-california.html)

From this experiment we *know* how certain plants will grow given certain conditions, and we *know* what range those conditions will take.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes necessarily. Your use of 'ratify' is incorrect. 

By providing you with the definition I was hoping you could have easily been able to put two and two together from the title of the article, or the abstract. 

NPP is a measure of plant growth. Therefore the significance of NPP in the context of this article is exactly as the title states. That is to say that NPP (the rate at which plants grow) is reduced under post 2050 climate conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No (please read the article). The study ran a number of field experiments, not models, under various conditions altering four aspects of climate changetemperature, precipitation, atmospheric composition (carbon dioxide concentration), and atmospheric deposition (nitrogen pollution). With all possible combinations of ambient and elevated levels of the four factors, the study explored ecosystem responses to sixteen different possible futures.^[1](http://healthmedicinet.com/i/grassland-tuned-to-present-suffers-in-a-warmer-future/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to have clarify your statement. As it stands, it doesn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Net primary productivity (NPP) is defined as the net flux of carbon from the atmosphere into green plants per unit time. NPP refers to a rate process, i.e., the amount of vegetable matter produced (net primary production) per day, week, or year.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Nonlinear, interacting responses to climate limit grassland production under global change](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/30/1606734113.abstract)
___

**Significance**:

Global environmental change involves many factors that occur simultaneously, yet they are usually studied in isolation. Here we report a long-term global change experiment that subjected California grassland to multiple individual and simultaneous changes in temperature, precipitation, carbon dioxide, and nitrogen. Our analysis revealed nonlinear and interactive effects of temperature and precipitation on grassland net primary production (NPP), which defined a ridge-shaped NPP response surface to these two variables. Added nitrogen raised the peak of the NPP response surface, and added CO2 shifted the peak to lower temperatures. Our approach was validated by tests showing an absence of progressive effects over the years. In other ecosystems, our approach may be similarly powerful for probing the effects of multifactor global change.

**Abstract**:

Global changes in climate, atmospheric composition, and pollutants are altering ecosystems and the goods and services they provide. Among approaches for predicting ecosystem responses, long-term observations and manipulative experiments can be powerful approaches for resolving single-factor and interactive effects of global changes on key metrics such as net primary production (NPP). Here we combine both approaches, developing multidimensional response surfaces for NPP based on the longest-running, best-replicated, most-multifactor global-change experiment at the ecosystem scalea 17-y study of California grassland exposed to full-factorial warming, added precipitation, elevated CO2, and nitrogen deposition. Single-factor and interactive effects were not time-dependent, enabling us to analyze each year as a separate realization of the experiment and extract NPP as a continuous function of global-change factors. We found a ridge-shaped response surface in which NPP is humped (unimodal) in response to temperature and precipitation when CO2 and nitrogen are ambient, with peak NPP rising under elevated CO2 or nitrogen but also shifting to lower temperatures. Our results suggest that future climate change will push this ecosystem away from conditions that maximize NPP, but with large year-to-year variability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the worlds longest-running, most comprehensive climate change experiments has produced some surprising results. The 17 year study on more than 1 million plants showed poorer plant growth under post 2050 climate conditions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Nonlinear, interacting responses to climate limit grassland production under global change](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/30/1606734113.abstract)
___

**Significance**:

*Global environmental change involves many factors that occur simultaneously, yet they are usually studied in isolation. Here we report a long-term global change experiment that subjected California grassland to multiple individual and simultaneous changes in temperature, precipitation, carbon dioxide, and nitrogen. Our analysis revealed nonlinear and interactive effects of temperature and precipitation on grassland net primary production (NPP), which defined a ridge-shaped NPP response surface to these two variables. Added nitrogen raised the peak of the NPP response surface, and added CO2 shifted the peak to lower temperatures. Our approach was validated by tests showing an absence of progressive effects over the years. In other ecosystems, our approach may be similarly powerful for probing the effects of multifactor global change.*

**Abstract**:

*Global changes in climate, atmospheric composition, and pollutants are altering ecosystems and the goods and services they provide. Among approaches for predicting ecosystem responses, long-term observations and manipulative experiments can be powerful approaches for resolving single-factor and interactive effects of global changes on key metrics such as net primary production (NPP). Here we combine both approaches, developing multidimensional response surfaces for NPP based on the longest-running, best-replicated, most-multifactor global-change experiment at the ecosystem scalea 17-y study of California grassland exposed to full-factorial warming, added precipitation, elevated CO2, and nitrogen deposition. Single-factor and interactive effects were not time-dependent, enabling us to analyze each year as a separate realization of the experiment and extract NPP as a continuous function of global-change factors. We found a ridge-shaped response surface in which NPP is humped (unimodal) in response to temperature and precipitation when CO2 and nitrogen are ambient, with peak NPP rising under elevated CO2 or nitrogen but also shifting to lower temperatures. Our results suggest that future climate change will push this ecosystem away from conditions that maximize NPP, but with large year-to-year variability.*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the worlds longest-running, most comprehensive climate change experiments has produced some surprising results. The 17 year study on more than 1 million plants showed poorer plant growth under post 2050 climate conditions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Sensitivity of Satellite-Derived Tropospheric Temperature Trends to the Diurnal Cycle Adjustment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... I cant seem to find the full article to read.

For future reference... top right of the page where the abstract is posted it says 'download.' Click pdf or xml. 

http://www.hydrol-earth-syst-sci-discuss.net/hess-2016-448/hess-2016-448.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [North Atlantic ocean circulation and abrupt climate change during the last glaciation](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2016/06/29/science.aaf5529)
___

**Abstract**:

*The last ice age was characterized by rapid and hemispherically asynchronous climate oscillations, whose origin remains unresolved. Variations in oceanic meridional heat transport may contribute to these repeated climate changes, which were most pronounced during marine isotope stage 3 (MIS3), the glacial interval twenty-five to sixty thousand years ago. We examined climate and ocean circulation proxies throughout this interval at high resolution in a deep North Atlantic sediment core, combining the kinematic tracer Pa/Th with the deep water-mass tracer, 13CBF. These indicators suggest reduced Atlantic overturning circulation during every cool northern stadial, with the greatest reductions during episodic Hudson Strait iceberg discharges, while sharp northern warming followed reinvigorated overturning. These results provide direct evidence for the ocean's persistent, central role in abrupt glacial climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocean Circulation Implicated in Past Abrupt Climate Changes: Circulation Slowed with Every Cooling During Last Ice Age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Anthropogenic impact on Antarctic surface mass balance, currently masked by natural variability, to emerge by mid-century](http://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/9/094001)
___

**Abstract**:

*Global and regional climate models robustly simulate increases in Antarctic surface mass balance (SMB) during the twentieth and twenty-first centuries in response to anthropogenic global warming. Despite these robust model projections, however, observations indicate that there has been no significant change in Antarctic SMB in recent decades. We show that this apparent discrepancy between models and observations can be explained by the fact that the anthropogenic climate change signal during the second half of the twentieth century is small compared to the noise associated with natural climate variability. Using an ensemble of 35 global coupled climate models to separate signal and noise, we find that the forced SMB increase due to global warming in recent decades is unlikely to be detectable as a result of large natural SMB variability. However, our analysis reveals that the anthropogenic impact on Antarctic SMB is very likely to emerge from natural variability by the middle of the current century, thus mitigating future increases in global sea level.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By Mid-Century, More Antarctic Snowfall May Help Offset Sea-Level Rise: Increasing Precipitation Masked by Natural VariabilityFor Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate scientists are people too! by Warm Regards Podcast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related Material(s)
___

- [Flood watch: putting Louisiana's epic floods in a climate context](https://soundcloud.com/warmregardspodcast/flood-watch-putting-louisianas-epic-floods-in-a-climate-context) (podcast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related Material(s):
___

- [Human and nature dynamics (HANDY): Modeling inequality and use of resources in the collapse or sustainability of societies](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0921800914000615) (open access) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Rapid attribution of the August 2016 flood-inducing extreme precipitation in south Louisiana to climate change](http://www.hydrol-earth-syst-sci-discuss.net/hess-2016-448/)
___

**Abstract**:

*A stationary low pressure system and elevated levels of precipitable water provided a nearly continuous source of precipitation over Louisiana, United States (U.S.) starting around 10 August, 2016. Precipitation was heaviest in the region broadly encompassing the city of Baton Rouge, with a three-day maximum found at a station in Livingston, LA (east of Baton Rouge) from 1214 August, 2016 (648.3 mm, 25.5 inches). The intense precipitation was followed by inland flash flooding and river flooding and in subsequent days produced additional backwater flooding. On 16 August, Louisiana officials reported that 30,000 people had been rescued, nearly 10,600 people had slept in shelters on the night of 14 August, and at least 60,600 homes had been impacted to varying degrees. As of 17 August, the floods were reported to have killed at least thirteen people. As the disaster was unfolding, the Red Cross called the flooding the worst natural disaster in the U.S. since Super Storm Sandy made landfall in New Jersey on 24 October, 2012. Before the floodwaters had receded, the media began questioning whether this extreme event was caused by anthropogenic climate change. To provide the necessary analysis to understand the potential role of anthropogenic climate change, a rapid attribution analysis was launched in real-time using the best readily available observational data and high-resolution global climate model simulations.*

*The objective of this study is to show the possibility of performing rapid attribution studies when both observational and model data, and analysis methods are readily available upon the start. It is the authors aspiration that the results be used to guide further studies of the devastating precipitation and flooding event. Here we present a first estimate of how anthropogenic climate change has affected the likelihood of a comparable extreme precipitation event in the Central U.S. Gulf Coast. While the flooding event of interest triggering this study occurred in south Louisiana, for the purposes of our analysis, we have defined an extreme precipitation event by taking the spatial maximum of annual 3-day inland maximum precipitation over the region: 2931 N, 8595 W, which we refer to as the Central U.S. Gulf Coast. Using observational data, we find that the observed local return time of the 1214 August precipitation event in 2016 is about 550 years (95 % confidence interval (C.I.): 4501450). The probability for an event like this to happen anywhere in the region is presently 1 in 30 years (C.I. 11110). We estimate that these probabilities and the intensity of extreme precipitation events of this return time have increased since 1900. A Central U.S. Gulf Coast extreme precipitation event has effectively become more likely in 2016 than it was in 1900. The global climate models tell a similar story, with the regional probability of 3-day extreme precipitation increasing due to anthropogenic climate change by a factor of more than a factor 1.4 in the most accurate analyses. The magnitude of the shift in probabilities is greater in the 25 km (higher resolution) climate model than in the 50 km model. The evidence for a relation to El Nio half a year earlier is equivocal, with some analyses showing a positive connection and others none.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human-caused climate change likely doubled the chances of the torrential rains that caused deadly flooding in Louisiana and damaged 60,000 homes in the state, a new study has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Rapid attribution of the August 2016 flood-inducing extreme precipitation in south Louisiana to climate change](http://www.hydrol-earth-syst-sci-discuss.net/hess-2016-448/)
___

**Abstract**:

A stationary low pressure system and elevated levels of precipitable water provided a nearly continuous source of precipitation over Louisiana, United States (U.S.) starting around 10 August, 2016. Precipitation was heaviest in the region broadly encompassing the city of Baton Rouge, with a three-day maximum found at a station in Livingston, LA (east of Baton Rouge) from 1214 August, 2016 (648.3mm, 25.5inches). The intense precipitation was followed by inland flash flooding and river flooding and in subsequent days produced additional backwater flooding. On 16 August, Louisiana officials reported that 30,000 people had been rescued, nearly 10,600 people had slept in shelters on the night of 14 August, and at least 60,600 homes had been impacted to varying degrees. As of 17 August, the floods were reported to have killed at least thirteen people. As the disaster was unfolding, the Red Cross called the flooding the worst natural disaster in the U.S. since Super Storm Sandy made landfall in New Jersey on 24 October, 2012. Before the floodwaters had receded, the media began questioning whether this extreme event was caused by anthropogenic climate change. To provide the necessary analysis to understand the potential role of anthropogenic climate change, a rapid attribution analysis was launched in real-time using the best readily available observational data and high-resolution global climate model simulations.

The objective of this study is to show the possibility of performing rapid attribution studies when both observational and model data, and analysis methods are readily available upon the start. It is the authors aspiration that the results be used to guide further studies of the devastating precipitation and flooding event. Here we present a first estimate of how anthropogenic climate change has affected the likelihood of a comparable extreme precipitation event in the Central U.S. Gulf Coast. While the flooding event of interest triggering this study occurred in south Louisiana, for the purposes of our analysis, we have defined an extreme precipitation event by taking the spatial maximum of annual 3-day inland maximum precipitation over the region: 2931N, 8595W, which we refer to as the Central U.S. Gulf Coast. Using observational data, we find that the observed local return time of the 1214 August precipitation event in 2016 is about 550 years (95% confidence interval (C.I.): 4501450). The probability for an event like this to happen anywhere in the region is presently 1 in 30 years (C.I. 11110). We estimate that these probabilities and the intensity of extreme precipitation events of this return time have increased since 1900. A Central U.S. Gulf Coast extreme precipitation event has effectively become more likely in 2016 than it was in 1900. The global climate models tell a similar story, with the regional probability of 3-day extreme precipitation increasing due to anthropogenic climate change by a factor of more than a factor 1.4 in the most accurate analyses. The magnitude of the shift in probabilities is greater in the 25km (higher resolution) climate model than in the 50km model. The evidence for a relation to El Nio half a year earlier is equivocal, with some analyses showing a positive connection and others none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human-caused climate change likely doubled the chances of the torrential rains that caused deadly flooding in Louisiana and damaged 60,000 homes in the state, a new study has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In The Oracle of Oil, Mason Inman examines the history of "peak oil" and the planet's ever-diminishing resources through the story of M. King Hubbert, the geologist who first realized oil's days were ultimately numbered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Global climate forcing of aerosols embodied in international trade](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2798.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*International trade separates regions consuming goods and services from regions where goods and related aerosol pollution are produced. Yet the role of trade in aerosol climate forcing attributed to different regions has never been quantified. Here, we contrast the direct radiative forcing of aerosols related to regions consumption of goods and services against the forcing due to emissions produced in each region. Aerosols assessed include black carbon, primary organic aerosol, and secondary inorganic aerosols, including sulfate, nitrate and ammonium. We find that global aerosol radiative forcing due to emissions produced in East Asia is much stronger than the forcing related to goods and services ultimately consumed in that region because of its large net export of emissions-intensive goods. The opposite is true for net importers such as Western Europe and North America: global radiative forcing related to consumption is much greater than the forcing due to emissions produced in these regions. Overall, trade is associated with a shift of radiative forcing from net importing to net exporting regions. Compared to greenhouse gases such as carbon dioxide, the short atmospheric lifetimes of aerosols cause large localized differences between consumption- and production-related radiative forcing. International efforts to reduce emissions in the exporting countries will help alleviate trade-related climate and health impacts of aerosols while lowering global emissions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aerosol emissions in East Asia driven by consumption in developed countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's robotic spacecraft Osiris-Rex, to be launched Thursday, will chase down the asteroid Bennu and then, hopefully, return with a sample from its surface. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These stunning new Alaska maps could transform our understanding of the Arctic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Sea ice decline and 21st century trans-Arctic shipping routes](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069315/full)
___

**Abstract**:

The observed decline in Arctic sea ice is projected to continue, opening shorter trade routes across the Arctic Ocean, with potentially global economic implications. Here we quantify, using CMIP5 global climate model simulations calibrated to remove spatial biases, how projected sea ice loss might increase opportunities for Arctic-transit shipping. By mid-century for standard Open Water vessels, the frequency of navigable periods doubles, with routes across the central Arctic becoming available. A sea ice  ship speed relationship is used to show that European routes to Asia typically become 10 days faster via the Arctic than alternatives by mid-century, and 13 days faster by late-century, while North American routes become 4 days faster. Future greenhouse-gas emissions have a larger impact by late-century; the shipping season reaching 4-8 months in RCP8.5, double that of RCP2.6, both with substantial inter-annual variability. Moderately ice-strengthened vessels likely enable Arctic transits for 10-12 months by late-century.
___

Related Material(s):

- A guest article by Dr Nathanael Melia, a post-doctoral research assistant in the Department of Meteorology at the University of Reading. [What will sea ice loss mean for Arctic shipping?](http://www.carbonbrief.org/guest-post-what-will-sea-ice-loss-mean-for-arctic-shipping)

- A guest post by Dr Alexandra Jahn, Assistant Professor in the Department of Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences and Fellow at the Institute of Arctic and Alpine Research at the University of Colorado. [How predictable is the first ice-free Arctic summer?](https://www.carbonbrief.org/guest-post-predictable-first-ice-free-arctic-summer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shipping routes across the Arctic are going to open up significantly this century even with a best-case reduction in CO2 emissions, a new study suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Sea ice decline and 21st century trans-Arctic shipping routes](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069315/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

The observed decline in Arctic sea ice is projected to continue, opening shorter trade routes across the Arctic Ocean, with potentially global economic implications. Here we quantify, using CMIP5 global climate model simulations calibrated to remove spatial biases, how projected sea ice loss might increase opportunities for Arctic-transit shipping. By mid-century for standard Open Water vessels, the frequency of navigable periods doubles, with routes across the central Arctic becoming available. A sea ice  ship speed relationship is used to show that European routes to Asia typically become 10 days faster via the Arctic than alternatives by mid-century, and 13 days faster by late-century, while North American routes become 4 days faster. Future greenhouse-gas emissions have a larger impact by late-century; the shipping season reaching 4-8 months in RCP8.5, double that of RCP2.6, both with substantial inter-annual variability. Moderately ice-strengthened vessels likely enable Arctic transits for 10-12 months by late-century.

Related Material(s):

- A guest article by Dr Nathanael Melia, lead author of the study above, and a post-doctoral research assistant in the Department of Meteorology at the University of Reading. [What will sea ice loss mean for Arctic shipping?](http://www.carbonbrief.org/guest-post-what-will-sea-ice-loss-mean-for-arctic-shipping)

- A guest post by Dr Alexandra Jahn, Assistant Professor in the Department of Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences and Fellow at the Institute of Arctic and Alpine Research at the University of Colorado. [How predictable is the first ice-free Arctic summer?](https://www.carbonbrief.org/guest-post-predictable-first-ice-free-arctic-summer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shipping routes across the Arctic are going to open up significantly this century even with a best-case reduction in CO2 emissions, a new study suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Ocean warming modulates the effects of acidification on Emiliania huxleyi calcification and sinking](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/lno.10292/abstract;jsessionid=9057F2B799C7CD4C62576C99280B8222.f02t04)
___

**Abstract**:

*Ongoing ocean warming and acidification are tied to the rapid accumulation of human-induced carbon dioxide (CO2) in the atmosphere and subsequent uptake of heat and CO2 by the surface ocean. These processes are expected to drive large changes in marine ecosystems. While numerous studies have examined the effects of ocean acidification on coccolithophores, less is known on their combined effect. In this study, we investigate temperature modulation of the carbonate chemistry sensitivity of the coccolithophore Emiliania huxleyi (RCC1827 from the Western Mediterranean) in a culture experiment. We analyzed the responses of coccolith morphology, particulate inorganic and organic carbon production, and sinking rate of individual cells. E. huxleyi was exposed to three CO2 levels (ca. 400 atm, 900 atm, and 1400 atm) at 15C and 20C. Temperature adds to the negative effect of increasing pCO2 on coccolith morphology, suggesting that a significant number of E. huxleyi strains might suffer from a temperature increase, hampering their evolutionary success. Temperature amplified the positive effect of increasing pCO2 on organic carbon production, while modulating the response of calcification rates, indicating that the response to increasing pCO2 must be taken with caution depending on the temperature range studied. Sinking rates were positively correlated with temperature, whereas pCO2 did not have any effect. The combined effect of carbonate chemistry and temperature on the E. huxleyi ratio between particulate inorganic carbon and particulate organic carbon (PIC/POC) might also lower the sinking rate of aggregates. In conclusion, in a warmer and more acidified ocean, individual coccolithophore cells might sink faster, while aggregates might sink slower.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocean warming and acidification impact on coccolithophore Emiliania huxleyi and reduce its ability to sequester atmospheric CO2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The anomalous change in the QBO in 20152016](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL070373/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*The quasi-biennial oscillation (QBO) is a tropical lower stratospheric, downward propagating zonal wind variation, with an average period of ~28months. The QBO has been constantly documented since 1953. Here we describe the evolution of the QBO during the Northern Hemisphere winter of 20152016 using radiosonde observations and meteorological reanalyses. Normally, the QBO would show a steady downward propagation of the westerly phase. In 20152016, there was an anomalous upward displacement of this westerly phase from ~30hPa to 15hPa. These westerlies impinge on or cutoff the normal downward propagation of the easterly phase. In addition, easterly winds develop at 40hPa. Comparisons to tropical wind statistics for the 1953 to present record demonstrate that this 20152016 QBO disruption is unprecedented.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The anomalous change in the quasi-biennial oscillation (QBO) in 20152016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Intensification of landfalling typhoons over the northwest Pacific since the late 1970s](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2792.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Intensity changes in landfalling typhoons are of great concern to East and Southeast Asian countries. Regional changes in typhoon intensity, however, are poorly known owing to inconsistencies among different data sets. Here, we apply cluster analysis to bias-corrected data and show that, over the past 37 years, typhoons that strike East and Southeast Asia have intensified by 1215%, with the proportion of storms of categories 4 and 5 having doubled or even tripled. In contrast, typhoons that stay over the open ocean have experienced only modest changes. These regional changes are consistent between operational data sets. To identify the physical mechanisms, we decompose intensity changes into contributions from intensification rate and intensification duration. We find that the increased intensity of landfalling typhoons is due to strengthened intensification rates, which in turn are tied to locally enhanced ocean surface warming on the rim of East and Southeast Asia. The projected ocean surface warming pattern under increasing greenhouse gas forcing suggests that typhoons striking eastern mainland China, Taiwan, Korea and Japan will intensify further. Given disproportionate damages by intense typhoons, this represents a heightened threat to people and properties in the region.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian typhoons becoming more intense, study finds. Over the past 37 years, typhoons that strike East and Southeast Asia have intensified by 1215%, with the proportion of storms of categories 4 and 5 having doubled or even tripled due to warmer coastal seas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Intensification of landfalling typhoons over the northwest Pacific since the late 1970s](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2792.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Intensity changes in landfalling typhoons are of great concern to East and Southeast Asian countries. Regional changes in typhoon intensity, however, are poorly known owing to inconsistencies among different data sets. Here, we apply cluster analysis to bias-corrected data and show that, over the past 37 years, typhoons that strike East and Southeast Asia have intensified by 1215%, with the proportion of storms of categories 4 and 5 having doubled or even tripled. In contrast, typhoons that stay over the open ocean have experienced only modest changes. These regional changes are consistent between operational data sets. To identify the physical mechanisms, we decompose intensity changes into contributions from intensification rate and intensification duration. We find that the increased intensity of landfalling typhoons is due to strengthened intensification rates, which in turn are tied to locally enhanced ocean surface warming on the rim of East and Southeast Asia. The projected ocean surface warming pattern under increasing greenhouse gas forcing suggests that typhoons striking eastern mainland China, Taiwan, Korea and Japan will intensify further. Given disproportionate damages by intense typhoons, this represents a heightened threat to people and properties in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian typhoons becoming more intense, study finds. Over the past 37 years, typhoons that strike East and Southeast Asia have intensified by 1215%, with the proportion of storms of categories 4 and 5 having doubled or even tripled due to warmer coastal seas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Climate Change Authority report: a dissenting view </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 18:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Misleading information on Katla eruption says Iceland Met Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 23:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Arctic fixation: Is nitrogen fixation really happening in the Arctic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moulins: Clarifying Impacts on Glacier Velocity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A number of articles are available to you regarding international agreements and their position within the scientific community. A quick search shows some articles that may be of interest to you [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/GlobalClimateChange/search?q=paris restrict_sr=on sort=relevance t=all).

In general, it's a mixed view. Some like Mann (iirc) believe such emissions targets are fully attainable, and coming to agreement on these targets is well worth the time and effort. Others, like Hansen^[1](https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2015/dec/12/james-hansen-climate-change-paris-talks-fraud), however, see COP21 as essentially useless. 

Some would argue that setting a target of 1.5C warming relative to pre-industrial times are pointless as that amount of warming may already be locked in. Whether or not 1.5C of warming relative to pre-industrial times is already locked in depends on what value we assign to the equilibrium climate sensitivity ([ECS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Climate_sensitivity)). The majority of studies show relatively broad agreement around 3C, which would mean that 1.5C warming is already locked. Should the ECS value be lower, however, then it makes it just that little bit more possible to stay below 1.5C of warming.

It's difficult to predict just how effective such talks are in general, but it is certainly reasonable to suggest that they are a) important and b) capable of having real world effects^[2](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montreal_Protocol) .   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Sharp Increase In Sunny Day Flooding: Global warming and rising seas are increasing the amount of tidal flooding on the Atlantic and Gulf Coasts. Flood levels are different from city to city, but the trends are similar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 20:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Invisible water, visible impact: groundwater use and Indian agriculture under climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Political affiliation affects adaptation to climate risks: Evidence from New York City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here We Go Again: Fossil Fuel Industry Takes a Play from Big Tobaccos Playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ANALYSIS: Wall Street Journal Opinion Section Is Chief Apologist For Exxon's Climate Change Deceit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres What to Expect From Hurricane Hermine: The storm is Floridas first hurricane in nearly 11 years, and forecasts are looking dire for the Northeast too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob DeConto and Antarctica in the climate system  Forecast: a podcast about climate science and climate scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Role of Seafloor Methane in Ancient Global Warming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Mechanistic insights into a hydrate contribution to the Paleocene-Eocene carbon cycle perturbation from coupled thermohydraulic simulations](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069676/abstract)
___
**Abstract**:

During the Paleocene-Eocene Thermal Maximum (PETM), the carbon isotopic signature (13C) of surface carbon-bearing phases decreased abruptly by at least 2.5 to 3.0. This carbon isotope excursion (CIE) has been attributed to widespread methane hydrate dissociation in response to rapid ocean warming. We ran a thermohydraulic modeling code to simulate hydrate dissociation due to ocean warming for various PETM scenarios. Our results show that hydrate dissociation in response to such warming can be rapid but suggest that methane release to the ocean is modest and delayed by hundreds to thousands of years after the onset of dissociation, limiting the potential for positive feedback from emission-induced warming. In all of our simulations at least half of the dissociated hydrate methane remains beneath the seabed, suggesting that the pre-PETM hydrate inventory needed to account for all of the CIE is at least double that required for isotopic mass balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research suggests that the release of methane from seafloor hydrates was much slower than hypothesized during a period of rapid global warming about 56 million years ago, challenging the hypothesized role of methane hydrates in the PETM. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 10:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 09:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Mechanistic insights into a hydrate contribution to the Paleocene-Eocene carbon cycle perturbation from coupled thermohydraulic simulations](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069676/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

*During the Paleocene-Eocene Thermal Maximum (PETM), the carbon isotopic signature (13C) of surface carbon-bearing phases decreased abruptly by at least 2.5 to 3.0. This carbon isotope excursion (CIE) has been attributed to widespread methane hydrate dissociation in response to rapid ocean warming. We ran a thermohydraulic modeling code to simulate hydrate dissociation due to ocean warming for various PETM scenarios. Our results show that hydrate dissociation in response to such warming can be rapid but suggest that methane release to the ocean is modest and delayed by hundreds to thousands of years after the onset of dissociation, limiting the potential for positive feedback from emission-induced warming. In all of our simulations at least half of the dissociated hydrate methane remains beneath the seabed, suggesting that the pre-PETM hydrate inventory needed to account for all of the CIE is at least double that required for isotopic mass balance.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research suggests that the release of methane from seafloor hydrates was much slower than hypothesized during a period of rapid global warming about 56 million years ago, challenging the hypothesized role of methane hydrates in the PETM. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 09:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Recent amplification of the North American winter temperature dipole](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JD025116/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*During the winters of 20132014 and 20142015, anomalously warm temperatures in western North America and anomalously cool temperatures in eastern North America resulted in substantial human and environmental impacts. Motivated by the impacts of these concurrent temperature extremes and the intrinsic atmospheric linkage between weather conditions in the western and eastern United States, we investigate the occurrence of concurrent warm-West/cool-East surface temperature anomalies, which we call the North American winter temperature dipole. We find that, historically, warm-West/cool-East dipole conditions have been associated with anomalous mid-tropospheric ridging over western North America and downstream troughing over eastern North America. We also find that the occurrence and severity of warm-West/cool-East events have increased significantly between 1980 and 2015, driven largely by an increase in the frequency with which high-amplitude ridge-trough wave patterns result in simultaneous severe temperature conditions in both the West and East. Using a large single-model ensemble of climate simulations, we show that the observed positive trend in the warm-West/cool-East events is attributable to historical anthropogenic emissions including greenhouse gases, but that the co-occurrence of extreme western warmth and eastern cold will likely decrease in the future as winter temperatures warm dramatically across the continent, thereby reducing the occurrence of severely cold conditions in the East. Although our analysis is focused on one particular region, our analysis framework is generally transferable to the physical conditions shaping different types of extreme events around the globe.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme-weather winters are becoming more common in U.S. The simultaneous occurrence of warm winters in the West and cold winters in the East has significantly increased in recent decades. The damaging and costly phenomenon is very likely attributable to human-caused climate change, research shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Recent amplification of the North American winter temperature dipole](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JD025116/full)
___

**Abstract**:

During the winters of 20132014 and 20142015, anomalously warm temperatures in western North America and anomalously cool temperatures in eastern North America resulted in substantial human and environmental impacts. Motivated by the impacts of these concurrent temperature extremes and the intrinsic atmospheric linkage between weather conditions in the western and eastern United States, we investigate the occurrence of concurrent warm-West/cool-East surface temperature anomalies, which we call the North American winter temperature dipole. We find that, historically, warm-West/cool-East dipole conditions have been associated with anomalous mid-tropospheric ridging over western North America and downstream troughing over eastern North America. We also find that the occurrence and severity of warm-West/cool-East events have increased significantly between 1980 and 2015, driven largely by an increase in the frequency with which high-amplitude ridge-trough wave patterns result in simultaneous severe temperature conditions in both the West and East. Using a large single-model ensemble of climate simulations, we show that the observed positive trend in the warm-West/cool-East events is attributable to historical anthropogenic emissions including greenhouse gases, but that the co-occurrence of extreme western warmth and eastern cold will likely decrease in the future as winter temperatures warm dramatically across the continent, thereby reducing the occurrence of severely cold conditions in the East. Although our analysis is focused on one particular region, our analysis framework is generally transferable to the physical conditions shaping different types of extreme events around the globe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme-weather winters are becoming more common in U.S. The simultaneous occurrence of warm winters in the West and cold winters in the East has significantly increased in recent decades. The damaging and costly phenomenon is very likely attributable to human-caused climate change, research shows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Findings Suggest Dwarf Planet Ceres Is Geologically Active: Cryovolcanoes, landslides, and water ice all point to current activity, researchers found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The tropical Pacific acts as a key pacemaker of the warming staircase, with radiative forcing driving the overall warming trend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Seismic moulin tremor](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JB012786/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*Through glacial moulins, meltwater is routed from the glacier surface to its base. Moulins are a main feature feeding subglacial drainage systems and thus influencing basal motion and ice dynamics, but their geometry remains poorly known. Here we show that analysis of the seismic wavefield generated by water falling into a moulin can help constrain its geometry. We present modeling results of hour-long seimic tremors emitted from a vertical moulin shaft, observed with a seismometer array installed at the surface of the Greenland Ice Sheet. The tremor was triggered when the moulin water level exceeded a certain height, which we associate with the threshold for the waterfall to hit directly the surface of the moulin water column. The amplitude of the tremor signal changed over each tremor episode, in close relation to the amount of inflowing water. The tremor spectrum features multiple prominent peaks, whose characteristic frequencies are distributed like the resonant modes of a semiopen organ pipe and were found to depend on the moulin water level, consistent with a source composed of resonant tube waves (water pressure waves coupled to elastic deformation of the moulin walls) along the water-filled moulin pipe. Analysis of surface particle motions lends further support to this interpretation. The seismic wavefield was modeled as a superposition of sustained wave radiation by pressure sources on the side walls and at the bottom of the moulin. The former was found to dominate the wave field at close distance and the latter at large distance to the moulin.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tremors Reveal the Structure of Deep Glacial Shafts: Seismic waves produced by free-falling meltwater could improve understanding of glacial drainage processes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Is green tea still green? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 10:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 10:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related material(s):
___

http://phys.org/news/2016-08-antarctica-region-vulnerability-climate.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [European Neolithic societies showed early warning signals of population collapse](http://www.pnas.org/content/113/35/9751.abstract.html)
___

**Significance**:

*This study explores whether archaeologically detectable declines in resilience precede the onset of large-scale human population collapses. Our case study is the European Neolithic: a period that began approximately 9,000 y ago when the introduction of agricultural technologies initiated phases of rapid population growth that were in many cases followed by demographic instability and dramatic collapse. Our study finds evidence that statistical signatures of decreasing resilience can be detected long before population decline begins. To our knowledge, this study is the first to find early warning signals of demographic regime shift among human populations. The results suggest that archaeological information can potentially be used to monitor social and ecological vulnerability in human societies at large spatial and temporal scales.*

**Abstract**:

*Ecosystems on the verge of major reorganizationregime shiftmay exhibit declining resilience, which can be detected using a collection of generic statistical tests known as early warning signals (EWSs). This study explores whether EWSs anticipated human population collapse during the European Neolithic. It analyzes recent reconstructions of European Neolithic (84 kya) population trends that reveal regime shifts from a period of rapid growth following the introduction of agriculture to a period of instability and collapse. We find statistical support for EWSs in advance of population collapse. Seven of nine regional datasets exhibit increasing autocorrelation and variance leading up to collapse, suggesting that these societies began to recover from perturbation more slowly as resilience declined. We derive EWS statistics from a prehistoric population proxy based on summed archaeological radiocarbon date probability densities. We use simulation to validate our methods and show that sampling biases, atmospheric effects, radiocarbon calibration error, and taphonomic processes are unlikely to explain the observed EWS patterns. The implications of these results for understanding the dynamics of Neolithic ecosystems are discussed, and we present a general framework for analyzing societal regime shifts using EWS at large spatial and temporal scales. We suggest that our findings are consistent with an adaptive cycling model that highlights both the vulnerability and resilience of early European populations. We close by discussing the implications of the detection of EWS in human systems for archaeology and sustainability science.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found that early Neolithic communities that existed approximately 9,000 years ago exhibited warning signs before collapsing. Knowing when a given community, town or city is about to collapse could prove useful in the future as the planet continues to warm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [European Neolithic societies showed early warning signals of population collapse](http://www.pnas.org/content/113/35/9751.abstract.html)
___

**Significance**:

This study explores whether archaeologically detectable declines in resilience precede the onset of large-scale human population collapses. Our case study is the European Neolithic: a period that began approximately 9,000 y ago when the introduction of agricultural technologies initiated phases of rapid population growth that were in many cases followed by demographic instability and dramatic collapse. Our study finds evidence that statistical signatures of decreasing resilience can be detected long before population decline begins. To our knowledge, this study is the first to find early warning signals of demographic regime shift among human populations. The results suggest that archaeological information can potentially be used to monitor social and ecological vulnerability in human societies at large spatial and temporal scales.

**Abstract**:

Ecosystems on the verge of major reorganizationregime shiftmay exhibit declining resilience, which can be detected using a collection of generic statistical tests known as early warning signals (EWSs). This study explores whether EWSs anticipated human population collapse during the European Neolithic. It analyzes recent reconstructions of European Neolithic (84 kya) population trends that reveal regime shifts from a period of rapid growth following the introduction of agriculture to a period of instability and collapse. We find statistical support for EWSs in advance of population collapse. Seven of nine regional datasets exhibit increasing autocorrelation and variance leading up to collapse, suggesting that these societies began to recover from perturbation more slowly as resilience declined. We derive EWS statistics from a prehistoric population proxy based on summed archaeological radiocarbon date probability densities. We use simulation to validate our methods and show that sampling biases, atmospheric effects, radiocarbon calibration error, and taphonomic processes are unlikely to explain the observed EWS patterns. The implications of these results for understanding the dynamics of Neolithic ecosystems are discussed, and we present a general framework for analyzing societal regime shifts using EWS at large spatial and temporal scales. We suggest that our findings are consistent with an adaptive cycling model that highlights both the vulnerability and resilience of early European populations. We close by discussing the implications of the detection of EWS in human systems for archaeology and sustainability science.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found that early Neolithic communities that existed approximately 9,000 years ago exhibited warning signs before collapsing. Knowing when a given community, town or city is about to collapse could prove useful in the future as the planet continues to warm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Radiative characteristics of clouds embedded in smoke derived from airborne multiangular measurements](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JD025309/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

*Clouds in the presence of absorbing aerosols result in their apparent darkening, observed at the top of atmosphere (TOA), which is associated with the radiative effects of aerosol absorption. Owing to the large radiative effect and potential impacts on regional climate, above-cloud aerosols have recently been characterized in multiple satellite-based studies. While satellite data are particularly useful in showing the radiative impact of above-cloud aerosols at the TOA, recent literature indicates large uncertainties in satellite retrievals of above-cloud aerosol optical depth (AOD) and single scattering albedo (SSA), which are among the most important parameters in the assessment of associated radiative effects. In this study, we analyze radiative characteristics of clouds in the presence of wildfire smoke using airborne data primarily from NASA's Cloud Absorption Radiometer, collected during the Arctic Research of the Composition of the Troposphere from Aircraft and Satellites campaign in Canada during the 2008 summer season. We found a strong positive reflectance (R) gradient in the UV-visible (VIS)-near infrared (NIR) spectrum for clouds embedded in dense smoke, as opposed to an (expected) negative gradient for cloud-free smoke and a flat spectrum for smoke-free cloud cover. Several cases of clouds embedded in thick smoke were found, when the aircraft made circular/spiral measurements, which not only allowed the complete characterization of angular distribution of smoke scattering but also provided the vertical distribution of smoke and clouds (within 0.55km). Specifically, the largest darkening by smoke was found in the UV/VIS, with R0.34m reducing to 0.2 (or 20%), in contrast to 0.8 at NIR wavelengths (e.g., 1.27m). The observed darkening is associated with large AODs (0.53.0) and moderately low SSA (0.850.93 at 0.53m), resulting in a significantly large instantaneous aerosol forcing efficiency of 25447Wm^2 ^1. Our observations of smoke-cloud radiative interactions were found to be physically consistent with theoretical plane-parallel 1-D and Monte Carlo 3-D radiative transfer calculations, capturing the observed gradient across UV-VIS-NIR. Results from this study offer insights into aerosol-cloud radiative interactions and may help in better constraining satellite retrieval algorithms.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plumes of wildfire smoke envelop and alter clouds, potentially affecting local weather, according to new research. The new data confirms clouds embedded in smoke are likely to warm up the atmosphere around clouds, causing the clouds to dissipate faster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's further evidence in a continuing area of research:

The new results add to scientists knowledge of how canine brains process human speech. Dogs have brain areas dedicated to interpreting voices, distinguishing sounds (in the left hemisphere), and analyzing the sounds that convey emotions (in the right hemisphere). - [source article](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2016/08/video-your-dog-understands-more-you-think) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Neural mechanisms for lexical processing in dogs](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2016/08/26/science.aaf3777)
___

**Abstract**:

During speech processing, human listeners can separately analyze lexical and intonational cues to arrive at a unified representation of communicative content. The evolution of this capacity can be best investigated by comparative studies. Using functional magnetic resonance imaging, we explored whether and how dog brains segregate and integrate lexical and intonational information. We found a left-hemisphere bias for processing meaningful words, independently of intonation; a right auditory brain region for distinguishing intonationally marked and unmarked words; and increased activity in primary reward regions only when both lexical and intonational information were consistent with praise. Neural mechanisms to separately analyze and integrate word meaning and intonation in dogs suggest that this capacity can evolve in the absence of language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs May Understand Even More Than We Thought: Brain scans show our faithful canine pals match words with intonation to process meaning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine charts show why the G20 matters for energy and climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would actually argue otherwise, and would agree with following statement:

The visualization couldnt be more straightforward: As the years progress, the number and intensity of the red-colored cells increases. Slowly at first, then dramatically from around the 1980s onward. Its useful for presenting a simple message: the world is getting warmer, Hawkins says.

In an instant you can convey precisely that by looking at the figure. It doesn't require sitting through minutes of animation and perhaps losing track of where things started. In the blink of an eye it's clear. Now keep in mind that I'm not saying that animations are bad, or even that these maps are better - but I am saying that there are several methods of looking at the data, and climate trends. This visualization is simply another method of analyzing the trend, which it conveys quite well. 

This would make a great poster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Science and the Public: Debate, Denial, and Skepticism](http://jspp.psychopen.eu/article/view/604/html)
___

**Abstract**:

*When the scientific method yields discoveries that imperil peoples lifestyle or worldviews or impinge on corporate vested interests, the public and political response can be anything but favorable. Sometimes the response slides into overt denial of scientific facts, although this denial is often claimed to involve skepticism. We outline the distinction between true skepticism and denial with several case studies. We propose some guidelines to enable researchers to differentiate legitimate critical engagement from bad-faith harassment, and to enable members of the public to pursue their skeptical engagement and critique without such engagement being mistaken for harassment.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate skeptics and climate deniers are not the same thing, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Science and the Public: Debate, Denial, and Skepticism](http://jspp.psychopen.eu/article/view/604/html)
___

**Abstract**:

*When the scientific method yields discoveries that imperil peoples lifestyle or worldviews or impinge on corporate vested interests, the public and political response can be anything but favorable. Sometimes the response slides into overt denial of scientific facts, although this denial is often claimed to involve skepticism. We outline the distinction between true skepticism and denial with several case studies. We propose some guidelines to enable researchers to differentiate legitimate critical engagement from bad-faith harassment, and to enable members of the public to pursue their skeptical engagement and critique without such engagement being mistaken for harassment.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate skeptics and climate deniers are not the same thing, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meltwater Pulse 2B </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Representing 3-D cloud radiation effects in two-stream schemes: 1. Longwave considerations and effective cloud edge length](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JD024876/abstract)

**Abstract**:

*Current weather and climate models neglect 3-D radiative transfer through cloud sides, which can change the cloud radiative effect (CRE) significantly. This two-part paper describes the development of the SPeedy Algorithm for Radiative TrAnsfer through CloUd Sides (SPARTACUS) to capture these effects efficiently in a two-stream radiation scheme for use in global models. The present paper concerns the longwave spectral region, where not much work has been done previously, although the limited previous work has suggested that radiative transfer through cloud sides increases the longwave surface CRE of shallow cumulus by around 30%. To assist the development of a longwave capability for SPARTACUS, we use a reference case of an isolated, isothermal, optically thick, cubic cloud in vacuum, for which 3-D effects increase CRE by exactly 200%. It is shown that for any cloud shape, the 3-D effect can be represented in SPARTACUS provided that correct account is made for (1) the effective zenith angle of diffuse radiation emitted from a cloud, (2) the spatial distribution of fluxes in the cloud, (3) cloud clustering that enhances the interception of emitted radiation by neighboring clouds, and (4) radiative smoothing leading to the effective cloud edge length being less than the measured value. We find empirically that the circumference of an ellipse fitted to a horizontal cross section through a cumulus cloud provides a good estimate of the radiatively effective cloud edge length, which provides some guidance to how cloud observations could be analyzed to extract their most important properties for radiation.*
___

Study: [Representing 3-D cloud radiation effects in two-stream schemes: 2. Matrix formulation and broadband evaluation](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JD024875/abstract)

**Abstract**:

*Estimating the impact of radiation transport through cloud sides on the global energy budget is hampered by the lack of a fast radiation scheme suitable for use in global atmospheric models that can represent these effects in both the shortwave and longwave. This two-part paper describes the development of such a scheme, which we refer to as the Speedy Algorithm for Radiative Transfer through Cloud Sides (SPARTACUS). The principle of the method is to add extra terms to the two-stream equations to represent lateral transport between clear and cloudy regions, which vary in proportion to the length of cloud edge as a function of height. The present paper describes a robust and accurate method for solving the coupled system of equations in both the shortwave and longwave in terms of matrix exponentials. This solver has been coupled to a correlated-k model for gas absorption. We then confirm the accuracy of SPARTACUS by performing broadband comparisons with fully 3-D radiation calculations by the Monte Carlo model MYSTIC for a cumulus cloud field, examining particularly the percentage change in cloud radiative effect (CRE) when 3-D effects are introduced. In the shortwave, SPARTACUS correctly captures this change to CRE, which varies with solar zenith angle between 25% and +120%. In the longwave, SPARTACUS captures well the increase in radiative cooling of the cloud, although it is only able to correctly simulate the 30% increase in surface CRE (around 4 W m2) if an approximate correction is made for cloud clustering.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incorporating 3-D Cloud Effects into Weather and Climate Models: Researchers explain how a new radiative scheme can be incorporated into global weather and climate models to better capture the effect of clouds on climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Understanding Sea Level Rise, part 1: Thermal Expansion  a Physical Foundation of several metres, irrespective of ice melting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change: Yep, still happening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This new weather satellite is a game changer  if it can survive the journey to launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Particulate air pollution from wildfires in the Western US under climate change](https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs10584-016-1762-6)
___

**Abstract**: 

*Wildfire can impose a direct impact on human health under climate change. While the potential impacts of climate change on wildfires and resulting air pollution have been studied, it is not known who will be most affected by the growing threat of wildfires. Identifying communities that will be most affected will inform development of fire management strategies and disaster preparedness programs. We estimate levels of fine particulate matter (PM2.5) directly attributable to wildfires in 561 western US counties during fire seasons for the present-day (20042009) and future (20462051), using a fire prediction model and GEOS-Chem, a 3-D global chemical transport model. Future estimates are obtained under a scenario of moderately increasing greenhouse gases by mid-century. We create a new term Smoke Wave, defined as 2 consecutive days with high wildfire-specific PM2.5, to describe episodes of high air pollution from wildfires. We develop an interactive map to demonstrate the counties likely to suffer from future high wildfire pollution events. For 20042009, on days exceeding regulatory PM2.5 standards, wildfires contributed an average of 71.3 % of total PM2.5. Under future climate change, we estimate that more than 82 million individuals will experience a 57 % and 31 % increase in the frequency and intensity, respectively, of Smoke Waves. Northern California, Western Oregon and the Great Plains are likely to suffer the highest exposure to widlfire smoke in the future. Results point to the potential health impacts of increasing wildfire activity on large numbers of people in a warming climate and the need to establish or modify US wildfire management and evacuation programs in high-risk regions. The study also adds to the growing literature arguing that extreme events in a changing climate could have significant consequences for human health.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme events in a changing climate could have significant consequences for human health. Under future climate change, more than 82 million individuals in the Western US will experience a 57% and 31% increase in the frequency and intensity, respectively, of Smoke Waves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Particulate air pollution from wildfires in the Western US under climate change](https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs10584-016-1762-6)
___

**Abstract**: 

Wildfire can impose a direct impact on human health under climate change. While the potential impacts of climate change on wildfires and resulting air pollution have been studied, it is not known who will be most affected by the growing threat of wildfires. Identifying communities that will be most affected will inform development of fire management strategies and disaster preparedness programs. We estimate levels of fine particulate matter (PM2.5) directly attributable to wildfires in 561 western US counties during fire seasons for the present-day (20042009) and future (20462051), using a fire prediction model and GEOS-Chem, a 3-D global chemical transport model. Future estimates are obtained under a scenario of moderately increasing greenhouse gases by mid-century. We create a new term Smoke Wave, defined as 2 consecutive days with high wildfire-specific PM2.5, to describe episodes of high air pollution from wildfires. We develop an interactive map to demonstrate the counties likely to suffer from future high wildfire pollution events. For 20042009, on days exceeding regulatory PM2.5 standards, wildfires contributed an average of 71.3 % of total PM2.5. Under future climate change, we estimate that more than 82 million individuals will experience a 57 % and 31 % increase in the frequency and intensity, respectively, of Smoke Waves. Northern California, Western Oregon and the Great Plains are likely to suffer the highest exposure to widlfire smoke in the future. Results point to the potential health impacts of increasing wildfire activity on large numbers of people in a warming climate and the need to establish or modify US wildfire management and evacuation programs in high-risk regions. The study also adds to the growing literature arguing that extreme events in a changing climate could have significant consequences for human health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme events in a changing climate could have significant consequences for human health. Under future climate change, more than 82 million individuals in the Western US will experience a 57% and 31% increase in the frequency and intensity, respectively, of Smoke Waves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Quickly Climate Change Is Accelerating, in 167 Maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth is warming at a pace 'unprecedented in 1,000 years': Records of temperature that go back far further than 1800s suggest warming of recent decades is out of step with any period over the past millennium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Political Divide on Climate Change: Partisan Polarization Widens in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Tesla Model 3 Delivers, Gas Vehicles Are History, Gasoline   Automotive Services Dealers Of America Exec Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 09:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Plant responses to increasing CO2 reduce estimates of climate impacts on drought severity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Carbon balance effects of U.S. biofuel production and use](https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10584-016-1764-4)
___

**Abstract**:

*The use of liquid biofuels has expanded over the past decade in response to policies such as the U.S. Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS) that promote their use for transportation. One rationale is the belief that biofuels are inherently carbon neutral, meaning that only production-related greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions need to be tallied when comparing them to fossil fuels. This assumption is embedded in the lifecycle analysis (LCA) modeling used to justify and administer such policies. LCA studies have often found that crop-based biofuels such as corn ethanol and biodiesel offer at least modest net GHG reductions relative to petroleum fuels. Data over the period of RFS expansion enable empirical assessment of net CO2 emission effects. This analysis evaluates the direct carbon exchanges (both emissions and uptake) between the atmosphere and the U.S. vehicle-fuel system (motor vehicles and the physical supply chain for motor fuels) over 20052013. While U.S. biofuel use rose from 0.37 to 1.34 EJ/yr over this period, additional carbon uptake on cropland was enough to offset only 37 % of the biofuel-related biogenic CO2 emissions. This result falsifies the assumption of a full offset made by LCA and other GHG accounting methods that assume biofuel carbon neutrality. Once estimates from the literature for process emissions and displacement effects including land-use change are considered, the conclusion is that U.S. biofuel use to date is associated with a net increase rather than a net decrease in CO2 emissions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study Finds Biofuels Worse for Climate than Gasoline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Carbon balance effects of U.S. biofuel production and use](https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10584-016-1764-4)
___

**Abstract**:

The use of liquid biofuels has expanded over the past decade in response to policies such as the U.S. Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS) that promote their use for transportation. One rationale is the belief that biofuels are inherently carbon neutral, meaning that only production-related greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions need to be tallied when comparing them to fossil fuels. This assumption is embedded in the lifecycle analysis (LCA) modeling used to justify and administer such policies. LCA studies have often found that crop-based biofuels such as corn ethanol and biodiesel offer at least modest net GHG reductions relative to petroleum fuels. Data over the period of RFS expansion enable empirical assessment of net CO2 emission effects. This analysis evaluates the direct carbon exchanges (both emissions and uptake) between the atmosphere and the U.S. vehicle-fuel system (motor vehicles and the physical supply chain for motor fuels) over 20052013. While U.S. biofuel use rose from 0.37 to 1.34 EJ/yr over this period, additional carbon uptake on cropland was enough to offset only 37 % of the biofuel-related biogenic CO2 emissions. This result falsifies the assumption of a full offset made by LCA and other GHG accounting methods that assume biofuel carbon neutrality. Once estimates from the literature for process emissions and displacement effects including land-use change are considered, the conclusion is that U.S. biofuel use to date is associated with a net increase rather than a net decrease in CO2 emissions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study Finds Biofuels Worse for Climate than Gasoline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, that new SETI signal everyone is babbling about? Yeah, not really that interesting. Via http://setiathome.ssl.berkeley.edu

https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CrDa4JfWIAEUb8N.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I'm not glued to reddit 24/7 and I just found out myself... maybe read my comment on the embargo before commenting. I'll be deleting the submission now anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Editors note: Earlier today we accidentally broke the embargo on a new study, "Neural mechanisms for lexical processing in dogs," led by A. Andics and published in Science. The mistake was due to miscommunication about dates on our publishing calendar, and we're reviewing how we track embargoes internally.

The embargo system for science publishing allows journalists worldwide to spend concerted effort in covering new research, which is essential for accuracy in science reporting. As such, by breaking this embargo we've put major strain on journalists hoping to cover the new study, which in turns means the researchers may have less coverage of their work than they hoped for. This helps no one, and we apologize sincerely for the error.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, that new SETI signal everyone is babbling about? Yeah, not really that interesting. Via http://setiathome.ssl.berkeley.edu

https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CrDa4JfWIAEUb8N.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study reduces future drought severity when using plant-centric rather than atmosphere-centric metrics from ESMs. Atmosphere-centric metrics predict future increases in drought stress for more than 70% of global land area. This area drops to 37% with the use of plant-centric metrics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /u/Followthebits, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s):

*It is a duplicate of an already submitted story: https://redd.it/4x37j8*

If you believe this to be in error please feel free to [message the moderators](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FGlobalClimateChange). Thank you for your support, and the /r/GlobalClimateChange community looks forward to your continued contributions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that's impossible given the geology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Papahnaumokukea (pronounced Pa-pa-hah-nou-mo-koo-ah-keh-ah) to Become the Worlds Largest Protected Marine Area. At 582,578 square miles, Papahnaumokukea will be nearly four times the size of California. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Papahnaumokukea (pronounced Pa-pa-hah-nou-mo-koo-ah-keh-ah) to Become the Worlds Largest Protected Marine Area. At 582,578 square miles, Papahnaumokukea will be nearly four times the size of California. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [El Nio and coral larval dispersal across the eastern Pacific marine barrier](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12571)
___

**Abstract**:

More than 5,000 km separates the frequently disturbed coral reefs of the Eastern Tropical Pacific (ETP) from western sources of population replenishment. It has been hypothesized that El Nio events facilitate eastward dispersal across this East Pacific Barrier (EPB). Here we present a biophysical coral larval dispersal model driven by 14.5 years of high-resolution surface ocean current data including the extreme 19971998 El Nio. We find no eastward cross-EPB connections over this period, which implies that ETP coral populations decimated by the 1998 bleaching event can only have recovered from eastern Pacific sources, in congruence with genetic data. Instead, rare connections between eastern and central Pacific reefs are simulated in a westward direction. Significant complexity and variability in the surface flows transporting larvae mean that generalized upper-ocean circulation patterns are poor descriptors of inter-regional connectivity, complicating the assessment of how climate change will impact coral gene flow Pacific wide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darwin's theory about 'impassable' marine barrier holds true for coral larvae in the Pacific. Even during the record-breaking El Nio of 1998, coral larvae could not survive long enough to make the trip from reefs in the central Pacific to those in the east. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [El Nio and coral larval dispersal across the eastern Pacific marine barrier](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12571)
___

**Abstract**:

*More than 5,000km separates the frequently disturbed coral reefs of the Eastern Tropical Pacific (ETP) from western sources of population replenishment. It has been hypothesized that El Nio events facilitate eastward dispersal across this East Pacific Barrier (EPB). Here we present a biophysical coral larval dispersal model driven by 14.5 years of high-resolution surface ocean current data including the extreme 19971998 El Nio. We find no eastward cross-EPB connections over this period, which implies that ETP coral populations decimated by the 1998 bleaching event can only have recovered from eastern Pacific sources, in congruence with genetic data. Instead, rare connections between eastern and central Pacific reefs are simulated in a westward direction. Significant complexity and variability in the surface flows transporting larvae mean that generalized upper-ocean circulation patterns are poor descriptors of inter-regional connectivity, complicating the assessment of how climate change will impact coral gene flow Pacific wide.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darwin's theory about 'impassable' marine barrier holds true for coral larvae in the Pacific. Even during the record-breaking El Nio of 1998, coral larvae could not survive long enough to make the trip from reefs in the central Pacific to those in the east. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The suppression of Antarctic bottom water formation by melting ice shelves in Prydz Bay](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12577)
___

**Abstract**:

A fourth production region for the globally important Antarctic bottom water has been attributed to dense shelf water formation in the Cape Darnley Polynya, adjoining Prydz Bay in East Antarctica. Here we show new observations from CTD-instrumented elephant seals in 20112013 that provide the first complete assessment of dense shelf water formation in Prydz Bay. After a complex evolution involving opposing contributions from three polynyas (positive) and two ice shelves (negative), dense shelf water (salinity 34.6534.7) is exported through Prydz Channel. This provides a distinct, relatively fresh contribution to Cape Darnley bottom water. Elsewhere, dense water formation is hindered by the freshwater input from the Amery and West Ice Shelves into the Prydz Bay Gyre. This study highlights the susceptibility of Antarctic bottom water to increased freshwater input from the enhanced melting of ice shelves, and ultimately the potential collapse of Antarctic bottom water formation in a warming climate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New observations from CTD-instrumented elephant seals highlights the susceptibility of Antarctic bottom water to increased freshwater input from the enhanced melting of ice shelves, and ultimately the potential collapse of Antarctic bottom water formation in a warming climate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The suppression of Antarctic bottom water formation by melting ice shelves in Prydz Bay](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12577)
___

**Abstract**:

*A fourth production region for the globally important Antarctic bottom water has been attributed to dense shelf water formation in the Cape Darnley Polynya, adjoining Prydz Bay in East Antarctica. Here we show new observations from CTD-instrumented elephant seals in 20112013 that provide the first complete assessment of dense shelf water formation in Prydz Bay. After a complex evolution involving opposing contributions from three polynyas (positive) and two ice shelves (negative), dense shelf water (salinity 34.6534.7) is exported through Prydz Channel. This provides a distinct, relatively fresh contribution to Cape Darnley bottom water. Elsewhere, dense water formation is hindered by the freshwater input from the Amery and West Ice Shelves into the Prydz Bay Gyre. This study highlights the susceptibility of Antarctic bottom water to increased freshwater input from the enhanced melting of ice shelves, and ultimately the potential collapse of Antarctic bottom water formation in a warming climate.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New observations from CTD-instrumented elephant seals highlights the susceptibility of Antarctic bottom water to increased freshwater input from the enhanced melting of ice shelves, and ultimately the potential collapse of Antarctic bottom water formation in a warming climate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Sources of black carbon to the HimalayanTibetan Plateau glaciers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Heterogeneous reduction of carbon dioxide by hydride-terminated silicon nanocrystals](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12553)
___

**Abstract**:

Silicon constitutes 28% of the earths mass. Its high abundance, lack of toxicity and low cost coupled with its electrical and optical properties, make silicon unique among the semiconductors for converting sunlight into electricity. In the quest for semiconductors that can make chemicals and fuels from sunlight and carbon dioxide, unfortunately the best performers are invariably made from rare and expensive elements. Here we report the observation that hydride-terminated silicon nanocrystals with average diameter 3.5 nm, denoted ncSi:H, can function as a single component heterogeneous reducing agent for converting gaseous carbon dioxide selectively to carbon monoxide, at a rate of hundreds of mol h^1  g^1. The large surface area, broadband visible to near infrared light harvesting and reducing power of SiH surface sites of ncSi:H, together play key roles in this conversion. Making use of the reducing power of nanostructured hydrides towards gaseous carbon dioxide is a conceptually distinct and commercially interesting strategy for making fuels directly from sunlight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Heterogeneous reduction of carbon dioxide by hydride-terminated silicon nanocrystals](http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12553)
___

**Abstract**:

Silicon constitutes 28% of the earths mass. Its high abundance, lack of toxicity and low cost coupled with its electrical and optical properties, make silicon unique among the semiconductors for converting sunlight into electricity. In the quest for semiconductors that can make chemicals and fuels from sunlight and carbon dioxide, unfortunately the best performers are invariably made from rare and expensive elements. Here we report the observation that hydride-terminated silicon nanocrystals with average diameter 3.5 nm, denoted ncSi:H, can function as a single component heterogeneous reducing agent for converting gaseous carbon dioxide selectively to carbon monoxide, at a rate of hundreds of mol h^1  g^1. The large surface area, broadband visible to near infrared light harvesting and reducing power of SiH surface sites of ncSi:H, together play key roles in this conversion. Making use of the reducing power of nanostructured hydrides towards gaseous carbon dioxide is a conceptually distinct and commercially interesting strategy for making fuels directly from sunlight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 02:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Climate Change and Future Pollen Allergy in Europe](http://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/EHP173/)
___

**Abstract**:

**Background**: *Globally pollen allergy is a major public health problem, but a fundamental unknown is the likely impact of climate change. To our knowledge, this is the first study to quantify the consequences of climate change upon pollen allergy in humans.*

**Objectives**: *To produce quantitative estimates of the potential impact of climate change upon pollen allergy in humans, focusing upon common ragweed (Ambrosia artemisiifolia) in Europe.*

**Methods**: *A process-based model estimated the change in ragweeds range under climate change. A second model simulated current and future ragweed pollen levels. These were translated into health burdens using a dose-response curve generated from a systematic review and current and future population data. Models considered two different suites of regional climate/pollen models, two greenhouse gas emissions scenarios (RCP4.5 and 8.5), and three different plant invasion scenarios.*

**Results**: *Our primary estimates indicate that sensitization to ragweed will more than double in Europe, from 33 to 77 million people, by 2041-2060. According to our projections, while sensitization will increase in countries with an existing ragweed problem (e.g. Hungary, the Balkans), the greatest proportional increases will occur where sensitization is uncommon (e.g. Germany, Poland, France). Higher pollen concentrations and a longer pollen season may also increase the severity of symptoms. Our model projections are driven predominantly by changes in climate (66%), but also are influenced by current trends in the spread of this invasive plant species. Assumptions about the rate at which ragweed spreads throughout Europe have a large influence upon the results.*

**Conclusions**: *Our quantitative estimates indicate that ragweed pollen allergy will become a common health problem across Europe, expanding into areas where it is currently uncommon. Control of ragweed spread may be an important adaptation strategy in response to climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
