<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8373</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 19:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me! I'd love to have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 06:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 21:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the US, unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I was hoping it was in the US and there was someway around it. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, how is the use of a drone justified in Ok Go's new music video? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u1ZB_rGFyeU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had more access to one, especially on smaller, indie projects.  What would be the easier option between the two? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 07:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you've heard of [this](http://www.dailytech.com/Court+Rules+that+FAA+Cannot+Ban+Commercial+Drones+Dismisses+10000+Fine+for+Drone+User/article34468.htm) court case.  Can somebody please explain what this really means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 07:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, yeah $40 isn't too bad.  I was just wondering if there were any cheaper options out there.  

I haven't looked at the 3DR Iris+.  What are the pros/cons? Better or worse than the phantom?  I'm iOS person.  

I've been pretty inspired by this [post](http://alaskavideoshooter.com/a-drone-for-all-seasons-dji-phantom-2-tips-for-aerial-filmmaking-gold/), so I haven't really been looking at any other multicopters. What's your opinion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 07:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So say I wanted to get a revolving shot of a building, maybe 8 feet above the ground.  This clip would be used as part of a commercial.  Would I be contacted by the FAA?

That sounds like a good idea.  I'd much rather crash the Hubsan while learning than the Phantom.  Are there any cheaper options than the Hubsan?  I'd like to try and save money where I can considering I'm about to spend a lot on the phantom.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about quadcopters, filming, and legality. Is it worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 06:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to pull the trigger and buy a DJ Phantom 2.  I don't have any experience operating a quadcopter, but I've been researching and I'll be sure to take it very slow.  I understand that it's not a toy and that above everything else, be safe and smart about it.

However, while I do want to buy this for recreation and getting cool shots, I eventually want to use it to help on shoots for ads, music videos, or other commercial types of gigs (Once I'm 100% confident in piloting it).  My question is: **How legal is it to fly and use video from a quadcopter for commercial purposes?**  If I'm going to be using it in a professional setting, I'm worried that the quadcopter might cause me more tickets and headache than it's worth. 

Does anyone have firsthand experience or knowledge on this topic? What are the rules on the matter? Everywhere I've looked, I've gotten mixed answers.  

Edit: I'm from the US, California specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about quadcopters and legality. Is it worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 05:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to pull the trigger and buy a DJ Phantom 2.  I don't have any experience operating a quadcopter, but I've been researching and I'll be sure to take it very slow.  I understand that it's not a toy and that above everything else, be safe and smart about it.

However, while I do want to buy this for recreation and getting cool shots, I eventually want to use it to help on shoots for ads, music videos, or other commercial types of gigs (Once I'm 100% confident in piloting it).  My question is: **How legal is it to fly and use video from a quadcopter for commercial purposes?**  If I'm going to be using it in a professional setting, I'm worried that the quadcopter might cause me more tickets and headache than it's worth. 

Does anyone have firsthand experience or knowledge on this topic? What are the rules on the matter? Everywhere I've looked, I've gotten mixed answers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A message I made to Florida State from Isla Vista. (UC Santa Barbara) Please help me get this to them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 17:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Our Coast To Yours: An Open Letter From Isla Vista To Florida State University [4:38] - Short video I made over the weekend. Let me know what you guys think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 22:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Our Coast To Yours: An Open Letter From Isla Vista To Florida State University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 18:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm creating a video as a message from our community to Florida State. Please read! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier this morning Florida State University was hit with a tragedy that's all too familiar to our Isla Vista Community. Three students were injured in the library located on the FSU campus as hundreds more hid behind bookshelves. Regardless of the details- the who, the where, the why - the feeling, no matter what, is unchanging. A sense of loss and fear that the places we find comfort in might no longer feel the same. Isla Vista went through this tragedy earlier this year and the outpouring of support we received from surrounding communities and universities guided us in the tough times. The beautiful messages and acts of kindness from strangers helped us realize that we were not alone and we, as a community would like to extend this same kindness to FSU in their time of need.

For these reasons, I want to create a video that will serve as a message to FSU from us, Isla Vista residents, reminding them to stay strong and that they will get through this, just as we still are.  If you or anyone you know are interested in contributing any kind of positive message and/or words of encouragement to students at FSU, email me at carterhiyama@gmail.com and I'll send you more details.  Shooting will begin on Friday 11/21. Please spread the word! And suggestions and advice would be appreciated as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Can someone please remove the glare in this photo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To specify, it's the glare from the light on the left side of the image. If someone could remove it, that would be awesome!

http://imgur.com/l10RuUn

Edit: Thanks guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #TeamMVMT SF - Video I made of a SF trip with a couple friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 20:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 18:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I found it on Amazon for about $250.  Do you recommend any mics to pair with the DR-60D? I was looking into the Rode NTG-2, especially since I get $70 off the DR-60D on B H when I both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tascam DR-40 or Zoom H4N? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 08:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I shoot a variety of things on my Canon 60D: shorts, interviews, skateboarding, and other types of video on my Canon 60D. I have some experience with the Zoom H4N and Tascam DR-40 from borrowing from my school and interning.  

But now I'm looking into buying my own, but I'm not sure which to buy. Do you guys have any advice on the pros and cons of each? Or possibly know of anything better? Also, do you recommend any mics that work well and aren't too expensive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just signed up and gave you five votes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What information should I include on a rsum for a production internship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 03:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making a resume for a production internship and I'm not exactly sure what skills,experience, and/or awards are most valuable to possible production employers.  

Just to give you guys examples, I was a DP Intern at a small production company for 6 months, I am the filmer/editor at a local skateboard shop making advertisements and am currently in the process of making a full length film (including skits), I was nominated for best cinematographer at a local digital film festival, and I've also won 2nd place in a University of California wide video contest.  

Which of these things should I include or leave out?  I'm not sure what employers are looking for.  Also, do you have any other general rsum tips?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undercover police issue citations at UCSB house party (x-post from r/ucsantabarbara) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 03:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 02:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome.  I'm just trying to spread awareness of these issues in our community by making videos like this to clear up any misconceptions or miscommunications that we have of IVFP as well as expressing our views and opinions on what they're doing.  I hope to see this video spread outside of /r/ucsantabarbara and my personal friends on Facebook so that our community in IV can be better educated as a whole.  Because let's face it, not every person in IV reads The Daily Nexus or other newspapers, but most people do have Facebook or some form of social media where they can hear about these issues and learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 20:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undercover Operations Discussion with UCSB Students and IVFP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 20:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 06:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm editing right now, and hoping to get the video up tonight. It will be up by the end of the week for sure though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What questions do you have for the IVFP regarding the undercover stings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 20:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be conducting an interview with LT. Robert Plastino from IVFP this week to discuss the stings.  This interview will be part of a short video I'm making to help express our voices and opinions on what the IVFP is doing and how it affects us.  What questions would you like me to ask? 

Edit: The video is up!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zCCR1BlEAfo app=desktop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 01:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly why I'm going to start creating short videos that use interviews with students, student body, IVFP (hopefully), and any others that are concerned about these very issues.  I want to start making these videos in an attempt to publicize the student perspective in IV on problems like Deltopia, IVFP, and so on.  I'm currently in the process of interviewing the houses where the undercover cops came in and handed out MIP's in the hopes that more people become aware of what is going on.  I also want to interview other students that weren't involved with the sting to express our opinions on the situation and what that means for us. So if anyone would like to say something and be in the video, PM me and we can set something up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone is interested, I'm going to be conducting interviews on Sunday for a short video discussing the undercover cops in IV. I'm going to be interviewing the residents at the houses where this happened and hopefully IVFP as well. PM me if you have any information or want to be interviewed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 19:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank the Tank!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 19:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toilet paper and/or baby wipes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An ad I filmed/edited for a local shop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 08:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short ad I filmed/edited for Movement Boardshop's first shop decks. Let me know what you guys think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 06:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 18:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agatha. Even in Pokemon she was ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 07:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't posting this to "blantantly advertise".  I was posting to get feedback from you guys on a student-made video for a local business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take a quick break from studying and watch this short ad I shot for Movement Boardshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 23:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out this "Day in the Life" project I made of a fellow skater/student at UC Santa Barbara! (Reposted because video was re-edited) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
