<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7382</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why male models? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! In one year to repost this exact image and title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post man, just the person I wanted to talk to.
  
I hear you on hist bark. I've been debating and testing it compared to mirage and I think you're right. It was nice having another slot for a skill, but better can be achieved.
  
Pariah is an interesting concept, I like it so far but the general consensus is what you illustrated. It's better than what most are saying but the root of the idea at 100% isn't great at all. I have a feeling they might up the 100% mitigation to proc at 60% health in future updates. Still the principle argument remains.
  
Juggernaut is what I'm working towards acquiring to test out next. Already have a few pieces. There aren't any jewelry drops for this right? 
  
Whitestrakes is pretty good, I tried it before going hist bark and think I'll go back. Maybe compare with jug and see what's up.
  
Leveling up resto right now. What are your go to skills/morphs? General advice? Haven't touched or even thought about going this path until about a month ago when I realized the potential utility.
  
Such a fun class/ play style. Was greatly surprised at how much fun it was when I respeced from a glass cannon stamblade. Now I can tank anything. Haven't tried it on prison yet though ;).
  
I appreciate your input/thoughts my friend. You wouldn't happen to be on AD NA Xbox? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good read. Makes my brain hurt with all this math you threw at me but I'm embracing the beauty of the numbers. The OP is quite talented in his breakdowns. Biggest thing I found out is infused on the 3 large pieces with the rest divines is the way to go depending on Mundus stones. 
  
I'm about to start crafting V16 gear for my NB sap tank. Wanted to figure this out before I start upgrading things to gold ;). Y'all have thoughts on 5 hist bark 5 pariah and 2 bloodspawn/malubeth? I've seen some flak over the pariah set but after trying it out in a huge group of ~20 adds it seems to work really well. Might pair well with orgnums scales also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [discussion] Armor Traits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the ideal armor traits to use for your sets? Regardless of pve/pve, I'd like to hear your thoughts. I see some people championing divines all the way, but I also heard that it leads to diminishing returns, is this true? I also hear some pvpers running some impenetrable for crit resist. Necessary? Personally I have been using 3-4 divines and the rest infused.. Give me your opinions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 19:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People want to cheese bosses when farming for the engine guardian set (or other sets for that matter) in order to speed up the process. So more tries to get the monster helm in a shorter time frame. Kind of a dick move to disband the group over the principle of cheesing, but to each is own... I will say that the group finder tool isn't ideal for farming monster helms. For obvious reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 15:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change the difficulty to veteran in social-group-difficulty. This works even if you aren't in a group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 14:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essential for nightblades in cyrodiil. Either morph. I thought I couldn't go without Dark cloak for the dot removal but the 100% crit from shawody when combined with concealed weapon is incredible. I find myself popping shadowy before my intros like lotus fan even just to add more burst. Great skill either way you cut it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 19:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your champ points there is a field for resistance to crit hits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not really. The speed boost from blur is only 4 or so secs, where rapid maneuver is for much longer. So much so that you will probably regain the Stam to reapply rapid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't like fusses around here bozo.. Move along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 19:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope! Tamriel doesn't recognize three ways and polygamists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you use the group finder tool, then it is scaled the vr16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get creative with and guesstimate. You can be off by a little if this is just for fun/practice. Don't recommend for real life practice.. You can also use google earth to get an idea of the overall dimensions using the ruler tool. FYI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bogdan's healers for example... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 16:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried both out and haven't found a difference in damage. IMO if you want to be truly tanky swallow soul is the way to go. Heal buffs are huge and the easier it is to keep tank up and aggroing the better for the group as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 21:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube/Google the sap mania 2.0 build. It's the basis of my khajiit Magicka tank build. First and foremost I have to say that I LOVE playing with this build. Very active, powerful, and rewarding. My build began as a Stam blade glass cannon til vet 8 when I respec'd to Magicka tank. So happy I did. Sap essence, swallow soul, siphoning attacks, caltrops, twisting path, puncture armor, inner fire, mirage, and the twin blade and blunt passive of dual wield (swords) are typically on my bars. Right now I'm using 5 piece seducer and 3 piece Magnus and 3 piece willpower in jewelry. PM me if you ever have questions about nightblade sap tank builds. I'm vet 11 and can tank almost everything. Save imp prison-wgt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 18:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, my friend quit clash and wants to give me his account. We tried linking it to my device to no avail. Any suggestions? iOS-iOS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 18:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice wrecking blows guy. Blow me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 18:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've also heard at 50-60 percent to focus on other elements of your character. If you're a healer it is my understanding to increase it as high as possible for more frequent heal crits. Correct me if I'm wrong por favor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 01:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War... War never changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good stuff good stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 00:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many dicks are about to be drawn all over cities world wide. Let's fill up those holes people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 16:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blades that hit close enemies every 3 seconds can throw you out of stealth. It has surprised me a few times. 20% AOE mitigation has saved my glass cannon a few times against flag bosses in IC.  Useful skill for PVE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can get great sustain using caltrops in conjunction with siphoning attacks and steel tornado. A wonderfully nasty AOE spam sesh that lasts basically forever as long as there are A LOT of enemies in the range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 23:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you suck so hard.
  
In all seriousness, what world do you live in where you think you can say "you're privileged to be a part of this community so show some respect." Im on the fucking Internet on a gaming subreddit, I'm more inclined to disrespect after reading your post, hence why I'm writing this. I'd rather have an inactive mod than a power tripping mod. Who the fuck "hired" this guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 04:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gaaaaaaaaaarrrrrryyyyyyyy...........  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 00:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the replies everyone! I'll post my current stats in a little, just got home from work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> StamBlade Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 18:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Khajiit here,

Vet 8 stamina nightblade - Bow, DW, 2H.
  
I like to PVP and run vet pledges.
  
Was wondering what is a good benchmark for things like weapon dmg, Stam recovery, max health and max Stam. Phys. and spell resist too.
  
Your expert thoughts are highly appreciated. Xbone NA if that matters, probably doesn't. 
  
Thanks for any input guys and gals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 23:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level cripple up I think. Until siphoning strikes. Highly recommend siphoning attacks. And then power drain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 18:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DW/bow for solo/2 person AOE grinding
  
2h/bow for PVP and single target dps
  
1h/shield/2h for nightblade tank builds
  
I recommend using dual wield for AOE grinding any nightblade build   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 17:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> khajiit stamblade here. I found for PVP and PVE that 2h and bow work incredibly well. I tried 1h and shield prior to vet levels and think it's better for tanking moreso than typical night blade builds. 
  
My bars-
2h: rally, vigor, killer's blade, wrecking blow, brawler(or critical charge or ambush)

Bow- poison injection, focused aim, bombard (or reapers mark) camo hunter(or double take) siphoning strikes(or dark cloak)
  
I change up the skills depending on the situation(PVP,PVE,boss,adds) just depends.
  
Ults- veil or blades/soul assault
  
I'm leveling up DW to replace 2h currently.
  
Edit: check out the spectre on Deltias gaming. Basically the same build but he uses a couple different skills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 22:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reaper's/piercing mark, rally, potions, teammates..dark cloak. Biggest one out of all these options in regards to sustaining life is STEALTH. Know when to dip out in a hurry with dark cloak, regain health/stam and acquire your next target. Practice thwarting ganks with dark cloak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 18:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2h (maul) with a bow for pvp. There is a passive under 2h that ignores 20% armor when using a maul. Oh, and uppercut is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 18:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it as "aggravating." Like when a queen notices an enemy in her radius </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 02:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted for granmar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought you meant clean as in language... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infernos set to single stop 2 stars. Infernos set to disco stop 3 stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm not mistaken, the quake spell has the chance to completely destroy a structure once a low health threshold is reached. Maybe the double lightning brings a lvl 5 AD to that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually been practicing that strat all day on my push back to champs. Worked like a charm and had a few 3k de raids. One at 5,300. Love the strat now, highly recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you're into technological determinism at all, it isn't so hard to reach this point. It's like me saying we can use wormholes to reach other galaxies and places in time using a teleporter. In my kitchen closet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so it begins... Moto-Tec... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 21:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name - Soul Stoned
Tag - #2UURPGGP
Req's - + 500 trophies, th8+, familiar with war strategies
Addtl notes - we war very frequently, currently at 125 war wins, approaching 126. Clan lvl 5. Attack twice per war or get benched. We go for sure three stars, not mirrors. Tight group of active members. We use Groupme and clashcaller for coordination. We help devise attack strategies. Request to join!
  
  
Edit: mention you saw this on reddit in your request, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 07:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You start off life with a bag of luck and a bag of skill. 
  
The trick is filling up that bag of skill before the bag of luck runs out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah pretty much my whole clan has been following him/her since the update. Congratulations, I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this isn't a very smart move bubs. Kind, but not smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He better lawyer up to. Do you even lift bruh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And everyone know trickle-down doesn't work ;P /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said broken element, not broken economy. As for fragility and self-righteousness... Wtf are you smoking? Did I piss you off a little? Want some ice? Bye bye lightning on DE. Don't get all Butthurt about it and whine to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether you think it's a smart move or not it is a broken element to the resource economy in clash. Luckily for us, supercell realizes this and is dealing with it. Enjoy it while you can homie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very much looking forward to no more DE zapping. It's a very dishonorable way to get DE when you can easily just barch a number of bases in the time it takes to train up enough lightning spells. It is so frustrating getting zapped repeatedly and lose thousands of DE to someone that quite frankly doesn't have the skill to take it to begin with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 20:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smaller cities in the Peloponnes are quite nice winter/summer. It is definitely quieter come winter but I've heard through family that the food is incredible during that time of year, even more so than usual. Nafplion, Monemvasia, and Gythio are my favorites in the area and I would go in a heartbeat anytime of year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when people generalize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 07:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooooo a lenticular. Me likey. Nice work OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems a little much, don't cha think? I will say I am glad there are tons of people out there looking at every pixel for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butter, butter, and butter. The real deal right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It improves health, and uh, endurance. In all seriousness having a high endurance means they can last longer, meaning more opportunities for findings loots. A high luck in conjunction with that leads to better loots found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 18:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do great work out there. War damn eagle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I thought about that. I assumed it was a handwritten typeface. Hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 08:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man... I wanted to read the whole thing but the font choice is atrocious. Would have preferred comic sans. Sorry not sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 08:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right. I'm an avid duck hunter and observe gun safety to the highest degree. Homie don't play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are really hell bent on calling these "liars" out? I'm not sure if it's true or not, but how could you be? I understand that they have similar formatting but that doesn't justify its illegitimacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right there with you bud. Most paranoid I've been in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 03:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with all the other comments- grids in lumion are distracting, fenestration at the front a little heavy-handed, way too much of it and without any environmental controls other than the mulls and sashes themselves.  More context in the renders would help understand scale as well as how successful the project is from the get go.
  
IMO the rear elevation( facing pool, courtyard) would probably be best as the front elevation, still with a little tweaking though, on both. This would aid in privacy, as well as environmental controls. Program arrangement seems ok, a floor plan would be nice but I understand this was a rendering/modeling exercise. 
  
Office oriented towards courtyard at the rear would also be a good call, most likely.
  
Take what I say with a grain of salt. Just graduated from arch. school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 00:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit Demons is Recruiting!
  
We are a tight group of sh6-8's and rising. We are looking for active SH6's and up!
  
Currently in Arrow League, we are heavy on donations and someone is always online to also donate troops. We help devise attack strategies and the like! 

We need you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 23:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If I have seen farther it is because I have stood atop the shoulders of giants." 
  
Sir Isaac Newton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All top comments deleted? Interesting?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 04:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yall are hilarious. Like a married couple. Referring to this comment thread. 
  
:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 05:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of you people bother me. But what really bothers me is how this comment thread even began.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's something I wish could be a filter setting within the stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.
  
I've had luck experimenting with it, an the times that they say is good for loot make sense as far as when people get off work, school, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 02:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't find much other information than what was provided on the website. The bottom right of the page details how the statistics lay out in something called "loot minutes." 
  
I don't think it's hooked up to supercell's servers, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [strategy] CoC Forecaster - Best Times to Raid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 22:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
http://www.clashofclansforecaster.com/
  
  
  
This tool forecasts the relative amounts and numbers of unharvested mines and collectors in Clash of Clans. It simulates players habits around the world to provide an overall view of the quality of raids you can expect to find in the game. Use the graph to help coordinate your raiding to make sure you are taking advantage of the best times to be raiding.
  
_A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't not do Jesus pizza because he's Jewish. They can't do it because of what our laws say about separation of church and state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I looking at here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
