<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember the last time Russia has ever helped me enough to justifying them taking up a diplomatic relationship slot. They are constantly plagued by whoever ends up gaining the upper hand in the region (Ottomans, or PLC, or Sweden, or even a horde). They have a lot of troops, but they're still a little garbage can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always have recommended watching videos by Arumba or DDRJake. I've found them to be pretty useful, regardless of whether the nation they are playing is something I'd want to ever try. They know mechanics really well. They also keep up with the expansions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayyy but they're beating back the highlanders! +1 warscore baby we're on fire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to my knowledge. As long as you pull a white peace or more they remain your lesser partner. Make sure to check the treaty terms, it should say something along the lines of "Bohemia will remain in a PU." You don't need a special treaty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bohemia. They're like the little Elector that could. No advantages and typically surrounded by enemies all game long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't need to analyze it unless people are trying to gauge the character of Dardoch. Looking at the way he presents himself during the interview: his posture (crossing his arms is typically a sign of defensiveness, and unwillingness to engage in constructive conversation) and the way he begins twitching into a smile when the crowd cheers him on shows an incredibly emotionally immature individual. He's letting his emotions guide his opinions, not the facts regarding how his team performed.

It's this kind of attitude that gets people riled up, and the same reason why when DL trash-talks people, others don't get as upset.  Dardoch is unstable and lets emotions dictate his opinions, whereas typical trash-talk is more benign banter and innocuous bravado. It's pretty apparent why he got suspended at the start of the season with this worrying, childish blame-game display here. He doesn't take full responsibility on what is objectively his team's fault for losing that game.

That being said, he's a teenager. He's so unique and divisive because he "speaks his mind," and I suppose that's why people think he's so edgy and great. But at the core of it he's a teenager who doesn't know how to appropriately deal with defeat. He won't develop positively as a player if he points to the reason of defeat on one teamfight, because that's the state of the game right now. "They're not the better team, not even close" is a statement someone oblivious, delusional, or simply emotionally heated would make, because while TL could be the better team, asserting that CLG is "not even close" is simply incorrect given they've beaten them in 2 series now. If he can't understand how to play the game all the way through to a win, then of course he'll lose and never get better. If he can't acknowledge that his team is much more close in skill level than the rest of the competition, then again, he'll continue to lose. It's kind of a part of growing up, accepting that you're not some invincible, special, unique little butterfly that deserves to win all the time. 

TL;DR For all the people defending him, saying he's merely showing confidence, they're wrong. He is clearly tilted based on his mannerisms and tone. He is, in fact, very tilted, and falls back on his usual display of defensiveness and brazen arrogance.

Who honestly cares whether this is trashtalk? It's his punk-ass busta mindset that should be a worrying trend for TL fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I understand your disappointment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I released Croatia and Venice to get out of a war with Poland and friends while conquering Brandenburg. Croatia then took over all of Venice and the subsequently lost all of their land to an Ottoman invasion. Poor Croats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I've ever expanded throughout the HRE without a care in the world about how much AE I was accumulating. Oh, it felt so good to finally be so (moderately) successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria-Hungarian Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want my crushing to MEAN something, my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 1720 I had the chance to contest Poland when they claimed a PU over France and thoroughly destroy 2/3 of my only enemies in the game. But I accidentally skipped over the notification when I clicked ESC. Since it was an RNG event, I couldn't even go back to a previously backup save. It was the worst moment of my life, hands down. 

I'll keep the dream alive, though. No one plays this game for fun. We play to remove kebab/baguette.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thinking, I'll look into those. Thanks! I've already formed Italy before, and I think I've got the City of Cities. Dismantling the HRE means France/Polish/Ottoman alliance will take me out rather quickly, I feel, but hey, whatever. Austria has had its time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Austria, noble duchy and member of the HRE. (I lost my emperor status and converted to reformed for fun.) I'm allied with Spain, Portugal, Brandenburg, Sweden, and Lithuania. Naples is my march and Bavaria is my highly rebellious vassal, with the Ottomans supporting their independence. 

I'm fairly certain I can win whatever war I choose next, but I'm running out of time and would like to make it worth my time. Not sure if there's anything cool I could do, cuz I usually never get this strong. Maybe I'll reconvert to catholicism and try and for Germany or something. I don't know, really. 

Any ideas, guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody have suggestions on what achievements I can do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, but what have you done to the Podebrads? Zerotin is a filthy Hapsburg puppet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 10:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took photos chronicling the progression of a completely AI dictated Europe over the miserable years plodding around Arabia and Persia. Castile and Aragon get special recognition for going at each others throats for 200+ years. http://imgur.com/a/YoVMB

Anyway, just thought I'd share my accomplishment. I don't care that the EU4 Wiki says its a medium difficulty achievement, I got it in a single go having never played a non-European country before, and it's 3:30am and I'm tired and need to sleep. I hope Freddy is proud of me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> only took 368 years to achieve Queen of Mercury AND I got the pleasure of witnessing the AI partition France. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 10:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
