<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8351</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there is a bone hole for his Bone now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I need to test this theory....you know, for science! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that happened to me and my life was ruined, I would be taking people lives for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he look......Goofy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but I wouldn't really call 1 archetype for rogues a release when all other UA releases for classes had at least 2 if not 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogue definitely looks like an afterthought on this release in that there is only 1 archetype but dam...Double sneak attacks a turn at 17 sounds insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we need to start being like Russia where we all have Dash-cams and start suing all the cops that are dirty. Once the city is buried in lawsuits they will either get rid of the bullies or bankrupt their city. 

If they do the latter, their lives might be at risk (from their constituents) so they might actually do something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always wanted to play an Underdark campaign. Have fun with it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you "harvest" rainwater? As far as I know it's only called collecting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sony fucked over the PS Vita crowd with very few US game releases, or even game companies making games, so I highly doubt they even care about handheld consoles at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hornet's nest being thrown in the middle of the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he die? His skull smashed into the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the title in an Asian accent...I laughed way too hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would cause a Paranormal activity outbreak by running through stores and throwing things off shelves and what not. After that 1 day I will have entertainment watching the "Professionals" look for ghosts for weeks on end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I thought I was fat before... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quigley Down Under 

Even if it is set in Australia, it is the first "Western" that I watched with my dad and mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a little disturbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ray, a drop of golden sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that old white man Warren Buffett is throwing off this Median Net Worth. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single White Male here, my bank account doesn't agree with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you see it flying toward the Space Needle there are 2 people there, my guess is those are the people that flew the drone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do have the greatest worth but until we realize life is finite and try and prolong the world for future generations instead of just caring about the "now", we will destroy the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drone "Click-bait adjective" Seattle's Space Needle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are blaming cows look at who is causing it...Humans. In reality herds are kept in check from predators, sickness/disease, and injuries. In a closed ecosystem everything would be working fine until you throw a human in there to change all aspects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT THE FLYING FUCK!?! He ran over a bunch of people's property just to jump out and shoot him 4 seconds later without saying anything.

We need a Punisher to start clearing out the dirty cops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans, we are the only animal that can destroy the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering Reddit is an American based company, website, and mostly Americans on it; it would be extremely hard to even try and do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you notice how he is a sheriffs deputy in your article and a Sargent in the latter one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is this at so I can "accidentally" fall on it and get compensation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone sued another person for farting in their kids face...I wouldn't put it past anyone for that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indian Gallagher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is all about positioning to keep your team away from the AOE. That is what I did and I only lost 1 at the start of the battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this was the US the mom would sue the guy because he "traumatized" the child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fargo

I'm gonna guess you mean the TV show because the people that actually live there do not sound like that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping for an Ion Cannon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I would've done that. I typed them all up on my old laptop and it died. I have the hard drive somewhere but don't know if it will even work to recover them.

I think I wrote about 150 to 200 before things got better for me. After everything I have tried to write again but I have just a giant writer's block after I wrote down all my emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This brings such joy to my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to write poems when I was in my darkest point. The poems were dark but it helped me to get everything out and work through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The picture was a lot better than I thought considering "Florida woman" on drunk charges at a Walmart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O LORDY, O LORDY, O LORDY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedro Alonso Lopez (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pedro_L%C3%B3pez_(serial_killer))

When he was caught he led police to 53 bodies in Ecuador, all girls between nine and twelve years old. Later he was found guilty of murdering 110 girls in Ecuador alone and confessed to 240 more murders of girls in Peru and Colombia. He was released from prison in 1998 and hasn't been seen since.

I like to think he hasn't been seen because the families of the murdered girls killed him.

[Documentary](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GPFhpM1CBS4) if anyone wants to see.

Edit: I guess he was picked up for a fresh murder in 2002, I doubt it was just 1 during that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It is cheap as shit, therefore it tastes like shit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  hasn't run

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beer, I don't need any ["Beer 30 Light"](http://cdn.totalfratmove.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/6811f73679d19edfb5f399eb1d780f992120850085.jpg) that would taste like cheap cat piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go a step further and Q-Tip your urethra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Richie Rich here with his expensive bathroom AND a WALL-E robot for his plant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is going places! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "HEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEELP MMMMMMMMMMMEEE!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby's cost a lot of money... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you die, your body is put in a casket and all it does it rot away to be forgotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is -11F outside with about 5 inches of fresh snow (and still snowing), it is like a natural scarf, but for my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Snack Bar? All I am thinking is they already make machines that obsolete your job, are you worried about a vending machine taking your job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Mel Gibson has paid his price for what he said...Trump get applauded for his shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it wouldn't be a Russian video without someone in a track suit, good on you Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can hit on the photography, I usually head off to the lakes for the photography. There are quite a few public beaches in Detroit Lakes that you can go to for Sunrise and Sunset pictures over the lake.

Also there is Buffalo State Park about 25min from town and Itasca State Park about 2.5 hours away if you want more "in nature" shots. I really like Buffalo State Park for the hiking and it is a short walk away from the Science Center there. 

Story: Last spring I got to witness the control burn of the prairie grass over at Buffalo State Park and the trail through that area after was very surreal and felt like a foreign world, I would suggest it if they do it again. (Sadly did not have my camera then for any pictures)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are also the only two that I beat to completion in my childhood, but those are also the only two that I would spend quarters on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had D D friends :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you cook the chicken for hours? That chicken will be drier than a nun's pussy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 11:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has to be the lamest attempt I have ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget all the snow from Monday too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahab? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, good thing Soulja Boy has Floyd Mayweather training him. Chris Brown has all that home training so he will need some help if he wants to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duct Tape, Rope, Hunting Knife, and a Gas Can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is only -14F here now but earlier in the week it was -18F but the windchill made it -45F. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lick everything while taking pictures and re-wrap everything. After 1 month of her being back, give her the pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to search through a billion items to find what I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing I'm 6'5" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this one was a Video on Facebook Live...hard to hide that, if there was a video of the Footballers doing that to the child it would be all over here AND the media. I have yet to see anything about these kids from Chicago on the media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never saw this story but that is fucking horrendous. This should be a hate crime also, and they should definitely have gotten some prison time for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [One of my favorites](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/26/d4/58/26d458396629a9aea385869e487c657c.jpg)

[A pair of Tits](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/GreatTit002.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this shit! If it was a bunch of white people doing it to a black person it is a fucking race crime but not the other way...fuck this country sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is...is that a bottle opener with an antler handle on the door knob? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male character to female character and vice versa. So a Female Joker instead of a Male Joker, Female Captain America instead of Male Captain America and so on and so forth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all get it as kids so when we become adults it is a comfort food for us. Also it is cheap and easy to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Community activist Andrew Holmes was made aware of the disturbing video, which he is calling a "hate crime."

Until the police and the law call it a hate crime it is not a hate crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just imagine if it was white kids torturing a black kid....it would be all over as a hate crime but this is nothing, because for some reason black against white is not hate crime.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religious beliefs is what influences political beliefs. Just look at the Planned Parenthood problem in the US, Gay marriage in the US till the past few years. Religious beliefs are what influenced the Congress and Senate on what they do....not their constituents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to force your religious beliefs and ideals on others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump and Ivanka Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I am a mom....with a penis...and no kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty hot.

Edit: As someone in the culinary field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea...US has nothing on those countries. When you go to jail for BEING raped, you live in a fucked up country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real Spartans over here everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why pass on dinner when you can "accidentally" spill that glass of red wine on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a euphemism for some sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says you need natural selection... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 21:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there embedded hyperlinks in the picture that lead to a mesothelioma lawsuit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As a born and raised Evertonian, this is so true but fuck you.

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's good to know I get good sleep since I never dream, or at least never remember them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat/Spanish/Waiter

- What a description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ok, I'm gonna eat the hell out of this while you film me

Said no woman ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 12:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small penis joke here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 12:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You add as well as a politician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least getting Salmonella can be delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you 2016! Will you not end yet?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must really have trust with those back claws a couple inches from your jugular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, they have some ovens they can use somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is still men vs women, different styles, speeds of serves and whatnot. That is like comparing Apples to Oranges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHY CAN'T I UNSEE THIS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider this is from [January 14, 2016](http://imgur.com/CUojXoF), you are a big fat [phoney](http://time.com/money/4181373/dad-gives-6-year-old-fantastic-corporate-response-to-allowance-advance/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's how you get "The Runs" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you be OK if he was rubbing another woman's butt? Even if they are friends you don't do that when in a relationship unless it's an open one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep an eye on it, cat bites can become infected very easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Mall of America I got to watch a couple break up. The girl was working at a fast food place there and the boyfriend went up to the counter to break up with her. She was bawling and he didn't really care, the boss made her go to the back and compose herself so she could work again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, if she sees this post, all the comments will hurt her feelings for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for Shame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you fall on your neck when you sat up to release the straps? Gravity is instant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a flat surface on top for cooking or is this just for heat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, sorry OP but that is funny.

Story time: I use to work banquets and there was some event where we needed to cut a case (5lbs) of Habaneros. My coworker had to cut them all and them and once he finished he went to go to the bathroom. He forgot about it and we hear screaming from down a 150ft hall and through a bathroom door. He left for the day, he was mocked relentlessly until someone else did something stupid to replace that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather have someone paid to kill and gut them by hand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missed opportunity to use your belly button in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am against all religions that force you to conform to what they believe or want. Religion has no place in laws of a country and just because you believe in it does not mean you have any authority to make others follow it also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hope" in that 2017 is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What. The. Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your address? I will send her the strap-on from Se7ven so I don't have to hear this joke anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right in the pussy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess 1 year of baseball is hard to forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing I have to ask is: "Why?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you are a T-Rex and can't reach the fridge door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they are worse...they are Big Pharma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how many threats have you received from the OxyContin people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until the Nazis just blow up the house and move onto the next one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you miss the time before kids? 

AKA: Free time,  vacations, and not worrying about little "yous" running around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was thinking that helmets were not needed, I was wrong.

edit: words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP your inbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intense hatred for people that are not like yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kittens, definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
