<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5644</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pennywise - All or Nothing (album)

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WpIcREWRPUM

Loads of positivity and energy! Favourite tracks:

All or Nothing
Let us hear your voice
We have it all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost 100% sure OP is between 30-35 years of age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 12:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a street party to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange, couldn't find Adolf's burgers anywhere. That name really died out didn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it safe to say that we may not see Kim Wexler in the next season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the closer we get to Saul Goodman being introduced, there may not be a need for Kim's character anymore. She's essential to the plot as it currently stands, but we all know where Saul Goodman will end up and I don't see how Kim helps to get him to that point. Your thoughts?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Chuck's been waiting for a moment like this for a very long time. Kim having MV is actually Jimmy having MV in Chuck's mind. His face lit up like a childs when he realised he can screw with Jimmy's life. The MV meeting really was an attack on Jimmy, not Kim.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Howard tells Kim she's got her hands full in doc review... scene changes showing the flag waving in the wind. It looks like Kim is standing at attention, showing full loyalty like we do when a country's flag gets hoisted. Almost patriotic like.

http://imgur.com/9AcEKBT

She can leave when she wants, she's got no reason to stay at HHM. Wonder why she's so loyal to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit, I came here to make that point hoping that I'd be the first haha. This show... damn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
