<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2951</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 00:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're dating a man child, time to dump him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhhhhmygod. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *undignified squeeing noises*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His face. 

Poor fella tho, I hope he's gonna be okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog is also helpful in that way. Especially with the vacuum cleaner, which is his MORTAL ENEMY.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SQUEEEEE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #facepalm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So fucking ADORABLE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 20:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She assaulted you and she wants YOU to apologise? HELLNO. Ask her if she wants to talk to the cops about slapping you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 13:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuff like this makes me so angry. You have a legitimate medical problem and the way healthcare always assumes people in your condition are drug seeking, is utterly abhorrent. I'm so very sorry for your loss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 04:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on to the way his fur felt beneath your fingers. They never really leave you, and neither does their unconditional love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 03:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My beautiful olde tyme bulldog had to be euthanised last year because his body was riddled with cancer. He'd saved my life twice, and he was a light for me when I couldn't see any other. I had him put to sleep at home so he wouldn't be scared. I held him and his body fell against mine as he took his last breaths. I have never sobbed so hard in my entire life. He was brain damaged from birth but he had a full and wonderful life. Losing him was the worst pain I've ever felt. I cried like a baby for so long. 

You don't know pain until you've lost an animal. They give you unconditional love with ever fibre of their being.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 03:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a shit boyfriend and a shit friend. Be rid of him and let his friends know he's been scapegoating you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 03:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would dump him and never look back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 02:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dump him. You deserve better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eject that racist shit from your circle of friends and have done with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Restraining order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you're fundamentally incompatible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why you need to cut contact with him entirely, end it and block him and refuse any contact with him until he gets the message.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 19:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bootiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a serious issue with respecting boundaries. If you were looking for people to tell you to keep pushing, you're in for disappointment. Leave. Her. Alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it was her father who put it there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's to women subjugating men ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call the police. You don't know if it was put there by someone outside the house, or someone in it. Either way it's a horrible situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else lives there aside from you and your brother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to leave her alone and get some help for YOURSELF. Your inability to see this is a huge part of the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a load of bollocks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a monumental waste of molecules and you deserve better. Dump his stupid infantile arse, and leave him to play with the other toddlers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Tell her, show her the evidence, tell her what he's been saying to you and let her confront him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty rude to be texting/engaging in stuff like that when you're physically with someone else, especially to excess. However if it is platonic then there's no reason to be upset; I'd be more upset at the fact that she's spending time texting constantly when she's supposed to be spending time with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to say this, they strike me as being narcissists, and very dangerous ones at that. Filing a restraining order might be the only thing to keep them away from her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and yet you're still talking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your parents are failing you HARD here. Your sister is being an utter terror and this is abuse, plain and simple. My suggestion is that you speak to an adult outside of the situation, explain what's going on and that you don't feel safe or secure at home because of this. Your sister seems like she needs an attitude adjustment, and your parents apathy towards it is quite alarming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop trying to take the moral high ground. You were entirely complicit in this, KNOWING how uncomfortable his girlfriend was and you did it anyway. You should tell her so she can get him out of her life, but don't for a moment think you're blameless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow the fuck up. She's better off without you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 16:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dump him. He's a controlling asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 16:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shouldn't drink, end of story. He also needs to apologise to those folks he has upset because of his disgusting behaviour. If he doesn't stop drinking, cut him loose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 16:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you quite finished?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a troll. Go away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it really won't. Good gods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You weren't kidding on the JS-esque front. Okay so, ask yourself this; how do you see your life progressing if you removed her from it, and if you kept her in it. Make lists. I realise friendships aren't to be reduced to lists, but make pros and cons. Would you be lost without her? Could you move on and potentially find another BFF that you can bond with and have a more rewarding and stable friendship? Do you think she can make that critical professional introduction for you regardless of any friendship issues?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which planet are you on exactly? Having your significant other with you for moral support does not imply weakness or subjugation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just exactly where did I say he needed to hand hold her, or help her like she's a little girl? You're making a mountain out a molehill where she might want to lean on him for support. She can also not take her husband with her too, if that's what she wants. Settle down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing the right thing writing this stuff down.  Write down how you would feel to be clean every day, how healthy it might make you feel and better about yourself. I used to live with someone who had a fear of showers but it was down to the fact that they were autistic and the sensation and sound of running water was one of their absolute no-no things. As you can imagine it made life quite difficult. We helped them by trying to make positive associations with the running water; playing their favourite song on repeat for example, and also telling them it would all be over in five minutes etc. You're definitely not alone with this. 

If you choose to go and seek help, a psychologist that specialises in exposure therapy might be useful for you. They specifically help people face fears and the like, if other options have failed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it very odd that people would not want to draft in the support of their significant other in a time where support is needed. Moreover I find it even more odd that people assume I meant her husband is in charge and owns her. Jesus wept. This is 2016.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moral support, that's what husbands and wives do remember? Christ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear gods - where on earth did you get that from? I'm not talking from an ownership position, he's her husband not her owner! Her husband would be there for moral support! Of course it's not 19bloody50. Rein your neck in. She's facing a huge nightmare and needs support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 05:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell your husband. Have him be with you when you speak to someone in authority about this. This man is grossly overstepping your boundaries and this is NOT okay. It's their responsibility to handle getting you another mentor because the one you have now, is incompetent and dangerous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUMP HIM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 04:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels like a potential obsessive compulsive response to a stress situation. What you need to do is speak to a professional and ask for guidance. In the meantime, write down what your worst case scenario is when you are showering. Are you afraid of being caught naked? Is it that people will make fun of you or take photos and humiliate you etc? 

For every negative worry, try and write down a logical and rational response. Remind yourself doors are locked. It's okay to tell yourself these things when you shower out loud, or in your head. 

Do you have any other areas where you are concerned about control that aren't related to showering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 04:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's being a complete prick who's stringing you along, and he can't make up his mind. Do it for him and completely cut contact. He's playing stupid games and you deserve better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 00:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who are horrible to animals are fucking shit excuses for a human being. Dogs are utterly fantastic, I'm glad you decided to dump her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 23:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sweetie. There's no easy way around this. How you've been treated is utterly reprehensible and you deserve so much better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 23:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the wedding, your mother will just have to suck it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 23:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not going to be able to enjoy time with her until you're honest with her about who you are, which potentially has the capacity to explode horribly because after that, enjoying time with her might be entirely off the table. I suggest you talk to your father about this and have him be with you if you choose to talk to your mother. There's no way you can deal with this without being totally honest with her first. It'll probably be very messy, but if you're to reconcile with her, honesty needs to be up front.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mind your own business until she talks about it herself, because you're coming off as being incredibly insensitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Okay no you should walk away. She should have responded to that with nothing but kindness and understanding. You deserve way better than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you told her you're deaf and she cancelled a date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *applause* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's being a total prick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is eerily similar to a relationship I used to be in some years ago. Ultimately his behaviour because so obnoxious that he was impossible to live with, and I kicked him out. This isn't going to get any better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like she's being ridiculous, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's for them to worry about. Your personal account stands for something, tell them what you've seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have a choice - PLEASE call them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing to have to do this because he obviously isn't going to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll find out who your friends really are. A. It's none of their business. B. If they so readily believe him without even speaking to you first, then they're shit friends. C. You tell them you didn't cheat and he's accessed your account out of spite and leave it at that. Everyone loves drama even if it's bullshit drama.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So very many alarm bells and red flags. This genuinely needs help from social services. You should also be prepared to hear things that will repulse you. Don't leave this another moment, please call someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 16:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hard because whilst it's absolutely a person's right to be how they want to be, it might very well be that she's never been taught how to do this. Do you know any of her family? Is she battling any mental health issues like depression?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 15:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an adult, figure it out. Unless you need help when you are outside on your own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 15:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aaaand we wouldn't need feminism if we didn't have people making stupid comments like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing I've seen all day - FANTASTIC THAT YOU GOT AWAY FROM HIM! he can bawl down the phone to his mother from jail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dump him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heaven forfend should a woman ever check a guy out to make sure he's safe! I mean there's NEVER ANY reason a woman should worry right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this thing called "personal responsibility." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah he did that on purpose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 23:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need someone to remove her from your property, the police seem like a good plan since she abuses you and treats you horribly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Candidate for a vasectomy..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in the not-answering-the-door-unless-I'm-expecting-someone-camp. Put a please do not disturb sign on your door. Totally reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 21:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you actively know the reason why she was sent to live with you? The fact that there are no restrictions here are the entire problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You married someone of whom you knew had little to no sex drive, you almost never have sex and now you're mad about it? What did you think was going to happen? You think it's awful for you? Imagine what it's like being married to someone who whines about a lack of sex when the entire time you've been together, you've known she wasn't into it. Some people are asexual and don't want a sex life at all. 

You're going to have to get used to zero sex life, or you're going to have to file for divorce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaaaand there's the problem. Your aggression. Your girlfriend isn't the problem here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
