<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it depends on age. Like 2% of girls my age find me attractive while 80% of old ladies find me attractive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What ridiculous "inventions" will Apple introduce at next year's keynote presentation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 06:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight Outta Compton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Crabtree Valley Mall shooting in Raleigh, NC. Except there's no evidence of shell casings or a shooting even taking place. That's how uneventful Raleigh is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 20:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing. What did he contribute to GTA and which game in the series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love these kind of redemption stories; I never hear anything like this in the working world. Thank you for being awesome, hope he's still doing well in your business! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eminem, Marilyn Manson or Maynard James Keenan. Sorry, couldn't choose just one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. He's capable of completely changing your mind about something in the span of two minutes during his sets. My favorite comedians are the ones who can make me howl with laughter while making me think critically at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby Boomers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Job recruiters of Reddit, what's the most bizarre resume and cover letter you've read that actually scored the candidate an interview? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peep Show started dropping in quality in the last few series imo. It just didn't have the magic and constant laughs of the first 4 or 5 series. I do like that Mark and Jeremy end up at square one again. Still one of my favorite comedies of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dark Knight. The pencil scene had everyone howling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, let's have a rap battle. What devastating line can you deliver to the commenter above you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe a manageable work-life balance is essential for overall health and well-being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Through rhyme, what is your current life struggle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America's "live to work" mentality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, having a morbid sense of humor. Then I found Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25. Still looking for my first full-time salaried position with benefits. At the moment working 3 jobs, one in retail and the other two that's part time but relevant to what I want to do in life. I can't afford to not live with my parents even with 3 jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 00:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mojo Pin by Jeff Buckley. RIP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The genie of self-consciousness appears out of nowhere and says, "You have one wish, but you can only change one thing you don't like about yourself." What do you change and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 00:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
