<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't seem like you would love those... You said that you do it to people you love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just kill him for real haha. He would have killed you when you were younger... 
or pay someone to kill him, you have money. 

Lawyer up for your wife, her innocence can be proven because it wasn't her.
You seem nice, don't let them ruin it. 

You can't actually get in trouble for murder as the guy is alive.. but he could get done for extortion or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What... He was in a picture... Then killed two girls, and used a cellphone and what. He never got caught? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im fairly certain that Chris was the one eating her... That's why she was doing it he had the money, and maybe she loved him? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 03:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this all started when you got your new job abd started reading the broken GPS.
Now, I'm thinking that the GPS is broken in the car.. and something or someone is causing you this problem on purpose.

The question is why. 
It's obviously escalating now, as you're hearing voices. I thinking that this force whatever it is is trying to wear you down, to make you easier to manipulate or control. Stop using the GPS for a while, maybe walk or use public transport. 
Otherwise you could end up someone bad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont come back, Dont post more. 

This is bad, you should feel bad.
Also, killing animals is not a nice thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 02:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. I didn't see that coming, not at all.
Poor Mary, stuck there with that man... But at least she finally has a bit of peace. I hope she finds the other person, and can finally move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 11:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ask your mum.. if the other girl died, you might have been adopted.
Your family has taken care of you, so I doubt that it's anything sinister.

If you were kidnapped as a replacement, the photo albums would still be decorated and swirly.. because you would be the same child in her mind. (i would say) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 11:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how do you vet the live audiences to make sure that they have the appropriate tastes for the show? How do you make sure that no one reports you?
Where do you get your victims? 

Bit sick aint it? Cooking babies... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 11:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was fairly close to the end that you mentioned her age.
Three weeks is more than enough time to call the appropriate authorities about this girl, who made you feel uncomfortable.
It seems like harmony rules the roost in your house, maybe thats why she brings home strangers all the time. But hopefully after this she learnt some kindof lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 04:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was written as if harmony was much younger. So the entire story all I could think about was how little care you had for her safety.

It kind of spoiled it for me.
Also, I would have just called social services, she clearly needed more help than a futon to sleep on. Your actions could have saved a families lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 04:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sounds lovely..
Her poor eyesight probably makes her even more sensitive to the visions of the spirits, souls etc.
If she was being kept outside and not primarily as a house cat, that would explain some of the other behaviors ie the claws being out a lot and the pacing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but he saw them... Which is worse? :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name of the show?
How can I watch and / or report it to authorities. Either or, depending on the quality of the production.

How did your honest friends buy into this deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would keoni steal money? 
If keoni had stolen the money, he wouldn't have been kept alive.. Generally speaking, if you cross 'the mob' you end up dead. I think the mob knew of his ability, and kept him there for a reason.. maybe to heighten his desire to do things, but the tipster gave the game away maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 03:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very similar to another story I read on creepy pasta (before it went down the toilet) in fact I'd say that it's a rewrite.... Can you confirm that op? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 02:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read that honest Abe post before... But I can't remember where. I saw it posted somewhere, just that.
Kinda creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 03:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for explaining, I just wanted to be sure :)
I painted a really odd imagine in my head haha.

And thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 03:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for replying, I was worried that I missed something :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only confused by one thing... This park, is it like a playground or a park? 
When you say model village is is like a full sized building or mini buildings?

I'm from the UK, and I think I'm using like different definitions haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that plain old elk would come across this sinister :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 02:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the first part? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 11:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you see?
Please tell us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh burn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only comment is that the behavior of this thing is changing, regardless of what you do. It started as taps that got louder, and now it's talking.

You need to try something, especially if the word does mean hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 04:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a bit confusing to read. It was a little jumbled... But very interesting.
But I do wonder why your parents killed so young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 03:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile poor old diddy was in his cage thinking 'im in a crate, how can I come to you?' Must have been super confusing :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 03:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get this one.
It's just too vague... Maybe an update would help out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 03:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuuuuuck. Somehow it's actually worse that she used her own damn legs.
What. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 03:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw keeping the lights on... I'd have tried to sell on asap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you basically lived five nights at freddys huh.
Plus, you watched camera nine and the puppets still attacked you...

Also; what was the shout thing about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed this, I wish that there was more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 11:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An outwards opening front door is so weird! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 11:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, was the cat bowl real?
If so, why was the mum not concerned about anty cat food chilling about the place?

Love the story though, id love to hear more updates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you still in character? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do psychiatrists not get access to doctors notes? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the walkie talkie get under the bed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree, but each to their own.
The black mold may still be around, but the main story concluded a while ago I believe.
Youd have to be pretty unlucky to tango with it now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 05:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was in your room, it doesn't seem like it needed an invite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good to see someone writing a decent goodtime story, not another one of the fan service ones that make no sense.
It's also a bit strange for Alan to be doing a good deed.. but I'm so glad he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The black mold is black mold... This is a creature that dribbles black goo.
If this was the mold, it's too late. It was on her face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're about 10 years old, the police won't tell you off for wasting their time. Especially as you're going to be telling them that this guy has done this loads of times.... And he is scary.
If the guy has a really badly scarred face, that's pretty much an accurate description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, if he had received the proper psychological help he might have been able to live a normal life. Or were you just in it for a paycheck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no need to lose anyone.. the world has a natural order and it cares for itself. It's not man's job to decide who to lose and who to keep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smiling at someone getting hit by a car is not very 'beautiful' behavior.
Fake IDs, breaking the law is not very beautiful behavior. Would your mother enjoy knowing about this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, but you watched... Why did you watch?
Why didn't you get him help?

I'm pretty sure you committed a crime or, or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 02:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for replying, it did help me organize my understanding :)
It very creepy that you saw your own copy.

I'm almost curious to know what the price was to get your town back to it's former self. Almost.

Good luck for the future OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, a poor story leads to poor reception.
You shouldnt blame the audience for the fact that you didn't give them any reason to come back.

I'm sorry. I don't usually give out such hoarse criticism but your response was a little meh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a lot of words, for very little information.
Are you on some divine mission to rid the world of ugly people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I move in? I'd love to be around some supportive ladies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how did you get out? 
I see in the comments above that you refer to a 'he'.... I hope you didn't break character! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 16:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just doesn't make sense.
The other story said that it was a quarry sealed off.. but you kinda described a junk yard or something, in a field.

I dont think the stories are linked to be honest. It doesn't even sound like the same place.. maybe you should have done a bit more research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how did you survive to write this story?
Hurry and let us know!

Did you find any significance to the numbers? Is it a date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No body, no murder... Wouldn't it still be missing persons?
Unless you file for death in absentia or whatever it's called.

How do the police know she died or got hit by a car?
Also, any trial outcomes are listed in public records. So waiting so many years for the police reports was a waste of time.

And again, with the guys name just go straight to public records. Asking random people on the streets is daft....

The story didn't go anywhere. It seems that nosleep is getting a lot of stories like this lately. Series for series sack. No offence man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of ambiguous. I need some more details...

Kids who went swimming disappeared? Was that part of the deal?
That wouldn't make sense though, because of all the passed time.

Did your mum change, or everyone? Did you change or did you see a copy of you? 
Please explain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I different to all women then?
Or do you gals live in a commune? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with the other comments...

Where did the random car come from and where did the tractor go? What does that have to do with the phone and the button?

Also, why do you even want an old phone?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's literally written on the right hand side of every page haha.

No worries, now you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok ok, hold on... That other story is about suspected cult activity in a quarry.

It doesn't seem to have anything to do with this one.

Also, if you have internet signal you'd definitely have calling signal and you don't need credit to call an emergency service.

The other story talks about humanoid 'people' not monsters either.
Are you sure it's related? Or are you just attached to that as the closest possible explanation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of nosleep is presumed real... It's in the rules.

Also, this 'story' doesn't have an ending, of course we want to know more.
Why would I read this otherwise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you were in some shady motel, drunk off your ass you definitely could have left.
Or screamed and called the cops... Pretending to be asleep sounds like the worst idea.

Also, it's for cops to investigate this stuff. Did you not even inform the police? What if he really did kill someone and now is still free to kill or rape again?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even an accident shouldn't involve hiding a body though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what happens in vegas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the rules of this sub liamawesome... Everything here is taken as real.
I hate it when people break that rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't expect this from the title.. and to think, I almost skipped this one.
I'm sorry to hear about this, but as shocking and unbelievable as it is, I hope that someone can learn from your pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 05:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats are a mystical breed of creature all their own. 
They come to us for food and safety, they domesticated themselves... But to a cat, we are just giant hairless cats that can't hunt. So they do sometimes watch over us.
Some people believe that cats can see into our souls, so maybe junior saw your bad dream and came to comfort you.

Also, that dream is messed up. youre probably stressed. I have weird recurring dreams all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 05:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks sally, or carina... You the real mvp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 05:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that they have had a lot of nannies is kinda off putting... The next time they go out, just leave. Go to a motel, or a friends house... If they pay you well, book a plane ride home. 

It's creepy, get out now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 04:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... If all of your skin is gone can you still feel pain?
I mean, if the devil took every layer of skin thats most of your pain receptors right? (serious question)
Couldn't you just live in some kind of rubber suit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 16:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much.

Did your mother not teach you about the beauty within all things?
I'm sure that you mentioned inner and outer beauty. The way hannah acts and speaks, makes it seem as though her beauty is not quite total. Unless that is just the way it has been written.

It shouldn't fall to any one person to decide who is an ugly. Some people would even argue that your constant judgement makes you an ugly.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
