<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7391</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> roll a joint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's apparent you have the time to research it yourself. This is a photo I enjoy so I posted it, who gives a fuck what the caption says or means. If you like/don't like my photo, then that is wonderful, I would love to hear your feedback. There is no need to be a smart ass. Kindly get back to... whatever it is that you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else who has something to say about the picture... Great! I would love to hear it. If it pertains to the caption I would kindly invite you to continually kiss my contiguous ass cheeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it is NOT the highest point on any given road, it's the highest point on a continuous road. There are countless access roads that are NOT continuous, that reach much higher altitudes... like Mt. Evans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is not the wrong word. do some research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said Mt Evans road was a US highway. it is the highest vehicle accessible point in the United States, NOT a highway though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I put this here for you fuck wads to enjoy, not criticize my word choice Jesus fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continuous meaning it doesn't have an 'end', like when you reach the top of Mt. Evans or any other access road. Trail Ridge Road is US Highway 34. It does not end when you reach the highest point, it continues on to Granby or Estes Park (depending on your direction). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I can understand! It is a very unusual spot, indeed. It is unmarked and there is absolutely no area to park your car (observation points are about 1/4 mile in each direction). You would not know this spot were anything special unless you had a RMNP map. I had to stop my car in the middle of the road, and keep an eye out for oncoming traffic, while i took this picture. It was about 80 degrees in Estes Park that day, and a mere 30 degrees at this spot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is indeed! i have been up there. Again, I am talking about the highest US HIGHWAY. I am fully aware of higher access roads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiking Boulder Mountain Park a few weeks ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trail Ridge Road (U.S. 34) in Rocky Mountain National Park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
