<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8477</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on gods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-02 01:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother is a christian. She had indoctrinated since birth by my grandparents. I don't think them to have been unpleasant people. I conclude that they too were recruited into the religion at an early age and so on and so forth. 

My take on god is such that, I view them to be a hindrance on personal willpower. My mother, a fiscally responsible nurse of about forty years, credits her god with her success. When I stated that she was a good parent and person not because her religious beliefs, but because of her hard work and excellent moral compass, she said,

"Don't say things like that because I don't want to die yet."

As if taking credit for her own hard work was some sort of sin. Gods will make a person weak and doubtful of their own abilities. They will torment the mind of an otherwise reasonable person. God are petty, greedy and spiteful. Even if gods had existed, they wouldn't be worthy of our love and praise. Gods are immature children. I'm sure this sentiment is shared with many others in the world, but I felt a distinct need to articulate my feelings in prose.

Thank you for taking the time to read my useless rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A child with me or would anyone do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 00:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just thinking about some of the shows and movies that portray some women as being in a hurried frenzy to have children. The motive is so strong that they schedule sex, nag their SO for sex at the "right" time, etc. Then there is real life. Women such as Nadia Suleman (I name here because of her prominence in the media spotlight), have eight babies and no father in the picture. I realize this isn't the case for all women, but I am curious as to whether the desire to have a child outweighs the decision as to with whom you will have the child. Sure seemed that way with Mr. Brad Pitt. Although, I know nothing of his personal life, so please take that last part as blatant speculation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 20:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. Greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 20:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a bit perturbed by that last bit in the article. I felt tricked. Deceived even. Please understand that religion has nothing to do with this. It even seems as though there is a slily bit of mockery involved. The article clearly states that the scientist, Peter Higgs, isn't at all amused by the nickname given to the particle and then the religious portion, which does all of the work accomplished by these dedicated scientists a great discredit, is included. Very crass, very inappropriate and very disrespectful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 06:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you mind giving the title and edition of that book please? It would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 18:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest calling a free clinic in your area, if there is one, and asking just to make sure. You're going to have to take the time to call and ask your health care providers questions regarding whether or not insurance will cover it and if so, how much of it they will cover.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 17:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Question has nothing to do with those subs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 17:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if you're in America or not. Even then, I'm not sure this would apply just because you are. Is there no free clinic available to you in your area? I've received HIV testing for free that way. 

edit: sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suddenly...Relationship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 17:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was helping my neighbor set up her grill so that her and her friend could make some burgers. I heard them talking behind me and in a louder voice my neighbor says to her friend, "Oh, this is my new boyfriend".

Now, I know she was kidding, but it made me think about others out there.  Have any of you guys/gals ever sprung this on someone and meant it? Conversely, have you ever been put in that situation and thought, "Guess I'm in a relationship" ?

edit: sense.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random mumblings from a bumbling idiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 22:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not well versed in many things. I don't have the best social skills. I do, however, know people.  I'm nearing thirty years and I feel as though people are the one thing that I have learned very well. What I am thinking, so are others. What I am doing, so are others. Thus, it is easy to decipher the halfhearted smile you give at nights end. Even easier to detect is the lie that you just told me. You are convinced that I am not aware or your treachery, but I am. I'm noting everything.  Keeping record of your discord and taking in future lessons of future people. 

I do apologize for my rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
