<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7051</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 16:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people think that life is all about money and success and fame. Some people do not need vast amounts of money, or want fame. Each person has their own measure of success and obviously this gentleman prefers to live simply, doing what he loves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 16:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, figuratively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 04:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogtor. I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 03:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This broke my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 23:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm much better now. I feel a huge weight lifted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 03:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore it isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 03:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My calico had a calico kitten, a grey tabby kitten and a ginger kitten in the same litter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 20:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to stand up for yourself and be honest. I can't afford to buy you lunch, you need to cut back on your expenses to afford food for your kids, I have responsibilities during the day, you aren't my priority. If she can't handle your honest, truthful life, she will back away. You need to start living life for you and not others. You'll feel much better for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 18:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally was able to run five times this week since rolling my car in November and injuring both shoulders, my neck and back. Feels great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 15:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I giggled when I saw this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Baby Polar Bear Discovering Snow For The First Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 18:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 21:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. Now I have to drag out my earthworm boots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 15:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, like throwing a grenade in a cancer ward, people don't get to end it on their own terms, it ends up ugly and complicated. Innocent people get hurt by cheating, just like if you throw a grenade in a cancer ward, and remember, people survive cancer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 15:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she'll cheat on him, she'll cheat on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have grouse in rural Alberta, those things are stupid as fuck. If they see a car coming they freeze. Icy roads at 80km/hr is no time to become a grouse lover. Those sons a bitches die over me hitting the ditch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are up to two grouse on our Roadkill Bingo Tally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 18:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to say congrats on the weight loss! GREAT job!! You losing weight has exposed the women in your office's self-consciousness. They don't REALLY have a problem with you looking good. They have a problem with themselves NOT looking like you. That is their problem. Keep on keeping on, honey. The good people will weed themselves from the bad. Let them talk, because they are just making themselves look like the bitter old bitties that they are. You look fabulous, you feel fabulous, DO NOT let their jealousy take that away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 15:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because this guy has a problem other people can't? Good theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it even have to be classified? Why does sexuality have to be a black or white issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it's sickening. If he wants to get a blowjob from a dude, all the power to him. If this was a better world this wouldn't even HAVE to be a Confession Bear. Just the fact that he has to hide who he's attracted to proves this world is still too full of hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep that with you! Your hobbies, work and loves will keep you sane! And now you don't have to feel guilty!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like you've taken a lot of the right steps on your own. Glad you found your way to the amazing place where you'll realize, not only are you NOT crazy, you're NOT alone either!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same thing, "ohhhhh, typo", but then thought "but is it, really?". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 03:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell you how lucky I got. My husband latched on and never, ever let go. My mom was N and my Dad was relatively normal. My hubby is much like him, but a hundred times better. OP, you deserve someone great. Try not to fight love too much, it can be hard at first, but if you let yourself go to it (it'll take work) it'll be the best thing that ever happens to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 15:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My shared mailbox has two larger boxes. When you get a parcel they leave the key in your mailbox. You retrieve your parcel and deposit the key in the mail slot for mail in the shared box. It's brilliant (and rather exciting when you discover the key in your mailbox!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 14:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stated a CLEARLY obvious double standard in today's society. You inferred the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 05:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little sterilization goes a LONG way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 23:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is practically required. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 23:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect is earned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 22:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you try to punish everyone that pisses you off you are in for a stressful life. Keep your cool and your happy and you've already proved that they are a jerk and you are better than them. Just because they need to learn a lesson doesn't mean you have to be the one to do it. You can change exactly one person in this life. Yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 22:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And no Daredevil movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 22:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see you edited your original post from 30 paragraphs to 6 that still ramble on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 01:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to call bullshit on this. It's sex. Your outdated beliefs do not negate the fact that a man with many sexual partners is a stud, but a woman with many sexual partners is a slut. What if she had to work reall hard to sleep with those guys? Does that change the dynamic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 01:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree! How antiquated is it that men have to do all the convincing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 01:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Promiscuity". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 01:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could I get the Cliff's Notes of that? I was too damn lazy to read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 00:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daaaaang.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 00:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Men are studs, women are sluts. FOR THE SAME BEHAVIOR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 20:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the same could be said about arousal responses and rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's we called it for ours. We gave the command "House" and she went into it to be locked up for the day. It was nice knowing she was safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 19:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you give them a favorite toy of treat when you put them in it they start to look at it as a reward. When we got my dog as a puppy she was crated for two years, she's now to large to comfortably fit most crates, and trained well enough not to need one, but the crate is really an assets to puppy training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 19:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evil woman. I like her style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 04:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY BAD. Thought you were talking about the powder. There are only two or three flavors available where I am from, so Mio is our choice. I prefer the Nesfruita Orange-Mango flavor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 03:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Powdery aftertaste BLECH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 02:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm drinking a $6.99 bottle of wine from Costco. But I'm happy! CHEERS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 02:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so drunk that one-half symbol is weirding me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I wouldn't doubt it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was talking to my husband when I noticed something watching me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Albertan here, as a kid we called it "face-washing". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 05:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're gonna die, bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think your wife appreciates you calling her fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google-fu. I like that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than in the off position! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This entire thread is KILLING ME. I'm so sorry about Isabelle. I have three cats and a dog to hug VERY tight. Gotta go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like my Willis. We moved six months ago to an acreage, so now he has to worry more about coyotes and less about cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 01:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddammit. My girl Abby had to be put down a few years ago at 13. She was a ball of claws and attitude and only loved me and had teeth rotting out of her head. The vet told us the stress from getting her teeth pulled and getting labs for her incontinence would probably kill her. It was a hard damned decision. Thinking about her makes me cry all over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 00:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. Yes. _  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 23:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragging the .crx to the extensions page is key. Missed it the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 23:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the country with the SHITTIEST internet service in the world. It took me 20 min to watch a 10 min clip last night because the fucking thing kept pausing, skipping and farting its way along. This was a very well timed post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 17:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> APPLE CIDER VINEGAR, Thank-you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 06:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those cheap brand cookies are AWESOME! Especially with 17 and 11 year old boys who devour everything in their path. Cheap, full of fat, DELICIOUS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get complex migraines from things like this, computer screens, fluorescent lights, etc. not as bad as seizures (my son is epileptic, however) so I agree, that while cool, it needed a tag, for safety! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Migraines too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 23:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept expecting "BLAM!"

"OOPS, Sorry, Fluffy!". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 21:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an IUD and had very little pain with both the initial insertion and the removal and re-insertion of the new one. Like a little pinch when it went in and done. Bled for maybe an hour, then I have had maybe three periods in the seven years total I've had it. The periods are so light they could be considered light spotting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 06:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is the cutest thing I've read today :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 04:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tricksy hobbitses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 03:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son has been working part time for a year and a half. He's saved up and bought a computer, a second monitor, his own clothes and paid his own way to France and Germany for his school's Spring Break Trip. I'm super proud of him and he's definitely learned the value of hard work, as well as become super independent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 01:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And another hug. Please keep us updated, if anything so you have a place to vent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 22:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a blanket statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 07:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flannel: Yum. Beard: YUMMMM. Cock: YUMMY YUM YUMMY YUM.

Yum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 21:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We took many parenting classes that help IMMENSELY. I HIGHLY recommend that if you are having problems with your children acting out that you look both at the children AND yourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 21:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there is an audience and everybody is patting them on the back thinking it is clever or funny this narcissistic behavior is justifiable to them, and others that will copy this. Of course, a true narcissist hardly needs approval to justify narcissistic behavior. Social Media panders to narcissists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 17:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do periodic clean-outs still, as well. I just don't like having people on my Facebook for the sake of having people on my Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 17:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to look at the ROOT of what acting out is. Acting out is a cry for attention. With children even negative attention is attention. They are doing ANYTHING they can do to get your attention. A lot of families have very high expectations for behavior but do not ever acknowledge when their children are behaving good. They expect it. They never praise the good, we always punish the bad. With children, they begin to realise that if they want a parents attention, they need to act badly because the good behavior is ignored. This needs to change. If you want good behavior from your children, make sure that you reward it even in small ways, such as praise and rewards. My son, who is 11 has had behavioral problems for 8+ years and it wasn't until we moved to a reward for good behavior model that he did a 180 in his behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 17:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's on par, just that it's justified narcissism now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 09:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can neither claim it nor disclaim it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 08:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, humiliating a child is NEVER a good way to punish them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 08:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously, seriously fear for the new generation of kids being brought up. Social media is not a parenting platform. STOP TRYING TO OUT-PARENT EVERYONE ELSE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 06:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mirena here, best thing EVER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 06:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My "audience" is family and people I 100% trust. About 50 people. It's a very supportive environment for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 06:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why anyone wouldn't! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 06:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That feature is being removed from Facebook, I had mine set to that as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 05:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being in a bad mood is no excuse to be an asshole to someone who is doing their job by assisting you. If that annoys, maybe you should shop online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 01:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eeeeeeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 20:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you meant in the country. Ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 13:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute cheeks! No...not those ones ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 04:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwwwww. I LOVE YOU AGAIN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 04:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 04:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. I have gone off on disability several times both on EI and on private insurance for mental illness related claims. If anything Canada is MORE understanding about mental illness that most countries I have read on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 23:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU'RE KILLING ME!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 23:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that shit is behind a paywall. I'm the lacky at my work that has to drive my ass to the nearest University to get it for free. SUCKS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 23:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is making me ill, between you and backwards elbow guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 23:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally squirmed in my chair reading that ICKYYUCKYICKYPOOEY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 22:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nardledanglers. Jim and the Twins. I got some new material today. My boys are going to hate me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 22:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother did this. I still have nightmares. WHY?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 18:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Orwell's 1984. I read it in High School. Thought I'd hate. LOVED it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 01:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My NMom told me about the "towel" my Dad kept beside the bed for.......things I shouldn't know at that age. And that he bloodied her nose (she did it herself to make him look bad) and so many other things, just like those you said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 01:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I VOLUNTEER AS TRIBUTE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 00:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother died of cancer two years ago, the bitch deserved it. If you're an asshole, so am I. I'm not an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 00:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My horrid mother, who I hadn't talked to in years, died of cancer a few years back. Sometimes cancer is GREAT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 22:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOWZA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK-YOU. I read it on the recommendation of a friend and it started off good and then just fizzled. So bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 01:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. That's a really awful idea. You have to wait until you're ready. Do not make another puppy suffer because you got it on a whim out of grief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 01:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like douchebitches. They just happen to stereotypically (well, here in Alberta they do) be over-make-upped, Lululemon wearing, Ugg boot strutting, Coach bag carrying, Starbucks sipping entitled douchebitches. I love Lulu and Northface, for working out in/camping in. But I prefer to spend my hard earned cash on the shit that ACTUALLY matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 16:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I say I didn't like them? Well, I hate Uggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
