<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4858</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 12:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this related to the oil corruption reports? If not it is convenient that reports about individuals leak now distracting us all from the global rigging and corruption in an industry blamed for starting wars and defrauding everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 12:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you be happy with your own house or your parents house having shitty tags sprayed on them? That's what is getting sprayed, shit tags not epic cat faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 12:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Links to some articles on how bad she was.
http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/fighting_words/2003/10/mommie_dearest.html https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=65JxnUW7Wk4 https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2015/02/25/why-to-many-critics-mother-teresa-is-still-no-saint/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 20:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I KNEW porn was true!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do keep up, you are several years out of date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you live where firefighters and cops are on shit pay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 11:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that it seems to be all about setting legal precedent surely the tech giants would have a common interest in preventing that precedent getting set? Perhaps an industry lobby group that could fund legal defence costs if a smaller company or start up needed it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 00:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where we're going, we won't need eyes to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Illuminati will do anything to bring a successful man down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some old people music.

N-Joi Live in Manchester. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=egpIbXJEee4
Altern8 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GnqAuRHgIsg
LFO LFO https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HROMVIHGpLE
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 13:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That mosque is a nightmare and is heavily mired in the nepotism and racism commonly found in Pakistan, clannish and one hand washing the other. So is the internal political scene in the community, it is all very opaque and insider. Hopefully more moderates can gain control of the mosque.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 10:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know what would happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 10:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this? Sushi for ants? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emma Watson feminism? Strong woman role model? Please! Natalie Portman will fuck you up! 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7D4gRq4_aAQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that and naked children flying around... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ground is lower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 12:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the point they didn't need to go outside their own community because their targets and aims were so small whereas Irish republican terrorism crossed borders and tried to fight a country so needed lots more funding and resources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 12:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Loyalist terrorists were very local and only needed a small amount of guns and small amount of bombs to kill Republican Nationalist terrorists random Catholics to maintain division in the society. Needing fewer resources they could be easily supported from within their own community. The IRA was international in scope needing logistics to attack and train overseas, and needed a much larger volume of arms to try to fight the police and army.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 12:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immigration has fucked public services in many areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 10:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if he is a massive roided up gym bro and he is shouting at you there is all probability he will just make his point "win" then walk off. If another unknown man gets in his face that isn't looking like a pro heavyweight MMA fighter there is every chance he is going to get a beating. When men chat shit and get in each others face it will often lead to violence. White knighting is fine online in the office etc but there is a chance you are going to get your ass kicked. Its not fair but if there is no physical violence sometimes best to not create it. Watch a cop show and see how hard it is to stop a gym freak kicking off. I know it is totally unfair but just pointing out that the people who watch bullying are not actually worse than the bullies. 
Edit: seen OPs replies further down and it is way out of order that staff or his friends didn't calm him down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 11:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you use fb or google? You volunteered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 11:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Germans conducted large scale bombing of civilian targets first and set the tone. Sow the wind etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all seriousness it would only take a few ISIS pamphlets or maybe some neo nazi propaganda on your laptop or in your workshop/bomb factory and you will be in jail. Top tip don't take any tourist photos as you travel/recce near airports or popular attractions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not fear, anger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still probably less murder and assaults than amongst the USA ghettos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? You think the Tories are the biggest proponents of the nanny state? The Tories are the least nanny state party except for UKIP. Labour is far more nanny state, in Scotland the SNP are creating a nanny state (for better or worse). So you clearly don't support Cameron but look at the voting numbers the majority of Britons do support the nanny state if you think the Tories are a nanny state party because the rest are about more social control by government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way Bush was as stupid as his public persona was made out to be. I think it was genius image management like mild trumpism and done to get a specific demographics vote, just like how he became a cowboy from Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 23:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comedian Glen wool on Al Qaeda vs China 03:30

http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=6e8_1337549919 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lump lingered last in line for brains and the one she got was kind of rotten and insane....

Fucking zombies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a trap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it wasn't 1 bad cop it was 5 plus the rest on radios aware of the "incident" that required 5 cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they prisoners? No number six, it is a real bus stop.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 09:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Galaxy quest probably quite close to the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know they have courts and a legal process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 09:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some journalists used to be respected pros. Even back in the hay days of print media there were always scumbag hacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 09:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ren%C3%A9e_Richards. Great tennis career move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 11:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Norwegian athletics team is about to get really good!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 15:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the John McLean/Samuel L Jackson Harlam social experiment video? Prank with a vengeance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 14:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Roman Catholics were enforcing this there would be outrage and demonstrations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scumbags.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 23:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geo F Trumpers west indian lime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 20:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insanity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collecting knives as a hobby. I don't mean having a few knives for different things but the collectors usually banging on about the EDC loadout have 100 of a very similar knife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just shaking there head thinking what a cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is like  - What the fuck did you just fucking say about me, you little bitch?Ill have you know I graduated top of my class in the Navy Seals -   was written just for him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct! See the De Lisle carbine.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/De_Lisle_carbine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What changed? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in the 80s/90s everyones mates had escorts ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if there is a hint of steam somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL women are just as corrupt as men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assembling a crack commando unit that was sent to prison by a military court for a crime they didn't commit. These men promptly escaped from a maximum security stockade to the Los Angeles underground. Today, still wanted by the government they survive as soldiers of fortune. If you have a problem, if no one else can help, and if you can find them....maybe you can hire The A-Team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must really struggle with most of your maps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex panther is NOT a recognised treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 15:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well once you hit your late 20's.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we can create driverless lorries then why not driverless tube trains that run in tunnels on tracks? Or trams systems? Automate the London tube system and make it open 24/7 roving ticket inspectors for safety, job done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank god some knowledge to counter the general ignorance and received wisdom of the Oirish history. They still go on about Cromwell FFS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 11:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.standard.co.uk/news/heroin-wars-loan-sharks-and-executions-the-turkish-gangs-terrorising-north-london-6795004.html

http://www.theguardian.com/society/2015/dec/20/heroin-gangs-london-wood-green-shooting

http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-21592288

http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/news/6813429/The-slap-that-led-to-the-bloody-gangland-war-that-ripped-North-London-to-pieces.html

The money laundering part is common to all crime gangs and might vary where you live but usually small cash transactions so traditionally pubs could run phantom stock through the books with a front man as licensee but any business could run extra phantom customers through it. It could be taxis, tanning salons, manned car washes or site security all of these industries are dominated by crime gangs in some big cities. And you wouldn't know as a customer but you would know if you tried to open competition. Remember it is not TV they don't need to launder truck loads of cash a lot of their money will disappear into the black economy, hookers, drugs and cash spending like flash holidays, clothes, clubs. Their cars will be leased so they only need to put through enough money to show they legally paid a mortgage, normal expenses and some legal cash to invest in more small businesses so these things won't be taken by the state if they get found guilty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 22:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$$$$$$$$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 22:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you live but much of the serious orgainised crime in many places is exactly from the Turkish/Kurdish diaspora who quietly import and wholesale the drugs. The piss poor immigrant who you think owns the kebab shop, barbers shop, taxi firm etc either is a front man or has borrowed money or rents from "friends" then runs a percentage of extra business through the till. However that only applies to the ones who are actually fronts for money laundering most aren't and far from being piss poor a decent takeaway will be raking it in. Plenty of owners nipping around in Mercs and BMs and plenty of cash business. 

But the point was that they wouldn't be there if no one ate from them - supply and demand - isn't as clear cut as you might think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 18:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless they are laundering money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 14:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The black woman? Did no one at any of the production meetings think it was just a little racist and demeaning? The original black character Winston in 1984 was less of a stereotype and basically represented the "everyman" character anybody could identify with. If he had been as cliched as the modern African American character they would have needed Flavor Flav to play him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 14:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True and way more stereotyped and demeaning to black people than Winston was in 1984. She is hyper black in a way Winston wasn't and is borderline racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 12:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they will be spared Glee re-runs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 21:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what protestant influence has to do with anything. Perhaps it is just America is a young country without a long history of anything let alone dealing with prostitution. All the other countries have history and culture going back thousands of years and that tends to give a broader perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 10:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you haven't read about Yellowstone super volcano yet. Canada is toast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 10:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ever say that to an archaeologist or they will laugh at you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 09:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes not acid but the exact opposite something extremely alkaline like caustic soda, drain cleaner etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 17:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those fucking Danes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 16:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleopatra really is not a good example of a woman being written out of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 20:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want retro homage... https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oMLCrzy9TEs list=RDoMLCrzy9TEs#t=70 The running man will never die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 13:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America really seems to be reveling in its own ignorance and outrage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 13:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More cashing in on tumblr wave feminism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 13:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 19:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps a purple one? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=us4_Wllv65w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuclear deterrence works, see lack of nuclear war for details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 11:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is "burglarized" optimised?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 19:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah just don't have 3.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 12:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ish he a shpy? Becaush if he ishn't a shpy I'll do it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 12:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have a space program but still third world.
Edit - Third world/ developing country blah blah. And the comment is based on the article. Did anyone read it? Poor animal control guy knows his stuff but is ignored by police and all the people there  which makes the cat freak out he is then badly bitten. Do the police take him to the hospital? No a bystander takes him to the hospital where the wrong type of doctor messes him up, then some members of the public try to take him to a proper doctor at a different hospital but he is not allowed to leave until he pays his bill for the crap treatment. But he lost his wallet in the cat attack and have the police by now found his money and rushed to the hospital to help him? No, a member of the public has to pay his bill before the shit hospital will let him go. These are the problems not the fact there was a leopard trapped in a building! The leopard was captured and moved deep into a forest park it is just a shame that the civil authorities response was so bad, feel sorry for the animal control guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 12:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to see if they let fph back yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 09:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is only applying the same standards that USA applies to the rest of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 19:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck did you just fucking say about me, you little bitch? Ill have you know I graduated top of my class, and Ive been involved in numerous secret raids and stuff, and I have over 300 confirmed girls and beers. I am trained in gorilla warfare and Im the top sniper in the internets. You are nothing to me but just another target. I will wipe you the fuck out with precision the likes of which has never been seen before on this Earth, mark my fucking words. You think you can get away with saying that shit to me over the Internet? Think again, fucker. As we speak I am contacting my secret network of 4chans across the USA and your IP is being traced right now so you better prepare for the storm, maggot. The storm that wipes out the pathetic little thing you call your life. Youre fucking dead, kid. I can be online anywhere, anytime, and I can kill you in over seven hundred ways, and thats just with my bare hands. Not only am I extensively trained in things, but I have access to the entire training program of the United States Marine Corps and I will use it to its full extent to wipe your miserable ass off the face of the continent, you little shit. If only you could have known what unholy retribution your little clever comment was about to bring down upon you, maybe you would have held your fucking tongue. But you couldnt, you didnt, and now youre paying the price, you goddamn idiot. I will shit fury all over you and you will drown in it. Youre fucking dead, kiddo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ultimate irony is the moral high ground is occupied by someone who chose the username cocaine_anus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe just learn how to storm beaches properly?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except in most of Europe less lethal weapons like the tazer can only be used to prevent violence or threat of violence. The cops would be in jail in most of EU.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just getting the best ice cream on the planet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil money is what changed and the ability to fund and export your particular shitty version of Islam. Saudi Arabia we are looking at you. Also Iran went the wrong way too but that can't be blamed on the Saudis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 19:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP bet his sense of humour let him appreciate T-Wogz pirate radio https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3z9uLdARaNU   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 16:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammar schools were before comprehensive schools. Comprehensive education closed many grammar schools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
