<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7338</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, What Did You Do Last Night? The Economics of Infidelity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 21:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research paper on "Are Preferential Agreements Significant for the World Trade Structure? A Network Community Analysis" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 10:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 23:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract: We match individual senators voting behavior on legislative proposals with 24 real referendum decisions on exactly the same issues with identical wording. This setting allows us to evaluate the median voter models quality with revealed constituents preferences. Results indicate a limited explanatory power of the median voter model: It explains 17.6% points more than random voting and that a senators probability to accept a proposal in parliament increases on average by 8.4% points when the district median voter accepts the proposal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evidence against the Median Voter Theorem from referendum decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 23:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 08:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to the free version: http://degreesofdemocracy.net/Soroka Wlezien%28ES%29.pdf

Here is the abstract: Although previous research demonstrates that proportionality positively impacts the congruence between the positions of the government and the public after elections, recent work argues and shows that proportionality dampens policy responsiveness in between elections. Why this is true is unclear, however. This paper considers how proportionality matters for policy responsiveness, focusing on two primary suspects: (1) the friction associated with coalitions in proportional systems and (2) the comparatively weaker electoral incentives in those systems. In this paper we first assess the general effect of electoral systems, showing that results are robust across measures, and also that the impact of electoral systems increases exponentially alongside party fragmentation. We then examine two alternative mechanisms at work in proportional systems, and preliminary results point towards the potential importance of government fractionalization in accounting for weakened inter-election responsiveness. In the concluding section we consider implications for our understanding of democratic representation, and also for future research on opinion-policy congruence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Differences Between the Majoritarian and Proportional Visions and Democratic Responsiveness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 08:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Establishments reduce investments shortly before funding: Using German establishment panel data to analyze the effects of economic promotion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 08:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the abstract: ummary

It has been shown that higher levels of subjective well-being lead to greater work productivity, better physical health and enhanced social skills. Because of these positive externalities, policymakers across the world should be interested in attracting and retaining happy and life-satisfied migrants. This paper studies the link between life satisfaction and one's intentions to move abroad. Using survey data from 35 European and Central Asian countries, I find a U-shaped association between life satisfaction and emigration intentions: it is the most and the least life-satisfied people who are the most likely to express intentions to emigrate. This result is found in countries with different levels of economic development and institutional quality. The instrumental variable results suggest that higher levels of life satisfaction have a positive effect on the probability of reporting intentions to migrate. The findings of this paper raise concerns about possible happiness drain in migrant-sending countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Higher levels of subjective well-being lead to greater work productivity, better physical health and enhanced social skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 08:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 23:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract: In this paper I discuss the effectiveness of foreign aid from a historical perspective. I show that foreign aid is a relatively new concept in economics, and I emphasize the role of exchange rate policies in the foreign aid controversies of the 1970s through 1990s. I show that in the early 1980s there were major changes in views regarding aid and agriculture. I emphasize the role of ownership of aid programs by the recipient countries as a way of increasing effectiveness. I argue that there is little hope of making progress in these debates if the economics profession continues to rely, almost exclusively, on cross section regressions. In order to move forward, these analyses need to be supplemented by in depth case studies that follow a country's history for many decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 16:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is /r/globaldev but there are only a few users.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 14:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends what you want to do... STATA or R are great for statistics and econometrics. For symbolic computation Mathematica and Maple are fantastic tools. I would try to be open for different software. Personally, I prefer R to STATA but that is a matter of taste. The cool and modern stuff is for R but STATA is more convenient in many ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract: We use the UK Labor Force survey to investigate whether the socio-economic outcomes of people born on the 13th day of the month, and of those born on Friday the 13th, differ from the outcomes of people born on more auspicious days. In many European countries, including the UK, number 13 is considered unlucky and Friday the 13th is seen as an especially unlucky day. We find little evidence that people born on the 13th or those born on Friday the 13th are significantly less likely to be employed, earn lower wages or that they are more likely to stay unmarried compared to people born on other days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
