<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 02:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was one for the few films to deal with the financial crisis well and expose the corrupt heart of rampant capitalism.  Cate Blanchett's performance is unbelieveable, though the character owes a massive debt to Blanche DuBois, and Allen is clearly more comfortable writing priviliged characters than poor ones, which were a cartoonish, but that aside, a brave and important film.  One about the world we live in now rather than superhero escapism hollywood spoonfeeds us everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 02:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the worst movie I've seen in the last year.  I didn't have high expectations but I did think I was in for a reasonably sci fi thriller.  It was a hodge podge of different unrelated ideas, like three different movies stuck together.  Ideas are introduced and never explored, the clones!  What's with the fucking clones?  Oh right it's an excuse to stitch on a ridiculous happy ending.  Excuse me why I go puke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fascinating in depth expose of the pharmaseutical industries manipulations of the FDA and the deadly cost to unwitting consumers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Side Effects May Include Death: The Story Of The Biggest Advance In Birth Control Since The Pill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 17:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 00:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really sorry, man.  I hope you can get through this and love again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 00:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **No help for that** - *a poem by Charles Bukowski I saw today that I thought was relevant -
*




There is a place in the heart that will never be filled


a space


and even during 

the best moments

and

the greatest times

we will know it


we will know it more than ever

There is a place in the heart that will never be filled

and

we will wait

and wait

in that space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refillable electronic cigarettes face EU ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 19:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Football faces a legal challenge that could result in the end of transfer fees and have as big an impact on the game as the landmark Bosman ruling. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 19:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 04:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing photograph, you forget they had to sleep there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Most Powerful Weapon Against Wall Street? The Rise of Reverse Eminent Domain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 04:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Most Powerful Weapon Against Wall Street? The Rise of Reverse Eminent Domain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 04:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suarez: Reds must maintain charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 02:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'despite all my rage I'm still just a rat in a cage.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Phone Program Likely Unconstitutional, Federal Judge Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 20:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Supreme Court Declares Pussy Riot Sentence Unlawful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 23:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it hasn't.  I remember at interview when he was at UTD he was asked who had the greatest influence on his career and he said Alex Ferguson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Scorsese suggests possible retirement from directing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 15:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 21:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but remember Ferguson launched this round of recriminations by breaking the dressing room code to sell books.  Pretty shitty move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 23:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, message me if you want to talk again sometime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, no worries, get that [book](http://www.amazon.co.uk/s/?ie=UTF8 keywords=brain+lock+schwartz tag=googiehydra-21 index=stripbooks hvadid=3947355210 hvpos=1t1 hvexid= hvnetw=g hvrand=1063154281716127755 hvpone= hvptwo= hvqmt=b hvdev=c ref=pd_sl_yhvbg3fn2_b) and see a shrink!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 16:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you are not a pedophile, you are suffering from OCD, pure and simple.  Have you read Jeff Scwhartz's book Brian lock?  One of the things I took from it is when you have an OCD thought, instead of being drawn into it, say 'it's not me, it's my OCD.'  Your OCD is telling you you're a pedophile but it is and will always be a liar.  Have you got any treatment for OCD, medication can lessen it quite a bit.  Also meditation is a great way to create some calm in your mind and lessen anxiety.  Please get as much help as you can for yourself, I know it is a very hard battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 03:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just wait and see.  Manchester united are more used to winning things than any other club in the premier league.  Will they stick by Moyes if they finish midtable? Because that's where they are right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll see if he's still there next season, if results keep going this way pressure will mount, doesn't matter how long his contract is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great analysis of the current state of capitalism and society in America by David Simon, creator of the Wire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Simon: 'There are now two Americas. My country is a horror show' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 05:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, I've struggled with self loathing and chose some bad partners because I felt I didn't deserve better and when I had good partners I unconsciously sabotaged them because I felt I wasn't good enough for them and it was only a matter of time before they discovered that.  Really get counseling if you want to keep the relationship, it will help you a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six Things Nelson Mandela Believed That Most People Won't Talk About </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 16:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six Things Nelson Mandela Believed That Most People Won't Talk About </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 16:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six Things Nelson Mandela Believed That Most People Won't Talk About </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 16:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 04:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weird guy in American movie played the character again in one of the scary movie parodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 04:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just a guess but I'm going to give analyzing you a go.  Maybe deep down you don't love yourself, in fact you hate yourself and are convinced you are not worthy of a good person's love.  You fear one day he is going to see you for the horrible person you think you really are and then leave you, which would be devastating.  The only defense you think you have against this scenario happening is to sabotage the relationship so he gets hurt first and you get hurt less.  Fear and self loathing.  If this is the case then you need to seek counselling to trash it all out.  But obviously you would need to try to begin to love yourself.  The key to this to begin to view yourself with compassion, the same compassion you would give someone you love deeply.  Take note of all the good points you have, all the times you are loving and understanding and kind and you can begin to change your view of yourself.  Hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greencore, the 1bn-valued sandwich maker run by Agriculture Minister Simon Coveney's brother Patrick, had an effective tax rate of just one per cent this year, as sales smashed through the 1.4bn barrier. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 01:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gareth Bale vs Real Valladolid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 01:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reverse-Engineering a Genius (Has a Vermeer Mystery Been Solved?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 00:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 02:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm inclined to agree with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 02:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bullshit.  The story is from the 20th of May.  Mark Mahon has been pushing his Boru script for years to no avail, no-one will pony up the money after the pile of shit that was strength and honour.  So, he's released it as a graphic novel and made up the story about it being filmed next year to garner some publicity.  There's no studio attached, no actors, no crew, nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish woman found in London house held for more than 30 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 01:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great, keep on keeping on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Taoiseach Bertie Ahern the victim of attempted assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 01:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad Branded Unfit Parent For Refusing To Take Son To McDonald's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 01:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google reveals purpose of Those Mysterious Barges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 01:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google reveals purpose of Those Mysterious Barges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 01:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel winner Stiglitz warns of Irelands lost decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 21:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Lydon reveals Mick Jagger secretly paid Sid Vicious legal fees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 21:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Handouts For Frackers: The Pennsylvania Plan to Give Drillers $1 Billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 20:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Secret to Breaking Out of Our Most Destructive Habits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 20:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Jane Got a Gun' Producers Allege Lynne Ramsay Was Drunk and 'Abusive' On Set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 20:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Scorsese On Set Gallery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 20:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In radical departure from tradition, Pope ASKS his flock about gay marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 12:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garda identify girl found on OConnell Street in Dublin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 22:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Martin ONeill: Ill be the bad cop, Roy will be the bad, bad cop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 21:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love/Hate actor in court on drug rap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 15:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 worrying signs that Ireland has developed notions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 15:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two billion planets in our galaxy may be suitable for life, far more than previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 01:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two billion planets in our galaxy may be suitable for life, far more than previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 01:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 02:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Dunphy, he is a bit fickle and calls for the managers head very quickly, but isn't that how most fans think too?  I remember he called for Staunton's head after two games, which seemed ridiculous but he was ultimately right.  Also, he's great entertainment, otherwise it would be like the English panels, full of bland platitudes and meaningless cliches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 02:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's warmed to him a bit again since, but he doesn't have the hard on he had for him during the Saipan days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.thescore.ie/eamon-dunphy-roy-keane-rant-irish-fans-spain-euro-2012-ireland-488499-Jun2012/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the only way this might work is if O'Neill tells Roy he can't talk to the media.  I still expect an Epic fallout somewhere along the way when Roy decides the players and O'Neill aren't up to his standards.  But I don't care, it's going to be great drama.  I sometimes think I enjoy the soap opera aspect of the game more than the game itself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 01:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah, he turned on Roy years ago.  Eamonn's passions run hot but they burn out quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corcaighn [little Cork] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 21:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA surveillance: Merkel's phone may have been monitored 'for over 10 years' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 22:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic Temperatures Reach Highest Levels In 44,000 Years, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic Temperatures Reach Highest Levels In 44,000 Years, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic Temperatures Reach Highest Levels In 44,000 Years, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Eszterhas: 'Mel Gibson needs help' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Eszterhas: 'Mel Gibson needs help' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NC GOP official fired after bragging voter ID law would kick the Democrats butt on The Daily Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 00:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NC GOP official fired after bragging voter ID law would kick the Democrats butt on The Daily Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 00:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Yemen Drone Strike Creates 40 To 60 New Enemies, Former U.S. Official Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 02:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Yemen Drone Strike Creates 40 To 60 New Enemies, Former U.S. Official Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 02:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retired Catholic Priest Gets Married To Jewish Partner Of 20 Years in New Jersey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 22:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retired Catholic Priest Gets Married To Jewish Partner Of 20 Years in New Jersey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 22:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ian Holloway leaves dispirited Crystal Palace a tired and resigned man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 22:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piracy charges against jailed Greenpeace activists in Russia have been dropped and they have been charged with hooliganism instead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 20:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 15:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take the helicopter to Canada! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson: 'Roy Keane had begun to think he was the United manager' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 16:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shane MacGowan to make Christmas appearance in Corrie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 14:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Republican Judge Switches Party, Denouncing GOP as Party of Bigots and Hate-Mongers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 23:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Republican Judge Switches Party, Denouncing GOP as Party of Bigots and Hate-Mongers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 23:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlusconi banned from public office for two years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 19:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mourinho sent off as Chelsea go second </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recipient of Nobel Prize in Economics: Wealth Inequality is World's Greatest Problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 01:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recipient of Nobel Prize in Economics: Wealth Inequality is World's Greatest Problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 01:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Ireland have become the antithesis of everything Roy Keane stood for </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A COUPLE claiming they cannot hope to meet their mortgage payments and give their child an education are taking on their bank in the High Court. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 17:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Budget 2014: the key things to know from todays announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 17:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malala Yousafzai Meets President Obama, Asks Him to Stop Drone Attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 15:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malala Yousafzai Meets President Obama, Asks Him to Stop Drone Attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 15:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Hopkins' 'Breaking Bad' Fan Letter To Bryan Cranston Is Awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 02:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Hopkins' 'Breaking Bad' Fan Letter To Bryan Cranston Is Awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 02:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir Alex Ferguson has had a street near the club's Old Trafford home renamed in his honour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 01:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sir Alex Ferguson has had a street near the club's Old Trafford home renamed in his honour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 01:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liverpool's hopes of redeveloping Anfield are under threat because bats have been seen flying around the stadium. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 02:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 00:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never heard of any of these organisations, how much power do they have?  If google, facebook, microsoft and yahoo were to announce they would stop sharing information with the US or any govt. I'd be a lot more impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Craig Venter who created the world's first synthetic life, is building a gadget that could teletransport medicine and vaccines into our homes or to colonists in space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 00:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Craig Venter who created the world's first synthetic life, is building a gadget that could teletransport medicine and vaccines into our homes or to colonists in space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Craig Venter who created the world's first synthetic life, is building a gadget that could teletransport medicine and vaccines into our homes or to colonists in space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 46 per cent global wealth owned by richest 1 per cent: Credit Suisse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 19:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TD's girlfriend working as barrister and Dail assistant (on a 50,000 euro salary) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 13:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Eve Of Shutdown, House GOP Rigged The House Rules To Prevent Democrats Reopening Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 01:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lorde: 'I'm just a freak' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 22:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lorde: 'I'm just a freak' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 22:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeffrey Katzenberg Offered $75 Million For Three More Breaking Bad Episodes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 19:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Read Dead: Notorious Aussie Criminal Known As 'Chopper' Dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 03:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being from Kerry, I never had much gra for hurling, I found it a frustrating game to watch on the old 21 inch square tvs of old as I could never see the ball it was hard to follow what was going on.  But this year i watched the finals in hd on a 42 inch screen and suddenly it's the best sport ever to watch, you can really see the skill and subtleties of the game.  I think the new tvs revolutionize hurling as a spectacle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Capitol In Lockdown After Gunshots Heard Outside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 20:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PHOTOS: World War II Veterans Force Open WWII Memorial During Shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 19:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PHOTOS: World War II Veterans Force Open WWII Memorial During Shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 19:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walter Whites sickness mirrors America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 20:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rabbitte welcomes bank chiefs U-turn on disgraceful Anglo Tapes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kenyan terror: government points to involvement of Irish-born White Widow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 16:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pussy Riot's Nadezhda Tolokonnikova: Why I have gone on hunger strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 16:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 15:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would guess 'Loser' by Beck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 22:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think Wellbeck made any impression either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darron Gibson keen to make Republic of Ireland return </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 21:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 21:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to impeach the entire Congress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigerian woman wins beauty pageant billed as Islam's answer to Miss World Obabiyi Aishah Ajibola wins contest where participants are judged on their knowledge of Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 23:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis: Catholic Church Is Too 'Obsessed' With Abortion, Birth Control, And Gay Marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 18:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis: Catholic Church Is Too 'Obsessed' With Abortion, Birth Control, And Gay Marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 18:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The farrago of John McCain's article for Pravda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 18:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samantha Geimer on Roman Polanski: 'We email a little bit' In 1977, the film director had 'unlawful sex' with 13-year-old Samantha Geimer, an event that has overshadowed their lives ever since. So why would he get in touch with her now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 01:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Mad Men' Final Season Split, Will Air In Two Parts And End in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No One Understands The Scariest, Most Dangerous Part Of A Self-Driving Car: Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luis Suarez won't be the main man on Liverpool return, warns Brendan Rodgers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 01:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 17:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the drug fuelled insane hilarity of the opening of Fear and loathing in Las Vegas.  The rest of the film couldn't live up to funny it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 23:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grief is the sudden absence of someone you loved from your life.  You are both experiencing that.  Perhaps this desire you are feeling is really a displaced desire to fill the hole that has opened up inside of you, and who better than someone who understands deeply, who has the same gap inside them.  So maybe you unconsciously see her as a quick fix for your grief.  But there are no quick fixes, you must go through your grief, experience it fully in order to heal.  Running away from it will only  prolong the suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'My Left Foot' Oscar-winner Brenda Fricker insists her acting career is over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 22:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 17:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have I gone mad or does the earring look like metal and not pearl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinead O'Connor Debuts Face Tattoos At Bestival 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 16:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes it is better to forget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 22:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 21:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in fairness we could have better players than Whelan and Andrews in midfield if Trap didn't have such a hard on for 'diggers' as Giles would call them.  McCarthy, Gibson, Steven Reid are all more talented midfielders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, I think Richard Sadlier is very good.  Kenny Cunningham isn't bad either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Reasons Legalized Marijuana Might Be Bad for Pot Smokers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 20:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 02:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure it'll all be posted on soundcloud or somewhere in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think things are bad for us? Northern Ireland just lost to luxembourg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 23:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 22:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're an unsigned band from Cork in Ireland.  They've just recorded their album, they're friends of mine, this is their facebook page if you're interested https://www.facebook.com/dissolutes?fref=ts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingfisher and The Hummingbird - The Eulogys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 17:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - storm's gonna lock you up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 16:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 22:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that after 5 years Trap's English hasn't improved one jot shows how much he really cares about the job.  It's a final paycheck before retirement, work a few days every couple of months, smell the roses the rest of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giovanni Trapattoni admits his Republic reign almost over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 22:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giovanni Trapattoni admits his Republic reign almost over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 22:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin O'Neill installed as favourite to replace Giovanni Trapattoni as Ireland manager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 02:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin O'Neill installed as favourite to replace Giovanni Trapattoni as Ireland manager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 02:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Movie Theater of the Future Will Be In Your Mind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 15:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do e-cigarettes compare to nicotine patches in helping smokers quit? First study results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 15:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 15:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's okay, believe what you want, I'm not trying to convert you. Once you do good in the world that's the most important thing.  I don't think God is to blame for everything that goes wrong in the world, but there we disagree.  I wish you the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 02:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bad stuff happens in this world, in this life.When you think about it, you, me, everyone around is going to die.  That's the way it's always been.  I don't think that's prove of the absence of God.  I think a lot of people use the idea of God to cope with the bad stuff, especially our own death.   Birth and death are simple the basic facts of our existence on this plane.  That's the way it is whether there is a God or not, whether you believe there's a God or not.  I do believe there is one, I feel sure in it.  If you think about it, we live in a universe which has produced consciousness, which implies consciousness in somehow inherent in the fabric of the universe.  It doesn't compute to me that consciousness could grow out of particles and chemistry as just some kind of miraculous happenstance.  Now you have consciousness, this life, it's what you are going to do with it that's important.  People are doing bad things in the world, yes, what are you going to do in it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naomi Klein: Why Big Green Groups Can Be More Damaging Than Right-Wing Climate Deniers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 02:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naomi Klein: Why Big Green Groups Can Be More Damaging Than Right-Wing Climate Deniers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 02:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naomi Klein: Why Big Green Groups Can Be More Damaging Than Right-Wing Climate Deniers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 02:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russell Brand booted out of GQ bash for Nazi jibes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 12:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manchester United have reiterated that they did not know the lawyers involved in their move for Bilbao's Ander Herrera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 21:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Douglas Says His Marriage Is Not In Crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 00:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Ozil is a great signing, Arsenal had 70m to spend and only spent half it.  They have only one top quality striker in Giroud, what happens if he gets injured?  Bendtner?  I really felt Arsenal needed three top signing and have only got one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have a problem with pregnancy, you have a problem with anxiety.  Can you get an appointment with a shrink?  Some light medication may reduce your fear levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry Summers and the Secret "End-Game" Memo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 19:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry Summers and the Secret "End-Game" Memo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 19:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry Summers and the Secret "End-Game" Memo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catherine Zeta-Jones And Michael Douglas Separate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 15:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 01:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you go from regular cigarettes to the ecig? and was quitting ecigs easier than quitting regulars?  I tried to give up cigarettes cold turkey but couldn't do it, but i wonder if i could find e cigs easier to quit in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland's first legal abortion carried out in Dublin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 16:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch: The Coen Brothers' 'Inside Llewyn Davis' Gets a New, Fuller Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Brom confirm Nicolas Anelka has been granted leave on 'compassionate grounds' amid reports of retirement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 20:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradley Manning announces decision to live as a woman named 'Chelsea' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 14:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradley Manning announces decision to live as a woman named 'Chelsea' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 14:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradley Manning announces decision to live as a woman named 'Chelsea' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 14:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Jazeera America: the news channel Americans deserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Jazeera America: the news channel Americans deserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 01:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 01:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan Shearer is a legend of the game and as dull as dishwater as a pundit.  Richie is an excellent analyst and that's what matters as it's the job he is currently paid to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-pope Benedict says God told him to resign during 'mystical experience' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 16:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 01:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Beware the fury of the quiet man' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 16:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you've had such a difficult time in life.  I don't think people, especially your family would get over losing you to suicide, that kind of wound never heals.  I think you are just rationalizing to make it seem more acceptable to yourself.  Have you ever tried meditation or cognitive behaviour therapy?  They can help a lot.  These [1](http://www.ananda.org/meditation/learn-to-meditate/) [2](https://moodgym.anu.edu.au/welcome) sites are an introduction. I believe people can change and their minds can change over time.  You will not be the same person in five years that you are now.  If you keep trying to get better, I believe you will, you will find out what works for you and what helps to reduce fear and increase wellbeing.  I think a lot of your efforts so far have been for other people, to make them think you are ok, to have the perfect mask.  I think it's time for you to work on helping yourself to get better at coping with life and shepherding your mind and moods.  You can learn this things, make it your mission in life to learn about yourself and your needs so that you can live a fulfilling and rewarding life, don't write yourself off as hopeless, you are not, you can change yourself and your life, you have the power within you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How low can it go? Millions of Americans live on LESS THAN $2 A DAY according to alarming new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How low can it go? Millions of Americans live on LESS THAN $2 A DAY according to alarming new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, post contravenes our rules, see [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/SuicideWatch/comments/xgrba/from_the_suicidewatch_mod_team_if_youre_here_to/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man found shot dead at Olivia Newton-Johns home in Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man found shot dead at Olivia Newton-Johns home in Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man found shot dead at Olivia Newton-Johns home in Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man found shot dead at Olivia Newton-Johns home in Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 18:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are strong mentally to struggle with depression for so long.  It hasn't beaten you yet, don't give up and let it win.  It can never win without your permission. I know it has been so long since you've been happy it seems impossible to experience it again, but it's not, don't give up on yourself and your life, who knows what value you can add to the world in time.  Can I ask you, what do you think is the root cause of your depression?  If there was one thing you could do, what would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt: 24 police officers killed by militants in Sinai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-19 13:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HBO Gives Pilot Order to 'The Money' Starring Brendan Gleeson (x-post from r/entertainment) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 01:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oprah sorry over racism reaction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 01:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wayne Rooney not for sale  at any price, Manchester United tell Chelsea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 20:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eccentric millionaire professor builds country villa on top of 26-story apartment block </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my favourite albums of all time.  A masterpiece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 18:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you haven't any replies yet, it's because the post was caught in the spam filter till now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 02:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I have ocd which is incurable.  I have had it 15 years, at times it was a very dark road.  But by doing the right things, getting help, medication, meditation, exercise, counselling, following my dreams I have gotten much, much better.  There were many times over those years i thought there was no hope for me and I longed to die.  I couldn't have imagined how much better I have gotten and how much I enjoy life now.  I have learnt that it will amaze you what you can recover from and there is always hope, even when you can't see it, even when you don't believe in it, you can always get better.  Never give up on yourself, you are worth seeing this life out all the way, one thing I promise, it will surprise you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the teeth are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 01:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to thine own self be true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 00:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catinca Untaru in The Fall was amazing, she seemed like an actual child rather than a miniture adult a lot of precocious child actors come across as (I'm looking at you Dakota Fanning).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 10:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, your post was caught in the spam filter so no-one saw it till now.  I'm sorry you are having a hard time, how are you doing now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 03:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is always hope, you can change your mind.  You can become a new, better version of you.  Don't let anyone convince you you can't improve your life and yourself.  You are free to become whatever kind of person you want, if you work at it.  Please don't give up.  Talk to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 17:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, my mom is dying too, of huntington's disease.  It's hard to watch her waste away.  It must be much harder for you as she is self inflicting it.  Maybe you need to accept you are not in control of the situation, there's nothing you can really do except be some emotional comfort for her.  I'm sorry you have to go through this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opening to father's day, a pretty weak comedy starring robin williams, opens with williams holding at pistol and saying in v.o. 'I've thought about suicide for years, it's the only thing that's been keeping me going.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 15:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost no old movies on this list, I would go for Sunset Boulevard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 23:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could go to an emergency room and tell them you are an immediate suicide risk.  Or call a hotline first and see if you feel a bit safer after.  But taking care of your health and saving your life must be your top priority now.  You can get through and one day you will be glad you did, please take care of yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 18:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bradley Cooper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
