<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 09:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks all for responses! Tried it out on PTR and I'm satisfied that S6 is boosted enough to make it worthwhile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 06:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto profile link request. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 22:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your goal exactly? If you want to run an effective HT there's no alternative to Humongoid b/c of it's AOE and range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much more viable is Shadow in 2.4.1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 04:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dropped DH after Shadow disappointment. Worth revisiting in 2.4.1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LoN   Helltooth Garg on 2.4.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard some speculation that HT would outpace LoN with new bonuses, is that what's happening on the boards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know math on how much stronger that makes Ritual? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confidence Ritual vs. Pierce the Veil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 18:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen comments that Confidence is a separate dmg multiplier, apparently Pierce is not? Aside from the obvious gameplay difference is there a significant difference between these 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see. I assumed it was based on char range not pets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 09:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already cleared a 70 for first time after swapping in Uhkapian and Confidence Ritual (still had BotS equipped). Having played DH a lot I always wonder why no one ever mentions Zei's? Combined with Peirce the Veil and some practice couldn't that outperform both BotP/S? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 07:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have some decent Manajuma's another alternative to Chicken is In-geom/SH-Soul to Waste/Spirit Walk-Severence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 07:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would second that Flashfire Tal/Sage Wiz is fastest DB build. The only down side would be if you are still gearing some things on your WD you miss out on possible drops while running the Wiz. In my case I have limited game time so I use Chicken over Wiz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got my first Sacred Harvester finally, trying to push into 70's now, thanks for the tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also seems possible based on 2.4.1 notes that HT will outperform LoN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 07:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thx! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 06:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mm ya. What was I thinking? I'll put in an order for 13 ancients right away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 01:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would require you to sacrifice one of the following: Small Man's Finger, MoJ, or T T. How would F/R outperform one of those pieces? Not to mention losing a skill slot to a resource generator that you don't need for anything else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A better way to put this question is probably:
Extra passive (most likely Piece the Veil or Confidence Ritual) + CoE VS. EW bonus to reduction and dps

I will say I expected the HFA+CoE to perform better but was unimpressed. Switching back to EW seems better for dps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're still running HT mind linking your profile? I'm expecting to be pushing w/ HT for rest of season, I'm at GR 69 atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HT Garg Amulet: HFA vs. EW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 19:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is best and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 09:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gear is still missing a Sacred Harvester, but I felt I was dodging around too much to make full use of EW. But maybe with 10 SH stacks on its easier to stay put? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have an ancient twisted sword and not too many other ancient legs, maybe thats my best option - you cubed deathwish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with 'The Thrill' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 08:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have basically all Wiz legs, what works well for GR45 with no set items? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! What is max discipline? I read someone saying they had 90, don't see how they could have that much, seems like 81 is max including invigoration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 06:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used M6 on season while I was collecting my first set of UE. F+R definitely increases M6 power. With identical other gear for UE my dmg increased 2-3X once I collected UE (but I only had 3 sentries cause no rucksack drops). Top tier M6 w/ F+R would be fairly close I think to top UE's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UE - Can anyone list sources of discipline? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 04:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 06:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how many pieces of Marauders are you wearing? How many of Nats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 20:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see how hex+teauk beats out Prides/BotP by a large percentage, but man that's seems like a lot of micro to avoid dmg and keep skill rotation/stutter step going... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, do you know of a post on RCR vs. Hatred Regen? I have noted that Rank 1 US DH has regen on quiver.

Rank 1 Also uses Hexing Pants which I guess replaces Prides Fall RCR w/ microing Focus+Teauk a lot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideal RCR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 07:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any benefit in stacking RCR over 50%? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 03:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What level grift can you clear consistently with each build? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Higher Drop Rates in Seasons = Tinfoil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 21:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so why play it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think about MS instead of CA for T6? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 10:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep i do, ty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 09:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, must have prides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 06:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it the consensus that Maelstrom is best for fast T6 rifting?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 05:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone pease explain why Stars is better single target damage? Is it because multiple rockets cannot hit the same target? ie. Stars 600% vs. Mal. 450% on one target? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I wasn't sure how much it mattered, unfortunately Im resource-broke so have to grind mats awhile to make mass barbs *sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have thunderfury but I think i salvaged my only wyrdward awhile ago (argh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I forgot I had my skills set for T6 rifting - I use awareness + special recipe usually in Grift, never thought about swapping custom in but duh, way more boost than any of the other passives huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solo GR37, how can I climb higher? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 06:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any DH clans accepting new members? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 03:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Para 450+, geared, on daily
West coast USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 00:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Phys 10% higher dmg than cold?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you don't use BotT or Cull the Weak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you use spitfire and completely rely on scoundrel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you use 2 spenders? EA and CA? How long does EA chill for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you proc BotT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 22:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polar Sentry?
EA?
How do you choose which to use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are people procing BotT?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leg. Gems?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya its the only BiS weapon I've ever gotten lol, I do like Jade though so pretty happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 00:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I have about 30% CDR total w/ Furnace, para, and diamond - but I don't have any on actual Jade pieces or rings. My Quetz is also missing Crit and chest is missing Haunt%. So basically all my Jade pieces except boots and pants need upgrading. I also don't have Strong-arm...so theres a lot of Kadala-ing that can be done before Im working for anything really rare (my Furnace is decent.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 00:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking that because I still need improvements on basically all my Jade gear (I have only 8% CDR on gear). So I'm kind of math-stupid but correct me if I'm wrong: every drop during rift has equal %, so there's no benefit to staying in one rift longer over starting a new one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did new patch reduce the rarity of the rarest items along with the ancient leg adds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grift 35 yields what, 150 shards? or is it more? My Jade gear is mediocre so 35 is still difficult atm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I understand what you mean - you're saying 'speed rifts' (meaning clearing only through to RG) yield better odds than clearing the entire rift?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confirm or Correct: Best Item Farming Strategy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 21:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. 4 person WD lootshare T6 rifts: a. Speed rifts for fast blood shards are best for basic gearing, b. Weapons, rings, amulets better to clear entire rifts for max drop chance.
2. 4 person mixed party T6 rifts
3. Solo T6 rifts

*Where do Grift drops fit in? How much does a high level grift increase drop chances - at some point would running high grift be better for item farming than T6 even though only RG has drops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen anyone using fire rune.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you attack: 1. nado 2. haunt 3. locust (which receives poison haunt bonus) 4. harvest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 2 Jade Using Poison?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 00:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top Jades on Norm NS leaderboard using poison despite bug? They both have Furnace... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's right, Jade is frustrating at first but a lot of fun once you develop some technique - also check the guide, your gear may be far from optimal i.e. giving you a mistaken idea of what real build is like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 04:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Grift performance improved, but I assumed boost was working so I guess it was just the improved grift density..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poison Jade Gems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any consensus so far on whether Poison Haunt Rune effects best gem choices? Anyone experimenting with something new to compliment Poison? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 22:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related question: Does Hwoj Wrap proc BotT? Wouldn't it be even better to stack poison bonus and BotT if you keep slow effect up consistently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 21:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm counting correctly he has 77% Cooldown w/ gear + Gogok, with another 10% i assume from para for 87%... so God-mode basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 21:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are seasonal items only available during the season they are introduced? Like if you didn't get a Dagger of Darts in season 1 will it be impossible to get one after season closes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 20:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you agree that BotP is still better for lower Grifts   that Gogok only becomes essential on high Grift? Or is Gogok better even for lower lvl Grift/T6 rifting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Bliz change Siphon animation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 19:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was useful for getting a read on kills... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of belts, I'm surprised no mention of Witching Hour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding RoRG desired stats: why would you want AS? Or is it not possible to reroll that stat? I know it always drops w/ AS but if you happened to get a great drop with a INT/CC/Socket, couldn't you reroll AS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 01:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand it's possible, wondering if anyone has tried using Gogok gem to hit the BP... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone tried using Gogok to hit 2.8BP w/ 2HXBow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
