<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject792</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 18:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look how far tormund is beyond those burning crosses! Also, WHERE IS ROOSE?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, TWO great trailers. Fully erekt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 14:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> off topic slightly, but i would love wun wun to somehow get to kingslanding. Theres two worlds at the moment, one of dragons, magic and giants, and one of money and power plays. 
Wun wun at the trial of the seven would be something else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 21:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i want him to poke his head through that hole in the door so ghost can rip it clean off. Two faced olly getting whats due.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great shatners ghost! The pace of this makes the tension unbearable!!! So hyped for ghost ripping ollys throat out!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it looks cool, but standing near it the smell is, uh, not so good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> soo, no ones talking about the circular fields? Normal in the u.s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 19:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm absolutely biased to this era of electro/indie crossover sorta stuff, but imagine this getting played nowdays? It wouldn't happen. Interesting, weird, creative stuff like this just isn't being made anymore. (granted, theres exceptions)


Just what happened to interesting remixes? There was a time when a remix would get more hype than the original track, they would both feed of each other. Everything seems to polished nowdays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 20:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who the fuck had the job of de-boning the cats?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their ruthless ideals of open plan kitchens will be the end of us all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 16:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that star wars kid has come a long way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 % agree. Also, he kinda 'rehearsed' the pyscho role via [The Shoes - Time To Dance] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pt9wnawn7xQ) music video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jake Jillianhalls in nightcrawler is brilliant. Also, although obvsly a much smaller role, he played a very convincing hipster killing pyscho in the (awesome) music video for The Shoes - Time to dance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 21:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same old same old with sansa. "very excited where shes going this season" blah blah blah. They came out with the same crap last year, so i guess sansa is in for another (pointless) shit time of it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think thats too obvious. Roose should be too smart for him, even if he's raging out. I can see Roose stitching Ramsay up during the battle of winterfell. Roose is no fool, if he can see a loss, he will back out, leaving Ramsay all on his own, bar his twenty good men... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Olly will die. In the very first episode ghost is gonna rip that little cunts throat out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Least is Braavos, which is a shame cuz i think maisies great, but i can't see much happening there of any interest (at least til the end). Just annoying little 'lessons'. 


I'm most excited for....Bran i guess. Def all the politics in KL will be great, but this is beyond book Bran, god knows what he's gonna get up to warging the crap outta people. I pretty much jizzed my pants when mr frosty touched his arm in that teaser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year she was the hype queen, insinuated all kinds of stuff and massively bigged up her character, saying that she played a much larger role and was growing up blah blah blah. And just look what they did with her story last season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 17:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly the sort of thing that justifies men being paid more than female players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm gonna wait to see this in gif form, but i will write on here telling you that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 13:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait, which way is the wind blowing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 09:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bran, i am your father" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 00:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can get behind this. They want the whites and the long winter in westeros, then to use danys dragons to melt the ice which, uh, flows south, to green up their deserts. ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, i found at least a part of it, hopefully someoe will jump in with any more. its in ASOS, chapter 53, tyrion talking to tywin.

Prince Oberyn's presence here is unfortunate. His brother is a cautious man, a reasoned man, subtle, deliberate, even indolent to a degree. He is a man who weighs the consequences of every word and every action. But Oberyn has always been half-mad."
"Is it true he tried to raise Dorne for Viserys?"
"No one speaks of it, but yes. Ravens flew and riders rode, with what secret messages I never knew. Jon Arryn sailed to Sunspear to return Prince Lewyn's bones, sat down with Prince Doran, and ended all the talk of war. But Robert never went to Dorne thereafter, and Prince Oberyn seldom left it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tywin lannister supposedly holds him in high regards as a master planner. Doran himself says he's been planning revenge since elia was murdered, can't quote exact paragraphs off the top of my head. Which i suppose doesn't mean he's actually smart, but if youve been planning that long, even an idiot (that has lived dorans life) would have something better in the works than the mess he seems to have atm. 


He has a lot of players across the board, even tho on the face of it, they essentially aren't (weren't in the case of oberyn) having much impact on things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 15:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad he's returned to the dornish. Theres a crap load going on in asoiaf, but everything dornish has always intrigued me, as none of it adds up. I still don't know what to think of Doran. For such a smart man, he's made some (apparently) terrible decisions. Maybe theres more to his plans or maybe thats just his character, and dorne will have no real impact in westeros. I'm not sure we as readers have enough info to know right now, unless preston has managed to join the dots that lead to something. 


 Either way, i'm looking forward to the rest of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i, agree...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats the deal with people led on the floor next to their luggage? They get up at the end when told, so i assume someone had already told them to stay down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even cudder was shocked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like the ass end of a mutilated cat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 20:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a ... burn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 19:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes and no. A little back draft when pouring, which you should never do onto a flame unless you are a crazy russian. Combined with the hair products, meant she got a little hot under the collar.....ahem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sorta thing could get a man fired </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he was mouthing off which got him the red. Refs are fucking annoying sometimes, especially when they try and make a point, but this should warrant a lifetime ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess its time to get started if you want one of these </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> toon fan here. nope, i hate them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 13:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just a normal weekend in the west country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 19:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post! Love reading more about Roose. One of my fav characters in the books, for simply how prudently abominable a person he is. I've always insisted he is so much worse than Ramsay, 'the mad dog', compared to a calculating pyschopath. Something which i think is overlooked because of how strong 'show ramsay' is. Show Ramsay makes a great villain which will (hopefully) mean a huge twist for show watchers, when Roose royally fucks him over. 


I say hopefully, because that will be the test for Ramsay. Will he see it coming and be prepared? I'm really not sure who will survive in the end, but the way its set up, i'm pretty sure one will die at the hands of the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 12:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who ever thought doing this kinda shit was a good idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember racing games from the early 90's? Heres the soundtrack to every one of them. 

[Mille - Crysteena] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yvvizr8wCvM) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yes, forgot all about this. HUGE tune  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like a kavinsky-off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 18:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is clearly someone messing around. Crazy, but not bat shit crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah could be, same could be said of mel. Show-wise we won't need much more explanation than that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hah yh true. Maybe of a more discerning character then. A royal, a noble, a child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be that mel finds ghost over jons body before tormund n co even hears about it, and is the only one able to approach because of her dog whispering skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exactly he was revived wasn't very clear, not sure that mel has the same power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 18:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah yes i forgot about them agreeing to burning each other if any of them die. It was mentioned a few times between them i think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah yeah good spot, i guess on a bench then? Either way ghost is guarding him. Incidentally, not sure how the show is gonna explain where ghost was during the stabbing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Apologies for what you're about to see" (Spoilers Everything) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, this is an awesome line to end what is, i think, the best trailer for a season yet. A great line because it could mean so many things in the context of that scene, and also because clearly the people who made the trailer are either trolling us, or genuinely are sorry for how off-book this season will go. But yeah, perfect hype makers.


As for that scene tho. So many questions. I'm not entirely sure the "i've never been much of a fighter" comes directly before that line. It sounds like its been cut in, but also Davos isn't exactly the sort to wise crack just before a fight in pretty dire circumstances. Is he?


So what/to whom is he apologising for? To me it looks like they are defending Jon. Ghost is laying guard (and not attacking the people in the room) So i don't think anyone is trying to immediately sacrifice anyone here or slice up jon to prevent re-animation. It seems like they are stopping the men in the previous shots from getting in. Which we can guess is for Mel to do her work? Which hopefully doesn't mean, seven fucking save me, the sacrifice of Ghost. Altho its worryingly plausible. As shown previously on screen (for no apparent reason) mel has a way with ghost and gets very friendly with him. I would much prefer a self scarifice on mels part or better yet for her to simply to shag Jon back to life, i mean necrophilia is one of the few faux pas left for GoT to explore. 



So Davos is apologising to the men? For being shit at swordplay? Maybe there's soemone else in that room, someone less familiar with bloodshed? It doesn't sound right that Davos would give a shit what those nightswatch think and wouldn't it be more likely him making the orders? 
Maybe i'm reading way too much into it, as i will with every other scene in that trailer until the season starts! Got me thinking tho, thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 15:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah true, its easy to forget to seperate book from show at times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 08:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope that doesn't happen. Roose is the boss, ramsay shouldnt have the power to do anything of the sort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are we gonna have a scene where mel shags jons corpse back to life whilst davos keeps the nightswatch from getting in on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probs cuz drogon is stood on top after fucking off for a bit. again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no eye patch tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i reluctantly concur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but whos the two stood next to reverend mental? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more dany walking round the desert. fuck yeah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shot is getting no attention, but i don't recognise anyone?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be the best season yet (as we don't know how badly they're messing it up) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hope its not roose, but thats what it implies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what? hes not dead, hes standing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost protecting jon, not attacking the people in the room. Davos whipping his longclaw out. WHAT AM I SEEING HERE!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, best GOT trailer to date. By a fucking mile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well yes, however, they had no idea that the people they slaughtered were in the same group. They only had the word of the hilltop who obviously have beef with these guys. Negan is bad to the bone, but nothing they've seen so far *should justify what they did. 

It makes a good story but logically it makes no sense whatsoever for team rick to go looking for trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf murica.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not oblivious at all, if you watch the video again youll see he's looking straight at the man the whole time, i assume wondering why the fuck he's shooting in the air and throwing himself on the floor. 


No doubt he changed up his security after this tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing confusing here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its [Coldplay - Hymn for the weekend] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YykjpeuMNEk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CUT MY LIFE INTO PIECES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  5 golden eggs for the line that everyone who watched this clip muttered to themselves. Bloody el reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL HYPE DENIERS MUST KNEEL BEFORE THE MCSHANE!!! HIS MESSAGE MUST BE SPREAD.


HYPE IS UPON US!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 08:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As ever, a picture (and t shirt) with no context whatsoever. Who knows wtf is happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to start with i was hoping he didn't get sprayed, but then i noticed the sock/sandal combo, and so wished a thousand skunks upon him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> france is like half catholic, half muslim, half normal. But again, they're only showing the 'interesting' reactions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, can i state the obvious, as most people are ignoring it. THEY ARE ONLY SHOWING THE PEOPLE WHO REACT. Thats why it looks like everyone is angry. 
I'm sure there was plenty of people that shrugged or laughed it off, but thats not interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at their 'targets'. Plus they only show the interesting ones. I'm sure there was plenty that shrugged it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going with, a Yasmin from Bristol accompanied by an american friend, is to blame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 08:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was a joy to behold my child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh Maggie [Show Spoiler] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 22:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 22:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maggie comes out with the line, "its gonna cost us something". 
yelp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Synth rock? emo-rock? electronica rock? hard to put 'We are pilots' in a genre... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shiny Toy Guns - Rainy Monday [Alternative Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 22:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe i'll be the same from now, but hopefully not!

 We, the audience were Theo, who was very good at seeing through the bullshit of any of faiths in the film. He was the perfect cynic. In the end it was kinda more about hope than faith to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny i didnt get that from the film. The obvious bits were there, but it didn't over power the film for me. I wasn't focused on the christian symbolism at all tbh. Religion is obviously a big part of humanity and i think it dealt with it without shoving any opinions down our throats.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 21:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not sure it hits you over the head. Th barn scene is almost a way of dealing with any christian similarities or symbolism. What other scenes did you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 19:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it exists irl?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spoiler tag or nah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The emotion that goes with this scene, coupled with the music, after the journey we've been on through the film, always chokes me up. Such a truly great film. So many layers and little details that you notice when coming back to rewatch it. Its quite a tough watch, but necessary.


 Particularly relevant with the possible zika pandemic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Powerful scene from a beautifully bleak film. Children Of Men (2006) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 13:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *drunk friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW i learn one move which my friends insist i perform every time i'm on the dance floor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 13:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would it take for the internet to be 'offline'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 13:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 10:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dogs are great cuz we have bred them over 1000's over years to be our obedient slaves. 

Although i've always thought if humans ever died out through a pandemic etc, then dogs would inherit this earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 20:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some trees have sticks on them which are like bigger versions of twigs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 18:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As this thread has already pretty much come to agreement, it probs is stannis. 

All they have to do in the show is have brienne and co arrive at the wall with stannis as prisoner. Problem solved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 19:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> next video we see a robot with the hockey stick. Robots making robots means they can't turn on us humans right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 20:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this piece of horseshit article is so far up its own ass its gonna choke on its own regurgitated shlong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 20:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find me in the manatee [the dark of the manatee]
 (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r8k-iy_tWtQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 12:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there should be a follow up to this thread asking, what secret do you know about a family member that they don't know you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 09:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they are competitive, but there are other countries that french supermarkets can trade with can massively undercut them. The underlying issue here is france, and in this case, bretagne losing its cultural identity. The knock on effect is huge. More and more, local shops are closing because of big supermarkets opening in rural areas. Its something that happened in the uk 20 or so years ago, without much struggle i might add. But its soemthing that a large number of people in these rural villages don't want. 

Its easy to say 'become competitive', but thats not what its about. Getting rich is not what these people aspire to. Food already is comparatively expensive in france, but people (or at least the ones i have spoken with or heard from) don't mind paying because the food is their land, its their culture. Food is important. The bigger issue is them trying to protect their country from being overhauled by 'western' ideas and philosophy. Probably a losing battle, especially as they're in the eu. Like you said, they already do get huge subsidies from the eu, so they are caught in a catch 22.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 09:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we're like, all cousins man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they blocked the south side of the city as far as i'm aware and let through all emergency services. They built up to this too and everyone in the area had plenty of advance warning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whereas the english mentality is to bend over and take it like a man? I really don't like strikes but its the only power they have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta love the french farmers. Just back from the very same area where theyve been doing this to many other smaller towns. Rennes is their biggest target yet. The locals complain that its the farmers way of getting rid of all their rubbish! They rock up with trailers full of old tyres, hay bales or just straight shit. Set it on fire if it burns, then fuck off and drink some pastis.


To be fair to them, its their land, their country. They don't like the deal they're getting, so they're doing something about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 12:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [artists impression] (http://vignette1.wikia.nocookie.net/muppet/images/c/c3/4058s.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20070802220508) of how it likely interacted with its environment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 14:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'killed' is a stretch. Relocated, died, did not reproduce, would be more fitting in light of the evidence?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 14:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stuck the camera on the floor and pointed it at trees </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all this has me so hyped to be disappointed. I can't wait for the trailer, so my readiness for disappointed can increase yet further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep. but it doesn't matter cuz shes dead soon anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an Englishman that only occasionally peers across the pond into the workings of the us democratic system, it seems that 'reddit' as a whole, is very pro sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm happy how normal everyone looks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
