<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, it's not real.  This is more fake news created by those who want to keep the focus diverted from the many mistakes Trump is making even before he takes office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to you think you developed those beliefs to begin with?  Was it the way you were raised or some other cause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then a followup question: Do you believe the stereotypes you've seen develop more from socio-economic, instinctive, or cultural roots?

Also, what are the stereotypes you believe are real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Racists/bigots: What do you think caused you to hate and/or fear those different from yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks to me like you've posted three pictures of the same event and are now claiming, without any proof whatsoever, that CNN used the same girl in three different stories in three separate places.  Again, you've posted this without any proof that CNN ever did this.

Can you prove that CNN used the same girl in three different news stories?  If not, then anyone calling you a liar and a troll would be completely justified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm glad you've started to turn your expectations around; that's an important first step.

As you say, you're graduating from engineering school and seeking a job in SF.  This would probably be a great time to bond with older relatives who can teach you how to cook and how to do basic self-repair.  Those two things will help you go very far and improve every aspect of living.

I won't go so far as to suggest you live off legumes and tap water.  On ~$100k, you can still buy tasty groceries and go out to eat rather often without breaking the budget.  However, if you make eating out a treat rather than a routine, you'll find it far more enjoyable and satisfying.

Finally, it's great that you're planning to dump a decent amount into a retirement account, but I'd also make sure to tuck away some cash in a readily available account for emergencies, because there WILL BE emergencies.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be brutally honest here....

Seriously, people keep telling you over and over where you're going wrong, but you're not listening.

Either make more money or choose a cheaper place to live.  "Wanting" to live in an expensive location isn't a need, it's a desire.  This isn't a difficult problem to work out.

And as others have pointed out, learn to cook so that you aren't spending $30/day on food.  Again, not tricky.

Basically, it sounds like you want someone to tell you how to pull money out of thin air so you can live like a prince fresh out of college.  

I'll agree with you that you are fucked.  And you'll stay fucked until you learn to live within your means and listen to people who are doing their best to give you good advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I'd strongly suggest you take some time to sort out how you feel about this situation.  Logically, you've already come to terms with the fact that most of us wanted to experience more partners and alternatives when we were younger.  Emotionally, it sounds like you're not there.  That's where spending some time with your thoughts and asking what is really important to you in your relationship comes in.

Second, once you've sorted out your feelings, you need to sit down with your partner and talk about what that means to your relationship.  

If you decide that you can't share him/his body with other partners, then you should be prepared to either end the relationship then, or after you find out he's been with someone else.  He's already made his needs known and stifling him won't end well for either of you.

On the other hand, agreeing to let him see other men while secretly resenting it, will also lead to frustrations and resentment.  Basically, if you can understand and truly accept his needs, you'll be in a far better place in your relationship than if you either deny him or resent him.

Good luck and I hope it all works out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be blunt, but this kind of calls for it.  Let him go.  Don't text or reach out in any way.  If you see him at a club or bar, ignore him.  He's made it clear that is what he wants so respect that.

As for why, he's given you the brush, it could be nearly anything but it almost certainly wasn't your fault.  I'd guess that there was something that didn't click and he wasn't willing to work with it or even give you the chance to address it.  I've seen it many, many times.

Look at it this way, you're a young man in NYC.  There are so many opportunities out there to find someone who will be interested in you for being you, that getting hung up on the one who wasn't is simply wasting your time.  Remember what you said about him moving on from his long-term partner after four years?  I think one year is more than sufficient to move on from someone you've met three times.

Good luck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh.  Some alt-right propaganda rag uses "a close friend" to smear an ex-candidate to get clicks.  Not really news or politics at this point.

This story (fairy-tale?) is no more than red meat being slung out for the least informed and those deranged with hatred to keep them distracted from the many promises Trump is already reneging on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I'm sure there are aspects of your relationship in which you're compatible with your partner, the divide sounds pretty large.  You're not sexually compatible and you're jealous of your partner for reaching out to others he is compatible with.  

I also note that you excuse your outside activity as "friends with benefits" while condemning his as "random hookups."  It sounds like you want to unilaterally set the terms of your outside relationships.

I agree with others who have said it's time to let go.  Find someone you're very compatible with so that neither has to look outside the relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as an older guy who has the same problem at 48, I think the best solution is to open up to your SO that you're still a young guy who wants to experience life as a young man while also spending time with a special guy who fulfills your higher interests and romantic needs.  If your relationship is strong and you are really compatible, you both can make it work.  If he balks, it wasn't meant to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Joseph Watson is a bit of an idiot, isn't he?  Some (i.e. not all or even half) foolish partisans who wanted to elect Clinton at all costs, like Madeline Albright, made stupid assertions about supporting women just because they're women.  The vast majority of us "leftists" either supported Clinton because she was better than the con artist or didn't support her because she is also a con artist.  And some people actually supported her because they agreed with her center-right policies.

But that kind of non-black/white thinking is obviously far too difficult for Mr. Watson, so he creates a strawman argument that he thinks he can knock down.

As I said, he's a bit of an idiot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says even more that you don't understand the concept of propaganda and how David Brock uses it to distort facts and downright lie.

Also, calling everyone you disagree with a 20 year old liberal makes you look rather petty and ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly don't understand that you've been called out on your lies.

Dean stated that Unions ARE super-PACs.  Plain and simple.  He didn't say "well, they act LIKE super-pacs when they donate money."  He said what he thought and that disqualifies him from retaking the DNC chair position for those of us who actually support the working class, not the elite "moderate" neo-Democrats who think that they can keep winning elections by making different minorities fear white men and each other.

I'm happy to suggest that anyone interested go to the link above and watch the clip for themselves.  Then they can come back and read your "Correct-the-record" spin to make an informed decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quoted the article in context.  You made up a quote and tried to pass it off.  I called you out on it so you make up another story.

Your user name is "I_Need_Sources" and I gave you one with full context and quotes.  You now try to mislead others by making up what was said and how it was meant.
 
You're wrong and won't admit it.  I proved it twice now.  Why are you so adamant about pushing untrue information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please try not to pull a Hillary and lie about what Dean said.

For Bernie to say he doesnt have a super-PAClabor unions are super-PACs. Labor unions are super-PACs Democrats like so we dont go after labor unions.

That is the direct quote.  Dean did not say "Unions act like Super-Pacs" as you inaccurately stated, he said they ARE super-PACs Democrats like.  It's a big difference and distorting his wording to serve your argument only demonstrates that problem so many of us had with the Democratic nominee.

Now, if you want to defend Dean's assertions on an honest level, let's do it.  If you want to distort his comment to suggest he didn't say what he said, I'm going to call you out on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't understand how calling Unions nothing more than "super-PACS Democrats like" is attacking them, I think we've discovered the problem with the neo-Democratic party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think calling Unions "super-PACs that Democrats like" is going to win working class voters over?
http://thehill.com/blogs/ballot-box/presidential-races/268444-dean-labor-unions-are-super-pacs-democrats-like

I donated to Dean's campaign and voted for him in the primary.  He was a great DNC chair who returned us to a 50 state strategy which was instrumental in taking back the House, Senate, and Presidency.  

That said, his conduct while shilling for Hillary was unacceptable to working class voters who still look to Unions to protect their jobs, wages, and health benefits.  He needs to understand the difference between political operations and organizations that support actual people.

If there's one lesson the Democratic party needs to learn from this election its that you can't abandon a large minority of voters and expect them to support you.  There is no indication that Dean has relearned that lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could have gotten behind Dean as DNC chair until he said that Unions were no more than super-PACs while defending Hillary's collusion with Brocks's Correct the Record.

If Dean doesn't support Unions, he doesn't support the working class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way you spell "centre" strongly suggests you don't live in the U.S. anyway, so who you're willing to vote for is kind of a moot point in this conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your pastor is doing the work of Satan.  Jesus is not welcome in your Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like there's a groundswell of support for Ellison, which is a very good thing.  We need someone heading the DNC who can remove the taint of corruption and venality that DWS and her cronies left behind (i.e. Brazile).

As for Howard Dean, I supported him for president in 2004 and I think he did a great job as DNC chair before Obama removed him and installed Kaine.  That said, Dean lost all credibility when he trashed Sanders and the Unions while acting as a surrogate for Clinton.  He sold us out to the Clintons for some reason and that makes him part of the problem when we desperately need a solution.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with Hillary's unethical and possibly illegal collusion with the DNC, he didn't.

Which is funny, in a morbid sort of way, because it's now obvious that Hillary didn't have a chance in Hell despite all her unethical cheating.

Doesn't that make you feel at least the slightest bit angry that Hillary and her trolls lied to you about everything while they were fucking up our futures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that!  I'm already tired of reading and hearing "you did this" bullshit.  I didn't do this and you didn't do this.  We all did this.  We did it by allowing the system to get so corrupted that the DNC was able to put up the most reviled candidate in history and convince us that there was no way she could lose.  We did it by ignoring the very real economic problems faced by a large minority of the population.  We did it by allowing wealth to become synonymous with morality.

So some asshole from Slate wants to blame everyone else for Sarah Palin possibly getting a cabinet position.  Again, fuck him.  He needs to look in the mirror and ask why he said nothing before now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard this argument and disagree with it strongly.  There's a faction that wants to make us believe that helping people is a bad thing and that politicians will be punished at the polls for it, which twists the facts.

Democrats aren't being punished for being "uber social justice warriors," they're being punished for the exact opposite - for abandoning a large segment in our society who rightly feel that everyone is getting help but them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
