<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7831</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 18:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe so, I've never seen it served with noodles, and it certainly has lots of Prawn.  thx though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 04:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, have been breadmaking for a couple weeks, these were the best so far.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 03:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely stunning loaves!
Thanks for the inspiration to try something more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Malaysian Spicy Prawn Soup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 03:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks in advance to anyone who can provide a recipe for Spicy Prawn Soup as served in Malaysian restuarants (such as Banana Leaf or Penang in Philadelphia).

Been trying to recreate this puppy with Prawn heads and tom-yum but am so far, unhappy with the results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first Sourdough after suffering a week of waiting for the starter to mature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 05:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did the leper say to the hooker?
.... keep the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 03:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice Shot.  My family visited a Cenote at Chichen Itza as well, but not this one...   beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 00:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 100% sure that I'm high while I'm watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 17:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mix 3 cups of bread flour, 1 1/2 cups of water, 1 teaspoon of dry yeast (after sitting in water for 5 min) and a teaspoon of salt.  

Knead for 5 minutes on a flour dusted surface.

Cover (plastic wrap) in a bowl and let rise for 2 hours.

Punch and Knead for 30 seconds, shape and put it on corn-flour-covered parchment paper in a pan and let rise for 40 minutes covered with plastic wrap. Make sure you flour the top of the dough heavily before covering.

Heat oven to 475 with a pan of water in it (NOT convection bake). remove plastic wrap and pop it in for 30 minutes or until even the sides are dark.

Then remove, put it on a cooling rack and brush with melted butter.

Wait at least 15 min then nom nom nom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a week, I have a solid simple rustic boule method [656x875] [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 13:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 19:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family and I were at a restaurant and while i was talking with my wife, my son had stretched his penis from his shorts and had it tacked to the table with his thumb.

The waitress was the first to notice and had a stunned look on her face.  I immediately turned, surveyed the scenario and said "He's just trying to leave you his tip".

My quickest response ever.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not tried it with the eggplant, what I can say is that it had a nice robust flavor.  It certainly did not taste "lacking".

Next time, I will definitely include the eggplant, but there were no complaints without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 17:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Approximately 2 to 2 1/2 hours at 275.
It could have stood a bit longer, most-likely.  Hunger and two teenage kids took over :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 13:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An excellent recipe:  http://snapguide.com/guides/make-confit-byaldi/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First attempt at Confit Byaldi, was pretty tasty even without the eggplant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 13:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the sticker is there ONLY to tell you to remove the sticker then? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 14:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 13:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does take quite a while, a dinner for 3 or 4 used to take me 3 hours, but i have it down to 2, and 1 and a half if the family pitches in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 13:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This time we made tuna rolls (some with avacodo, some without), spicy tuna rolls, some spicy tuna chirashi, crab and cucumber, sweet potato, and avacado bomb rolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 03:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 00:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 23:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my son, Sage. I know.... he's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this batch was a family effort and not necessarily the cleanest, best rolls that we can make.

But the only advice is practice!  If you want to get good at something, just do it as often as possibe.  Watch some youtube instructional videos, and then focus on one certain type (regular rolls, or inside-out rolls, etc.)

I will say that the first mistake I made was to not thoroughly wash my rice.  Now I hand-wash the rice in water at least 3 or 4 times before cooking it which has greatly improved the quality.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe $20 for the entire meal which fed 3.

We had leftovers as well..... the only problem being that the fridge will ruin the rice, refrigerating left over rolls is really not an option.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
