<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6654</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend purchasing the car after you move.  You never know, it's really hit or miss with most things I try to get in there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice side pinstripe/detailing, what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not!  rust = weight reduction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend told me I'm indecisive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told her I disagree.  Then I took it back and agreed with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My office uses a $2000+ doorstop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe I have a job lined up working IT for a high school in northern NJ, which will hopefully be a good gig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh out of University, what job types can I aspire for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graduating from a no-name university this Sunday (BS in Computer Science   Info Systems, concentration in Info Systems). I have been working an IT Internship/Co-op in a corporate office for a retail chain (Desktop Support/Help Desk) for the past year, but I'm not staying with the company post-graduation due to the department's budgets.

I've been applying like a mad man to jobs all around the Greater NYC area, and all are a similar position to what I have now.
I know certifications are important too, and I'm already studying to take Security+ from CompTIA. Security might be the area I want to end up in, I'm not entirely sure yet.

My question is, right out of college, can I expect to find a higher-tier job than just working at a help desk? I understand the longer I stay with it, the more experience I will have and will be able to move onto greater positions, such as network and server administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh out of University, what job types can I aspire for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graduating from a no-name university this Sunday (BS in Computer Science   Info Systems, concentration in Info Systems).  I have been working an IT Internship/Co-op in a corporate office for a retail chain (Desktop Support/Help Desk) for the past year, but I'm not staying with the company post-graduation due to the department's budgets.

I've been applying like a mad man to jobs all around the Greater NYC area, and all are a similar position to what I have now.  

I know certifications are important too, and I'm already studying to take Security+ from CompTIA.  Security might be the area I want to end up in, I'm not entirely sure yet.

My question is, right out of college, can I expect to find a higher-tier job than just working at a help desk?  I understand the longer I stay with it, the more experience I will have and will be able to move onto greater positions, such as network and server administration.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend told me that the Moon goes through phases. When will it get on with its life and move forward? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 18:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget, fire decals add horsepower! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 20:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still owe about 10k on it and selling would be a financial mistake.  Not much more to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Financially, I think I'd be fine (car payments are like $150/mo).  It's my first car that I've been saving up for for years and I have no plans to sell it in the near future.  More of a matter of "will my car be safe?  is it troublesome to own in the city?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philly was not in my plans a few months back when I bought the car. Things changed and I won't be able to live where I am anymore (South NJ).

What's the use in being an anonymous asshole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a matter of priority from what I understand, which I don't have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really an option at the moment but thanks for the input, idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philly was not in my plans a few months back when I bought the car.  Things changed and I won't be able to live where I am anymore (South NJ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 car garage...  4 cars :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living in Philadelphi with a car... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all-  I might be moving to Philly soon!  In either the Poplar/Northern liberties area (I believe)- right next to the highway and not far from center city. 

Thing is, I just bought a new car and I'm not sure how comfortable I am living in the city with it.  Keeping the car is a high priority, but so is finding a place to live.  Ideally, I wouldn't be driving to work if I work in Philly.  

How do you guys fair having a car in Philadelphia?  To make things that much more annoying, it's a manual transmission- which will probably never see passed 4th-5th gear due to city driving.  

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah- Bulltown Road by Wharton State Forest.  Probably the only twisty 5-mile road down here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RWD roommates take on the NJ Pine Barrens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 14:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is it possible that everyone on Facebook and Instagram to have the best mother in the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 23:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I sorta feel that way.  She's attractive and all but I'm just not there.  I'm moving at the end of the month and won't be seeing her much longer anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL it took Jupiter 137 years to gain color. Amazing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 23:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 04:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Basically, this](http://www.ft86club.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=14401 stc=1 d=1346734791) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When/how to ask what my salary will be like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 17:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Just got a callback for another interview regarding an IT Tech position at a high school. Because of my distance (still away at Uni until graduation), we have done one Skype interview, and I believe the next interview will be over Skype as well.

One thing I haven't brought up previously was the salary I would be making. I feel that waiting until the 2nd interview to inquire about compensation is the more professional thing to do, to make it look like I'm not only in it for the money.

If I feel comfortable enough during the interview, I want to bring up the inquiry about how much I will be making (keep in mind, this is my first "real-world" job right out of college, excluding internships). How can I do so in a professional and humble way?
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made sure my dealership didn't drill holes so I could do this: https://www.reddit.com/r/ft86/comments/4c2uvw/magnets/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blunt checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missed my school's graduation toast, so I made my own </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 22:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/pm5eOfk

edit: I'M NOT A FATHER BTW
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a previous comment of yours regarding spacers.  You recommended this for a proper setup:
Extended ARP Studs

Open ended lug nuts

Spacers

Question, what Extended ARP Studs and open ended lugs are compatible with stock wheels?  Or is that all standard?

Also...
20mm-25mm will make you "flush"

Do you mean 20mm front, 25mm rear?
Sorry for noob..  Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snap from a friend... I wish my driving instructor had this :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 16:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is probably why the foundation's named after her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 19:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  The other day I looked in the rear view to see it and it was nowhere to be found...  it's just that low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 00:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that was uncalled for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/RifleNA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fr-sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't North American 86's come with headlamp washers? Not a big deal, I'm just curious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missed my school's graduation toast, so I made my own </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.  What can be done to fix it?  I bought touch-up paint but I don't want to do this kind of work myself.  Probably bring it to a detailing shop right?  What would they do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a brand-new 2015 that's had 0 exposure to trees... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's a brand new car that's had 0 exposure to trees..  What about the crack underneith? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought my (new) car in February, noticed a crack in the paint (update w/ pic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something caught my eye on the roof of my car; what looked to be dried tree sap actually seems to be a drop of clear coat over an un-touched up crack in my paint. Whatever, the dealership did a crappy job and I'm not going back there to get it redone (distance too far). Thoughts?

What I might do (once I get the equipment) is wet sand the hump of clear coat down a bit then wax it all over. I don't think there's any sense of adding any touch up, because the cracks have been filled in by the previously applied clear coat. I unfortunately don't have a picture at the moment.

What would you do?

pic: http://imgur.com/f2cyerS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pic:  http://imgur.com/f2cyerS  See the spider web-like crack and the darker area that's over it.  The darker area looks like a crappy clear coat job, to me as the blue doesn't seem to change color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pic:  http://imgur.com/f2cyerS  See the spider web-like crack and the darker area that's over it.  The darker area looks like a crappy clear coat job, to me as the blue doesn't seem to change color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totaled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't tree sap...  I thought it was but it looks like clear coat- as in a drop of clear coat over the original coat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought my car in February, noticed a crack in the paint today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 01:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something caught my eye on the roof of my (new) car; what looked to be dried tree sap actually seems to be a drop of clear coat over an un-touched up crack in my paint.  Whatever, the dealership did a crappy job and I'm not going back there to get it redone (distance too far).  Thoughts?


   What I might do (once I get the equipment) is wet sand the hump of clear coat down a bit then wax it all over.  I don't think there's any sense of adding any touch up, because the cracks have been filled in by the previously applied clear coat.   I unfortunately don't have a picture at the moment.

What would you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it make sense to hang onto the loan for a few months so I can work up some credit experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Auto Loan: Pay off now or continue monthly payments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all!  I just purchased a new car.  I had enough aside (plus a trade in) to make the down payment the majority of the payment, and only financing about $10k @ 2.49%.  This comes out to a very low $154/month.  I recently came into a bit of money and was wondering what to do.  I can increase my monthly payments and pay off the loan sooner, or I can even just pay it off in full now if I wanted to- and save myself the interest, while still having some savings left over.  What would you do in this situation?  The interest rate doesn't pose too much of a threat to me but I'd rather pay off my loan sooner than later.  
Any advice is appreciated!  Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any of you guys in Philly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 03:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly relocating to Philly this summer and the thought of having my BRZ there scares the shit out of me...  A brand new manual car in the city really doesn't sound appealing, even though I would be moving into a house with a garage.  Any of you guys in Philly?  How do you and your cars fare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 01:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible, they're out there.  I bought my Series.Blue a year after it came out after some extensive research (which took months to find a seller).  Wound up driving 5 hours from South Jersey to Connecticut to pick it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but it's the best of both worlds.  Car mobile! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 04:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until the shampoo until it runs out.  Then grab another bottle of shampoo from your 1000+ stock and continue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a fix for the 86 during the winter! (x-post from /r/gifs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 17:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watches upwards of $1,000 and they don't even come with time... Can someone please explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 17:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Scion, not Subaru..  it's the RS 2.0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that out with /r/desirepath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 22:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/r/AutoDetailing](https://reddit.com/r/AutoDetailing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just gonna do a spotty touch-up paint job.  Do yourself the favor and buy your own touch up, and spend a Saturday detailing the car.  You'll learn a lot about how to properly keep up with the paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My coworker questions how he still has a job (x-post from /r/gifs). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 14:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My coworker questions how he still has a job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 14:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How sticky are Pilot Super Sports? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will I be able to get a little tail happy with the added grip PSS brings?  Everything else stock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 16:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate just calls my car the VCR cause he can never get the letters right.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 16:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I lost the fender gap then I would not be able to park over the curb as such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 02:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why would you want to do this?  Won't it show that there is a missing area of clear coat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 02:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...So wet sanding doesn't remove clear coat?  I'm confused.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about touch up paint. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched this video a few times in preparation for touching up a few nicks on my car.  In the video, he wet sands the area so touch up is flush with the regular paint.  Then, he waxes away the wet sand marks.  
My question is, why on earth would you put sandpaper up to your paint, even if you're wet sanding?  Doesn't this just rip apart the clear coat?
And if it does take away the clear coat, how does the wax restore its shine?  Thanks!

video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6xi3xmeO6C4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha because I can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's all about the clearance.](https://imgur.com/a/HPwA0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's all about the clearance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 22:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone red-eye correction gone wrong.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was in NJ.  Snowed like crazy out of nowhere yesterday...  Happy April! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my problem exists within my backup.  I've gone through 3 different 6s replacements all with the same problem- it overheats and the battery drains significantly when it does so (I'm talking like 50% within 30 minutes of my phone being in my pocket doing nothing).  I think there's something corrupt in the backup causing this, so I want to save all photos externally not through iTunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Export live photos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 6s has been running poorly lately and I want to restore and start from scratch (not a backup).  Before doing so, I would back up all my photos to my Mac, then transfer them back to my phone post-restore.

I tried this as a test with live photos, but when I sent them back to my iPhone from my Mac, they were just still images.  How can I preserve the live-aspect of the live photos during the transition to a fresh OS?

Thanks!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BRRRRRRRRRRZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 00:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 00:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought mine over a month ago, I really haven't taken in yet how small this car is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 00:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily explained.  Invisible kickstand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is so "custom" about Customs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 17:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panada?  Canama? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GPS Tracking devices are attached to the dorsal fins of sharks, much like the "shark fin" antennae on our cars which carry the same signals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 04:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOING HER HOMEWORK WHILE DRIVING??  Damn, looks like the Darwin Awards are happening a bit early this year...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this sign fucking retarded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totaled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 14:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what u/columusstard said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 23:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't understand why it's beneficial to scuff up an area of clear coat, then polish it and wax it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 20:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like this [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6xi3xmeO6C4)?  I'm just scared about scuffing up the area around the chip with sandpaper...  then wet sanding the area afterwards.  Wouldn't doing so remove the clear coat?  I see he polishes it all afterwards with the polisher.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a silver twin at Uni. It was the only appropriate thing to do. Is she yours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid arab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also good to know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my thoughts exactly...  kinda sketchy lol.  Just called my dealership too, and while they have the color, the touch up is only one coat.  So automotivetouchup.com is looking good to me.  About to buy the color and clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The site I linked in my original post (paintscratch.com) seems to have a tri coat solution...  I just want it to look good haha, and don't know what I should do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What'd you get?  Just the touchup bottle?  I would probably get the clear coat on top of that.  But isn't the K7X WRB a tri-coat color? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for touch up paint. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 14:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to get some touch up paint, already seeing some spots on the front bumper cover from the road.  I have a 2015 WRB BRZ (the NEW WRB), paint code K7X.  Anyone have recommendations what paint to buy/where to buy it from for a the best match?  Some sites I've found sell paint kits, which includes all tricoat layers; basecoat, midcoat and clearcoat.  I've looked at paintscratch.com which seems to be the safest bet.  Also, would you recommend getting the touch up pens, or opt for the paint-brush style?

Looking at this: https://www.paintscratch.com/cgi-bin/order-form.cgi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took her on a stroll through the twilight hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 17:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 00:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that all depends on the types of tires you get too, like what they're designed for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 00:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On stock wheels?  Does the extra 10mm add any noticeable grip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also assuming no coil overs, stock suspension? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could someone explain what the 225 and 215 mean in terms of tire measurement for stock wheels 7"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This only applies to Humans.  Sorry to say, your dog won't be getting autism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 17:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't see how it's a comfortable experience in this car if you're tall.  I'm 5'8 so I fit very cozy.  How do y'all do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 17:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have to replace the amber bulbs that were originally in the orange side markers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 01:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, that's a strange connection but sounds like it might make sense.  Will have to try with no phone on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Premiums don't come equipped with the smart key/push to start.  Not applicable for these models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't much of a mechanical issue/concern, more of a technical one.  Sometimes, when I lock my car and walk away, then come back some 5-10 minutes later, the car won't sense my proximity when I walk up to it and sometimes it won't unlock the doors, and sometimes even the trunk.  It works for the most part, just not all the time.  Is the tech just being finicky, or is this something I should go to Subaru about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I can't stand immatures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been talking with this girl on-and-off for the past year or so.  We've hooked up, but I was never so attracted to her that I wanted to *date* her.  That ship has sailed; I've tried countless times to like her in a "relationship way" but I can't seem to do it.  I just don't like her that way, and I can't force an attraction as such.  I've expressed how I don't want a relationship.  Then she goes and posts this on facebook:  

[http://www.puckermob.com/relationships/how-to-move-on-from-an-almost-relationship](http://www.puckermob.com/relationships/how-to-move-on-from-an-almost-relationship)

She did this last year with a similar article when we were at about the exact same point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Calculator vs Phone Dial Pad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MAGNETS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 21:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by telling my classmate she chews like a cow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 22:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been annoyed by people chewing in a disgusting manner.  That includes chewing with your mouth open or like a slob, obnoxiously crunching and the dreaded gum chewers.  Today I was in my quilting class, which is arranged so that four students sit at each table.  As we were working on our projects, I noticed the girl across from me chewing and cracking her gum like she was getting paid to do so.  Instinctively, I plug in my headphones and tune her out.  Seconds later, she asks me "is our conversation not good enough for you?  Why would you put on your headphones in class?" to which I reply (keep in mind, I was about to explode) "BECAUSE YOU CHEW YOUR GUM LIKE A FUCKING COW."  Everyone looked up.  Professor looked up.  Then everyone went about their business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took her on a stroll through the twilight hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 16:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appetite Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 13:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since I was young, I've had major anxiety throughout my life.  Overthinking things, being too cautious, you name it.  There are even some times when the anxiety becomes too great and I lose my appetite.  
I'm approaching graduation from Uni and leaving my best friends, current job and living arrangements.  Needless to say, it's been quite the anxious wreck for me.  Not to mention that I really haven't had a full meal in days.
I can't bring myself to eat.  As much as I try to force-feed myself, it will just come back up.  My stomach is growling because of its emptiness, but when I look at food it makes me want to throw up.  It's a Catch-22 because I'm trying to help myself but my body won't allow it.  Even drinking water is a bit hopeless.
I'm noticing I'm getting very tired, exhausted, and losing a little weight.  All things I don't want to be doing..  but it's very hard to come out of this "food strike".

Any advice?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioShack worker's name is Optimus Prime. (x-post from pics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioShack worker's name is Optimus Prime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asteroid Hunters Around the World Just Spotted Something Incredible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 18:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any love for the NJ Pine Barrens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would a plate mount like this impede airflow into the engine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here remove the sound generator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 23:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've already plugged up the hole in the cabin underneath the glove box, but I want to go all the way and remove the sound tube all together.  Looking to cap the ends off with end caps from Home Depot...  Does anyone know what size caps I would need?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys recommend for superficial scratches (that will buff out, no touch up paint required)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 22:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys recommend for superficial scratches on the paint? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 19:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coming from a sedan, I still have no idea where the ass of this car is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I put pepper in my coke and walked with it when I received my PhD at graduation. Is it now considered Dr Pepper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jetski stunt knocks $3000+ drone out of the sky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Removing the clutch spring? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been reading many posts about removing the clutch spring, typically as the first mod people do to make the clutch feel less numb (correct?).  I've looked at the guide on ft86club.com (http://www.ft86club.com/forums/showthread.php?t=35621) but the pictures are no longer on the thread and I have no idea what the guide is referring to.  Is there a better guide or video showing how to do this?  I'm a car noob and don't want to fuck anything up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This came in the mail today. Not sure who sent it, but thank you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 20:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dealership didn't sell me on the car; this video segment did. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This came in the mail today. Not sure who sent it, but thank you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 14:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone here done this? What have your experiences been like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 01:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out with the Old, in with the Blue! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 23:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out with the Old, in with the Blue! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 23:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grippier tires? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 02:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey...  Car n00b here.  What are some grippy tires that fit the BRZ's stock wheels, and are better than the stock Prius ones (not necessarily looking for winter tires just yet...  just anything better than the current setup)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 2+ years of lusting, I finally have a BRZ Series.Blue to call my own! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally buying my BRZ tomorrow! What should I check for to make sure everything is OK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 05:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a test car for a Subaru of America executive, there are roughly 6400 miles on it.  Never been state registered nor registered to a person- it's legally "brand new".  Anything I should check for in particular (crickets, mechanical issues, strange noises etc. )?  

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modem/router rental? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 21:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it finally happened, Comcast dropped our promotional plan and now we have to pay $80 instead of $50 every month.  Is this cost primarily for the modem/router unit that we're renting from them?  If I brought my own modem, would this bring the monthly cost down?  Also, what's a compatible cable modem for Comcast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Choice of warranties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 20:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dealership is giving me a choice between 2 different warranties:  Subaru Certified (7 years/100k miles) OR a Lifetime Powertrain Warranty (Does not expire).  What route would you go here?  I could only assume to take the Lifetime Powertrain right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just put down a deposit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 01:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This time next week I should have my own BRZ Series.Blue!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New mail not showing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Unfortunately) still have AOL.  I have new mail, but when I go into the web app, it says in my inbox "This Folder is Empty"...  Please advise!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best way to memorize all ports? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 03:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Struggling memorizing all TCP/UDP ports needed for Security+.  How'd you do it?  Flash cards/quizlet tests don't seem to work for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to expect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 02:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!  I'm right on the verge of buying a BRZ within a week or so.  Coming from a Nissan Altima, there's going to be a lot I will be adjusting to (Auto (CVT) to Manual, FWD to RWD, 4-door to 2-door, to name a few)...  Any of you guys come from a sedan, what has your experience been like?  What should one expect with a vehicle change as drastic as this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Federal vs State Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say the Feds (for whatever reason) say they're going to legalize marijuana.  Can a state (say, NJ) still keep it illegal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CertMaster vs. Actual Exam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 22:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What have your experiences been with taking your exam (any exam really, I'm taking Sec+ soon) after using CertMaster to study?  Did CertMaster help you out, and were questions similar to what you saw in your studies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car n00b, question about tires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 19:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When one gets winter tires for their car, are they just replacing the tires and keeping the wheels?  Or you guys usually have another set of wheels with winter tires for the colder months?  What's the recommendation here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't we just eat napkins so we don't have to use toilet paper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Campaigners Rally to Support Apple's Stance on Government Backdoors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush's website redirects to DonaldJTrump.com. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Below is just a luxurious dollar store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what name change ruins a game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 14:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keyless access on the BRZ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 23:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this apply to both doors?  Not asking if unlocking it unlocks both doors.  But does the passenger size have that same sensor as well?  Basically, can I walk up to the passenger side door, tap the handle, and it will unlock just like the driver's side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please explain how a radio station protects this room?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 18:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Series.Blue STI Wheels... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these the same dimensions as stock wheels? 17x7? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shark gives zero fucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 03:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My local ER displays its wait time on a billboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 03:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just test drove a BRZ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  I had no idea how easy it is to drive!  I DD an automatic, but am familiar with driving manual.  I rolled the BRZ right out of the lot with no problems whatsoever!  It shifted like a dream, steering was fantastic.  Although the main 'problem' with the car is its power, it's lack of that did not bother me one bit.  I don't even think I can recreate the stupid little grin I had on my face when I was behind the wheel, until I drive another.  Looking to buy a Series.Blue in the March timeframe, I can't wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What color tie would go well with this color shirt? Preferably skinny tie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 01:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
