<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing that about fitting rooms, but these are above the entrance to our stock room. I work in the shoe department of a high end department store so this is just where we keep any items that aren't on display (other sizes, colors, out of season styles, etc.) idk. My store is pretty serious about internal theft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna be careful anyway, lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way! That's interesting. Good to know!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'll ask a manager. I've never seen a camera like that in my life, and there's like 5 of them right next to each other. Plus they're at the entrance to the stock room and I don't think anyone would do anything suspicious there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I kinda doubt they're cameras because there's like 5 of them right next to each other and they're all at the entrance to the stock room. I'd think if someone was gonna lift from the stock room, they wouldn't do it in the entrance. Lmao. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've seen a few requests for this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this isn't perfect, but I recently made a post detailing my experiences at stores and my advice as far as risk level goes, and I saw a few commenters who wanted to make a master list of personal experiences with stores.

Here's my idea: comment with your experiences below and rate each store's risk level (in your opinion) on a scale of 1-5. (One being the lowest, 5 being the highest) 
Once I get an ample amount of responses, I'll compile a master list and average the risk rating for each store, and add on a short description of general comments. 

Let me know what you guys think of this idea/format and add on your experiences with different stores and a 1-5 risk level. 

Happy lifting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely think everyone's personal experiences would be interesting too, to assess a general risk level and get a better idea of what everyone else has to say.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a good idea too. I'd definitely be interested in contributing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several of these are above our stock room in the store I work at. Do you think they're cameras? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I realize that store layouts vary. These were just my personal experiences (partly because I wanted to sit down and make a solid list of every place I've lifted from, LOL) and because I hoped maybe you guys could take something from it. I know lifting is different for everyone but I just figured I'd give you all my 2 cents. Definitely scope the place out, and pay attention to the atmosphere. If you get a bad vibe, LEAVE.

Also, that is a fair point about the mesh shopping bags, but I have a fairly large purse and that concealed the shopping bag easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
