<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2561</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a block for everything from 2 cycles ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Fort Minor had a recipe for it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep that's pretty much it. If you put more than $3,167 in groceries on the Preferred, it makes up the cost of the AF compared to the regular Blue Cash. Note that this tops out at $6,000 per year.

There's also the additional 1% on gas to consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend starting off with a secured credit card, which usually has no annual fee but also doesn't give cash back. You deposit some money with the bank and they use that as a security deposit against your credit card.

If you're a student, you can also look into student credit cards, which also have no annual fee and decent APR's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The AmEx Blue cards tend to be delayed a little bit in terms of giving rewards, usually taking 2 statement cycles before putting them in your account. As u/sleepyguy22 said, it shouldn't matter whether you pay the card off before or after the statement closes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It usually takes 2 statements to post, so hopefully after your next statement closes you'll receive the rewards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, the Everyday is a great choice because you can keep that card forever to store your MR points without any fee. You could feel free to use whatever other credit/charge cards to earn the points and close cards without worrying.

edit: You can also find incognito offers for 25K MR for the Everyday, which is the highest non-targeted offer available </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably would be okay after April 14, but it's best to wait a little longer just to be safe. I'd recommend May 1 or later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a few dollars is needed, something that will show up on the statement. I'll usually take one of my old cards to a coffee shop and put a little (or a latte!) on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer: bad at crowd sizes, good at fashion-forward footwear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend keeping cards open until the AF hits, and then calling to see if you can get a retention offer or AF waiver. If not, then you can cancel stating that you don't feel the AF is justified. If you do it within 30 days, you will get the AF refunded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Option 3, once every few months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HR195. Here's a link to the bill, though at the time of writing this comment a summary hasn't been posted yet:

https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/house-resolution/195/all-info?r=1
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep any Medallion status or a Skymiles Amex gives you a discounted rate of $79 per annum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can try searching it through a VPN, which may help. It seems hit or miss, I am only able to see it on some days.

If you do decide to just go with the 15K/$1k....please use a referral?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally not, unless they show up on your personal report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amex PRG will get you 3 MR / $ on the fees, while Delta will get you 2 Skymiles / $2. I'd recommend the former. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no downgrade you can do, unfortunately. You can call and ask for a retention offer (some people have had success) or cancel it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just to keep on Chase's good side. If you want to keep the card open indefinitely, that would help your credit scare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into the Blue Cash cards from Amex. They offer 3-6% cash back on groceries, and can really be powerful if you're spending $5k a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it hasn't been a year yet since you opened it, I'd recommend keeping it open at least for that period of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transferring points from Chase to your airline typically does not give you miles towards status. It would only help for award travel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also recommend the Travel Butter Bundle (which gives you the full size + a travel size of the shave butter) for $11 + free shipping. Net cost of $1 for more butter (After all, this is r/churning) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I haven't tried it (and don't have any AGC's to try it with at the moment). If you have one, see if you can add it as a payment method from within Google Wallet (and if it classifies as "debit"). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Everyday currently has a 25K MR/$2k spend via incognito or, if you aren't able to get that, 15K MR / $1k spend via referral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do need an MR card open. The Amex Everyday card is a no-AF card which is part of the MR program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have no other Amex cards, it might be good to keep that open for two reasons:

1) Keep your MR points

2) Receive and use Amex offers

Admittedly, this can be done with a variety of Amex cards (including the no-AF Everday).

Amex's purchase protection also seems to be better than Chase's (based on various anecdotes throughout this subreddit).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Wallet only allows sending and receiving money via debit card or a linked bank account

edit: Here's the source of that info- https://support.google.com/wallet/answer/6285500?hl=en ref_topic=6285490 authuser=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's allegedly medicinal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a break from the GOP party line, 17 House Reps introduced a resolution that acknowledges human impact on global warming and promotes finding an "innovative" way to address climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Got this on my Delta Plat, but not on ED or BCE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange you glad it's not called a lime! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true. If you go to google.com then click Ctrl+S, you essentially get a local copy of the web on your computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Via the new throttling policy, Chrome 57 will delay timers to limit average CPU load to 1% of a core if an application uses too much CPU in background. Tabs playing audio or maintaining real-time connections like WebSockets or WebRTC wont be affected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Chrome: Reducing power consumption for background tabs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the data from this Wikipedia article, the 2,600 Gwh of electricity would be enough to supply the entire annual energy consumption of 695,000 Chileans, based on an average use of 3.739 Mwh per capita per annum.

Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_electricity_consumption </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the moon should be at least....3 times....bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you met my friend Jack? He had some magic beans which he was able to grow. You should talk with him for advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bambooz-owl-ed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Does this automatically apply to existing referral links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only seen it as a targeted mailer unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your post got deleted by the bot, it should also tell you how much karma you currently have in this subreddit in the past 6 months. That can be a useful benchmark for knowing how much more you need to earn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can only product change within charge cards, and the cheapest would be the Green card for $95. If you want to keep the PRG, you can ask for a retention offer which may offset some of the AF.

Otherwise, to prevent losing any MR points you have, I would recommend opening up an Amex Everyday credit card. It is a no-AF card which lets you keep your MR points. Current offers for that are either 25K MR after $2k spend (if you can get it via incognito mode), or 15K MR after $1k spend (via referral). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $100 cash back after $1k spend and 10% back on restaurants up to $200 back for the referee.

$100 for the referrer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.americanexpress.com/us/credit-cards/card-application/apply/blue-cash-everyday-credit-card/45127-750-0-3E8E61CB89396C25BD1CF007433234E6F630B68437904BAA-200589-6VksnZOexsbZZgsKzRA7hD97X8Q=?cellid= cellid= om_rid=Nwlhqc om_mid=_BZCkMKB9a8AWAG om_lid=axp9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was traveling alone so I don't have that DP, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm that this works, did it last month. I paid the ticket entirely with UR points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can pay your taxes (federal + state) via a CC. The fee for that is just under 2%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it looked very exciting when I first ran across the article. It's also outside my area of study, and I would love to hear thoughts from someone who is more familiar with cell wetlab techniques about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great way to keep the card "active" without really using it. I'd recommend also setting up autopay for the CC statement so that you don't forget and end up missing a payment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would put the payment towards the CC with higher APR. Over the course of a year in interest, it would save you $435 vs $382 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's the first 3D glimpse of how DNA is packaged up in a single cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great reply, thanks for your insights! I especially appreciate the last salient point you made in the second paragraph, about how assuming that "my media is unbiased but the other guys' is not" can be dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's usually $50, but occasionally it's bumped up to $100. Mine is up at $100 too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend calling and seeing if they can give you a retention offer / waive the AF if you'd like to keep the card open for credit history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the Everyday cards, the regular has 2x at grocery stores whereas the Everyday Preferred ($95 AF) gives 3x. If you check in incognito mode, you may be able to get some higher sign up bonuses (25K for Everyday, 30K for Everyday Preferred).

As a side note, the Everyday is a good card to keep longterm because it has no AF and will maintain your MR points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the owner's last name rhyme with "bump"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This website works to opt you out from most of the big banks. While the website does look a little sketchy, it is the one that the FTC links to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding Amex offers - they are a separate thing altogether compared to your SPG or MR or other award program. They are often statement credits which will be applied after meeting the offer requirements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. Would there be a time where you want the media to be biased / take a side in a story? For example, with something more controversial like healthcare policy, would it be appropriate for a news report to support one viewpoint? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's correct, you can't combine a referral offer with a targeted offer. I appreciate that you're thinking about the community, but go for the higher offer :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also depends on how much time you have left on your mortgage. Reducing your principal by 1/3 can have a huge benefit in interest savings if you have several years left on your mortgage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the media try to be as unbiased as possible when reporting on a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While there has been lots of discussion in past threads about whether or not rankt.com should become the "official" referral location, it is pulling the data from the reddit threads. Personally, I am a fan of rankt.com, especially because it lets you sort by bonuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great deal for the Gold cards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend starting off with a secured or student credit card, such as one from Discover. Use it to pay for groceries, gas, etc, and always remember to pay it off in full and on time. It will start slowly building your credit up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to you and your family on this awesome achievement! Hope Friday brings a lot of happiness and excitement to ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple's ResearchKit generates reliable health data for asthma patients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google experiments with communal YouTube-watching with new app Uptime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skymiles are used to pay for award travel. They do not expire.

MQMs are Medallion Qualifying Miles, which are Delta's currency for achieving frequent flyer status. They do reset every calendar year, and can generally only be earned by flying or bonuses like this on the credit cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do have a qualifying federal loan, you can look into the Public Service Loan Forgiveness. Essentially, you would spend the first part of your post-residency career working in an area with physician need (often rural primary practices or urban care centers), and over a period of time the remainder of your loan would be forgiven. I would highly recommend speaking to your med school's advisers about this and other options. Best of luck to you!

Sources:
https://www.aamc.org/advocacy/meded/79048/student_loan_repayment.html

https://studentaid.ed.gov/sa/repay-loans/forgiveness-cancellation/public-service </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meet up at a restaurant, then ask to split the bill 75,000 ways so that everyone can pay with a CSR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for Amex unfortunately. You have to email yourself an offer and then copy the link from the email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paragraph A: The original purpose of daylight savings time was to shift the working day during spring/summer so as to maximize house of sunlight. This way, farmers (which was the dominant career for most Americans back then) could spend most of their labor hours with sunlight. Similarly, when the winter months arrive, the time is shifted back so as to again maximize sunlight. While there are fewer Americans in agriculture these days, daylight savings time still enables better synchronicity of the working day with the sun.

Paragraph B: While daylight savings time may have been useful in the former agrarian society of the US, it is no longer necessary since the majority of Americans work indoors. Even for agriculture, much of the work is now automated and the extra hour of daylight does not make much of a difference. Instead, like OP pointed out, the time shifts cause distractions and disorientations in the days immediately following. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exchange rates vary from day to day, but generally you can exchange a picture for only a thousand words. Sadly, it hasn't kept up with inflation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how much cheese sauce you eat with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What temperature is the room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use this link to generate the 40K referral offer (worked for me): https://www.americanexpress.com/mgmfall2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This link gives higher offers for most cards (ED, EDP, Delta cards, PRG, etc.): https://www.americanexpress.com/mgmfall2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you and your wife have the same household address on file with Chase, you can transfer the UR points between your accounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course there are no guarantees, but if you're booking award travel, it should be okay to wait until early May. Award travel mileage rates come in tiers, and so as long as the same tier is available, the price will be the same.

That being said, there are some fantastic cash deals to Europe right now, and you might be better off with one of those. If you do have (or later get) a Delta Amex card, you can even pay the cash price in miles using a 5k=$50 conversion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your goals. There is another referral offer available for 35K skymiles + 5K MQM, if you're looking for status. But if you're not interested in status, this is a decent offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to purchase the ticket with cash, not an award ticket or using the cash+miles option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be honest with the numbers you put in. You can just put your name in for the business name, but for the annual sales provide an accurate estimate of how much revenue your "business" generates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of factors at play in your credit score, some of which may be helping you even though it's only been a couple months. If you open new cards and have them all paid off, your utilization likely is lower because of your overall increased credit limit. Furthermore, you have more on-time payments and more accounts which have been paid off, both of which marginally help and could counter the negative effects of reducing your average age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PSA: The Delta Platinum (both personal and business) referral offers for 50K skymiles + $100 credit after $1k spend expires on March 29th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland demands new independence vote before Brexit: Sturgeon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article 28 states that in times of great need, the Constitution may be converted into $1 billion of 1776 currency, which is enough to make a small but significant impact on the lives of Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that NCAA March Madness is also unofficially known as "The Big Dance", named so by the 1977 champions Marquette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would burn the candle at both ends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they wouldn't unless you were on the itinerary too, sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For ease of use, I'd recommend using Plastiq. You pay them with a credit card and they will cut a check to your mortgage company. There is a 2.5% (sometimes less) fee associated with it, which I think is worth it considering you can do it all from your computer. 

Look into it and, if you decide to go for it, please use a referral link from the sidebar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.americanexpress.com/us/credit-cards/personal-card-application/delta-gold-credit-card/45125-750-0-C1CD61DFC0ABFEEBD48906CEEAE7F251F630B68437904BAA-200587-jJHhs6NB0YEZH3TRY5qmCGekWNE=?cellid= cellid= om_rid=NwsyP9 om_mid=_BY3B7jB9ZVQwb6 om_lid=axp13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do exist but cannot be used in combination (1 code per order allowed) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a 20k referral available for the EDP. Try logging in and generating the referral at this link (which helped me get the higher offer for the regular ED): https://www.americanexpress.com/mgmfall2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing an incognito offer for the Delta Skymiles Gold card for 50K miles + $50 statement credit after $1,000 min spend, with first year AF waived. I know it's not as high as the 60K targeted some people are getting, but otherwise a decent offer if you're not targeted.

http://imgur.com/a/8DtMP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We never earned enough daylight to save any for a rainy day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first Gull War, a truly terrible affair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will probably continue for approx. 3 months more until everyone meets / fails to meet min spends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same for me using the Reddit app on Android. Sent a message to the mods about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Passengers on the Mayflower were allotted a gallon of beer each per day. Given that beer at the time was 5-6% alcohol, one could presume the Pilgrims were inebriated more often than not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we can't have nice things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get a head of yourself, lettuce take some time to think of the implications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to Palestinian leader: Its time for a peace deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it looks like older threads are still affected, could we do a reset of all referral threads over the weekend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Latvia   Georgia (the country)

edit: Japan already mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Just confirm that the MR account number is the same on all your cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Flying an American flag upside down is not necessarily meant as political protest. The practice has its origin in a distress signal; displaying a flag in this manner is "a signal of dire distress in instances of extreme danger to life or property"; It can also be viewed as an act of desecration. It has been used by extension to make a statement about distress in civic, political, or other areas. 

Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flag_desecration#Flying_an_American_flag_upside_down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, good to know. I'm surprised they're mentioning it on their blog. Thanks for catching that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer wears American flag pin upside down at press briefing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paragraph A:
Attending a university will provide you with the skills and social credentials you need in order to get a better job down the road. Adults with a bachelor's or advanced degree tend to get higher starting salaries at jobs. Furthermore, for some careers, it is necessary to develop skills at university beyond what you would get in high school / vocational school. Invest in yourself now, and it will pay off down the road.

Paragraph B:
Society has progressed for hundreds of years without needing everyone to go to college. While there are some professions which require degrees in order to practice, most of the skills you will need for a successful career are things you will learn outside of the classroom. Why spend an extra 4 (or more) years studying theory when you can start working now, start earning money, and eventually build your way up. Many of the most successful people in business, marketing, the arts, politics, etc., did not need to have formal university training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How meta(stasis) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see this posted elsewhere (and the bots deleted it when I posted). Plastiq has a new promo for Mastercard, where if you schedule 6 or more payments for rent/mortgage, you will get the first 2 payments fee-free. Needs to be setup by March 31, but the payments can be after that. 

Link to promo: https://www.plastiq.com/blog/2017/03/promotion-no-plastiq-fee-on-first-2-rentmortgage-payments-with-mastercard/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The promo expires at the end of the month (you have to create the payment series before March 31, but they don't have to be paid by then). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I'm right there with you in that it would be great if CLEAR could be used as part of the TSA/GE credits. Even if it were a partial subsidy like $25 off of CLEAR each year, kind of like an Amex Offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Clinton [...] warned repeatedly against us versus them thinking that he said has become such an active part of politics in America, in the Brexit vote, in the Philippines and throughout Europe.

It's not just blaming the GOP or the Brexiters. We all could do a better job to try and be civil, engage with those we disagree with, and point out the facts without making ad hominem attacks. Even if some of them won't listen, I have to believe that the majority of people are still reasonable and coming from different perspectives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
