<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a game where the turn-over rate is kept at a minimum and characters get the chance to be developed, ownerless PCs usually end up NPCs or allies or adversaries, depending on the situation.

What they absolutely never get is the red-shirt treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, the previous podcast said a lot of very niche stuff. Stuff that only applies to his particular flavour of gaming.

Made it a terribly unimpressive podcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I was just showing what you might wanna do if you *[really](https://youtu.be/dicBb4t07io?t=54s)* wanna get serious. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 00:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BoEF introduced Appearance.

That's always fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 00:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=95EErdouO2w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 00:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tactics and greater numbers of lower level mooks are your answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably endeavour to be the youngest physics graduate and invent GUT or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's also been my experience with roll20. I don't use that site anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there are times when it is acceptable to feature rape in the narrative, but they never include its use as a demonstration of power over other players or how edgy and grim your campaign is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.giantitp.com/forums/showthread.php?187851-3-5-Lists-of-Necessary-Magic-Items </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concrete blocks weather away.

'sides, spending a few years in a concrete block builds character, as we all know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KotOR was d20, so duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This, and heroes 3 were the first games I ever laid my hands on.

I suspect DF2 is single-handedly responsible for my obsession with Star Wars. I still have the old discs somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shift in colour was cool.

Nature is neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 00:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine. Yahoo has always been my spam mailbox.

Every shady site, I needed to register on, I used my yahoo.

Hope NSA enjoyed the penis enlargement ads and distressed nigerian princes that tend to acrue as a result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the "game design theorist" guy, so there's a lot of them(way to many to even think of posting here).

I have a soft spot for martials, so this is where the majority of tweaks go.

But I'm most proud of the Fumble system that is not complete and utter shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rape is totally okay, you guys. It's just a make-belief anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, the continuing ornithological theme hinted as much.

 It's the name of an Anatolian/Balkan demon.

I should know... I live there.  
:D

Taking names from mythologies halfway around the world is like a "secret D D hack". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I'mma go ahead and say fuck the uploader and region locking.

Here's the original:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=54VJWHL2K3I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These 4 words... they make a shiver run down my spine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LA is an adjustment that compensates for the greater power of the race compared to other races.

All it says is that the abilities of the race bump it up in power enough for it to be considered of equal power level as someone of higher class levels, but a less powerful race.

Playing around with LA and racial abilities is the DMs domain. And even then, only if he's got system mastery.

It's impossible to give reasonable answers for unqualified statements like yours.

So either give us specifics - what kind of race or type of character you wanna play, how far your DM is willing to work with you, etc. or just stick to the rules, which are there for a reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ECL = LA + RHD + Class levels.

It is that simple.

ECL means Effective Class Level, which should be self-explanatory(the power your character is considered). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 13:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Skeet is programming [Chuck Norris](https://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/9134/jon-skeet-facts). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 13:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one with ~~Hugh Herr~~ David Sarif:  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CDsNZJTWw0w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't DM because it's hard, thankless work.

Being a DM is not trivial. Those who enjoy killing their players are egotistical dinks who simply want a power-trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A kindred soul!

Except with me it's demons. For reasons... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea... kobold bard isn't exactly new. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you think monks are stronK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DM as Eng. Lit major is not surprising AT ALL.

For a bit I also thought he was an avid sci-fi buff, what with names like:
Kallikantzaros [Zelazny, The immortal] and Shrike [Simmons, Hyperion] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really.

My personal setting is one where I try to subvert every D D or generic fantasy trope I can think of and don't like.

A choice few things are played straight(the real gods), but most are deliberately subverted, mostly with the goal of consistency and some modicum of logic. And IMO all these changes actually make it more "D D" than even the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superconductors "exclude" magnetic fields, making them flow around the substance. This can be adapted to all sorts of applications, not the least of which is floating things on magnets in a very efficient manner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 13:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how this works. You don't ask the experienced guy to get down to the level of the inexperienced. You ask him to bring the inexperienced to his level.

Purely unrelated to the game itself, just ask him to help others enjoy this activity you share together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that gets us closer to room-temperature superconductors is Nobel worthy.

Woot, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 23:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Away.*

I homebrew it away.

And less story milestones, but rather character milestones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now these look like actual bloody continents.

So many times you see maps of entire worlds, where calling it an "island" would actually be generous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do my own thing, but if the languages are obscure, I make sure I validate the player's choices in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have the correct interpretation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 13:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I may suggest, you could go for the [Grand Moff Tarkin](http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Wilhuff_tarkin) vibe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Encounter Level... you know, characters have to face challenging encounters if they wanna gain XP. Same with players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once the whole saga is over, you can go  
*"Congratulations, you have leveled up. And I'm not talking about your characters."*

Training players is a difficult and lengthy process. Thankfully your EL seems to be more than enough for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alignment is descriptive, not prescriptive.

Subreddit circlejerky wisdoms aside, motherfucking Vash. You **cannot** get more on the nose of that particular archetype than him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more that the size and clustering of the features suggest a smaller scale, at least to my eye.

On continental scales, features like forests, plains, etc. look more "patchy" - not so uniformly clustered. And there's usually clear terrain distinctions due to climate. Your map, despite its scale, looks like it resides in a single climate region.

All of this makes the scale look much smaller than the numbers you explicitly list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is not too big.

If you wanna call it a "continent", you'd got the scale down pat(it's about the size of Asia).

The features look like they're on a smaller scale however(i.e. seems the map should be denser given its scale). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the former when the people possess great abstraction skills and the latter when they do not.

The problem is when players, even if unwittingly, let conflict get out of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sort of deeply invested in 3.PF.

I've tried others - 5e, 2e, Dark Heresy, Cypher, at least 1 dice pool game(Burning wheel, I think?), but no other can give me what I'm looking for.

I do like to borrow mechanics from other games, but the core is always the 3.P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Float the die.

But yes, it does seem to be skewed. But no dice are perfect. Ideally the skew is around the 10, so you might even count yourself lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DM is not being unfair, but he could stand to be more understanding. You are certainly not wrong either. People get different things out of this game. You seem to be about character drama, so getting to develop a character is important to you(I'm the same, so I understand your pain).

3.5e DMG2 has a very interesting chapter on player motivations. Some of which do not require a persistent character, other - like this one do. They name this particular type of motivation "psychodrama". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 for "a significant amount".

I.e. both should be tied. After that you can diverge through play.

With me, it's usually take something that inspires me(a build or character idea) and make the other thing fit. 'course I play 3.5 and PF, where there is more to "fit". Gets iffy in 5e. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 16:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rambunctious

Such a fun word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 16:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started as noise. Got trippy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 14:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super misleading title!

He merely talked about *other* critics potentially giving it a different treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 14:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are some very logical and good changes. This coming from a guy who enjoys modded Civ4. It makes me excited for Civ again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the kind of player you have. Some people identify more strongly with their characters.

Others merely view their character as an interface for the social interaction or their interaction with the game world and place no special meaning to each individual character.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 01:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even as I'm aware I'll get flak for this...

*Just don't do time travel.*

It's not about getting it right. No one can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exact same reason I don't wanna live on this planet anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes... and the brainwashing and the propaganda and Iroh's tale.

The genius of the show is them managing to tackle surprisingly dark themes in such a subtle way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The answer to the title question is simple: When there is something you want in your campaign that is not addressed by any pre-existing rule or piece of content.

Homebrewing is always the last step, after you've exhausted the million other options(well, a little bit less for 5e). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are ways to avoid verbal components, but they require greater expenditure of resources - metamagic feats, etc.

However, there is one relevant option you have, that isn't technically "mute", but it is available from L1 and does avoid the need for normal verbal components, called "Surrogate casting" - it allows you to substitute any sounds or flailing you are capable of for verbal and somatic components. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you need an explanation? Because of fallacious comparisons to some vague notion of realism? You shut such silly talk down *fast*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choo choo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cam is so shaky, it makes me think it's fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how do you get to this magical land of terabithia? A bridge or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always rush that wonder in Civ. Power for an entire continent... so valuable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HL2, Super Mario World, Heroes 3, many LucasArts classics.

These games are a prime example of the difference between graphics and aesthetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that saying from Civilization. It's one of my favourite blurbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's plenty of people who already weighed in on the people problem.

I'm gonna address a small tidbit everyone else missed:
 spend most time when we're not playing scouring the various D D themed subreddits and youtube videos

That will likely leave you with a very skewed view of the game.  
**Read the books instead.** Your time is better spent scouring the actual D D books than browsing subreddits and youtube videos.

I can't tell you the number of times I wished people would just read the books. This is *NOT* a new game. Most of what can be said about the game(and RPing in general) has already been said - and has made its way in the books. All the clever insights and tricks that these outlets keep spouting like some unfathomable wisdom they had to meditate on for 2 years atop a mountain peak to unlock... chances are, it's already in one DMG or another. Believe me, I've read most of them - from 2e to 5e('cept 4e, I couldn't be bothered with that edition). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have to agree with that dude.

Keep religion to the spiritual. A piece of paper that identifies you in front of some government has nothing spiritual in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... they'll be longer for certain. You need to even out the action economy. Absolutely do not throw single creatures at them, they'll get swarmed. Get creative in taxing their action potential to its limit and beyond - multiple creatures, challenges, extra goals during combat, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... it's not that I'm intentionally hipster. More that I try to deconstruct DMing and then stick to the most optimal techniques. For example I'm definitely the "game design theorist" type. It's... complicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was his channel called before?

I remember way back in the day, it was something different, then it took me like a year to discover his new channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a hack for producing laminar flow out of turbulent: Pack a cross-section of your tube/hose with straws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God... I can see myself in here.

You've captured every obscure trope there is.

I can tell, because I am all of the obscure ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story of how a writer learned about "player agency". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiendish Codex II: Tyrants of the Nine Hells, p.23.

If you clearly make it known you are willing to make a Faustian deal, you can expect them to be pretty friendly. However, standard fiend summoning precautions are prudent (circle against evil, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, yes. Here's the math:

TWF: 2*(die(d6)+enh) + 1.5*str  
2H: die(d12) + enh + 1.5(str + 2)

The die difference is a 0.5 lead for TWF.  
That last +2 assumes the use of power attack, making both styles attack at equal attack bonus. The power attack is usually higher.  
2H is more action efficient however. TWF must usually focus on delivering full attacks.  
TWF is also much more feat intensive. 2H requires just one thing - Power Attack.  
TWF's bonus is mostly in the doubling of enhancements. However, it is often not ideal to take enhancement bonuses. Your gold is better spent in qualitative improvements to your weapons(such as ghost touch or transmuting or the like) rather than quantitative.

Overall, money and action-wise, 2H is the better, more efficient fighting style. Statistically, you do more damage with less action, feat and gold cost with 2H weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 21:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is EXACTLY the opposite.

You have to pay for enchantments twice with TWF. While 2H receives the same benefit from a single enchantment. The (admittedly minor) bonus is, the enchantments can vary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 21:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you are misunderstanding the concept.

Saying "yes" isn't about anarchy or going wild or throwing away all rules(even if for the sake of fun/hilarity).

Saying *"yes"* is about affording your players with ***agency***. The ability to affect your world in meaningful ways. This is as much about sticking to the rules(because players have to be able to reliably reason about your world to affect it) as it is about allowing them to occasionally pull off something cool or fun, even if it doesn't quite mesh with the rules.

The *"but..."* part is about knowing where to draw the line to accomplish this goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 11:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, uh... Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 11:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's sort of a cultural/societal pressure.

Tick all da boxes, or else society tells you you haven't lived your life properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 11:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/8XGHNwk8eiQ?t=25s

Besides, I happen to know all of these words and regularly use half of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 06:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An actual honest-to-god technology discussion and not a single "I understand some of these words" in /r/dota2 of all places. I am amazed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 05:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read that as "Pull out debunked". Was expecting something else entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 02:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master Manipulator is pretty great.  
Other notable examples are Social Recovery and Smooth Talk.  
There's a couple of relevant skill tricks too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \#4.... people do that IRL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did mine to set up the central conflict and in such a way that I can add gods or even entire pantheons as I see fit. I wanted it to be open enough to allow all existing settings to coexist - leave your options open I always say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a 10 lvl char. The more relevant bit was that the campaign ended literally 5 sec(1 round) after he died.

He died after attacking a monster that another player had successfully evaded. I was 40-ish HP. Got one-shot after MAKING my save. Not even multiple attacks.

I'm like *"seriously"*?

I sulked for the 2 minutes the end boss death animation played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 15:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you use one of the non-flat Massive Damage variants.

I'm fond of the PF version(half-hp).

The rest are located here:  
http://www.d20srd.org/srd/variant/adventuring/massaveDamageThresholdsAndResults.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 14:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from what sources are permitted, you also need to tell us what kind of wizard you're running. Do you wanna blast? Buff your party? Battlefield control? A batman wizard dragon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 03:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH that(tldr) should be standard practice at every table.

It isn't in 90% of cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You collected that in 2 years?  
You seem to be mildly passionate over that hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feat is specifically so you can keep up when multiclassing.

As such, it will not push your CL past your HD, but it will allow you to catch up if your casting levels are less than your HD(i.e. you multiclassed). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either he's stupid, or he's playing you for laughs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Mass Effect + Star Citizen + Starcraft + Homeworld + Civilization(in space) combo. Possibly set in the Star Wars universe.

I want ALL DA SCALES - from playing individual characters to commanding armies to guiding entire galactic civilizations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another explanation of the phenomenon by [Veritasium](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cebFWOlx848). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiend Folio p.209. Go wild. Or demonic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \#2 is much more than skipping the boring bits.

It's the ability to separate the real world from the imaginary. Lack of this is what causes 95% of all problems at a table.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's silly. Just take the grafts in lieu of taking a half-progression class that wastes 10 levels for something you can get for 50K or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is better:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RS46s0EXm1M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 03:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls are humans too. Fancy that.

Also, in a "teenage boys" environment making her character male is probably going to make her immune to most ingame nastiness - if they're juvenile enough for stupid jokes, they're probably wouldn't want to appear "gay" by hitting on a male character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw, the original D D was very machiavellian in that sense - all you had was law vs chaos. Alignment as we know it today did not exist and good vs evil simply wasn't a part of the game back then. I think it was expected or viewed that all "adventurers" were morally gray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Craft(Bookbinding) check? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a fan of the "luck" interpretation, "combat endurance/fatigue" seems much more reasonable.

Besides, if you're gonna houserule, first try the official house-rules(a.k.a. the variant rules), which in this case is nat20=30, nat1=-10. It's in the DMG in the 20-ish pages I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max: 6  
Preferred: 3

I'm a simple man with simple needs, a nice, cozy story, with a tight-knit party, where characterization can stay in the forefront all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
