<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6310</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm just going to put my 2 cents in, While i agree i don't want magic powers in this game, we are already injecting ourselves with fuel and metal fragments to heal. I could see an "adrenaline" shot boosting our speed but lowering our FOV and aim steadiness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree, i wish at least the raid ships were new skins like oryx one was. this just looks like the first ship we get with a big diamond/triangle siva'd on top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone once told me that time is a flat circle so it we will keep repeating the same steps over and over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well did the chicken just pop out of the creature beforehand? or was it born in an egg?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> since you're trying to be discrete, here is my advice. Now i don't know the limitations of your projects or if you're only allowed to use one shared document. I would send it to your superiors saying something along the lines of here is my portion, the others will be sending theirs in separately. If they haven't touched the shared document and expect you to do the work this is a decent way of showing that 1. you are taking owner ship for your work and 2. you can feign ignorance and say that since they did not touch the shared document you assumed they were using their own document to turn in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the kick was taylored for her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not mine but the Arnold = MiB theory. I personally think its dumb and it doesn't make sense that the MiB would somehow be arnold. It seems like the same people that tried to force the William = MiB theory are grasping for different straws. Can't the MiB be someone we haven't heard about yet and have a completely different story line?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> scone cold steve austin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no other guests are antagonizing the hosts the way TMIB is. i'm sure if they were to push the limits of WW the way he is, they would shoot too just so they wouldn't break the immersion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow that is a really good idea, don't know how they would implement it. maybe 2 different playlists? if you've gone flawless you only have access to the flawless playlist? All three character in fireteam needs to not have gone flawless to enter the nonflawless playlist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we did, and we continued to. Got myself a nice shiny blue cat emblem to go with the continuous wins. Also 2v3 sucks im sorry that happened to you :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
