<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aggressive plan  no plan at all! I'm happy things are moving forward, and I so wish you a 2017 baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First crosshairs!! So many questions! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little backstory for everyone:
Stopped HBC in August after 11 years, never had regular cycles but was in for a rude awakening. 1st cycle lasted 106 days (most probably anovulatory). Half of me was gearing up for a long, crappy cycle 2, half of me was still hopeful for *something* to happen. 

Went to see my doctor in November, had bloodwork done and an ultrasound which revealed normal blood results (however progesterone was not tested and TSH was 3.69, so I'm keeping that in mind in case things keep being wacky) and a 3-cm kyst on my left ovary. Follow-up ultrasound last week revealed everything was normal. 
I finally migrated my cycle 2 data onto FF (was using Glow since August) because I *finally* ovulated on CD41! Currently 7DPO and I have a question:

- I'm just glad I ovulated at all, but I'm also hoping things might have worked. However, I've had NO symptoms at all, but then again I never really have PMS symptoms or ovulation symptoms, so should I expect the same here? What else can I do except wait?
Thanks in advance :)

EDIT: Removed my chart to comply with rules (and x-posted on /TFABChartStalkers) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preach girl. I feel ya, you sound 100% like me, and I'm also fine with not being a cool girl, right now I just want to do all I can to try and make it work. I really hope it works out for you soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow what a week! Despite how shitty it must feel I think you're reacting quite well, and I so wish you a BfP soon so that you and your sister can have little cousin play dates! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome back, best of luck!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had my first-ever temp rise so I'm pretty sure I ovulated for the first time ever... on CD40! Since we weren't expecting me to ovulate we didn't have sex quite nearly as much as I would have liked, especially since DH went out of town for 3 days during that week (I think I O'ed either the day he left or the day before). This puts me at 7DPO. No symptoms at all. I'm starting to doubt my body, like I can't believe I even ovulated. I know so many of us have symptoms suuuuper early, but is having *no* symptoms at all a bad thing? What can I expect? I don't want to get my hopes up so I keep telling myself that of course it probably didn't work, but at least I ovulated. *haalp pls* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome!! We all need laughs about silly stuff like that! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was also on Yasmin as of age 15 due to acne and irregular/absent periods (thanks for giving me BC instead of checking why I was so irregular). I never thoguht much of it, but since coming off HBC in August I had a 106-day anovulatory cycle, am currently on CD47 (but 6 DPO, yay!). Since coming off BC, I've had hella lots of acne (and even backne FML), greasier hair, and I find I have a bit more facial hair (luckily I'm blonde), however not overweight, no problems with insulin or glucose and no kysts on my ovaries.... Not too sure what my problem is but definitely BC just masked some of my issues for 11 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I don't think testing earlier can be a bad thing, if there is something that needs to be helped along by medicine might as well know asap, like you say "every month with a BFN is a month you can't get back". I wish you the best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read it but will def check it out! Please let us know how you found it, it's nice that it's actually written by a registered dietician and non a pseudo-professional! (I'm a bit partial as I have a bachelors in Nutrition) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give up and keep charting!! Sounds like me, I had a 106-day anovulatory cycle after stopping HBC in August, and cycle 2 was looking like a bust since I hadn't gotten any positive OPKs, no EWCM and no temp rise. Well lo and behold, I never got a positive OPK but I seem to have ovulated at CD43 or CD44 because my temps have risen and stayed high for 5 days now!! I temp orally and did have a few wonky readings but it seems better now. You might want to temp vaginally as I hear it's supposed to give more consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, I hope it works out for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much to report here, still trailing last week's bad cold and it's January, so snow/freezing rain/ice everywhere. I managed to do 30 minutes on the elliptical yesterday, and I plan to go for a run this weekend. Fingers crossed that I actually go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah, miles!! (Canadian here, sorry haha) Just converted your miles to km and "Good job!" Fried chicken and donuts sound awesomeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TTC has definitely been good for our intimacy and for forcning us to take the time for each other. I've really irregular/long/anovulatory cycles so far (but I think I just O'ed for the 1st time 3 days ago, yay!), so our gameplan was to just try and have sex every 2 days (3 at the most) since we never knew when the *right time* could happen... There have been only 1 or 2 times where it felt truly forced, and that sucks, but overall this is the (almost only) positive aspect about this stressful TTC journey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for the support... I've started seeing a therapist and it is what's making me realize that the way I'm living in my head is not sustainable if I want to actually enjoy life. I'm starting to be able to talk to my SO about it, but even then the shame, the fears are always there even though he says he's there for me and loves me no matter what. I'll get better, or anyway I'll work hard to get better... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome!! Just followed you :)
Edited to add: I also "wasted" half of 2016 saying "Well I should be pregnant by then, so...". NOT. I've also booked 3 races so far and will definitely try to stop projecting into the future and playing the "if I'm pregnant" game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I third the motion for a SA soon so that you guys know what you're working with! And of course having his epilepsy under control is super important, so I wish you good luck on that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, I hope that things go well for you, and good on you to prevent and try to see what you can proactively do :)
I've never been diagnosed with depression, but I've always felt that despite having everything I needed all throughout my life, I was never happy enough, and I did have periods where I felt that it might be easier if I weren't *there*. I'm at a low point now where I'm actually wondering if I should be trying to get pregnant at all, because how will I possibly get better and get through this if I'm not good *before* getting pregnant? I'm scared and am not sure how to bring it up with anyone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sit at work (pretending to work) waiting to go to my follow-up ultrasound... I don't know what I'm expecting, not even sure what I want to see on that screen.
8 weeks ago I had a 3-cm kyst on my ovary, I hope it's gone, but I'm afraid there will be others in its place, as I feel like my body is unable to ovulate on its own. At least I'll know, and I'll be able to go see my doctor shortly to hopefully get some answers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring it on, Ruby! Posts like this make me want to also just stop whining and just gear up for whatever is coming. Thanks for the badass reminder!
(After my hard-boiled egg, my full-fat greek yogurt and granola breakfast, I'll have my clementines and nuts as a morning snack and my colourful salad with grilled chicken and avocado for lunch! :) Healthy eats all around!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, my plan was to not tell anyone when we started in order to avoid everyone asking for updates... I have the worst poker face and cannot lie to save my life, and I'm really close to my family so of course I told everyone. I also told my close friends because my best friend and I started trying at the same time, so I was happy as I thought I'd have someone sharing the same experience as me... Well, she's now 21 weeks pregnant and I haven't even ovulated once yet (actually waiting for my first temp spike, but who knows!). As for my family, I've shared my irregular cycle problems just because that's the open book I am, but they know me well enough not to ask too many questions... So I'd say that it really depends on your family dynamic, how close to them you are, etc... I'm a bit ambivalent with how I feel about everyone knowing. On one hand it's nice to know that people know what you're going through and they care about you so they'll be there, but then again I feel like no one understands and older ladies (mother, aunts, etc) seem to downplay the whole thing, like I'm dramatizing for nothing..

Sorry for the long post haha, relationships can get pretty complicated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you the best, TTC sex can be really good or really bad, depending on the circumstances... Either way, it isn't solely up to you to be sexier for sure, both of you have to make time and make BDing a priority during your fertile window. As you mentioned, maybe giving him less fertility details would help, whereas some guys prefer knowing. I think the key here is open and honest conversation about all of this.
Good luck, I hope things work out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my first-ever EWCM day before yesterday!! However I wasn't able to get a positive OPK, and my temp was higher this morning but I'm still not sure I did O. Waiting for that! (Would be my first O in 5 months woot!)
Have a good time BD'ing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like temping for FAM is just a quick 1-minute routine to integrate. For me, even doing it while TTC is not a drag so I don't feel like it'll be something hard to keep up with while using FAM. I think that the constant waiting and expectation of TTC is what's harder, not the actual act of temping or checking CM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing I know is that I do NOT want to go back to HBC. For now my cycles are so fucked up that I'm not sure I could effectively use FAM, but then again I'm not ovulating so no risk of a pregnancy, right? All kidding aside, DH and I discussed that after having baby #1, we'll probably use FAM for a bit until we're ready for #2 and so on, and once the family is complete, then he does his side of the contract and gets a vasectomy. And if FAM fails and we get pregnant by accident, then hell that's how it'll be, but considering how long and wacky my cycles are right now I think it's unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! I hope I get good news like that on Thursday at my follow-up ultrasound! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad to read that it went well! Hug him tight and good luck for the rest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently CD40 and still waiting to ovulate... I'm not sure how I feel about that... Yesterday I had quite a lot of CM (maybe something close to eggwhite, not too sure as it was the first time I had anything remotely resembling it), my cervix felt higher, softer and maybe a bit more open, but the OPK I took only had a pale 2nd line... We BD'd anyway, but I don't know if this is just another fake surge of my body *trying* to ovulate or if this will really happen, but I desperately hope that my body is getting back on track after 5 months off HBC.. Fingers crossed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can get tiring, that's true! DH and I had been slacking off in the BD department for a while when we started TTC (we could go almost 2 weeks without sometimes, due to my low libido and frequent pain during the act). Stopping HBC really helped me though, less pain, mor libido, and an actual goal that we want to reach through BD. We now go every 2 or 3 days, and it has happened a few times where we didn't really feel into it when we started, but it usually finishes well (ha!). However, I feel like it has revived our sex life overall. And if we're too tired to do it one night, we just make sure to do it the next day. Don't put too much pressure on yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Us too! Together for 6 years, we don't have a joint account but own a house together and plan our budget as one, he pays some things I pay others, so far TTC expenses have been me but it's all the same to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the place to vent! We know how crappy that can feel... On Saturday night we were at DH's work party, and his colleague's GF is 34 weeks pregnant (accidental pregnancy) and she keeps mentioning how she doesn't enjoy pregnancy, it took **all** my effort not to tell her to shut up about because some of us would just die to be in her place... It happens, keep your chin up and good luck, I hope the arthritis won't give you too much trouble! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are me 3-4 months ago. Starting this journey I was like, "Hey, I'm healthy, 27, got my shit (mostly) together, so we should get pregnant within a few months". HA! Fast forward to 5 months later, and I absolutely don't get how most women go about their lives not knowing all there is to know about our reproductive system, like, I feel cheated by the system, as if somehow someone should have warned us! I'm temping, taking OPKs and trying to monitor CM, but haven't even ovulated once... It's hard on the morale of course, and there are good days and horrible days, but right now I'm getting to the point where I'm steeling myself for a long and hard time to get pregnant, and I think that adjusting your expectations is key to staying sane through this. 
I also started seeing a therapist (not just because of TTC, but many issues that I've had for a long while just become *more* amplified with the stress of TTC), so my hope is that by the time I DO get pregnant, I'll be better on my way to managing my anxiety and I'll have climbed out of the steep slope towards depression I'm currently on... Sorry for the long post, but TL;DR: Welcome to the club, hope you don't stay on TFAB for too long! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I hope so too! At this point I *know* there must be something wrong, but I'd just like to know what it is so that we can work on fixing it. Not knowing is the worst part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are they waiting for to market caffeine IVs? Honestly I'd be lining up at the door :)
On another topic, I hope that your early shift means that you'll get off work earlier as well? Just trying to find a silver lining hehe.


My brain is in a fog from my huge cold, so not too productive here either, thankfully I don't have a new employee to train </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are me! Haha we are extreme outliers maybe... All this makes me mad that when I was 16 with very infrequent cycles, all the doctor did was prescribe the pill. Yay for masking potential future problems instead of trying to fix them right away! Now I feel like I'm paying the price of our general ignorance of what's going on in our bodies. Don't give up Pilea :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had been taking Yasmin for 11 years and went off it in August 2016. I had a period right after stopping (withdrawal bleeding), then nothing until December 1st (106 days). Now, my second cycle is on CD 39, still no O, no AF. So yes, of course it can take some time to regulate, and your LP of 12 days is not too concerning either. It's normal to be paranoid a bit and to question whether things are working normally, but I wouldn't worry too much if I was you. And good on you to follow-up with your OB/GYN promptly. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently CD 39 and still nothing. Been battling an intense cold for almost a week, feeling like crap at work this morning (and wasting what little energy I have browsing TFAB, oops). I'm just looking forward to my follow-up ultrasound on Thursday where they'll check if the 3-cm kyst I had on my left ovary in November is gone. Hopefully I'll get more answers as to why my cycles are at a standstill and nothing at all is happening. I just hope my doctor doesn't think I'm freaking out for nothing.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck for the surgery, and I agree that hospital waiting rooms should not be dealt with alone. Fingers crossed for you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We haven't had to do that as of yet even though DH travels for work quite often only because I haven't ovulated at all in the past 5 months... But it was my fear that I'd get my first positive OPK while he was a 5-hour fight away! I couldn't just drop everything and fly to him, but driving a few hours would be something I'd do. He's scheduled to be working at the other end of the country (Canada, so it's quite far) from January 30th until the end of February, which frickin sucks... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to see you go... I've thought about taking a step back as well, with the anxiety of waiting for stuff to happen (which is **not** happening at all for me, haven't ovulated at all in 5 months), but the information and the support have really helped. I hope that 2017 brings you what you want and that NTNP works out for you, but most of all I hope that you are happy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very often below 97, and my lowest has been 96.1, almost scary when I compare to most of you!! I've never seen a temp jump either so I haven't had anything above 97.5 (which was rare unto itself, and probably due to temping a bit later or having 1-2 drinks the night before) I temp orally btw
Edited to add: how low is too low?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I've got my list in my notes as well! DH and I did it while on a roadtrip this summer :)
I'm in Quebec so all names need to be bilingual (I don't want francophones massacreing my child's name all their life), and our top contenders right now are Simone, Eloise or Beatrice for a girl, and Victor, Theo and Arthur for a boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My situation is very similar to yours (CD 36 right now and no O, last cycle was 106 days and anovulatory), so I just *try* to do the best I can about limiting myself to 2 coffes max/day and being reasonable on the drinking. I personally don't feel the need to take HPTs because I temp and am pretty sure nothing happened. I am however doing OPKs almost every day and have been since CD12 this cycle... Bought a big box of Easy@Home from Amazon. Also, just to be safe in case I do ovulate at some point, we try to BD every 2 days, 3 at most. I'm going to see my doctor again in a few weeks as well (saw her in November and she told me if 3 months afterward my cycles were still weird/too long we'd do more tests) Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phew, I already have bad acne and mood swings since stopping HBC :( I can't imagine how I'll be if I have to take progesterone! Thanks for the info though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I wish I didn't have to be!! My best friend got pregnant 2 weeks after stopping BC, so she does NOT understand how it is, she didn't even have to *think* about temping and taking OPKs, and now she's telling me to "just relax".... right.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you the best of luck, and honestly it might be better to start with the knowledge that it might take a while, that way if all goes smooth and you get a BFP in the first few cycles then you'll be pleasantly surprised! For my part, it's a back-and-forth between being overly optimistic (started trying in August and I was seeing myself pregnant at Christmas) and just being convinced it'll never work (so far my cycles have been super long, irregular and probably anovulatory). On the other hand, I'm trying to tell myself to just trust in life and that all I can do is prepare myself, educate myself and just take all the steps I can to make my body a healthy house for a baby... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal for the next few weeks/months is to get back into the habit of exercising. Seems like the past few months there hs always been something in the way of me going running, doing yoga, or just weight-training, which always makes me feel better and I'm usually able to keep up. This TTC business coupled with a job for which I am overqualified and zero motivated, all while trying to finish my Master's degreee has got me stressed, depressed and exhausted. 2017 has to be the year where I really start taking good care of myself physically but also mentally. That's my goal (quite hefty but hey, a girl's gotta try) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bluez, can I ask what were the side effects of the progesterone? I'm rwading up on hormonal issues as I'm pretty sure *something* is wrong with me, but I'm trying to figure out if it's low progesterone, subclinical hypothyroidism, high prolactin or something else, so the more I know, the better-prepared I'll be for asking my doctor ALL the questions! Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay!! That's so great, I'll probably be like you if I ever end up ovulating and seeing a nice temp spike!! Oh the little things that mean so much when you're TTC-crazy! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, sure looks like I'll be hanging around here for a while! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this back-to-work, post-holiday, long-crap-no-ovulation-cycle slump, I'm grateful for my SO (clich, I know, but oh so true). He's always there, is almost the only one who can make me laugh, and is really making an extra effort to make me feel a bit better. Also, it's not necessarily something *fun*, but I've started seeing a therapist... It was long overdue, it's hard as well and it's making me realize just how broken I am, but I'm grateful to myself to have had the courage to go to my appointments thus far. Last thing, it's Thursday already even though I went back to work yesterday! *yay for 3-day weeks!* :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I"m just getting to that part (Chapter 8 or 9 if I recall) in TCOYF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ordered the Easy@Home OPKs on Amazon and was wondering if they're any good? I've got long wacky cycles too, so trying not to go broke peeing on too many expensive sticks haha! If things don't work out in the next few months I might just splurge on a monitor though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! I have a lot of the symptoms you're describing and low progesterone is definitely a possibility that I'll float by my doctor when I see her in a few weeks. My advice is for you to talk to your doctor about your concerns and ask for bloodwork (not only progesterone, but also other reproductive hormones as well as TSH to check for thyroid function, since hypothyroidism can give some similar symptoms). I'm also reading through *Taking Charge of Your Fertility* which has lots of great info about all these symptoms. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got long/irregular/probably anovulatory cycles and I might be crazy, but I am using OPKs *just in case*...
I stopped the pill in August and so had no idea if/when I'd ovulate, I used a few OPKs in September (with only negative results). Turns out my first cycle lasted 106 days with no visible ovulation (was also temping). On to cycle 2 with some optimism (ha!), started taking OPKs almost every day between CD 12 and now (CD 36) without any positives, only a few days with a very faint second line.
I'm starting to be pretty bummed out and frustrated with my body, but I also order a big box of cheap Amazon OPKs to keep on *trying* to see something happening, although my hopes are crumbling to dust right about now...
Will be seeing my doctor very soon if this keeps up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I'm so sorry you're going through that. Heating pads and ibuprofen or tylenol are my go-to for cramps. Take care of yourself and take the time you need to process all the feels.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, not really, although since I've known it's there I *may* have felt a few twinges of pain, but it might just be my troll brain knowing there's something in there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well hello then :)
I found out about the cyst in November during an ultrasound that my doctor had prescribed after I went to see her after stopping BC for 2.5 months without a period. She then sent me for some basic bloodwork and an ultrasound to see if there was anything blatantly wrong with me (there wasn't outright, but I have some more questions as things don't seem to be getting any better). I'm anxious to see what the follow-up ultrasound will show, but I'll see my doctor again because I have a shitload of questions haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to all you guys I have better questions to ask my doctor, so that I can figure out what's the next best move :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I'm starting to be worried I might be in subclinical hypothyroidism, November bloodwork revealed a 3.89 TSH, I have extremely long and anovulatory cycles... Seeing my doctor in a few weeks and will definitely try to push for more tests, especially as prolactin was not tested in November. Thanks for the info :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense taken! I overindulged as well haha, 'twas the season for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not taking Vitex or any special supplements. I take a multivitamin + folic acid + omega-3.
Originally, I stopped the pill mid-August, and went to see my doctor in November because nothing had happened (no ovulation, no period except BC withdrawal mid-august). She had me do bloodowrk and an ultrasound to see if there was anything blatantly wrong with my uterus/ovaries etc. Things came back mostly normal (my TSH level is at 3.89 which is considered normal but maybe a bit too high to conceive, and I had a 3-cm kyst on my ovary, which will be re-checked next week with a follow-up ultrasound) She told me to go back and see her in 3 months (February) if things were still at a standstill. So that's what I'l do. I didn't take Vitex just because I want to see how my body does without it, and I think my doctor would probably tell me to not take it anyway for now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. At this point, I don't even dare wish for a BFP, I just want **something** to happen! Ovulation, AF, anything to let me know that something is happening in my body... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll definitely keep that in mind!
As for the calories in lattes, I'm not *really* looking to lose weight (I'm a perfectly healthy weight but if I could drop 5 lbs without doing anything drastic I wouldn't say no) so I wouldn't cut back just for those few calories, plus, right now I put cream so it'll probably come out almost the same :) But that's a good point for someone really wishing to lose weight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire you!! Honestly I'm on the fence about cutting out caffeine. I just love my coffee way too damn much! I did reduce from 3 cups/day to 2, but I'm having trouble going lower. I think I'll try to slowly switch to decaf at least, and make it a latte so that I get a portion of dairy for the calcium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like we're (almost) in the same shitty anovulatory boat.. I'm in month #5, but only cycle 2 (CD34 and no ovulation in sight). I am definitely seeing my doctor in a few weeks since this is not normal. I had some bloodwork done in the fall and an ultrasound in November, going back in a week for a follow-up ultrasound (I had a 3-cm cyst on an ovary), but I know I don't want to wait a full year before taking the next steps. I encourage you to do the same if you can, it feels just a bit better knowing we're doing what we can to get the ball rolling. Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm feeling a bit down today, but also... neutral, like I've run out of emotions. It's my first day back at work after the holidays, the office is empty, there was a snowstorm during the night so it took me an hour to drive to work in the snow and I'm tired, because who wakes up at 6 a.m. on Christmas vacation? On the TTC front, I'm getting a bit discouraged and I'm trying to distance myself from obssessing but it's impossible... I'm on CD34 of my second cycle and have had no hint of ovulation (am temping and took about 15 OPKs since CD 14, first cycle lasted 106 days and was most likely anovulatory). I'm getting impatient. And mad. After 5 months I haven't even gotten one single chance to conceive, but in the meantime we're trying to get busy every 2 or 3 days, "just in case"... It's starting to take a toll. The only upside is that I've signed up for 3 races for 2017, so at least if I'm not pregnant I'll have at least something to look forward to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay for runners!!
I ran my first half-marathon at the end of August when we started TTC, with the naive "plan" that I'd be having a baby in the summer/fall of 2017, so I'd be off from running and return with a vengeance in 2018.. Well, that plan didn't work out so far, but in the meantime I slacked off running all fall, so here I am, starting 2017, out of shape with a body and hormones that seem to just hate me and an empty uterus.. So I've signed up for 3 races for 2017 so far (5K in May, 10K in June, and 21K in August). Here's to hoping that I'll either get pregnant just because I'm making so many plans for summer, or kick some butt in my races! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, same. I'm on CD 34 (after a "definitely probably" anovulatory 106-day cycle) with no glimmer of ovulation at all so far, temping, peeing on OPKs (got a few squinters but no real line). When DH asked last night if I wanted to have sex, I was like, "Sure, but you do know I'm definitely probably not ovulating right?" It's hard to toe the line between being realistic, being pessimistic, and being just plain angry at the unfairness of it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, this is crap. Been there as well. Started TTC 2 weeks after my best friend... She got pregnant on her first cycle and is now 21 weeks pregnant, and I am 21 weeks' worth of stress, anger, despair as I haven't even ovulated once and didn't even get a real chance yet at conceiving... So any pregnancy announcements right now are like a kick in the face. At this point, I'm not even asking for a BFP  right now, I'd just like to see a positive OPK and I'd be relieved, ya know? At least I've got you guys :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh that sucks.. I don't have useful advice, except for checking into more bloodwork... I just wanted to send positive vibes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope that all will be fine and that it'll happen soon for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww, love it! Looks like something my guy would do were he to get me a card for an "occasion" like this. Some humor is certainly needed to get through this with a parcel of sanity left, and it feels good when our SO does little things that make us feel like we're on the same page. Mine seemed to think I was being a bit overly dramatic, but after 5 months and not one ovulation, he's starting to get that this is not gonna be easy. Hey, at least we're in the same boat!! Wishing you cycle 10'll be THE one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks for all that info, I will definitely look into this more closely!! Looks like my 2nd cycle is also on the slow side, CD 27 and no ovulation yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 23:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miroet, can you tell me where you got the info on TSH levels and trying to conceive? Is this scientific known fact? My TsH was 3.89 on my blood tests a month ago, and my doctor did not mention anything about it being too high. i'm aware of the "normal" upper limit of 5 for anyone not taking synthroid, but I've been hearing different values for TTC and it's got me a bit worried as I don't think I'm ovulating at all (no positive OPKs and no temp rise ever). Thanks in advance if you have an answer for me! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had anything remotely resembling EWCM, both in quality and quantity, so yep... Just gonna go back to my baking haha, then I can eat away my disappointment! :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, doctors prescribe that like it's a vitamin or something. I actually started taking it because of acne, and never ever thought that its effects would be that long-lasting... Honestly, had I known I would have stopped it much earlier, but all you hear is, "You can get pregnant like, the second you stop birth control", it's been drilled into our heads for so long that I just took it at face value. Now, when actually trying to get pregnant, I marvel at how some people can accidentally get pregnant whilst some that try for years (without any major infertility problems) just can't... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaaaat? 2 cycles in 8 months? Man oh man that sucks.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Impatient Woman's Guide is a gem! It reads like a friend is talking to you, and she really makes all the science understandable!

As for me, I started temping right away just to get into the habit and to see how my body would act after 11 years on the pill. I don't regret starting that right away, as my cycles are proving to be reallly messed up (cycle 1: 106 days, currently on CD22 of cycle 2 and have not ovulated yet). I took a few OPKs last cycle when I thought I might be ovulating, and am doing so right now as well, but that's juste me, I'm impatient and I hate not knowing what's going on in my body, and I want to be pregnant like, last August, so.... There you have it! Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I know (bachelor's degree in nutrition) it's fine if you don't have any other medical conditions that could affect how your body absorbs nutrients. That is what I'm doing: regular multivitamin + folic acid + omega-3 (I don't eat enough fish and the mutlivitamin does not have omega-3 in it). I've never had a problem with iron and eat quite well so do not feel the need for iron supplement for now. I think you're fine if you keep doing what you're doing right now :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I got my period on December 1st (cycle day 106), pretty sure I didn't ovulate, and it was pretty light as well, and now that you mention it, it wasn't as red as usual. I counted Dec. 1st as CD1 and am currently at 5 months post HBC and cycle 2. I hate the pill man, screwed me up more than I thought it would! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, like I try to explain to people telling me to just relax, I'd just like to know that it will work at one point, and I'd just like my stupid body to function somewhat normally.... My first cycle coming off BC was 106 days during which I'm pretty sure I didn't even ovulate, so it was like 4 months without one single chance at really trying, and that pissed me off... Currently CD22, still no sign of ovulation yet. I'mma lose my shit pretty soon if nothing happens again... 
And your dog is so cute!! My Great Dane barely puts up with the hats and stuff I adorn her with hahaha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
