<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 23:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because this problem never happened in history until the government got involved....

[Read this book](http://www.amazon.com/Merchants-Grain-Profits-Companies-Center/dp/0595142109) if you actually believe this.  Not saying governments haven't fucked things up in the past, but the grain industry has seen periods of near complete free market which were absolutely devastating to people around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 18:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never put it past WSJ to incorrectly use most in the sense of the the single largest source rather than correctly using most as more than half of total electricity.

In today's edition, "Study blames Humans for Most Glacier Melting" was tiny blurb hidden in US News, while a few pages later, in opinion granted, was a half page rant about [A Climate Crusader's Comeuppance](http://online.wsj.com/articles/kim-strassel-a-climate-crusaders-comeuppance-1408057542).

I just used the original title. The maps are pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Electricity in U.S. Still Comes From Coal; Where Does Your State Stand? - The Numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid information.

Also note that local non-profits use data gathered under these administrative costs in their own structure.  For example, a local non-profit foodbank with a Charity Navigator rating of around 96 uses SNAP and free school lunch data to determine need and how much food is provided. Without these administrative costs, the non-profit's rating would have likely decreased significantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 22:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garrett, you are contributing to MarketWatch now?  Grats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 22:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to others in the thread about international prospects, many wells in the US which were previously deemed dead are being re-drilled and yielding more than the original well. There is so much more increase in production to be had in the next years domestically. Technologies are advancing so quickly, and firms are talking about 10%+ recovery rates.

If you look at EIA charts from 2010-2011, the forecasts are a sharp increase for the following year, then flattening out. Every year. So the actuals are a very steep curve.  [This article is a really good read about increased production and demand for technology.](http://fuelfix.com/blog/2014/08/06/pioneer-ceo-us-oil-production-could-hit-14-million-barrelsday/) I'll try to find the chart he made with the prediction.

Whether this is priced in, I can't say.  But there is still a lot of demand for domestic oil field services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 17:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the breakdown of growth for Texas 2013.](https://www.dallasfed.org/assets/documents/research/swe/2014/swe1401b.pdf)

Look at chart 3 - the major gains in jobs was in energy and mining because of the fracking boom, and all the other growths sectors are very correlated to the boom.  All domestic energy trading is headquartered in Houston, which is included in business services. Construction is booming due to new home constructions around the well building.

No doubt that California is losing jobs due to tax implications, but saying Texas is gaining jobs because of lower taxes is misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 20:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's take my previous example and compare it to this one.

The Wapichan, who live in southern Guyana, have just completed a high-resolution map of their traditional lands to justify their claim for legal title. They want 14,000 square kilometres to be protected as a community forest.

My local city government (chosen by locals) a long time ago decided it wanted to make a specific area a community forest-like greenbelt, so they are prohibiting excessive development on specific plots of land. There are certainly people who disagree with this, as I'm sure there are with the tribes in the Wapichan people.

There isn't much more about the group in this article, but I imagine there are so many similarities between the two.  To your point below, I believe it's the exact opposite - these two groups have so many similarities, but the one that's called government is berated in this sub as horrible institutions destroying other people's rights, simply because it's called government. And these "common resource pools" are heralded and champions of non-government, simply because they aren't called government, while in all reality they behave much like what is called a local government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 18:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the thoughtful response, but I think this gets to the basis of my point - so much of the responses in this sub go to theoretical implications based on a tiny subset not representative of any real life situations applicable to *our* society.  There are so many other social and political stigma protecting these indigenous people and lands from the market, which would likely change their behavior.

To be clear, I do believe more decentralized control is better at preserving environment, but I still think that the research in your response simply calls government by a different name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 00:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, my name is government and you can only do this with your land. If you do more, we will extort you. If you don't pay our extortion fee, we will kidnap you and hold you ransom. If you choose to resist, we will kill you.

More dumb ranting and hyperbole when I'm trying to give a real life example of my personal struggles with the ideology vs. what I see day-to-day

You're either consistent with your beliefs of you're not. You don't get to pick and choose exceptions to the rule, otherwise being a libertarian is just basically being extra picky with which rules you do or don't like, which isn't a very defensible position

Which is precisely why I don't consider myself a libertarian - because the *true libertarians* like yourself like to rant about  black and white. I think this goes to the core of why the Libertarian party will always be a marginalized party. And why libertarians get so much shit in the media. It's all theory with little life experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 22:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legitimate question:

What do you think would have happened if the US were an ancap society during WWII?  

Japan's attacks were certainly a response to Western imperialism, but the Nanjing Massacre happened starting in 1937, and similar atrocities happened throughout the Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity Sphere areas that Japan invaded, way before the US imposed any sanctions. Why would they have stopped in Nanjing? You don't think they would have swept across all of China as well as SE Asia, killing, torturing, and enslaving way more than 36 million?  After that, they wouldn't come towards the US?

I guess my question comes down to how does an ancap society deal with a world that is anything but? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 21:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title should be "local *governments* preserve the environment better than *federal* governments." Calling these tribes anything different is silly, and they are certainly not free market.

I think environment is one of those dividing points with libertarians. Where I grew up, there is an amazingly beautiful, huge swath of land up for sale right up against mountains. Without a doubt, if sold on the free market a large developer would come in a develop the shit out of the land, ruining the natural beauty of a large portion of the city (a drunk professor showed us offers). So the local government set permit restrictions to 2 structure developments on the land. Is this wrong? Clearly the locals don't think so, or they would have found a way to restructure the local government and bring in more free market advocates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I highly recommend this Planet Money](http://www.npr.org/blogs/money/2013/06/28/196355493/economists-have-a-one-page-solution-to-climate-change) on how a carbon tax would work, and essentially cost nothing for an average energy user.

This podcast proposes a tax on carbon, returning that money as an offsetting reduction in income tax. The income tax reduction would be set to the average of all carbon use, so highly efficient users would save a little money, and heavy carbon users would lose a little bit of money.

Taxes are disincentives, so putting a tax on carbon would create incentives for individuals to reduce energy use, and would put alternative energies in a price competitive position with fossil fuels.

There are small government libertarians out there who believe that one of the few roles of government is macro-environmental protection, and I think this is a very positive solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 16:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.sciencemag.org/content/296/5573/1694.short

Lower yields but less dependent on external inputs. This is a science paper so they don't say anything controversial, but the dependence becomes extreme because pesticides sterilize the soil which depends upon a diverse ecosystem to naturally rejuvenate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 15:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Chinese_Famine

Drought, poor weather, and the policies of the Communist Party of China contributed to the famine, although the relative weights of the contributions are disputed due to the Great Leap Forward.

Great Leap Forward policies meaning local communist cadres wanted to impress the central government so they over-reported local yields, meaning that they had excess and the excess was shipped away, creating local famines, exacerbated by extreme weather.  You should research the Great Leap Forward.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Category:Famines_in_Africa

The region I'm working with in Africa, the main issues for yields are nonexistence of irrigation and reliance on rainfall, as well as aflatoxin. This is primarily post-harvest issue that can be prevented by proper drying and storage, as well as some fumigation which is much less damaging than spraying fields. 

In the US, advanced irrigation is what prevented famine, and there have certainly been some more localized famine issues, such as the dust bowl.  

I'm saying that the pesticides are doing harm to our natural ecosystem and the effects will be long term, with some effects already showing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 23:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not agreeing with the article by any means, but I personally believe that in long term we will learn that the rampant use of glyphosate and neonicotinoids,  as well as overuse of  chemical fertilizers will not prove a negative contribution, primarily through destruction of biodiversity especially within species necessary for our agricultural production.

There are so many people in the middle of the GMOs are nazis, and the hive mind that is presented within /r/conspiratard of the world would not survive without GMOs, which is bullshit.

I replied this a little bit back when the cracked.com article was posted, a few rational issues I bring up:

[Hypoxic dead zones cause by fertilizer run off](http://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/deadzone.html)

[Destroying biodiversity, the cornerstone of our existence and development](http://www.plosbiology.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pbio.1001456)

The devastating effect of neonicitinoids on bees, worms, butterflies, birds, and other creatures necessary to humans (still definitive causal linkage needed, but before conclusive evidence, the populations will be decimated).

Finally, and the most prevalent: the ideology that the human race cannot survive without GMOs and chemicals. This angers me more than any of the harmful effects listed above. I have done ag work in China, India, and currently doing a project in Africa, which is still on the edge of GMO introduction and artificial fertilizer. One of our partners there is the only official Monsonta dealer at the moment, and I can't really say anything to them.

This ideology is complete bullshit put forth by industry to justify harmful ag techniques.

China had the most advanced organic farming techniques in the world, and all this development was thrown out the window for short term, marginal increases in production. These farms who switched are now addicted to fertilizer, and take 3-4 years to bring soil back to self-sustaining organic levels, which puts any small farmer out of business.

It's a shame because Africa still has these natural techniques, but will soon be switching and likely will never be able to go back.

Edit: To the ideology of the world won't survive using primarily organic:

http://journals.cambridge.org/action/displayAbstract;jsessionid=15B2334DD4B1E78277A019084860ECF2.journals?fromPage=online aid=1091304 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 16:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything, this sub should encourage non-libertarians to come here. Other opinions slow down the "we're so smart" circle jerk and bring some actual substance filled conversations, and I feel like trolls from both sides regularly get shut down.

There's certainly aspects of libertarianism that I don't agree with, and honestly don't ever think would be accepted in the US, but the main ideas implemented into our system could do so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 00:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To put contracts for 126 tonnes of gold into perspective, the Comex is currently reporting that 27 tonnes of actual physical gold are classified as being available for deliver should the buyers of futures contracts want delivery. But the buyers are the banks themselves who wont be taking delivery.

This is how futures markets work... Speculators provide liquidity and will never take delivery. Futures 101. Gold is unique in its role in commodity trading, but volume and open interest in futures contracts always exceeds deliverable amounts.

The big hedge funds primarily trade gold futures using **computers** and algorithm programs.

Computers, yes. Primarily algorithms, no. Algorithms factor into some hedge funds strategies, but saying *primarily* is bullshit.

The banks use the selling from the hedge funds to cover the short positions theyve amassed and book trading profits as they cover their short positions at price levels that are below the prices at which their short positions were established. 

So, the hedge funds take huge potential losses so that the banks can cover their short positions? If their positions are that significant to make a profit, the market moves back the other way.

The thing about futures contracts is there is one pool of liquidity - either CME or ICE. With equities, if you want to get rid of a large position, you spread your trades across venues. You can't do this with futures. If you want to close a position, you can only do that through one single exchange. Maybe a large player was on the fence and wanted to exit their position because the completely unwarranted run on gold filled their coffers, and they believed that *after* Yellen was done speaking, people would make moves and it would be too late.

And, to end it:

The only explanation for this is that the Government is complicit in the price suppression and manipulation of gold and silver and welcomes the insider trading that helps to achieve this result.

Lol.  Another prime example of /r/libertarian 's naivety of finance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 21:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be a long, long time before the dollar is overturned as the world currency reserves, but I'm not sure what you're forever timeline is.

Or commodities like generics like soybeans ... Do they go up or down in dollars?

All the major ag futures contracts are priced in dollars, and global physical trade is generally priced in dollars.

Do south American companies seem more likely to relatively succed if say a BRIC currency emerges as a strong world reserve?

No matter the growth you see in these counties, and your personal negative view of the US, look at the protectionist policies in these countries, the political uncertainty, and the ability to enforce a contract as a foreigner.

As an aside, China is an interesting case with currency manipulation.  On the one hand, the PBOC controls the exchange rate, bringing accusations of undervalued currency, but there are plenty of studies that say if China releases capital controls for RMB leaving the country, there will be huge capital flight and the yuan will tank.  Having lived in China for a long time, there is zero trust in the yuan or government.

The other three countries are laughable as a currency reserve.

Doesurope win or lose overall if the US dollar collapses leaving the USA unable to support or defend Europe if it still does anyway.

The only other real candidate is from Europe. 

If this is from a practical purpose, if you try to time the collapse of the $ as a currency reserve, you will lose. I will guarantee that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 23:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the good old attacking people when you have no more arguments.   I said I have experience in administration, that's not what I do now.

Not sure what kind of university you went to and taught at then, and I am assuming you were getting your masters, which means you were a very low level teacher. The standard for a PhD at a top tier university is 30-50k a year stipend which requires Teaching/TA'ing as well as some research, and starting finance teachers make 215k.

So, I am saying one more time, if you think that you were an amazing teacher and your $3,500 was the only cost to the school, you have zero experience on how universities run, and should really educate yourself before arguments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 23:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly were not a business teacher or have any experience on how a business is run.

Scheduling of the building?! You gotta be kidding me haha. I think a piece of average software would do.

They use software, actually quite expensive licensing costs, but still requires someone to review.

"powered by google" whatever the f that means

Google apps suite is not cheap, especially for a huge enterprise like a university.

10% of the revenue with no additional cost really 

Again, zero experience with any sort of business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 22:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you seriously saying that the school's profit = revenue of students - variable cost of teacher?

Even if you exclude the administrative overhead, necessary or not, there are other huge considerations such as depreciating capital expenditures.  If you think that your $3,500 salary is even a small portion of the total costs of running a class, you are seriously mistaken.

Now adding back in administrative costs, would you as an individual be able to handle scheduling of the building, front to end email contact with students, reporting, and everything else that goes into what you consider unnecessary administrative costs.

As someone who has seen the back end of the processes, I think you are overinflating your individual roll in the university. Are there ways to cut down on that overhead?  Of course, but the efficiencies of running it as a business would simply put more responsibility on you and everyone else in the system without increasing your pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 18:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this you giving this video?

There is no intuition behind contango and backwardation.  Without the intuition of contango and backwardation, this is too advanced for a beginner, but too simple for a commodity professional.

This guy is just reading this straight out of textbook, and I think investopdia does a better job of explaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking futures, physicals, or production and processing companies?  

If futures, Brent or WTI? 

One major driver is the US export restriction of crude, which has recently been tested with the commerce department allowing two companies to export minimally processed ultralight. The government has said there will not be any complete repeal of the ban on crude exports this year, but could be very possible to some extent next year.  When this happens, the Brent-WTI spread will likely narrow, and American refineries' margins will decrease while producers margins will increase.

As for the ME being a mess, Iraq is at record production and projected to increase. Libya is set to pick up production, and Iran's nuclear talks are moving forward. The Israel Palestine at the moment is really more of a sentiment issue than an actual production issue, unless it drags the region into a war, which isn't unlikely.

Depending on what happens with the the downed plane could bring serious energy sanctions to Russia, a major producer of both.

My opinion is that production will continue to increase and NG and CL prices will stay within similar seasonal swings at current levels, refiner margins will decrease, and production companies will have another strong year (don't know where they are priced and if this is priced in).

Edit word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 20:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One main issue I see here is that the consumer is the end user of the product. 

Many of the polluters are at the raw production level, which is so far disconnected from the end user. No end user knows which mining company the metals in your electronics products come from, so how are they supposed to vote with their dollar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 05:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [regulation forcing competition worked in the UK](http://www.engadget.com/2011/06/28/why-is-european-broadband-faster-and-cheaper-blame-the-governme/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 02:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please please please specify which regulations you feel are protectionist and should be repealed. If you think all of them, specify those which qualify as *all of them* and how that would lead to better competition, reducing rates and increasing quality in both the long term and short term.

I know it's a complex market, but the whole repealing all government regulations goes against empirical evidence in this case, and the ignorant rhetoric regurgitated within this board shows that libertarians have no better answers than "statists"

From my empirical evidence regarding the current situation, more government regulation solves my problem. Please prove me wrong and not in a theoretical and philosophical sense, because I would love to move to the other side.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we are getting a little closer here.

We have eminent domain and "massive amounts of federal funds."

But give me a specific game plan.  Just immediately repeal all laws pertaining to ISPs? Any other specific ones? It's nice to say *government get the fuck out*, but we live in a real world and this is just talk, not an actual game plan.

On the contrary, forcing monopoly ISPs to lease lines to other ISPs has empirical evidence of actually producing the wanted results, and a strategy we can follow. I'm not saying this is the way to go, but so often I see the attitude of *get the government out of X* without having any sort of A to B strategy, or any contingency plans. It's cute talking about philosophy and all, but if you really want to get anything done you have to provide more than that attitude. 

Government caused this problem, so it can only fix it by getting the fuck out.
 
Empirical evidence proves this statement patently false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 23:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is that [regulation forcing competition worked in the UK](http://www.engadget.com/2011/06/28/why-is-european-broadband-faster-and-cheaper-blame-the-governme/), and most European nations which have stronger regulations have much faster, cheaper internet.

I agree that more competition through less regulation would be better, but I haven't seen a good game plan on how to roll it out, it's all just "let them duke it out in the free market" talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is defense of Rick?  He's just rambling again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gave a "speech" when I was at the CME, and he just shouted about monetary policy and the fed destroying the free market, all while sidestepping relatively easy questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I got a subscription, I looked at more articles a month than any site would allow, so I don't believe that's true. In addition, it wouldn't be the IP address, so if you open a new private window, it should work again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they print out this picture of a lady holding the printout of the chart to disperse to clients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 20:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when the market is dead quiet, you can't get matched up to orders sitting on the market because someone does some trickery with them. Ok?

The legal issue that the class action lawsuit alleges is that the exchanges breached contracts to provide legitimate market information.

How is this any worse than bid-ask spreads, commissions, and other stupid shit we already deal with in the market? 

These are explicitly stated and agreed upon.

Moreover, in every single discussion I've had, no one can definitively prove that the HFT dudes can actually consistently 'steal' from you using these methods.

That's what they are trying to bring to light with the lawsuit.  I would really like to see this exact experiment done with a market order.  My guess of what you would see is the HFT trade would be filled first, the book would walk, and the same HFT trade would then fill your order as the price moved up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 03:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment will probably be buried, but I think it's very interesting that the GMO debate is thrown into the whole conspiracy debate.  I think there is just as much hive mind behind the "conspiratard" aspect of the GMO debate as to anti-GMO

I know some people take the GMO to the level of giving kids autism, diseases, whatever, but I believe there is legitimate argument to the anti-GMO movement, just not those who get the stage.  Full disclosure: my family owns a small to medium sized farm and we do organic agronomy education in our region.

The main, *real* arguments against GMO products is that they promote an unstudied, harmful manner of harvesting crops. Because GMOs promote the use and overuse of fertilizer and pesticide, they give short term benefits for unknown medium and long term harms.

Some major issues for me:

[Hypoxic dead zones cause by fertilizer run off](http://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/deadzone.html)

[Destroying biodiversity, the cornerstone of our existence](http://www.plosbiology.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pbio.1001456)

The devastating effect of neonicitinoids on bees, worms, butterflies, birds, and other creatures necessary to humans (still definitive causal linkage needed, but before conclusive evidence, the populations will be decimated).

Finally, and the most prevalent: the ideology that the human race cannot survive without GMOs and chemicals. This angers me more than any of the harmful effects listed above. I have done ag work in China, India, and currently doing a project in Africa, which is still on the edge of GMO introduction and artificial fertilizer. This ideology is complete bullshit put forth by industry to justify harmful ag techniques.

China had the most advanced organic farming techniques in the world, and all this development was thrown out the window for short term, marginal increases in production. These farms who switched are now addicted to fertilizer, and take 3-4 years to bring soil back to self-sustaining organic levels, which puts any small farmer out of business. 

It's a shame because Africa still has these natural techniques, but will soon be switching and likely will never be able to go back.

So while Sandy Hook "deniers" should be ashamed of their ignorance, other sides should do research as well before jumping to conclusions.

Edit: A couple words, kinda drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans are vehemently pushing for more government as well, and in places which I more strongly oppose. What gets me the most is that the whole premise of the Republican party is a lie.  Democrats certainly have the same issue, but not to the same extent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 20:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to angrily comment about how you would rather side with Republicans who can't even understand evolution. Then I looked at [Pew Research study on views of evolution](http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2014/01/03/republican-views-on-evolution-tracking-how-its-changed/) and realized that while there is about a 20 point difference, it isn't that big of a difference.  Then I got sad.

That being said, democrats are the only ones moving in the right direction.  And if you can't understand basic science, your overall competence in public service is seriously deteriorated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 22:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just joking, I could care less about karma. At least the article got some attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 21:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One step further, it better visually represents percentage changes.  

A 10% increase at a nominal index value of 100 is 10. 

A 10% increase at a nominal index value of 10,000 is 1,000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 04:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which then makes the produced goods cheaper thus increasing others' relative incomes.

Are you suggesting deflation would be healthy for our economy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 03:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like an archive of the new world order, illuminati and chemtrails to give some credibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I have to post the mobile version, 2 weeks after it comes out to make /r/Libertarian front page.  ;)


http://www.reddit.com/r/Libertarian/comments/28zt1n/taxi_medallions_have_been_the_best_investment_in/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except many believe the climate is not continuing to warm (see above) and that there has been no significant warming for 17 years (see more at climatedepot.com).

Debunked.

The global warmers are the ones refusing to discuss, debate or even mention the growing body of science questioning and in increasing instances disproving their theories

This is just silly.

 They also mostly ignore news of manipulated climate models and the serious concerns of scientists who no longer believe the climate is changing significantly.

There are no manipulated models. Again, debunked.

Denying anthropomorphic climate change makes you look incredibly foolish and anti-science. Please take this bullshit to climate skeptic and conservative subs.  If you present a well respected scientific article saying that increasing energy costs now will stifle future technologies to deal with carbon in the future, well that's something that we could talk about. Posting this spam makes you look dumb.

 /u/countfizix has been posting [this series](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52KLGqDSAjo list=PL82yk73N8eoX-Xobr_TfHsWPfAIyI7VAP) which explains the actual science and the myths on both sides. I suggest you read it before you regurgitate the same garbage these blogs make up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 20:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The local climate changed through natural cycles vs. Anthropomorphic Climate Change. If you can't read the article and figure out the difference between the two, you should not be involved in the greater debate.

Please take your bullshit conservative views discrediting libertarians away from this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 18:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this serious? It seems like a parody...

Far from running out of space, as the Commission constantly asserts, the UK is producing approximately 70 million cubic metres of municipal waste each year, while it has over 819 million cubic metres available for landfill and is creating about 114 million cubic metres of new space each year, mainly from quarrying and gravel extraction.

God, these slave driving eco-terrorists stealing from our landfills!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Institute for Energy Research*  What an unbiased source.

IPCCs best guess of the cost of achieving the aggressive outcome rises by 44% in the years 2030-2050 and 37% in the years 2050-2100.

I guess what this guy is arguing is the rhetoric of catastrophic - that 40% increase isn't catastrophic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please take this spam elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 19:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they not set up a call for you when you first signed up? My rep was local very helpful, and I can call at any time.

Swim lessons are also pretty solid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 17:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mamie is a known troll on WSJ, and perfectly demonstrates conservatives hiding behind the libertarian label.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 23:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As well as IUDs, which have similar hormonal effects for women who have adverse effects to pill or patch treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 20:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that a lot of women use birth control as a medicine... Women I know, if they aren't on a birth control of some sort, they have horribly painful, irregular periods. 

Calling access to birth control killing an unborn child is incredibly ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taxi medallions have been the best investment in America for years. Now Uber may be changing that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 21:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 00:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever had feral hog meat?  If so, how does it compare to farm raised hog?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 20:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you meaning that they hired the foreign scientists instead of low wage/skill employees?  

I would think that the STEM positions they are talking about wouldn't be able to be filled by low skilled employees. The current visa process is very costly, I'd have to imagine that companies would love to hire lower wage, local workers if they were available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 16:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife's company has an office in Thailand. She called them making sure everything was alright.  They said they were used to it because it is a common occurrence.  Aside from curfews and military presence, which many Thais don't see as intimidating, there wasn't much change to daily lives.

There have been major struggles recently with which way the parties have been pulling. The ruling party has made incredibly harmful economic decisions to "support" the populist, rural, poor vote. [They were guaranteeing prices on rice and buying directly from farmers at above market rates and stockpiling excess](http://www.eastasiaforum.org/2014/03/17/thailands-rice-subsidy-scheme-rotting-away/). But when they want to decrease stockpiles, the market tanks and they will lose billions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want an 8% Raise? Let Foreign Scientists Immigrate to Your City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 16:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 20:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police officer clearly believes that drunk driving is an issue and that drunk drivers infringe on him and his family's right to safety, life, whatever.  He appears to agree with the overall strategy, but disagrees with a few minor aspects of the implementation process.  In public, he conforms to the decided upon line in order to keep face within the institution. I don't think that what the documentary maker said was comparable, and overall weakened his argument.

I do agree with the whole argument against ticketing people for other issues such as expired tags, I think many of the arguments are a stretch, and overall the officer who did respond did so in a very respectable manner, as honestly as he could while on duty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adults are trying to have a conversation here, please take your trolling back to /r/libertarianmeme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comparing ~~Officers~~ this officer accepting ~~their~~ his duty, squelching personal opinions about DUI Checkpoints to the Nuremberg trials... 

Edit: see comment below. Sure some cops can be dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 21:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, looks terrible.  All that pristine blue water, amazing looking bays and natural beaches.  You must be miserable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 14:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A private company is asking you not to bring firearms onto their private property. Don't support them if you don't want, which I am hoping why you put this up. I, for one, support their decision and will continue to give them business.

I was bartender at a bar that got pretty rowdy at night. Fights every night. Someone was stabbed with a broken bottle and spent some time in the ICU. Nasty shit. There was a libertarian group that came in once a month or so. One of the guys would bring a handgun in. My manager told me it was against our policy to have firearms in the bar for safety reasons. What if some drunk asshole grabbed his gun.

I told him our policy and asked him to leave his gun outside of the bar. He was a complete dick about it, ranting about the second amendment.  My first introduction to libertarians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 18:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fracking industry is an interesting study into environmental concerns and regulation. There was an article in the [WSJ energy report](http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304831304579544092287190238?mg=reno64-wsj) from this morning (if you get the paywall, copy the title, open a new tab google the title).  

Regulations are lagging way behind fracking development, but firms are cutting emissions and reducing environmental damage by developing new technologies. Companies are also setting up websites to get information about fracking and attempting to set up industry safety standards before government can come in a regulate the hell out of production. But my question is: are these initiatives at least in part response to the threat of regulation? Would the rush to reduce emissions and set standards be there without that threat?

I also think it's a stretch with the correlation between regulations and start-ups going out of business. The four industries she mentioned are hugely capital intensive and firms in those industries are much more likely to run into cash flow issues than say a software firm (which also have high failure rates). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 19:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dude's trolling has reached the point where I really think he is a government agent planted by the left to discredit libertarian thought and make outsiders believe they are a bunch of ignorant republicans who regurgitate fox news words and phrases like "regime," "your boy Barry," "Obummer," etc.

I am on to you, liberal troll. Take your spamming elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 23:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be criminal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry man, Coloradan born and raised. You clearly have zero serious camping or backpacking experience if you think that:

1) Carrying a rifle or shotgun is a valuable weight and space. Even a two night in backpack trip and that extra weight is silly.

2) Bears and mountain lions are a statistically significant threat that can't be prevented by smart behavior, a bear bell and possibly mace if you are in high bear activity mountainous area (which there are essentially zero in CO). I've backpacked all over Yosemite and Glacier, high bear activity areas, with nothing more than a bear bell with no problems. In addition, bears and mountain lions are valuable to the ecosystem and not there to hurt you...

And to your point about the moose. She fired the pistol (3 times?) and the moose didn't flinch...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 20:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love (in a very sad way) [this interview of David Kelly](http://youtu.be/_9TIspgTbLM?t=8m7s) about the advice Steve Jobs gave him after Kelly was diagnosed with cancer. If you aren't familiar with IDEO and David Kelly, highly suggest this video. Kind of an aside from the cancer topic besides the quick quote, but great nonetheless.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 14:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife ate around this amount, maybe 1 more taco. We have been bad with exercise lately - busy with work and travel, but I think even double this with 20-30 minutes of exercise a day and she would be in a very healthy state.

On a side note, my father-in-law lost 60 pounds cutting the salt and not taking seconds, so best of luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say they are more sweet than tangy. If you want more tang, up the vinegars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 14:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black vinegar is rice wine vinegar made with black glutinous rice. Rice wine vinegar, wine vinegar, or even white vinegar would work in place of the black stuff. 

My mother in law made the sauce last night without the black vinegar and it turned out great. She didn't slow cook it with pork, just cooked it on the stove for about an hour and we put it over pork chops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 13:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got it. Now Sir Wookington knows where I live.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 00:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got back from Goa, I had something like this a few times.  I'll definitely have to try this recipe out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 22:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to make  (ganbian sijidou - fried green beans with minced pork), one of my favorite dishes in China.  It didn't turn out well. They use a different kind of green bean, thinner and more tender than the ones I was using. I think mine was also missing the  (MSG).  

I'm definitely going to try it again. I'll do it in the summer when I have green beans from my garden, the store bought ones are no comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 19:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. You might want to add the sauce back to the chicken after you shred it. I feel chicken gets a little bit drier than pork in the slow cooker. I tend to not trim the fat too much on pork shoulders, which usually cooks into the meat and sauce, giving a little extra moisture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 14:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just put up a recipe for [asian style pork tacos](http://www.reddit.com/r/slowcooking/comments/1xfkmx/sweet_and_tangy_asian_style_tacos/) with cliantro, lime, and crunchy chow mein. They were delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 14:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to [u/writergeek](http://www.reddit.com/user/writergeek) for the inspiration in [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/slowcooking/comments/1wxf0g/sticky_spicy_sweet_asian_bbq_ribs/). I saw this in the morning and my mouth started watering, so I started what I had in the fridge and pantry.

**Pork and Sauce:**

2.5 lbs. pork shoulder

 yellow onion, chopped

4 garlic cloves, minced

1-inch fresh ginger 

 cup brown sugar

 cup honey or agave nectar

 cup soy sauce

 sriracha

3 tablespoons white vinegar

3 tablespoons black Chinese vinegar

3 tablespoons sweet chili sauce

1 teaspoon salt

Freshly ground black pepper, to taste



Add all sauce ingredients in slow cooker and set to low. Let onions, garlic, and ginger release a little flavor. Add meat and cook on low 6-8 hours. Remove meat and shred. Mix 2 tablespoons water with 1 tablespoon corn starch. Pour into the sauce and stir until it thickens. I poured the sauce over each taco, but you can add back to the pork once you pull it. With 2.5 lbs. pork, this recipe will make it very saucy.

I added 3 finely ground Sichuan peppers kernels as well. They give a nice mild numbing flavor that goes really well with the sweet and spicy. You can probably find these in an Asian market. 



**Slaw:**
I used Alton Browns [Recipe](http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/alton-brown/asian-slaw-recipe.html) as a guide, then added and removed a few items.

1 (3-inch) piece ginger, grated fine 

 cup rice wine vinegar

1 tablespoon soy sauce 

1 lime, juiced 

2 tablespoons sesame oil 

2 tablespoons sesame seeds

 head Napa cabbage, sliced thin 

 red bell pepper, julienne fine 

 yellow bell pepper, julienne fine 

1 Serrano chile, minced fine

1 large carrot, grated fine with a peeler 

3 green onions, cut on the bias, all of white part and half of the green 

2 tablespoons cilantro 

 teaspoon ground black pepper



Chop all veggies in large bowl. Mix sauce ingredients in small bowl. Add to desired sauciness.

**Finishing**
Heat mini corn tacos in oven until warm. Garnish with lime, cilantro and crispy chow mein.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweet and Tangy Asian Style Tacos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 14:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 15:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's these new things called banks, you should really try them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 15:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Favorite: [Karl Denson - Because of Her Beauty](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MG0wZEb02XU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 22:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you renting your modem? Go buy one. You can get it on Newegg for around 55 with a deal, it pays for itself in under 6 months. 

I waited way too long to do this. At the same time, I flashed my router to dd-wrt firmware. It's seriously a whole different internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Off Limits, but Blessed by the Fed" - Shady Cronyism Promoting Illegal Activity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 21:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 22:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is that selling a security for a loss, then buying back the same security doesn't count as a loss. You can sell a security and buy back a very similar one to get the tax benefit.

Is that wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reality commenters

I laughed at that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 17:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hilarious:

http://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/1t5ofu/please_sticky_usa_suicide_hotline_1800273talk/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 20:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/libertarian  - PLEASE stop upvoting this spammer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if investors don't feel that the bonuses or raises are warranted, they will take their capital elsewhere, and the stock price will decrease, decreasing management payout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a question/clarification with an ADR, specifically AAUKY.

An ADR is issued by a bank that holds the underlying security, in this case AAL.L, then passes through dividends, withholding a small fee, is this correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 17:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a troubled kid who read some things he truly didn't understand. Then he rambled about things that he had little understanding of to other students who had even less understanding. Then the media interviewed those students who had even less understanding of the issues he rambled about or any insight to his actual beliefs, which were likely the thoughts of a troubled, confused teenager. And now people are trying to say that these "beliefs" are the reason that he committed this horrible act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnell Asks Defense Industry to Back Republicans Who Will Protect Military Spending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 17:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [GOP Incumbents Lean on Donors to Beat Back Primary Foes](http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304173704579260133964574284)

Text from article:

Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell recently delivered a direct pitch to one of America's top defense contractors: Get off the sidelines and start backing Republicans who will protect military spending.

Mr. McConnell's message, according to people who attended a Nov. 6 fundraiser with officials from BAE Systems Inc., was that if Republican lawmakers lose primary elections from challengers further to their right who have few qualms about trimming military budgets, the defense industry could expect dwindling support in Washington.

"In the current debate, spending cuts have trumped robust national-security spending," said one person at the McConnell fundraiser, held at a Capitol Hill townhouse. "The main message he was pushing was: Get involved, mainly to teach those who are primarying incumbents that it is not helpful to run against incumbents who are champions for the industry."
The Kentucky Republican's outreach to the defense community is part of an effort by party leaders to blunt the effects of conservatives who are stepping up in increasing numbers to challenge GOP incumbents. Many of the 12 Senate Republicans up for re-election next year are facing primary challengers aligned with the tea party, including Mr. McConnell.

In the House, Speaker John Boehner (R., Ohio) also has moved to undermine the power of the tea party, saying that groups supporting the movement had lost credibility in policy debates and accusing them of forcing GOP lawmakers to take ill-advised policy positions. That was a reference to the federal-government shutdown of October, which the public blamed largely on the Republican Party.

On Sunday, House Budget Committee Chairman Paul Ryan (R., Wis.) noted Mr. Boehner's frustration and said, "I was frustrated, too." But he also said on NBC that the tea party represents "very important elements of our conservative family, and I would prefer to keep those conversations within the family."

The effort to beat back challenges from the right goes beyond the defense industry. The U.S. Chamber of Commerce and other business groups have been stepping in to help business-friendly Republicans aligned with the GOP leadership, a reaction to the government shutdown in October, which the business groups opposed, and a sign of worries that tea party-aligned candidates might try to eliminate tax breaks and spending favored by businesses.

Mr. McConnell delivered his message at the fundraiser hours after a candidate backed by a number of GOP leaders in Washington, and the Chamber of Commerce, beat a more conservative challenger in a special congressional election in Alabama.

According to campaign-finance records, BAE Systems, a U.S. unit of U.K.-based BAE Systems PLC that works on such items as the F-35 jet fighter and the Bradley fighting vehicle, has given Mr. McConnell $5,000 so far this year, the maximum allowed, to help him beat back a 2014 challenge from tea-party ally Matt Bevin.
BAE, which has a large presence in Kentucky, declined to comment on the fundraiser or its discussions with Mr. McConnell.
"Our political action committee's contributions reflect our support for candidates who believe in strong national security and defense and represent districts where BAE Systems is a part of the local community," said spokesman Brian Roehrkasse.
Mr. McConnell's Senate office referred questions to his 2014 re-election campaign. Josh Holmes, a senior adviser to the McConnell campaign, defended the senator's appeal. "Sen. McConnell is a conservative who believes in a strong national defense and wants to ensure that those who share his opinion aren't silenced by a reluctance to voice their opinion in elections," he said.

The message appears to be rippling through the defense industry, where officials are voicing increasing resentment with tea party-aligned Republicans.

"There's definitely frustration within the defense community, and the frustration goes to tea partiers who are emphasizing cuts without internalizing the harm," said Roger Zakheim, an attorney at Covington   Burling LLP who served until October as general counsel for the House Armed Services Committee. "At times, our respective leaders in both branches have essentially allowed, and continue to allow, the military to be a pawn in the greater debate."

Mr. McConnell's pitch to the defense industry is a delicate one. As Senate Republican leader, he has supported sequestration, the across-the-board spending cuts that have hit domestic programs and the Defense Department.

Matt Hoskins, executive director of the Senate Conservatives Fund, a political-action committee backing Mr. McConnell's GOP challenger, called Mr. McConnell a hypocrite for casting himself as a defender of military spending while supporting the spending cuts. "All he's really doing is saying 'nudge-nudge, wink-wink, you know I'm a big spender, you know I'll take care of you,' " he said.

"What he's really saying is that he's a big spending Republican who will take care of these special interests if they help him in the primary," Mr. Hoskins said. "It's, you scratch my back, I will scratch your back."

In Georgia, Lockheed Martin Corp., General Dynamics Corp. and Boeing Co. have already stepped in to support Rep. Jack Kingston, who is battling Rep. Paul Broun and others in the GOP primary for retiring Sen. Saxby Chambliss's Senate seat. Mr. Kingston, who has faced accusations from the right that he is insufficiently committed to eliminating the president's health-care law, has collected at least $60,000 from defense firms for his campaign, according to finance records, making him a top recipient of defense industry dollars in the current campaign cycle.

In addition to BAE's contribution, Mr. McConnell has drawn donations from Lockheed Martin and Huntington Ingalls Industries Inc., which have each donated $2,500 to his campaign, records show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 23:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, got it. He definitely bought SCTY at the wrong time.

Thanks for the update! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 23:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 5 in the worst performing has buy date of 11-5-13.

That solar city 3 month vs. 1 month return. Woah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 22:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ever reputable PolitifactBias.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good ol' libertarian fuck em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 01:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is hilarious.

OP: Our theory says that the private market can take care of the poorer citizens. Let's brainstorm some ideas of how to help homelessness in NYC!

Responses: 
1) These kids don't even know who their dad is.
2) I'm looking out for my kids, the parent should put their kids up for adoption.
3) Stupid statists would never help their own people.
4) It's government policy through local zoning barriers that's really keeping them homeless.

I'm all for libertarian ideas to help our society, but I have to say that many self-proclaiming libertarians out there are just as big of liars as the current politicians and have no idea how the real world works.

Edit: And now to add to number 2: Or let them starve. Just don't make them my responsibility.

OP - it's naively cute of you to think that many libertarians hold this dear to them, I'm afraid you are likely in the minority, although there are others out there like you. 

I have one suggestion. Check out one of these foodbanks: [Feeding America Network](http://feedingamerica.org/foodbank-results.aspx?state=NY#)

I work with one of the local food banks, we give out over 12 million meals a year. Feeding America is an amazing organization that has deals with major grocery and distribution chains and does great work. They certainly have programs helping the homeless in NYC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 01:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   If the parents cant take care of them they should be put up for adoption.

You are joking, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 01:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitcoin when it hits $1100. It's only going up from there. 

Also, penny stocks. But when you are trading penny stocks, you have to trade as often as possible. The more trades, the more money you make.

When you make your few thousand within the year, invest all that in TSLA. Investing is easy as pie, and everyone makes money, so can you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 04:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But but but, it's *really* hard getting to the seventh word of an article. It's a good thing it's still the first line, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the market of crooks would never allow it.

Along with *the vast majority of the populous.* The AnCap type are under the impression that if people just read the theory, they would totally believe it would work and support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather this sub turn into a complete circle jerk? The way a theory becomes stronger is others trying to poke holes in it while followers explain the solution. If you want everyone who doesn't think like an idealistic libertarian to leave, you further marginalize the movement. 

IMO anyone who actually believes pure and idealistic libertarianism could be achieved in our society is just as foolish as those young, dumb, happily uninformed liberals. 

I come here because it gives me new ideas. Applying libertarian thought to our out of control system could add some amazing benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 21:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You would probably find that an even larger majority--probably over 90%-- could not give an accurate description of what GMOs actually are.

Wow, excellent assumption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 19:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't feed the trolls. Obama hating Neo-Cons pretending to be libertarians like OP are the reason why the this sub is such fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 13:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not disagreeing with your assessment of the effective vs. tax level.

But your idea that that all companies manufacture abroad for tax purposes in itself contradicts your earlier statements. A huge amount of small businesses manufacture in China for one reason: price. The price is so cheap because of labor prices, Chinese government investments and incentives, and the manufacturing and transportation infrastructure. 

As you said above, none of the SME receive any of the tax benefits of hiding profits abroad, so why are they manufacturing in China? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
