<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1779</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, what happened to Kate's job? The one where she worked for that lady, with the surly teenager? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I DID NOT see Randall adopting coming. But then, what are they going to do? What's Beth's job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the kids even know where Jack is going?! Good luck with that conversation Rebecca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy who broke her heart before Jack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very bad things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO! BAD JACK! BAD JACK! BAD DARRELL! BAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get counseling. Please. Pretty please. I am on my hands and knees. I beg of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They held off "Trial and Error" to premiere for this week special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing goes for Jack, of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, I didn't mean it when I suggested Jack and Rebecca separate! 

I DIDN'T MEAN IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, Mandy Moore can act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Something for yourself?" 

Rebecca. You are a wife. You are a mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But u/SusanBManthony still may be right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *lip trembles...*

waaaaaaaaa..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cease verbal communication and seize for thy own possession paper notes of monetary value that I currently hold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I just close my eyes and hope for the best in that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scary, but I doubt it.

If that thug isn't already in jail or six feet under in the Jack-Rebecca timeline, I'd be astonished.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Covers eyes* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a little story that will cheer us all up.

Once upon a time, each of those no-good gambling thugs had to pay in cash for everything for the rest of forever. And they had to pay in pennies.

Edit: Also, when one of the thugs tried to buy a house, he tripped over his shoelace, and his bag of pennies, which weighed well over a ton, squished him flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're in good company. The only poker I know is Red Dead Redemption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, who are you going to lose against? The coffee table? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh God Oh God Oh God Oh God....don't do it Jack. No, no... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Bites fingernails* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, Darrel. Not Miguel. Who's Darrel? Why haven't we seen him yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh...guys...a terrible thought just crossed my mind. What if the events tonight lead to Jack and Rebecca separating?

Edit: Fuck, this isn't what I wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm pretty sure Milo said we'd have to wait until next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough noodles, Ben. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it wasn't billed as a total flashback episode like that one Big Day when the babies were born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, then. Jack was born in 1944.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither are Rebecca's parents. It could just be simple passing on to old age...though I don't recall hearing about Jack's mom in 1990, when the Big Three were ten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punching in the face in three, two, one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Jack. Gambling bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Young Miguel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do have one question--why is Jack working odd jobs when he could get a job as a handyman with, well with his skills, any shop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seven minutes in and we're at the commercial again. Dammit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, but I guess, objectively speaking, it should have been a given. Jack was how old exactly when the Big Three were born? 32? That puts him being born in 1948? That's old enough for serving in Vietnam, and given his earlier occupations, it's apparent he didn't go to college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't a career Rebecca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot that Jack was in Vietnam... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOUNG JACK?! THAT WASN'T IN THE PREVIEW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it starts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Nods in agreement*

BIG THREE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin. Or jumper cables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great. I need to get myself a friend with supervillainous parents.

I'm glad you enjoyed it. I decided to go with the supers' children wanting to be mostly normal.

I had a lot of fun with this prompt. I hope we can get some more responses.

Bless her.

Ah, the best of all compliments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I still remember when I saw Sesame Street ABC for the first time.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LeYvZs4gHZ4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, why would you squint, if I'm the one who needs glasses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes, they kill more humans a year than any other animal (other than mosquitos and malaria) in Africa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The evil villain's secret lair was at the top of the very tall mountain. Of course, it wasn't exactly secret--the lair doubled as the house the villain, Evileenee von Villaineay, lived in with her daughter. (The real estate agent said it was a great deal, prime real estate. In reality, the Evileenee, whose real name is Rose Friar, didn't want to pay taxes on two dwellings)

There were advantages to having the evil lair in your home. It was much easier to transport all the devices, for one thing. And you could fire the ice ray at pedestrians and prepare your freezer for winter at the same time. But it did have the distinct disadvantage of the good guys being able to look you up in the phone book...

*****

"Freeze evil-doers! I, Hero McHeroMan, will stop you! And I--Hannah, honey, can you keep up? The bad guys will get away if you don't hurry."

"Ah haa, huuu haaaa...sorry....huhhh....Daddy."

Two masked figures glared at each other; one dressed in reds and golds, the other dressed entirely in black. Behind the red-and-gold champion, a small, thirteen-year-old girl, wearing jeans and hiking boots, was doubled over, panting.

"Freeze?! *Freeze?!* Good grief, Hero McHeroMan, you are losing your touch. That lame pun is the best you can do?!"

"Daddy...huff hufff...can't help it if he's...running out of ideas. There hasn't...been a new Dresden book in two years."

"Is this your new sidekick, McHeroMan? You should return it to the academy, it's defective."

"You fiend! All life is sacred! And there exists no human being is defective! Hannah, my Staff of Superness!"

"Uh...that's the one with the white spiral right?"

"What? No, that's the Righteousness Rod. The Staff has the yellow ball at the end, there's a good girl."

"You are too late, Hero McHeroMan! Nothing can stop me now!" She pointed towards a very large and shiny machine. "My new Robot--inator is creating me an army of powerful, cyborg-otic servants. They bend completely to my will. Maahaa-haa!"

"No! It is never too late for justice to stop the forces of evil!"

Hero McHeroMan waved his Righteousness Rod and smashed it against the Robot--inator. Despite the Righteous Rod being made of wood, and the Robot--inator being made of metal, the giant machine smashed into pieces.

"Aaaahh...that was expensive!"

"Surrender, evil-doer!"

"Daddy, can you slow down so that I can take notes?" Hannah smiled at her father. "Please? It's for school."

"Robots! Seize Hero McHeroMan and his brat!"

Six dozen robot drones of various sizes and abilities charged towards Hero McHeroMan and Hannah. Because Hero McHeroMan is a hero, he was able to smash many robots to pieces. However, he did not smash them all and several were able to catch Hannah, who had no fighting abilities whatsoever.

"Hannah! What happened to your martial arts training?!" Hero McHeroMan was grappling with a very tall robot with hook arms, as three robots wrapped Hannah from head to foot in ropes, taking her captive.

"I tried! But the walk up here hurt my legs. I probably have blisters the size of--hey!" The robots tied Hannah's ankles to a crane and it hoisted her into the air upside down. "All the blood is rushing to my head!"

"Didn't I tell you not to wear those new boots? You just bought those at that mall last week."

"But Daddddddddyyyyyy. They're so cute and pink and cute."

"Quiet captive! There is no escape! Your mindless shopping has led to your capture and now Hero McHeroMan, surrender or I will destroy your daughter!"

"You cannot win! Your machine is smashed, and most of your robots are destroyed."

"I can so win! I can have my machine repaired! Machinist!" Evileenee snapped her fingers. "Come and repair my machine. And bring in the other Inator! The Ice-inator!"

A short figure wearing a welding mask walked over, "Coming Mom. What hero are you fighting this time? Oh, hi Hero McHeroMan!"

"The Machinist?! What are you doing here?!"

"Fixing machines...and what the? Hannah, what are you doing up there?"

"Hi, Monica."

"You're Hero McHeroMan's daughter?!"

"Yeah."

"Wait, Monica?! You spent the night last Friday!"

"Yes, I had a very nice time, Mr. McHeroMan. Thank you again for having me. You look sick Hannah, let me get you down from there."

"WHAT?! No! Bad Monica, bad! That girl is my prisoner! Do not, do *not* untie her!"

"She's my best friend, Momma. Hannah, you alright?"

"Fine. A little dizzy, but I think I actually got worse during the hike up here."

"What? That's ten miles from your house!"

"I know! But Daddy says long hikes build character!"

"Easy for him to say, he has super speed and is friction proof!"

"I know, and he and your mom are too busy fighting for me to take notes for school!"

"What? You actually bought what Billy said about that? This "Take-Your-Daughter-To-Work-Day is just an excuse for the teachers to get an early start on summer vacation. There's no essay to write."

"What? Really? How do you know?"

"Hannah, summer starts on Monday."

"Oh...oh yeah."

"Never mind that, come on upstairs. The home theater is right above Mom's lair! It makes watching movies great!" Monica pulled up her mask and began pointing at various robots. "You, come with us and make us a pizza. You, set up the vanity and give us both pedicures. You, start the popcorn. You, you, you and you, come on, I'll think of other things to do."

Giggling, Monica and Hannah, and most of the remaining robots left the lair. When they got to the elevator, Hannah turned around and smiled.

"Can I sleep over, Daddy. Pleeeeeaaaaassseee?"

"Well, I...um...I...er...."

"Pretty please?"

"Well...okay."

"Thank you, thank you, thank you!"

Evileenee glared at Hero McHeroMan. "Pushover."

"And yet, evil-doer, all of your evil devices are destroyed. Do you surrender now?"

"Just get out of here, Clarence. This is going to take forever to clean, since you broke my home maintenance robot." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Irwin once said that the time he felt most nervous during a filming of his show is when they were near some hippos. Not the venomous snakes. Not the crocodiles. But the hippos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good grief, that dinner sounds delicious! Who gives up *that* for a Hot Pocket?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a draw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, I guess I need new glasses.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] A superhero fights a super villain, with the added complication that both of them observe Take-Your-Daughter-to-Work-Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Platonic Ginny/Luna request: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite friendships in Harry Potter is between Ginny Weasley and Luna Lovegood, and I'm looking for more stories. I would prefer not to have slash or bashing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Beast of Gvaudan was not a hyena or a wolf, but possibly a sub-mature lion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like to know about your world's werewolves and wolf-men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, it appears that a common rule of thumb for discussion is to comment on two other commenters, in addition to your own comment. That sounds fair, so we'll stick with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] A teenaged superhero is fighting a villain, unaware that he is her older brother. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some species of spiders form social groups and can reach populations up to fifty thousand individuals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] [IP] She stood her ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.deviantart.com/art/Shield-on-405797247 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney Channel's new series "Andi Mack" is centered around the topic of a teenaged pregnancy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] The teenaged daughter of a billionaire is kidnapped for ransom. It does not go quite as the kidnappers plan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] "We'd known each other for years, but I didn't fall in love with her, until the first time I heard her laugh." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The teenaged superhero has been captured by the supervillain and de-masked. One of the villain's henchmen is mortified--the superhero is his kid sister. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can play around with this a bit--could be a younger brother of one of the henchmen, or even the super villain's younger sibling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could you give a description of your favorite created character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty new to these parts. So, I decided to ask the most basic question related to world-building I could think of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, I got a paper cut. Will you kiss my boo-boo to make it better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already asked Carla. She said no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, did you hear about how much money "Logan" is making? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It made $33 MILLION on Friday! Isn't that awesome?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] I Need Your Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RWupOFcjlzE

I know the Theme Thursday encouraged Media that was as original as possible, and that the stills from this video are from the movie, but I thought the music was nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which fictional character would make the best President of the United States? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] Cometh a hero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3UNb52VedX0

I really hope I did this right.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] When Sirius Black fell through the Veil in the Department of Mysteries, he entered the Nevernever of the Dresdenverse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Librarians and bookstore clerks of Reddit, what is your greatest story concerning books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Last Stand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://xanatoast.deviantart.com/art/Duty-Unto-Death-JHKris-Edit-597791598 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] It's a nationwide scholastic tournament, and it's down to the final two teams: Ms. Frizzle's class is competing against Mr. Ratburn's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, it's too quiet in this hospital? Wanna sing a song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A duet! From La La Land!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GTWqwSNQCcg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions of the future. The harder you make her laugh, the longer and clearer the visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, I'm hungry. Will you make me a sandwich? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] If I lie here, if I just lay here, would you just lie with me and just forget the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GemKqzILV4w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, I'm bored. Will you tell me a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Robot Pirate Island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/dnDJVYm

"This plaque is to commemorate the brave pirates who gave their lives to keep this box safe from the Robot Menace. Lest we..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] After Horace Slughorn retires, Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry appoints a new Potions instructor. His name is Gordon Ramsey. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] [TT] Once there was an ugly barnacle. He was so ugly, that everyone died... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 12:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] After a long life, filled with teaching and puppet shows, Mr. Ratburn passes away. Arthur Read and his old classmates attend his funeral. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, why can't the new Batman movie keep a director? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] The last enemy to be destroyed is death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] While traveling through the Nevernever, Harry Dresden takes a wrong turn and when he exits, he finds himself at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, Doctor Cox, why is going to the movies so expensive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Pear-bear, did you watch the Super Bowl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, where do babies come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw this really, really, really great movie "Storks," and it was wonderful but I can't help but think it was just something they made up for the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While walking through a crowded parking lot, you glance at the car next to yours. Inside is a kidnapped girl. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best quote from Spongebob Squarepants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] You discover than when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions of the future. The harder you make her laugh, the longer and more detailed the visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of all superheroes, you are the one villains fear most of all. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Rather than brush him aside, Mr. Incredible decides to take on Buddy as his sidekick "Incrediboy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A vampire awakens from his centuries-long slumber to find a world far different than the one he left behind. The zombie apocalypse has started. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You walk to your car in a crowded parking lot and glance to the one next to yours. Inside is a kidnapped girl. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] In Vahalla, Thor approaches Ted from Accounting, with a job offer: Joining the Avengers Initiative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] When Krypton is destroyed, the infant Kal-El is sent to a planet called Earth. His little shuttle lands in the backyard of a boy named Lex Luthor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 05:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As you walk towards your car in a crowded parking lot, you glance over to the car next to yours. Inside is a kidnapped girl. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 23:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A storm came through last night. It's the first snow day of the year. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Alien diplomats come to Earth, curious. They wish to know more about Man, as well as Man's Best Friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] While fighting his/her arch-nemesis, a superhero's mask is torn off, revealing their identity as the villain's twin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions from the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have some fun with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] Three generations in a single family gather together for the holidays. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recognize that the title leaves a bit to be desired, but given that the holidays are almost upon us, it seemed appropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You're hosting Thanksgiving dinner. Your sister is a superhero. Your brother is a super-villain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 12:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am starting a novel that has mystery elements. I need some advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A novel idea I've had for a while is about a group of spies with minor supernatural abilities. The plot revolves around their newest recruit and a conspiracy he uncovers--the kidnapping of a politician's daughter.

Are there any resources that you would recommend for help on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [2016/11/17] Cops: Gun-toting grandma chases armed robbers from home (GA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, who would win in a fight? Spider-Man or Batman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The teenaged daughter of a billionaire is kidnapped for ransom. It is not as easy a way to make money as the kidnappers thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 11:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] A vampire awakens to find a world far different than the one he left behind. The zombie apocalypse has just started. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are the Spirit of Halloween, better known as the Boogie Man. One day, you are confronted by the other Legendary figures for your tactics. You must convince them that scaring children is justified. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 13:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] Various legendary figures confront the Boogie Man for scaring children with nightmares. The Boogie Man insists that his use of fear is justified. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 12:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Marine Standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://lithriel.deviantart.com/art/Drop-your-weapon-or-she-dies-274226546 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mariner Standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions from the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Communication Caravan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 13:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.deviantart.com/art/I-want-to-talk-to-you-562407480 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Communication Caravan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 13:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] A Bear in Battle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 13:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.deviantart.com/art/War-Bear-299651935 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Swing in a Meadow [IP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.deviantart.com/art/Swing-369132916 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You deliver pizzas to pay for college. One night, you deliver pizzas and a werewolf answers the door. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 12:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Werewolves have terrorized the countryside for years. One small village remains untouched. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 13:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A wannabee supervillain is about to rob a bank for the first time. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 13:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're the youngest grandchild of an eccentric billionaire. One day, he comes to you and says he wants to branch out from the family business, and he needs your help. He wants to become a Zoo Tycoon. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 13:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Roller Coaster Tycoon, if that's what game you preferred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions from the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Professor Kirke tells the Pevensie children of his adventures, in the earliest days of Narnia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 14:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
