<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5213</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 04:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they need to be.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 22:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because OP's husband would've wanted his own kids doesn't mean he LIKES this situation.  What if the husband doesn't want to watch over the kids any more than OP but he's doing it because he's selfless and the kids deserve better than the alternative?  He was literally thrown into this situation.  SIL didn't call him and ask permission and he said yes, she just showed up unannounced.

It's a shitty thing, but I can't say your husband should be demonized for choosing to take care of his own blood in a fucked up situation when no one else would.  Honestly, it sounds honorable.  OP, you chose to marry through thick and thin.  You should communicate and just hold off on "leaving" until you two can come up with short and long term goals. I know this is an unpopular opinion, but right now you need to communicate with your husband just as well as you did here on Reddit.  See if a compromise can be made.  Tell him how you feel.  Make plans TOGETHER about what you want to do if their mom doesn't show up after a month... 3 months... etc.  Maybe start setting up rules around the house for now so things aren't so crazy?  Bed times, chores, periods without TV or games.  

You don't have to "mother" them and you aren't being forced into "motherhood".  Just treat them as a normal aunt would?  They aren't exactly young kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But people mentally think to themselves "okay I want 4 slices" regardless of size.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 02:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say more around $2 for not just garnishes, but substantive additions to your meal.   But I agree, if you aren't a smart shopper you can easily defeat the purpose of a college-budget meal.  

1 egg - 13 cents
Tofu portion - 50 cents
Green onion - less than 10 cents 
Spices - like 30 cents (a little goes a long way)
1/8th jar of kimchi - 50 to 70 cents 

Hey, for around $2.50 I enjoy it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know such sorcery existed!  Right now where I live 2 large bundles sell for a $1 but once the price goes up I'll need to try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bananas are great, I eat them too.  But variety with things like ramen are important to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe frugal would have been a better word to use.  But altogether it costs a lot less than fast food and tastes better too.  Ramen is cheap, eggs are cheap, tofu I get on sale, chile powder is cheap in bulk, and a little kimchi goes a long way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me even for candy that you really have no business trying to chew early, like jolly ranchers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUS ROH DAHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being a broke student, I had to get creative with my boring ramen noodles. Added kimchi, tofu, green onions, eggs, hot pepper flakes. Which normal/junk meals do you upgrade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 11:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you believe you are capable of forgiving him and giving him the opportunity to regain your trust, there's a chance it could work.  But there's a few questions you need to ask him and yourself about.

If he felt so guilty about cheating, why did he recently look at them when transferring from his tablet.

Why did he STILL have her phone number saved and friended on Facebook.

These things are big red flags that he may feel zero remorse from cheating.

I would say consider staying ONLY if he's genuinely sorry for cheating, not just sorry he got caught.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
