<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not shoot at innocents at all because shooting one innocent is a violation of his oath to protect and serve. Being a cop is dangerous. If you don't accept the danger, become a security guard at a mall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That describes the general state of the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the cost difference is really not that much.  It only matters if you're buying thousands of rounds of ammo. When hunting, you only need a few rounds of non-lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad I read the sarcasm tag. You had me going there for a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I've phased out all lead in my tackle box. I use tungsten weights and tin shot for everything now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly wish more people would realize that wall street is not the economy. And there has been no economic progress in the economy attributable to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must make random shithole purges less he explode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not close enough to assume collusion unless you ignore the Russian collusion in cheating the election. Or if you ignore truth, facts, ethics and morals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also have the ability to get elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure they can, the want to throw out the first so they can get to their favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't tapping a rival candidate.  Obama wasn't running for office. He was the other end of communications with foreign officials. Recognize the difference. Understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bad policy disguised as 2nd amendment lip service.

It's not an attack on the second amendment. Protecting wildlife refuges from lead is just common sense. And there are plenty of non-lead loads to choose from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I'm glad we got the evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when 'one' doesn't know what's right, 'one' doesn't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yes they should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the POTUS can authorize wiretapping of anyone suspected of foreign intelligence activities inside the United States as part of his counter-intelligence policies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discharging a weapon into a full vehicle at a family even is a violation of every department policy and every iota of common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National pastime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miami </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in the past three weeks, in four separate incidents, I've had people try to crash into me on the Turnpike or I-95 because they're driving like idiots and I have to honk my horn. Three of them have cut me off, I honk and they look in their rear view mirror and slam on their brakes. The fourth, someone tried to change lanes into me and I honk. He looks at me and then tries to ram into me.

I'm sane and have avoided the accidents.  The last one, my son was in the car with me. When my family is present, I don't take chances, and I don't play. And I hope none of these people ever try to stop me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly doubt that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only policy of Trump that I currently support. And I have seen this several times over the course of my career. Luckily for me, I'm a necessary part of the machinery as long as I keep cutting rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> before he could be deposed in the google lawsuit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that John Boehner in the back of that Pelosi photo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is really the only qualifier in this whole "story".  There's a file photo of it. That means press was present. Not secret, not a secret meeting. And If you can't tell the difference in why this isn't remotely the same thing, you drank too much kool-aid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed that. As someone said a bit earlier, this has turned into the gong show. On what planet is, "no, you are" a valid form of government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extremely weak level of fake outrage being spun by conservative dip shits this time around is disappointing in its complete lack of ferocity. Weak, pedantic administration; weak pedantic party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, don't call them the liberal tea party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he does. Trump's their guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and yet he can't because the he didn't break the rules at that time. They later changed the rules. But he didn't break them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm extremely pro-gun, but banning lead on national wildlife refuges is not an attack on the 2nd amendment, it's good common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wouldn't surprise me at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is completely in line with their skill level. I'm not even surprised by this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ain't that the truth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They check verifiable sources, not some crackpot on the Internet. You are who they fight against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but Trump is their best chance to roll back everything from the Obama years, which is their true goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third world first lady, third world thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is funny and true. Calling Snopes left-wing is as dumb as you can get. Snopes doesn't care about politics. Snopes cares about the truth. If they get something wrong, they quickly correct it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he purgered himself, yes. If not, he still needs to be fired because he's proven himself untrusted. If the nation cannot trust the AG, we have a problem.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent work. Though, don't forget to add a happy little tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they choose HUD? Why wouldn't they nominate a world-class neurosurgeon for surgeon general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no issue with this at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So America elected it's crazy Uncle Don who gets spoon fed vitriolic infotainment. Now he's governing based on Fox news because he believes it hook, line, and sinker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So traditional. Good guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still going on and she can't seem to shut up and leave her statement to stand. It's turning into an embarrassing rant. Someone needs to get her off the air. At the end of her speech, she needs to have the words, "stop talking" printed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All we can hope for is that the whole of congress grows a backbone and does their jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't a lack of qualified candidates. Your company doesn't look very hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an employee shortage because America downsized in 2008. Most of the experienced skilled workers have since retired. Those that haven't cannot be hired due to their age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where you're wrong kiddo. a few are brought over, several are sent back to run their own departments in India. The department is cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Miami. It is exceptionally hard to keep contracts here because someone is always cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've known plenty of those too. But that's not what this is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not competing for a job like the rest of us. They're being hired specifically because they're cheaper. It's easier to hire them because of the H-1B visa program. And it's cheating because most of them who come over are not here because they're better than Americans. It's because they're cheaper. H-1B Visas were meant for scientists and doctors and innovators. It was never meant to replace American workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're cheap. It's always about money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it. It's at best a horrible conflict of interest. At worst, a global money laundering scheme. Not only don't lawmakers care about it, the Justice dept doesn't care about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel sorry for that guy. He's trying to cheat the system. I guarantee you there are highly skilled Americans who were passed over, or never found because they were too expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was BCP, not TSA.

And honestly, I don't think this is entirely a bad idea. I have worked with "engineers" who couldn't engineer their way out of a wet paper bag, but they worked cheaper than Americans. If cheap foreign labor can't enter the country, it means companies will be forced to pay for Americans. While that is a capitalism nightmare, it's perfectly in line with Trumps agenda. Not that I am specifically for Trump's agenda, but I am for cracking down on H-1B Visa abuse. H-1B Visas have unfairly tipped the scales against highly-skilled American workers.

Before the H-1B visa, I could easily get $85 an hour for highly-skilled field work. Now companies like work market bid out skilled field service to the lowest bidder. They want you to go onsite at your expense and perform what may account to several hours of work for a low flat fee in some cases $20. It has put a severe hamper on my business and my growth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the great disconnect between the neo-conservative movement and the rest of the country. You see, wealthy people give no thought for how things will get paid. They think in terms of, "I'm wealthy, I don't need to look at the price tag." They assume the money will materialize because they are wealthy. The rest of us question how.

This is not Lincoln's party. It hasn't been in over 60 years. 

The rest of us know that money has to come from somewhere. Trump said we should bring back all the dollars from the rest of the world. Yeah, that's a real sound strategy for finding a trillion dollars. Look in the couch cushions of the rest of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truman was a truly shitty president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steel I can understand, but coal is a bad move.
Especially when we could have those guys working in great factory jobs making components for solar and wind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The buck stops... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was only by the class and decorum set forth by the Democratic party that allowed Trump to appear as he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be a required civics class before taking office. "So you got yourself elected." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, when we get to the Twenty Firth century, I will let you know how it workth out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are at least three distinct sects of the Republican party. They should split up. And at least two distinct sects of the Democratic party. They should also split. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This petition has been updated and it not affiliated with the white house petition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And those issues only benefit the super wealthy. I often wonder how they have convinced the common man to advocate against his own interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ajit Pai has stated that strict regulation reduces network investment.

This is patently false. Reduced competition eliminates the need for network investment. Strict regulation balances the gap left by reduced competition. 

Ajit Pai is a bad apple from the core. The beginning of his career was spent providing regulatory relief from the Telecom Act of 1996. All he heard was how that act "hurt business". It has tainted his mind ever since. If you disregard the DSL competition boom of the late 1990's thanks entirely to the Telecom act of 1996, you might be persuaded it was harmful to business. In fact, it was a boon to business and harmful only to Ma Bell who had to endure competition for the first time.

His views are vehemently anti-consumer. He shows extreme disregard for consumer choice, price gouging, and industry monopolization. This man belongs nowhere near the FCC. He is a danger to the Internet. He is a danger to the economy. He is a danger to the first amendment of the Constitution of the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps it would help if we knew what they wanted to accomplish. For almost a decade, it's been nothing but talking points. Their losing "repeal and replace" strategy has bore no fruit. Their only agenda seems to be undo the Obama years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are disconnected from the world on many levels. You look at life through a keyhole. Come on up out of the cave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not leadership. This slimy snake needs to be impeached bigly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prescription drugs are pretty cheap on my insurance, definitely not cheaper paying cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the mounting evidence is certainly pointing towards price gouging. Not only that, but they're also gouging the federal government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we have such a great amount of unused commercial lands and properties in this country, why do they want to build more? Why can't they just use what they have already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really interesting to to a person devoid of introspection. It's demoralizing to see that it's the POTUS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's sorry for bringing shame to America and will now resign into obscurity until his trial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's your problem right there. Pro-Trump and Intellectualism don't belong in the same sentence unless separated by the word Opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see, they offered black students the choice of going to college or not. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure this is completely unrelated to Google suing Uber for theft of smart car tech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My belief is that Testosterone builds muscle mass at a much higher rate than estrogen. Perhaps this is why the kid won? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the worst president in US History sounds more presidential than the POTUS, we live in interesting times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, extreme ties to Russia. He was majority shareholder in a Cypriot bank whose chairman was "reassigned" from Deutsche Bank after the Russian money laundering scandal. Secondary shareholder was a Russian oligarch who laundered money and friend of Putin. Former chairman was a friend of Putin. And Ross brokered a saving grace for Trump in the form of a $100 million house sale ($60 million profit) to said Russian Oligarch trying to hide money from his wife. At a time when Trump was struggling to pay off a loan to Deutsche bank. Everything worked out great, didn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. It's time we cut off these freeloaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump building, or we're building? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is well said sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore. But I did live there for 30 years, not so long ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump to military industrial complex, "Expect something really special." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hates the military. He just called our soldiers a bunch of losers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite that, I've never seen this kind of hate coming from rednecks in those areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A (writ of) mandamus is an order from a court to an inferior government official ordering the government official to properly fulfill their official duties or correct an abuse of discretion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, what wars does he want to win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The satire from that site is a bit frightening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of odd. That JCC is in Cooper City, I believe. Heavy Jewish population in Cooper City, right in the middle of cracker country. They've never had issues like this before. I guess Trump emboldens hate in every community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> neat. This is good news for future burn victims.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he did. He used VX. The real question is, how did they transport it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US Media doesn't have 'dying' credibility. It has credibility under siege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He then has the nerve to try and sell his own steaks? Do they come with ketchup packets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm going to disagree with you. We have proof that, this man has no title in Sweden, no one in Swedish government has heard of him, and Fox News decided to create that title for him. It's not fake because you disagree. I asked for examples. You provided none. You have no credibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Writ of Mandamus has been filed to the SCOTUS docket, which has a less than 1% chance of nullifying the 2016 election, should it be heard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> give some examples please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he wont go away. He needs to be voted out by an awake constituency. With all this Cuban coffee, you'd think we'd pay more attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do secret world-influencing cabals have rules? I wouldn't advocate breaking reddit rules though. Those are meant to be followed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This list contains all of their emails. It would be a shame if someone signed them all up for never-ending spam lists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her father-in-law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we hear about a secret cabal, this is it.

A few other notable names from this list:

Rich DeVos, Phyllis Schlafly, Louis Bremer, Herman Cain, Steve Forbes, J.C. Huizenga, Wayne LaPierre, Jenny Beth Martin, Edwin Meese, Grover Norquist, Tony Perkins, Rick Santorum. These are the people working against progress in America. These and many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was once part of a telephone town hall with Marco Rubio a few years ago. I got a cold call out of nowhere one night around 7:30PM. It was a "town hall" meeting with around 20 people they cold called based on people who had contacted Rubio via his website in the past. There were 3 questions asked by "constituents" that were screened by staff prior to being allowed. Only suitable softball questions were allowed. The whole thing lasted about 40 minutes. Then Rubio was in the wind. Very stand-offish. Very us vs them mentality. Rubio hates his constituents. He is only in the Senate to advance someone else's agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's simple. He wants to hurt America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Fort Lauderdale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's clearly satire. But sadly, it's believable satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the Internet started infotainment. It's caught on like gangbusters in magazines too. The news hasn't really pushed infotainment except for the last few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
