<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7668</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insensitive AF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 09:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in ! My flair is off but I binged today so I'm probably 119 without all this water weight. 

Height: 5'6"
HW: 136
CW:~119
GW: 110

I'm so close yet so very far! These last ten are gonna be a bitch to lose but I just gotta stay disciplined. This accountability will hopefully help me stay on track (:
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me this look screams to add an inner corner highlight on your eyes! Also maybe a more pink lip color might flatter the look more :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks! I'm just worried they're gonna get worse because I've been eating like 1300 these past two days bc I'm sad but hopefully I'll get back on track tomorrow :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My flair is off but in down almost 20 pounds at around 118 and still haven't really seen dramatic progress. Although one or two people have said "oh you've lost weight!". So it's noticeable enough to people I haven't seen in awhile but I only very slightly see it. When I drop another 8-10 pounds hopefully it'll be more dramatic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 17:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the brand laughing cow? I love their wedges !!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it happen to say her stats?! She is goals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a natural kind of bubble butt, but I hate it because it affects my thighs and makes it harder to lose weight there.

 I also hate my face. I think it's probably deformed or something.

When I look at my face in the mirror I think it looks ok, if not even kinda nice but when I take a photo of myself or see myself in photos, it is horribly uneven. I only like one side of my face and am constantly Untagging photos of myself that were taken with the wrong side of my face facing the camera. I want to get my crooked nose and uneven jaw fixed but I don't have 15,000 dollars for all that ... AHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just barely brush against each other if my feel are super close together! I'm not planning to drop below 110 so unfortunately I may never get a true gap :/ but thanks for the info (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh goodness im sorry if my guess was way off. like i said, im bad at this because of my own disordered thinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOOOoooooooo ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.. 100 pounds? Sorry I'm super bad at this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the beach with my boyfriend and saw him checking out all the skinny girls, and felt insecure. I stopped eating that day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what I do to prevent this is eat at around 7 and have like a 600 cal dinner (today I had chicken breast, home made sweet potato fries, spinach and onion and cottage cheese) and then if I get hungry again later on I snack a bit but stay under 800 cal for the day. Because of this I will sometimes wake up a bit bloated because of my full tummy but it's helped me lose a lot of weight while feeling super full!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks awesome! Probably a dumb question but when measuring rice, are you supposed to measure it out before it's cooked or after?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. This is exactly how I feel too. It's why I stopped wearing my seatbelt while driving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow!!! What's your workout routine?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, I feel I look deformed in photos but pretty ok in the mirror. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you're right. I am 21 and live in the US in New Jersey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to avoid being hospitalized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 06:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone! As i am approaching underweight and have had people noticing my weight loss, people are starting to ask questions and raise concerns about my habits. I'm afraid my family will find out and have me hospitalized, or that my therapist/nutritionist will send me to be hospitalized.


Are there certain things I should avoid saying during sessions so that I cannot be hospitalized? What triggers a hospitalization in general? Is it the weight loss or the way I talk about it? Or is it the more physical symptoms that start appearing the longer my ED continues? Unfortunately I do not have the money for treatment anytime soon. 

As for my family, my father is ill and I do not want to add more stress into his life. He knows I'm seeing a nutritionist at school but I told him that I wanted to eat more balanced meals so that's why I decided to go, especially while I have student insurance. How can I reassure him/other members of my family?

TL:DR; how do I avoid being hospitalized while still losing weight?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 04:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate. My boyfriend once called me a "sausage " a few months ago at my high weight of 136..Not sure why.. I know he was annoyed with me. But it stuck with me and on days where I'm feeling like giving up on this and trying to eat more I remind myself of this scenario. I will not give him, or anyone, reason to call me a sausage again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 04:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow as I'm sitting in the car right now, self loathing and feeling deformed, I get this comment! Thank you! I actually don't workout, I just ride my bike around my college town or walk around everywhere. I do 100 squats a week tho with 10 pound weights but that's basically it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 23:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started at 136 and I'm 119 now, ~9 pounds from my goal. I started in June </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creep by radiohead lol

"I want a perfect body... I want a perfect soul. I want you to notice, when I'm not around. I wish I was special... So fuckin' special " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how, but yeah. Many of my gut feelings end up being the truth , even when I don't want them to be  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gain 2-3 pounds and then usually drop four!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so hard resisting the urge to eat ALL of the candy bars but so far so good!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I first gain like 2-3 pounds! But yeah I usually end up losing more than I gained somehow. But I become ravenously hungry during my period so that's why I hate it so much :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Period makes me gain 2-3 pounds... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg! I saw that yesterday. That ending tho ...... LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When shark week is coming... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 06:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make sure I don't eat or drink anything before I go and I also wear light clothes (flip flops, tank top and thin shorts). Trust me, I take that into account :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEP SPOT ON OMG  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm cracking up! Omg I forgot bb is ok  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 04:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm just anal but I only trust weights that the doctors give me. I always fear that my scale at home is telling me a much lower weight than I am and I'll be very let down ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also it's great that we use "bacon reader" to browse an ED subreddit lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 17:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I feel when I even talk about it to my therapist -_- I feel like since I'm not underweight yet, I must not have a big enough problem so I feel guilty bringing it up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG she is legit all I aspire to look like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg it's gorgeous! I'm pasty without a little self tanner lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT you inspire me so much!!! Also sorry if this is a weird question but is that your natural tan? I'm looking for better self tanners and your tan is so beautiful!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I posted and I'm definitely not skinny but it felt good knowing other people can see and appreciate my progress when sometimes I feel like my body basically looks the same! You don't have to wait to post a pic until you feel "skinny" but ofc stick to what you're comfortable with (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've Been telling myself that way too often lately :/ but alas, you're right. I'll do better tomorrow!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! I started out at about 136 pounds and then moved to 127 in the second photo. In the last two photos I'm probably around 122-123 (even though I totally just had a crazy binge and will be all bloated tomorrow -_-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I saw this comment earlier. I had a shit day and binged like crazy. I had 3/4 of basically a greasy grilled cheese and turkey sandwich and a TON of cheese, and two glasses of wine to top it all off. Ugh :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought of it that way. That actually makes me feel less worried about being recognized lol thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just afraid of being recognized /: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/fOvrG


So I know y'all like before and afters so here's where I'm at! The first comparison is when I first started losing and the last two images I'm at my current weight of about  (I think bc my scale is broken so I may be smaller) 123 pounds. I'll probably be deleting this soon... Idk yet lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok maybe a dumb question but how many cal are in a plain bagel? I have seen all different calorie ranges and am never sure what the actual amount is -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely beautiful! I love your legs! Also not to be a creep but you always have the best underwear lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly how I feel! Often times my bf will be like "wow you ate all of that?!" Without realizing I haven't eaten in almost 24 hours. The Meal will usually look large at around 600 to 700 cal of super low cal stuff so there's a lot of it, but he doesn't quite get that I'm eating less than 1000 cal a day on any given day. Instead he only sees me devour a "normal person meal" once a day at dinner time and probably doesn't think my ED is real. As much as I don't wanna worry him, I wish he realized how much this really is a struggle for me and how real it truly is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! I never thought I would feel ashamed eating a single rice cake, especially in front of someone. 

Also, this was my first time pre-eating and it helped me avoid eating a ton of fried chips that I didn't realize came with my meal. Instead, I ate boiled lobster without butter, a half an ear of corn, and a salad without any dressing. Thank god, lol. I even had two vodka diets and stayed under 1000! Yay for small victories  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boyfriend just got annoyed with me because I was eating a rice cake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today my boyfriend and I planned to cook a stir fry together but now plans have changed and we're going out to dinner. I planned to eat less than 200 cal and then have a good portion of stir fry for dinner. I ended up having a few spoonfuls of cottage cheese at around 2, which was 70-80 cal. Then my bf and I were talking and decided we could use a coupon to go out to dinner and even though I was anxious about going out I figured I could fit it in and stay under 1000 cal. 

Because my stomach was growling so much and started to ache, I decided to have a 40 cal rice cake to calm it down before we have dinner. The first thing he says is "why are you eating! We're going out to dinner soon." And he seemed annoyed/angry. My first thought was "hmm you're right, why am I eating" and I blurted out "I didn't really eat yet today". Then he felt bad and I asked him to not ever ask me "why" I'm eating. I already feel guilty enough as it is. He knows I've been diagnosed with en ED, and knows I've been trying to eat more without feeling guilty. I've communicated that to him.

I just feel like sometimes he's rather insensitive (without trying to be) because he's often very unobservant and doesn't pick up on certain things easily. I'm trying to get into losing weight the healthy way but my ED is preventing that, and sometimes my bf and other people just make it worse -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the actual fuck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm stuck in the Constipation Boat, I take some milk of magnesia to summon the Massive Shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 04:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only way I can restrict successfully! If my boyfriend isn't around/doesn't notice, I'll hold off till at least 8 (maybe ill have a pickle or a 100 cal breakfast bar to hold me over) and then I'll eat a large meal at dinner time and feel full. From there I just gotta make sure I don't snack at night and voila! I restricted!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same tho OMG  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bi-curious here! 

As for women, I'm attracted to all sorts. But the ones who catch my eye the most are the slim and toned women. I don't really like super muscley women though, so just like not "skinny fat". I want to have this body type as well.

For men, I'm not attracted to fat men.I prefer the low to mid range of a healthy bmi for men, and some tone as well. I guess I do like abs and a muscular back, and decent biceps, but not like overdone! I'm also particularly attracted to tall guys with a little bit of beard going on and glasses. Or like nerdy looking guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
