<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3080</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindale pastor resigns after prostitution arrest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor arrested for writing bad checks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married Atlanta Pastor Arrested For Allegedly Spreading HIV At Church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor Arrested for Shooting   Killing Man During Church Service Over Alleged Affair with His Wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marrero church pastor suspected of aggravated child rape, sexual </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delmar pastor arrested on felony charges - Spotlightnews.com - Spotlight Newspapers, Local, News, Weather, Sports, Election Coverage, Albany, Schenectady, Saratoga, Troy, Capital District, Capital Region, Capitol, NY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youth Pastor Arrested for Lewd Molestation - KTEN.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillsong pastor arrested: facing assault charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor Accused of Stealing From Church 9 Times in Month: Complaint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darlington pastor accused of inappropriately touching boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor found guilty on child molestation, sexual battery charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youth pastor fired by California church and arrested for rape, sodomy, sexual assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> St. Mary Parish pastor arrested, accused of attempted indecent b - KATC.com | Continuous News Coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local pastor arrested for sexual battery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darlington pastor jailed on charges of sex crimes against a child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indiana pastor, church employee arrested for beating school boys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local pastor arrested after being accused of indecency with a child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Pastor Arrested on Child Sex Assault Charge: Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Anson youth pastor arrested for indecency with a child | News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Church comes to terms after pastor arrested - KSWO, Lawton, OK- Wichita Falls, TX: News, Weather, Sports. ABC, 24/7, Telemundo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bond set for Columbia pastor, funeral home owner arrested in dom - wistv.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inspired by /u/PlanetoftheAtheists, I created /r/PastorArrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OC Youth Pastor Arrested On Suspicion Of Engaging In Inappropriate Conduct With Children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: Sex Offender Turned Pastor Arrested for Parole Violations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pensacola pastor arrested; accused of paying teen $500 for sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor Arrested For Sexually Assaulting Five Year Old Relatives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> COGIC Pastor Arrested For Sexually Abusing Teen Family Member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trinity Fellowship sued over accusations of sexual assault of child by volunteer pastor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popular church pastor arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 01:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dugout boat making in Siberia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dugout boat making in Siberia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something simple that can have a positive effect on your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 15:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/ireland trolls Irish Examiner, a newspaper that sourced an article entirely by embedded reddit comments; the comments were edited and updated live on the newspaper's site. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 21:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you think the odds of the Powerball are bad (1 in 292 million), the odds of you being born was 1 in 400 trillion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 02:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our phones are more powerful than the technology used to send man to the moon. It's about time we started investing in better pooping methods. I dont know about you but I waste over an hour a day in the toilet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 04:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodbye to All That: Why Americans Are Not Taught History by Christopher Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 15:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drinking a jar of Moonshine   enjoying Deadwood. I always rematch the show at this time of year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/ChristopherHitchens as the mod has gone missing and it's impacting user functionality [more in comments] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why would someone commit a murder when they're on the verge of raking in $36,000,000 from being wrongly convicted in 1985? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 03:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now what? What can we do to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 08:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP removes images of God-as-terrorist Charlie Hebdo cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 15:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP removes images of God-as-terrorist Charlie Hebdo cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 14:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Bieber claims he was spoken to by god. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What book are you currently reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 20:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run the Christopher Hitchens book club, so we're currently reading And Yet which came out late last year. It's a collection of essays, some unpublished before. I read an essay from it last night about the south which said "People wear shorts who shouldn't even wear jeans." Considering I'm living in the south, I found it hilarious. We've all seen people of Walmart by now.

I'm also reading my first ever Wodehouse book which is 3 books in one, called Life with Jeeves.

Wodehouse was quite an artist I have to say. His writing is hilarious, some of the stuff Bertie and Jeeves get up to is just brilliant. I tried to watch the TV series adaption called Fry and Laurie but I didn't like that at all. The book is brilliant though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens And That Dubious Iran Quote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 04:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If we suggest that it is okay to make fun of everything except certain aspects of Islam because Muslims are much more sensitive than the rest of the world, isn't that discrimination?" -- Charb (editor of Charlie Hebdo) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 02:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a castle for sale in Galway. Anyone wanna go halves on it with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 00:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there's a castle you can rent in the North Carolina mountains, and it's designed like a hobbit house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there's an 850 square foot castle in the North Carolina mountains and you can rent it. It's called Hobbit House Micro Castle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PZ Myers Gets Caught Lying About Christopher Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 01:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sounds about right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 00:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asides from reddit, what's a website you frequent often? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 23:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remembering Ian Murdock -- a touching tribute by Bruce Byfield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remembering Ian Murdock -- a touching tribute by Bruce Byfield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poirier broken nose, broken in two places. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 05:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We say it's humane to put our pets out of their misery with euthanasia, but we don't do this for humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 04:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's powerball jackpot is 334 million of the finest American freedom dollars. What would you do with the proceeds if you won? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 23:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love being a father, but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 20:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is only Doc McStuffins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 20:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tough, but fair. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 20:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It started at 1am on Wednesday and ended at 11 seconds past midnight in the new year.....FUCK THAT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 07:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 January Book Discussion: And Yet: Essays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 00:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical: My Journey Out Of Islamist Extremism by Maajid Nawaz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently purchased Radical, by Maajid Nawaz, after reading his conversation with Sam Harris which was released as a book called Islam and the Future of Tolerance.

Link to Radical is here: http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0762791365

I'm only about 25% of the way through the book but it's quite fascinating.

As ex-muslims yourselves, I assume a lot of you have read this book, or are familiar with Maajid.

What are your thoughts on this book, or on what Maajid has to say? Does it resonate well with you, can you relate?

I'd like to hear your stories on how you became an ex-Muslim, and if you're actually able to leave the religion (perhaps you're not able to due to fear for your safety).

Cheers, and Happy New Year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is not a rant. Quite the opposite in fact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent New Years Eve at a party at a friends house with my wife, and a bunch of people she knows through work, along with a few others. There were ten or twelve couples there, so a nice enough crowd for a house event.

At the start of the event there were six of us (3 couples), and we got talking about kids. Everyone was in agreement - kids are awful, nobody wants them. It was interesting because most of us wanted them at one point, but said when we sat down and thought about it it was just fucking horrifying and not something any of us wanted to do.

As the night went on more arrived, and said the same thing. I was extremely happy to find an entire group of childfree people who had no intention of having kids. We were all in our twenties and thirties. 

Not one "so when are you having kids?" question was asked. What a night.

Have a happy, healthy and child free 2016 everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 January Book Discussion: And Yet: Essays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with the schedule for 2016 is here:

https://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens_/comments/3yycrr/2016_book_club_schedule/

This month we are reading **And Yet** a posthumous book released in November 2015 as a [hard copy](http://www.amazon.com/Yet-Essays-Christopher-Hitchens/dp/1476772061) with the [paper back](http://www.amazon.com/Yet-Essays-Christopher-Hitchens/dp/1782394567) coming soon in January 2016. 

This book contains a wide variety of essays penned by Christopher throughout his career. Included is the infamous self improvement essays for Vanity Fair titled: "On the Limits of Self Improvement", along with a great takedowns of Hillary Clinton and Christmas, and a favourite of mine: "Charles Dickens's Inner Child", to name but a few.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Book Club Schedule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Book Club Schedule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The following is the proposed schedule for the 2016 book club.

If you have any suggestions or comments please let me know.

I created /r/ChristopherHitchens_ for the book club, because the mod of /r/ChristopherHitchens is non responsive and will not sticky any threads for us. This leads to loss of discussion.


* **January**: And Yet...: Essays (2015)
* **February**: Imperial Spoils: The Curious Case of the Elgin Marbles. Chatto and Windus (UK)/Hill and Wang (US, 1988) / 1997 UK Verso edition as The Elgin Marbles: Should They Be Returned to Greece? (with essays by Robert Browning and Graham Binns). Reissued and updated 2008 as The Parthenon Marbles: The Case for Reunification, Verso. 
* **March** Prepared for the Worst: Selected Essays and Minority Reports. Hill and Wang (US)/Chatto and Windus (UK).
* **April**: Blood, Class, and Nostalgia: Anglo-American Ironies. Farrar, Straus   Giroux. Reissued 2004, with a new introduction, as Blood, Class and Empire: The Enduring Anglo-American Relationship, Nation Books, ISBN 1-56025-592-7
* **May**: For the Sake of Argument: Essays and Minority Reports. Verso, ISBN 0-86091-435-6
* **June**: Unacknowledged Legislation: Writers in the Public Sphere. Verso
* **July**: A Long Short War: The Postponed Liberation of Iraq. Plume Books. Originally released as Regime Change (Penguin).
* **August**: Arguably: Essays by Christopher Hitchens. Twelve. UK edition as Arguably: Selected Prose. Atlantic.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, are big storms every few days going to be normal for December now? It's been like this the past few years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That cat is quite hirsute! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 02:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank You /r/mma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 18:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to thank all the members of this sub for helping me continue my love of MMA. The debates and discussions, sometimes heated, have been a great learning experience.

The threads where new fans can ask any question without being berated are one of the best things about this place.

Thanks for the fun, and the memories. Wishing you all a happy and safe 2016! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 17:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee Moonshine. My brother in law gave me this jar for Christmas. It's 140 proof and made from corn. It's so smooth, like liquid cornbread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 03:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee Moonshine. My brother in law gave me this jar for Christmas. It's 140 proof and made from corn. It's so smooth, like liquid cornbread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 03:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to write a compiler? Read this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 17:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 04:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably the only time a child has made me laugh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 03:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coal Truck vs Scooter. The scooter doesn't win. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 01:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting conversation with my wife's grandparents in the bible belt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 01:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm visiting the in-laws for the holiday period. I've discussed my situation on here before but to summarise my wife is Christian, I'm anti-theist. She's cool with it. We haven't told her family simply because it never really came up. I support my wife, I'll go to church with her on Christmas Eve for a candle light ceremony and some singing thing. No preachy shite.

Anyway, I was talking with her grandparents today. They're supposedly catholic, from upstate New York, but they haven't been to church in 15 or 20 years or so. They moved to Tennessee in 1989. They don't like the churches around here and don't trust the pastors. At one point the grandmother said she doesn't believe in heaven at all, and the grandfather talked about a few contradictions in the bible and said he thought it was all bullshit.

This was a welcome revelation to me, obviously. I didn't press the subject too much, I agreed and said you don't need religion to be a moral person. Christians say you do but The Good Samaritan wasn't a Christian and he was a good person. They agreed with that.

It appears as though it's just my wife's mother who is the religious one. My wife likes to sing in church but hates the preaching piece. 

Slowly but surely common sense is making it's way into the family. I'm a happy person presently.

Enjoy the holidays folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are companies allowed to fund presidential campaigns in the USA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 03:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the states a few years ago. Instantly I saw how politicised the country was. It's entertainment here. But I also saw that companies were behind the presidential candidates.

To me, it looks like companies pay presidents, the president brings lawyers with them who will pass the legislation the companies paid the president for.

Is that how this works? It seems corrupt as fuck to me.

Can someone please explain why companies are allowed to fund presidential campaigns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I registered /r/Ireland_ in case they lock this one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 02:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it set to private for now, but if the mods go crazy on here and lock this sub reddit I'll open it up for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A vintage behind-the-scenes picture of Yoda. Behind him, Kenny Baker can be seen inside the R2D2 suit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 02:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favourite author, Christopher Hitchens in Kurdistan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 01:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens in Kurdistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 01:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Office worker jumps out the window after being berated by her boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 20:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too Many Mods (Grand Theft Auto 5 Animation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 16:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't fucking sleep. How the hell are ya? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you (again) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted here ages ago, and thanked everyone for the support and community. 

I wish to do the same again. My social circle last time was filled with loads of people pressuring my wife and I to have kids.

I dropped a lot of friends, because it became unbearable. A lot of the friends I have now either have kids that are raised or no kids at all, and they all respect what I have to say. Some of the friends I have who have had kids agree with me when I say I have no interest.

With the help of this sub I was also able to get my mother in law to relax and stop asking every time she saw us. The advice on here has been extremely important to my relations with our families.

So thank you, everyone. You are all brilliant and beautiful people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaching a friend of mine how to drink whiskey tonight. He's in for a treat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 00:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could somehow give advice to yourself 5 years ago, what would you say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 19:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you feel is essential to a child's upbringing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 19:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conspiracy Theories by Christopher Hitchens (with a review of The Da Vinci Code) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 15:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore does not understand the difference between race and religion - We Are All Muslim | MICHAEL MOORE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 03:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Workers of reddit - are you permitted to work your defined hours and leave on time, or expected to stay late and "put in the extra effort" for free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 00:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else read the diaries of Victor Klemperer, a jew living in Nazi Germany? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the fourth anniversary of Hitchens death. Here he is talking about Christmas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 19:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tuesday is the fourth anniversary of Christopher's death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 03:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I encourage all of you to read an essay, or a chapter of one of his books in remembrance of him.

Feel free to raise a glass in his honour as well. 

Rest easy Christopher. You changed my life for the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have The American Atheist group ever put up billboards with biblical quotes? I think that would have a fantastic effect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 03:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens - The pernicious effects of banning words -- This is relevant now more than ever, given that a Philadelphia school just banned Huckleberry Finn because of the word 'nigger'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens - The pernicious effects of banning words -- This is relevant now more than ever, given that a Philadelphia school just banned Huckleberry Finn because of the word 'nigger'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 02:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At 1pm EST - The MMA Hour with John Kavanagh, Ido Portal, Anthony Pettis, Khabib Nurmagomedov, Rose Namajunas, Aljamain Sterling, Javier Mendez, Lance Palmer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 17:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts   opinions on assisted dying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those interested two documentaries have been recommended.

1. Terry Pratchett - Choosing to die.  
2. How to die in Oregen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Ariel asks Conor about rumors of dissension between him and Dana/Lorenzo. Conor responds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 23:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystic Mac. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 08:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Dan Henderson on Twitter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 07:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guinness   honey glazed ham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 01:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 11 Advent Calendar - Arran Batch 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very excited to try this whisky. Arran offer a limited number of casks for sale to the public, whereby they will age the whisky for you. I believe I may have posted here about that. It interests me greatly. 

This little number is very light in colour. It looks similar to the earlier Kilchoman.  

**Nose**  
Creamy vanilla. This is actually quite complex. There's more going on but I'm not talented enough to figure it out. Very interesting.  
**Palate**  
Wow, definitely cinnamon. Some spice and citrus as well. Malty.  
**Finish**  
Very malty. Beautiful. Some orange as well. It's a medium to long finish. Astonishingly good. 

This is a very good whisky that could kick your ass. Solid - 9/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 11 Advent Calendar - Arran - Batch 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very excited to try this whisky. Arran offer a limited number of casks for sale to the public, whereby they will age the whisky for you. I believe I may have posted here about that. It interests me greatly. 

This little number is very light in colour. It looks similar to the earlier Kilchoman.  

**Nose**  
Creamy vanilla. This is actually quite complex. There's more going on but I'm not talented enough to figure it out. Very interesting.  
**Palate**  
Wow, definitely cinnamon. Some spice and citrus as well. Malty.  
**Finish**  
Very malty. Beautiful. Some orange as well. It's a medium to long finish. Astonishingly good. 

This is a very good whisky that could kick your ass. Solid - 9/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 10 Advent Calendar - Monkey Shoulder Blended Malt Scotch Whisky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Nose**  
Creamy vanilla and some sort of spice. Fresh.  
**Palate**  
Light and oaky. Medium.  
**Finish**  
Medium and oaky. Quite light. No bad at all. 6/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm American. I'm the greatest" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 01:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could change something about Irish society, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 19:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 9 Advent Calendar - Tullamore D.E.W. 12 Year Old Special Reserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tullamore Dew from the crock is my every day whiskey. There's something the crock does to the whiskey to soften it. It's quite spectacular.

In saying that, I'm very apprehensive about this whiskey, as I haven't liked any Tullamore Dew from a bottle. 

I'm not too happy about the Irish offering in this advent calendar, it seems like a poor show.

**Nose**  
Spices and nutty. Perhaps some honey too.  
**Palate**  
Spices again, oaky, creamy. It's not bad actually.  
**Finish**  
Medium finishing, not long at all. Oak, bitter. 

This is an OK effort. I don't think I'd buy a bottle of it though. 6/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mick Wallace released from Limerick Prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Security Advisory 3123040 - Private key for *.xboxlive.com certificate disclosed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My provider says a service I received is not covered. What are my options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 15:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went for an eye exam. The medical team I used for the exam told me my insurance covered everything and I just had to pay a $40 co-pay. 

Unfortunately, my provider (Cigna) sent a letter saying the team I used were not in their network. I now owe $325.

What are my options here, if any? I feel cheated, as I would have went elsewhere had I been told I wasn't covered. Instead, I was told I was covered and trusted that advice.

I assume there's nothing I can do and I just have to pay up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 8 Advent Calendar - Balvenie 15 Year Old Single Barrel Sherry Cask (x-post from /r/whiskey) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 02:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so **excited** to try this whisky. I absolutely love the Balvenie 12 year DoubleWood.

**Nose**  
Sherry obviously, orange is quite prevalent, some sort of sugary thing. It's like Christmas! The Glenfarclas 25 was top quality on all counts, but the nose on this is a lot more interesting. There's so much going on.    
**Palate**  
Sherry again. It's top quality though. Fruity and nutty. This is special.  
**Finish**  
Spices. It's a medium-long finish. This is beautifully matured. 

This is on par with the Glenfarclas 25. Easily 9/10 no question about it. I'll be picking up a bottle of this very soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 8 Advent Calendar - Balvenie 15 Year Old Single Barrel Sherry Cask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 02:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so **excited** to try this whisky. I absolutely love the Balvenie 12 year DoubleWood.

**Nose**  
Sherry obviously, orange is quite prevalent, some sort of sugary thing. It's like Christmas! The Glenfarclas 25 was top quality on all counts, but the nose on this is a lot more interesting. There's so much going on.    
**Palate**  
Sherry again. It's top quality though. Fruity and nutty. This is special.  
**Finish**  
Spices. It's a medium-long finish. This is beautifully matured. 

This is on par with the Glenfarclas 25. Easily 9/10 no question about it. I'll be picking up a bottle of this very soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 7 Advent Calendar - Glen Scotia Double Cask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Nose**  
I'm getting some apple peel - similar to Green Spot. Oak and vanilla. It's very very nice. Leave it for a few minutes to let it open up.  
**Palate**  
Sherry, spices, vanilla again but not a lot. I didn't get much sherry on the nose but I can get it now.  
**Finish**
Very short finish. Sherry again.

This is a great effort. 7/10 from me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like Cork has changed its province. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The global sea level is expected to rise 1.5 meters by 2100. Check out the impact that will have to Ireland on this map. More inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 6 Advent Calendar - Kilchoman Machir Bay 2014 Release (x-post from /r/whiskey) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 02:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to try something from Kilchoman for a long time now, so I'm very excited about this. I'm a big lover of Connemara peated whiskey so I have high hopes for this.

**Nose**  
I could smell this all day long. The peat reminds me of home. There's some fruity thing going on in there as well.

**Palate**  
I'm very surprised by this. I thought it was too young, but it's not at all. This is very light, it's already quite soft. It's oily, smooth, vanilla and some sort of spice. Peat of course.

**Finish**  
It's a short finish as expected. Peat and fruit. 

I'm very surprised at how good this is. A solid 8/10 from me. Amazing work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 6 Advent Calendar - Kilchoman Machir Bay 2014 Release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 02:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to try something from Kilchoman for a long time now, so I'm very excited about this. I'm a big lover of Connemara peated whiskey so I have high hopes for this.

**Nose**  
I could smell this all day long. The peat reminds me of home. There's some fruity thing going on in there as well.

**Palate**  
I'm very surprised by this. I thought it was too young, but it's not at all. This is very light, it's already quite soft. It's oily, smooth, vanilla and some sort of spice. Peat of course.

**Finish**  
It's a short finish as expected. Peat and fruit. 

I'm very surprised at how good this is. A solid 8/10 from me. Amazing work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Hicks rare interview from 1988. Fucks sake I miss him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 01:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Herro! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 5 Advent Calendar - Dalmore 15 Year Old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 03:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Nose**  Sherry almost instantly. Orange maybe? Chocolate.

**Palate**  Wow this is smooth. Definitely orange. Chocolate. It's beautiful. It really is crazy how smooth this is.

**Finish** Not as long as I would like. Very very pleasant. 


8/10. An outstanding whisky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 4 Advent Calendar - Elijah Craig Small Batch Bourbon 12 Year Old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't drank much bourbon in my life, so I'm excited to try this. I'm a big fan of Evan Williams Single Barrel. 

**Nose**  
This smells amazing. Toffee, spices. It smells creamy. Very very interesting.  

**Palate**  
Not as smooth as I would have hoped, given how it is on the nose, but it is still quite smooth. Hints of spices again, oak too.  

**Finish**
A very long finish, very nice. One really notices the cream. This finish goes on and on and on. 

This isn't bad at all. 6/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think will happen to America if Donald Trump becomes president? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 19:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 3 Advent Calendar - Compass Box Great King Street - Artist's Blend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 02:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Nose**  
All I get is vanilla. Vanilla, vanilla, vanilla. It's perhaps citrusy too but I barely get that at all.

**Palate**  
Jesus I've no idea. It's... sort of rich or creamy I guess but there's other stuff going on and I just can't pick it up. Maybe some lemon or something like that. 

**Finish**  

Very rich, creamy again, lasts long enough actually. It's a beautiful finish. 7/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First batch of the Christmas whiskey has arrived [details inside] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 01:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Book Club - is anyone interested in continuing the reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 02:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you want to continue the book club? Most of the work we haven't covered are in essay form. We could do essay by essay or book by book, whatever suits.

We didn't cover the following in 2015:

* 1987: Imperial Spoils: The Curious Case of the Elgin Marbles. Chatto and Windus (UK)/Hill and Wang (US, 1988) / 1997 UK Verso edition as The Elgin Marbles: Should They Be Returned to Greece? (with essays by Robert Browning and Graham Binns). Reissued and updated 2008 as The Parthenon Marbles: The Case for Reunification, Verso. 
* 1988 Prepared for the Worst: Selected Essays and Minority Reports. Hill and Wang (US)/Chatto and Windus (UK).
* 1990 Blood, Class, and Nostalgia: Anglo-American Ironies. Farrar, Straus   Giroux. Reissued 2004, with a new introduction, as Blood, Class and Empire: The Enduring Anglo-American Relationship, Nation Books, ISBN 1-56025-592-7
* 1993 For the Sake of Argument: Essays and Minority Reports. Verso, ISBN 0-86091-435-6
* 2000 Unacknowledged Legislation: Writers in the Public Sphere. Verso
* 2003 A Long Short War: The Postponed Liberation of Iraq. Plume Books. Originally released as Regime Change (Penguin).
* 2011 Arguably: Essays by Christopher Hitchens. Twelve. UK edition as Arguably: Selected Prose. Atlantic.

We also have his latest book, And Yet to cover as well. 

Some of these books are huge (Arguably, for example, would take more than one month for most people to read, given that real life gets in the way and so on). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone says Hitler was an atheist.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 16:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have encountered religious people in the USA (and I am sure some of you have too) who have tried to say Hitler was atheist, and thereby use it to show that atheism is "bad" or "evil".

Christopher Hitchens countered this with the example that the Nazis had "Gott mit uns" on their belt buckles (god is with us).

I'm currently reading "I Will Bear Witness", a diary from 1933 to 1941 by Victor Klemperer. Victor was a Jew who lived in Nazi Germany. He writes in his diary an experience of living during this period.

Upon reading his diary, it becomes apparent how things changed on a day to day basis for Jews in Germany. New taxes are imposed "voluntarily", but as Victor notes "Who dares object?". Suddenly Jews are no longer allowed to use public transport, the public libraries, and so on. Their rights were being removed day by day.

Anyway, I wish to bring attention to the following note he made on June 29th 1937: 

Today a Hitler speech in Wrzburg once again pure religious madness. Only that he did not say I, but we. "Providence guides us, we act according to the will of the Almighty. No one can make national or world history without the blessing of this Providence".

I'll be memorizing the date, along with this diary entry for a future retort against someone who tries to claim Hitler was atheist.

P.S I highly recommend reading this book. I've been making notes along the way and keeping them in Microsoft OneNote. It's quite terrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patrick Cockburn: Christopher Hitchens made a cogent case for war  but he was wrong..... any thoughts on this article lads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 03:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What gets you out of bed in the morning; what do you live for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 01:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creating a library at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 01:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm converting a bedroom to an office/library. More info inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 01:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My copy of And Yet...: Essays by Christopher Hitchens shipped. Happy days lads! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that cold weather is here I can start using this again. My wife put the Hitchens quote on here for me. She knows me very well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my favourite drams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 00:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a nice evening for a dram. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 00:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas Whiskey - $500 limit for Irish Whiskey. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 03:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each year I usually spend $1000 on Irish whiskey for Christmas. I'm from Ireland and the price of whiskey here is so cheap compared to back home, so I like to indulge.

However, this year finances are kind of tight so I'm keeping it to $500. I usually get one of the fancy Midleton whiskies (like Barry Crockett Legacy), a few bottles of Green Spot, a few Tullamore Dew crocks, John Powers Lane, Redbreast 12 or 21, perhaps some Connemara.

However, I want to do something different this year and try some whiskies I haven't had before along with some that I have had. Of the list below I've had the Powers Signature Release and the Redbreast but haven't had the others.

Here's what I'm thinking so far:  

* Yellow Spot Irish Whiskey Pot Still 12 Year 750ML $89.77  
* Powers Irish Whiskey Single Pot Still Signature Release 750ML $54.99  
* Kilbeggan Irish Whiskey 750ML $29.99  
* Redbreast Irish Whiskey 12 Year 750ML $49.99  
* Clontarf Irish Whiskey 1014 Classic Blend 750ML $25.99  
* Concannon Irish Whiskey 750ML $21.99  
* Powers Irish Whiskey Gold Label 750ML $24.99  
* The Irishman Irish Whiskey The Original Clan 750ML $27.99  
* The Irishman Irish Whiskey Single Malt 750ml $41.39  
Subtotal	$367.09

What else should I add to this list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The growing trend of tu quoque on Reddit and elsewhere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 01:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you've all seen it. It's been a big trend for quite some time on Reddit. When someone is talking about a subject and they get labeled "edgy".

It happens a few ways:  
Don't cut yourself on that edge.  
You're so edgy.  

This is also an example: https://www.reddit.com/r/CringeAnarchy/comments/3stnmj/so_edgy_really_makes_me_question_everything

How do you lads usually handle this when it comes up in a conversation? It does nothing but attempt to shut down the conversation by making it look like someone is emotionally invested in something therefore unreasonable, which quite often is not the case at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain why people do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 18:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any chance of a rational conversation about religion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 12:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit, and most social networking sites like Facebook, and so on, have been absolute shit shows the past few days as a result of the awful events in Paris. It has been almost impossible, or in some cases impossible, to have an unbiased meaningful discussion about what happened,  without the dialogue descending into a toxic shit fest.

I dont really want to talk about what happened in Paris for the most part (I will a bit later), but instead I would like to attempt to have a meaningful discussion about religion (focusing on Christianity and Islam). Ive studied religion for a while now, and I believe I can offer some insight for people who are unfamiliar with either ideology. 

**Disclaimer**:  Sorry if some of this feels condescending. That was not my intention, but upon re-reading it some parts come off that way. 

**Why even bother?**  
Given the rise in the number of Muslim people moving into western countries, I think its important for people in those countries to have an understanding of what Islam is. This can help with integration, and hopefully reduce sectarianism, xenophobia and racism.

**Monotheism**  
There are three major monotheisms most of us are familiar with. Judaism, Christianity, and Islam. These three religions are also called Abrahamic religions. There are lots more Abrahamic religions, but these three are the biggest. 

Judaism is the religion of the descendants of Jacob, Abrahams grandson.  
Christianity started as a sect of Judaism, and evolved as a separate religion with distinct beliefs and practices. Jesus can be said to be the central figure, Gods messenger.  
Islam is also a separate religion which arose in Arabia in the 7th century. Muhammad  can be said to be the central figure, Gods messenger.

All three religions have the same God, with a different messenger. Islams Allah is Christianitys God. Allah is directly translated to God.

Jews dont believe that Jesus was Gods messenger. 
Christians obviously believe that Jesus was Gods son and messenger and thats what their faith is based on.
Muslims believe Muhammad was the most recent (and will be the last) messenger sent down by God and their faith is based on his teachings. They believe their religion is the one true religion, and it will be the final solution.  

**The Christian Bible**  
The bible was created a long time ago (parts of it are thousands of years old and were passed down as stories before the written word reached Palestine). The book is basically a collection of texts. 
The bible is broken up into two parts: The Old Testament and The New Testament. Were all familiar with this so I should not need to go into too much detail here. The Old Testament is pretty vicious in parts, and is almost the complete opposite of The New Testament. Most Christians who follow Jesus ignore the Old Testament completely and focus on Jesus teachings in The New Testament, however this part of the bible is not all unicorns and rainbows either. Basically the book suffers from being written a long time ago, when we had no understanding of germ theory, we thought the world was flat, we didnt know about DNA and the double helix, and so on.  

There was a time when most, if not all Christians believed the bible to be the true word of God, completely accurate, infallible. However, with the advancement of society, and scientific discovery, this is no longer the case because some of the texts have been proven to be inaccurate or wrong. For example, Exodus is a text about the mass movement of Hebrew people out of Egypt. Mainstream history and archaeology now consider this to never have happened.   

However, there are sects of Christianity who still think the bible is infallible and they take it literally (Creationists). They believe the world is a few thousand years old, that dinosaurs roamed the earth along side humans, that evolution is wrong and that climate change is not being made worse by man. These people have their own political party in the USA called The Tea Party. Im sure youve  heard of them.  

**The Koran**  
Theres different ways of spelling this (Koran, Quran, etc). Im going with Koran.

The Koran is made up of large parts of the Christian bible with some additional texts and stories added on to the narrative. These are said to have taken place after the Jesus story. Unlike Christianity, where not a lot of practitioners believe the bible to be the true word of God, infallible, and so on, the vast majority of people who follow Islam believe the Koran to be just that.

This can create issues because its a static text that does not change, and as societies move forward and advance, this text does not. The same can be said with the bible.

**Why is a static text a problem?**  
As I said above, as societies change, these texts do not. So people who follow them word for word end up having problems with societal changes. One example is gay marriage. Christians who follow the bible word for word, and Muslims who follow the Koran word for word, both have issues with gay marriage, gay relationships, and so on.  

Obviously, theres different sects. Some Christians are OK with gay marriage, they just believe in love thy neighbor and leave it at that. Others do not. Similarly with Islam, some Muslims are OK with gay marriage, the vast majority are not however.  

**Are there other societal issues that can arise?**  
Yes. I mentioned Creationists above. The Tea Party in America want America to become a theocracy. If this were to happen America would abandon its constitution and it would be ruled by biblical law. This would create obvious issues in a western society. I used gay marriage as an example above, but theres lots of other issues that would arise from this.  Im sure I dont need to go into them.  

**What is Sharia?**  
Im sure youve heard of Sharia by now (also incorrectly called Sharia Law. When you say Sharia Law youre saying Law Law).

Sharia is a system of law outlined in the Koran and also in the Sunnah (the life of Muhammad). This is obviously an old system of law that was created a long time ago. Its also a static law system, in that it does not change (for the most part). Issues arise here because it was written so long ago, parts of it are incompatible with western society today. Parts of it are also unchangeable, infallible, "the true word of God".

Sharia deals with public and private affairs. It rules over diet, sexual relations, crime, politics, economics. 

According to the Pew Research Centers Forum on Religion   Public Life there are approximately 1.62 billion Muslims world wide. Of these 1.62 billion, 1.1 billion believe Sharia should be the law of the land. So approximately two thirds of Muslims worldwide want to be ruled by the law outlined in the Koran.

Sharia also defines jihad, and this is an issue for Islam.

**What are some of the laws in Sharia?**  
1. The mosque and the state are one. For example: Iran.  
2. Jihad may be waged against injustice or an unjust nation. (	Classical texts say Islam is justice, and no Islam is injustice, therefore a just war can be waged against a nation or people who do not submit to Islam.)  
3. Jihad may be waged to spread Islam and force conversions  holy war.  
4. A captive in Jihad may be executed, enslaved, ransomed for money, exchanged for other prisoners, or released freely.  
5. A woman captive of Jihad may be forced to have sex with her captors  
6. Property can be destroyed of confiscated during jihad.  
7.  A second class submission tax must be imposed on Jews and Christians living in Islamic countries.  
8. Slavery is allowed.  
9. A male owner may have sex with his slaves, even if they are little girls.  
10. Apostasy laws including imprisonment and execution may be imposed on anyone who leaves Islam.  
11. Blasphemy laws including imprisonment and execution may be imposed on anyone who insults Muhammad.  
12. Drinkers and gamblers may be flogged.  
13. An eye for an eye is allowed (an injured plaintiff/private citizen is allowed to enact literal revenge).  
14. The hand of a male or female may be cut off.  
15. Homosexuals may be imprisoned, flogged or executed.  
16. Adulterers may be stoned to death.  
17. A woman inherits half what a man does.  
18. A womans testimony in court counts half of what a mans testimony does.  
19. Husbands may hit their wives.  
20. A man may have up to four wives.  
21. A man may marry a pre-pubescent girl.  

Its important to note that not all Muslims believe that Sharia should rule, as explained earlier. Its similarly important to note that of the Muslims who believe that Sharia should rule, not all of them want to obey all of the laws detailed in Sharia. 

If required, I can provide the exact passage in the Koran where the above passages exist. Im sure you can find them with some Google-fu as well.

**Sharia in Western Countries**  
Sharia is practiced in western countries, however not to the degree that is is practiced in the likes of Iran. Muslims living in Western countries usually use Sharia as guidance when dealing with Family affairs, marriages, and so on. Its a toned down version which respects some of the local laws. 

**Extremism**  
Based on the above laws from Sharia, you can see where extremists get their code from. To say groups like ISIS are not Islamic, or to disassociate Islam from the actions of these groups, is doing yourself an injustice. If governments and societies want to deal with jihad, and extremism, they have to face this head on and admit this. 

**Totalitarianism**  
Christianity and Islam have some totalitarian traits. Both say we are born sick and commanded to be well. Both say we have someone watching everything we do, watching us while we sleep, someone who can convict us of thought crime. By design, both religions try to control every aspect of ones life.

Bolshevism and National Socialism tried the same thing with Russian and German societies. Ultimately fascist regimes are doomed to fail because of human innateness. Deep down we want to be free, we want to be just, we want to be true. We get our morals from our genes. Morality has been demonstrated in animals, for example.

For the most part I would like to think that we all want everyone to live and let live. People can have their religion if it makes them feel better. The problem is when that ideology impacts other peoples lives. 

If Muslims wish to integrate successfully into western society they have to abandon certain parts of their faith. I believe the Muslim leaders need to be more upfront and honest about their religion, and the impact it can have on people and societies when followed exactly as is written in the Koran. Sharia is an issue for western societies, and I think it should be against the law. Western governments need to be more up front and honest as well, and admit that groups like ISIS are just following what the Koran says.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone imported a cask of scotch to the USA before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 03:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of Scottish distilleries selling whiskey by the cask, they age it for 10 years for you (which is insured and guaranteed, if the whiskey is shit they'll replace it with as close a match as they have). 

It works out ridiculously cheap, for example Arran distillery offer 200 liters of whiskey for 1650 GBP. There's taxes and stuff you have to pay, plus bottling etc. Those are bulk liters, so it equates to around 215 bottles after the angels share and all that jazz, that's if you age it 10 years. Aging it longer reduces the volume. 

The pricing is here: http://www.arranwhisky.com/sites/default/files/Arran%20CaskPurchaseOffer%20240215_0.pdf along with loads of info.

I am **very** interested in doing this, however I haven't decided on a distillery yet. I'm currently living in the USA, and my buddy and I would like to go halves on a  cask. I just have no idea about importing it here, with customs and what not.

So have any of you lads in the states done this? What's required for customs? Do I need some sort of permit or what? I'm worried that it's such a large amount of whiskey they may not believe it's for personal use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens | Little Atoms interview. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little Atoms magazine Issue 1 on sale now -- has some writing from Hitchens on Marxism. His son Alexander tweeted this today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time I hear the name "Michael Lowry" I'm reminded of this scene from Bad Boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are all on the front lines: Canadian reportedly killed fighting ISIL wrote essay about why he went to war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I keep getting over charged by the butcher in Harris Teeter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 01:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually go to the one in Apex, but it's not just that butcher who does it. The worst case was a few weeks ago, crab cakes were $1.99 each and he charged me $4.99 for each of them. I was buying 8 so this was obviously massively over priced. 

After I told him the sign said $1.99 each he charged me $2.99 each for them. I had to say it to him a third time before he charged me the correct price.

Today, marinated chicken breast was $3.99 per pound, and he charged me $4.99 per pound. After telling him about it he fixed the price today.

The store is expensive and I only go there for the fruit, veg and meat because the quality is really good but I'm seriously getting sick of being over priced all of the time. 

I could easily have listed 8 or 9 other instances of this.

Has anyone else noticed this happening as well? It can't just be happening to me....

**EDIT** There seems to be some confusion here. The prices I gave were the vic prices. It was the vic price I was looking at when I said he priced it incorrectly. Yesterday, the price of the meat was $6.99 and the vic price was $4.99, but the advertised price was $3.99. He changed it to $3.99 for me. I can show you lads the labels if need be. I still have both of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a link, or a list, of every book review Hitchens did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 00:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have all his books, so I have quite a few of his book reviews, however there are lots of reviews that never made it into book form, and were published in magazines and what not.

Is there an archive anywhere that has all of his book reviews? 

That would be fine, and great life time reading really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sauce do you put on your breakfast roll? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 15:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YR, HP, Chef, Ketchup, or just plain butter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graham King  Facebooks code quality problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 22:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gerry Adams: British intelligence chiefs putting peace process at risk to stop SF growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 21:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club: November Discussion: Hitch-22 Some Confessions and Contradictions: A Memoir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/


This month we are focusing on **Hitch-22**, which again I feel is a book that requires no introduction.

I'm honest when I say this book took me three attempts to successfully finish. I found it difficult for a lot of reasons. I'm 32 so I wasn't alive for a lot of what Hitchens talked about, unfamiliar with a lot of events he was protesting about in his youth, so I had to go look them up and educate myself in order to follow along with the story. That's not a bad thing at all. 

There's a lot of name dropping in this book, but if you can get past that you're in for a real treat.

The death of his mother, the relationship with his father, and his brother is barely even mentioned at all. He didn't mention the women he had relationships with either because he didn't want to offend any of them by leaving someone out; it was better not to tackle it at all.

His relationship with Martin Amis is wonderful and gets a full chapter to itself. Salman also gets his own chapter, as does Fenton. I'm really glad about the latter, because his poetry is outstanding. I recently read The memory of war: Poems, 1968-1982. If you haven't read this please do. You'll be the better for it.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spoke with TWC yesterday. They're upgrading everyone in Apex to TWC MAXX tomorrow, November 3rd. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 16:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm on 400mg of Tramadol for back pain. Been on it since August. It's causing issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 04:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's only causing issues when I ease back or stop taking it. I wanted to drink alcohol, so I didn't take Tramadol that day. I just had a glass of wine, and I hadn't drank in so long that I was feeling a little buzzed.  Had lots of water, was grand. It's funny because I used to be a big drinker and some nights would put away half a bottle of whiskey. I have zero tolerance now. I did the same yesterday, felt mad dizzy this morning. 

Anyway, on the first occasion, the day after I got really dizzy. When I would move my eyes or head I'd get this strange weird dizzy thing going on along with pulsing in my ears, chest and arms. It was so bad I passed out and I ended up in the ER.

When I started taking Tramadol again the issue went away within about 20 - 40 minutes. 

The doctors are worried because my sister had a brain aneurysm so they're sending me for an MRI to be sure, but I'm sure it's the drug. I almost instantly felt fine after taking Tramadol again.

Does anyone here have any experience with this? How hard will it be to ween myself of this shit? Are there other pain meds I could take that won't do this sort of crap?

Cheers lads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all those posts about idiots living abroad looking down their noses at people back home, I present An Ode to Living Abroadand Coming Home  a yanks story about living in France. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 23:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Largas: Paddy McGeady: "I would love to see Treasure Island again" he told me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 19:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wages in Ireland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 17:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the US in 2011. I started on 60k and I'm making 100k now. There's jobs in my area for 120k for a senior java developer, which is what I'm doing now.

I'm nowhere near the likes of New York City, or anything like that. I'm in the RTP (Research Technology Park) area of North Carolina. Ten minutes outside any of the towns here is pure hicksville USA. Point being the wages here are not inflated considering US levels at least.

I'd love to move back to Ireland, but the salaries seem way lower. This is a good thing because it drives investment, but it's also a bad thing because people should be paid more. Our Irish office in Galway, the lads doing exactly what I'm doing are on around 50 or 60 grand. If they knew what I was making they'd lose the plot I'm sure.

Is there any hope of wages rising in Ireland? Is there anything we can do to ensure Irish people get paid more? I see it as a company taking advantage of people to be honest. I don't think it's fair that a developer doing what I do gets paid way fucking less.

Sorry, bit of a rant there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens 1999 Discussing 'The Abolition of Britain' with Peter Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 00:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first dram since August. Slinte lads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 23:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Podge Collins set to return for Clare hurlers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 17:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite book about this beloved sport? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether it's an autobiographical account, or something else.

I'm an avid reader but I haven't read one book about rugby and I'd like to rectify that.

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Say hello to Mumbles. If you zoom in, he has crazy eyes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 02:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there was one thing you could change about Java, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 05:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #PrayforMexico is trending. That's just way for people to make themselves feel better without actually fucking helping Mexico at all. How about you fucking do something about it instead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 04:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Friday! What are you doing this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 00:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could change one thing about the universe, what would you change, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 00:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cathal Pendred said he was going to take time away from UFC to focusing on striking (he was going to box for a while). Why did he not do this? Why is he fighting again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Dublin came up so he had to fight again. Sorry for the grammar mistake in the title (focusing should be focus). I blame predictive text.

Cheers lads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tommy Bowe out for at least six months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 16:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tommy Bowe out for at least six months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 13:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else tried Outlook 2016 on their Mac? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 04:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my first time using Office on a Mac and I am really, really impressed. Outlook is miles ahead of the native OS X mail client. It really puts it to shame.

Have any of you tried Outlook 2016 yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens ~ The Morals of an Atheist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 01:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorted for the winter lads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emerald Isle, North Carolina. This doesn't look like Ireland.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 21:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to North Carolina - what's a must-do for a new resident in this state? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 21:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just looking for things to do in this state. I keep up to date with the weekly "things to do" thread that covers stuff to do in the Triangle area, but is there anything else I should be doing? 

I visited the coast this summer which was a great experience.  
I also visited the mountains and went hiking.  
Is there any sort of tradition I should be taking part in?

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland does what the US wont: 26 top bankers sent to prison for role in financial crisis (x-post from /r/worldnews) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 18:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ready for the winter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 04:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USA team wins domestic competition - calls self World Champions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 03:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that we are at the semi-final stage of the World Cup, who do you think is going to win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 01:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what we have seen so far, I think New Zealand have been the best, followed by Argentina. 

I would be very surprised if it was not a New Zealand vs Argentina final.

South Africa and Australia just haven't shown the form we've seen from New Zealand   Argentina. The explosive, moving at ease rugby. To be fair, New Zealand have had issues but their most recent game against France was very impressive. 16/1 is a massive price for Argentina in my opinion.

What do you see happening over the next two weeks? Who do you think will win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure what happened but I ended up in the emergency room. The Irish loss was too much perhaps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 20:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've no idea how this can be comfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 21:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is how you handle the Haka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> it's important to understand that something that works in a country a bit larger than Maryland with under 6 million people in it might not work in a country that is 600 times larger with about 60 times more people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 00:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a good alternative to Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 01:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Americans care about their family's heritage. So what. Move on. The fact this gets under this site's skin so much is proof that people are digging deep for reasons not to like America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 23:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a 2007 Rasteau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 23:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a 2007 Rasteau to drink tomorrow. The only one I could find in a store near me was this: 2007 Ortas / Cave de Rasteau Rasteau Les Hauts du Village. It's available here: http://www.totalwine.com/wine/red-wine/rhone-blend/rasteau-cotes-du-rhone-haut-villages/p/96051750?s=608 m=ship igrules=true

This wine has mixed reviews on CellarTracker which is why I'm asking on here. Have any of you tried it? Should I look for something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That was a long week. Anyone else suffering from withdrawals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 21:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This job description is hilarious. Do you understand the dark corners of Java 8 and understand how to properly romance the garbage collector.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This job description is hilarious. Do you understand the dark corners of Java 8 and understand how to properly romance the garbage collector? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland confirm that Paul OConnell will return to the camp for Sundays quarter-final. They aren't replacing Payne so he can remain in the squad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 18:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have left social media (Facebook, etc), how has your life been since leaving? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 20:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone remember Fives 5p Crisps? My favourite were the green ones. I think they were pickled onion flavour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 19:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given that Paul O'Connell has been replaced, will he be allowed to stay with the Irish team and be in their dressing room this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 15:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what the rules are given that he has been replaced.

Does anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the barn my wife's grandfather built after clearing their land by himself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 01:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the barn my wife's grandfather built after clearing their land by himself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 01:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite wineries in the area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 02:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NC has tonnes of wineries. See it for yourself here: http://www.ncwine.org/wineries

There's quite a few in the triangle area.

Have any of you been to the wineries around here? If so, how was the experience. Can you recommend a good one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Total newbie here. Bought some wine to age. Are any of these any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 00:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this subreddit last weekend. Only then did I find out most of the wine I had been drinking was too young.

I bought a wine cooler for short term aging. I should have a cellar in my house in 3 or 4 years.

Anyway, here's what's currently in my cooler. Have you had any of these? What can I expect from them?  

* 2011 Philippine de Saint Cyrille Chateauneuf Du Pape Grande Reserve  
* 2010 Les Combes d'Arnevel Chateauneuf du Pape Arnaves  
* 2014 Domaine du Bouscat Les Portes de L'Am  
* 2010 Chteau Cabrires Chteauneuf-du-Pape.  
* 2010 Chteau Croix De Mission Montagne-St. milion.  
* 2012 La Fiarre du Pape Chteauneuf-du-Pape.  
* 2010 Domaine Giraud Chteauneuf-du-Pape Tradition.  
* 2010 Domaine des Romarins Ctes du Rhne Villages Signargues Xavier Fabre. 
* 2010 Xavier Chteauneuf-du-Pape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
