<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6817</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the deal with Jeff Sessions? Can you guys fill me in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't really heard anything about him besides the collective freakout on r/all, is he a good choice for AG?

He seems kind of... uptight?

It seems I have been accidentally getting some fake news so I don't know the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He raped everyone no matter how ugly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont be silly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the people kicking in doors of exploding buildings... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDNY is certified cucked, forbids firefighters from hanging pictures of Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got the impression there are *more* guests than we see, even if it costs $40,000 per day per guest, thats not nearly enough to sustain the operation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started watching and I have a burning question but dont want any spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont trust Google not to ruin this for me so I cant do my own research so here goes:

How do Guests know who is a Host and who is just really into role-playing? And is there anything stopping a Guest from going full-tard and attacking/raping other Guests like they do to Hosts? There other weapons available besides guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NEEDS MORE FLAGS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vast majority of israelis are machinegun toting psychos. Very few cucks there. 

They are so fuckin happy donald won </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only when they are super annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hear so much about how Jews always use the Holocaust card, but I never actually heard or saw a jew use it, just other people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not only did it drop that much, everyone else also went up lol. You took a double loss by holding it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is incorrect, the entire tech segment is sliding while everything else is on a bull run.

The reason is that cheap H1B visas are going to disappear and Amazon, Facebook and Google will need to rehire all the American STEM workers they laid off and Wall Street knows the margins will be thinner.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason is that cheap H1B visas are going to disappear and Amazon, Facebook and Google will need to rehire all the American STEM workers they laid off and Wall Street knows the margins will be thinner.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is incorrect, the entire tech segment is sliding while everything else is on a bull run. 

The reason is that cheap H1B visas are going to disappear and Amazon, Facebook and Google will need to rehire all the American STEM workers they laid off and Wall Street knows the margins will be thinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMZAONFACEBOOKGOOGLE Shares are starting to slide, everyone is anticipating thinner margins in light of H1B visas going away (AMZN lost $35 Billion!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods plz sticky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/wsexdrcvtfg FOUND THIS: We can get John Oliver deported. He broke U.S. Immigration Law. [Here's a picture with the PROOF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2007 John Oliver was working on the Daily Show. He had a visitor's visa at the time which allowed him to work.

BUT in 2007 there was a writer's strike, and John Oliver went out on strike AND even carried a union picket sign.

Here's a picture of him going on strike and illegally walking the picket line:

http://gothamist.com/2007/11/15/john_oliver_wri.php

Foreigner's are not allowed to participate in a union strike. In fact it's grounds for deportation. This is tantamount to voting while being a non-citizen.

The irony is... he came to the U.S. because it's more free than the U.K. when it comes to freedom of speech laws. Yet he is constantly toting the Democrat line when it comes to the restriction of free speech.

Let's get him out of here. At the very least this can keep him from getting citizenship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best integrity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 20:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that should read: how many knees will bend for Mr Trump


just sayin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rekt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wanna help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 05:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to say mane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook promises to double down on censorship after being blamed for Trumps win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI, if Obama or Trump make any changes to the laws surrounding marijuana, Bitcoin will take a massive hit (in the short term at least) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole appeal to the industry (as of today) is they wont need to hold so much cash. If banks are allowed to work with cannabis sellers, they have zero reason to use crypto of any kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you play with Identity Politics and Virtue Signalling, youre going to have a bad time kay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC to proceed with racially charged rezoning plan at 3 schools, angering all the white people who didnt vote for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> daaaaaaaamn son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 13:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHADILAY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least i didnt vote for a criminal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald told you it was rigged and you didn't listen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing if you are a law abiding citizen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kek  this one

Kek

Kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry bro, Lena Dunham is yours no matter what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GUYS!! IF BERNIE TAKES 106% OF CALIFORNIA, WE CAN STILL WIN IF SOME SUPERDELEGATES SPONTANEOUSLY COMBUST! LETS GET BACK TO FACEBANKING! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bush has a very important message to the legion of Trump supporters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies and Gentlemen of Reddit, I would like to introduce the 45th President of The United States of America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally thought of that in the shower 20 minutes ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artificial Intelligence systems dont need to be smart enough to be creative or emotional, they just need to hire focus groups to do it for them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats quite the hog on the pony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Match me! 

Remember those guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lg hg2 i believe, the poop ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is u/mooch315 still the Battery Guy in Chief around here? its been a while since i last visited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battery Safety Question, please let me know if this is safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys,

So i just decided to quit smoking *again* and I have two devices that have been sitting on my desk for the last 6 months without being used.

One of them is an Evic-VT with a built in battery, the other is a Dovpo Executive 5.0 with an 18650.

Both devices haven't been charged in months and they both claim that the batteries are about 100% fully charged.

My question is it is safe to use either device and if not, what do I do for the Evic-VT as it is not user replaceable.

thanks, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to gamble on Presidential Election? (Research purposes only!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
