<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3967</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 01:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to elaborate on why you recommend against the M50X? I was considering them myself. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 23:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any reason you chose these vs [Audio-Technica M50x](http://www.amazon.com/Audio-Technica-ATH-M50x-Professional-Monitor-Headphones/dp/B00HVLUR86)? I'm in the exact situation as you and looking for some headphones for work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear beanies on my commute to and from work if it's cold enough. In the office (or anywhere indoors), I take em off.

edit: Might as well recommend, in case you care. I like Neff beanies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty cool, the old trail is a legend! I'll have to try the new one though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's much easier now. Longer, but not as thigh-burning. I wonder if they still allow access to the old trail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the statue still there? I haven't been to that little park in a long time. Nice photo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck all! RemindMe! 2 days Donation for /r/millionairemakers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the jacket. Is it fairly lightweight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched this video on low bar squats last month: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QhVC_AnZYYM

The very beginning of the video (about 2 minutes in) helped me understand the lift a lot better than I did before. Might be something you can take away from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 06:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I removed my rear sway bar, as suggested from this sub. Haven't noticed a real change at all in the ride. I'd say just leave it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle: Rival Fitness, Capitol Hill. 4 squat cages. A set of olympic-style weights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 06:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine does this going forward, what could that narrow it down to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 22:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't try too hard to do an actual "wave". I'll throw up a "peace" or "shaka" if my arm is already out the window or on the steering wheel. I wouldn't take it personal if the other driver didn't respond. I did my part... haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought my older peers (mid-30s) were exaggerating about hangovers being worse as you get older. Boy, was I wrong... and I'm only 29! I had about 7 pints of IPA this past week and it took until dinner time to fully recover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update. Sure enough, it was the relay. Replaced them both and everything works! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 22:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet looking hood vents! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Amazon link to leaf springs](http://www.amazon.com/Rubicon-Express-RE1463-Leaf-Spring/dp/B006GJKFHW)

Was looking into getting these myself. It sucks... I honestly have been buying [this kit](http://www.rubiconexpress.com/Lift-Kits-Suspensions-Shocks/3-5-Inch-Super-Ride-Short-Arm-Lift-Kit-with-Rear-Leaf-Springs-No-Shocks.aspx?t_c=1 t_s=38 t_pt=3533 t_pn=R%2fERE6025) over time, each piece individually. I should have just saved up and been patient... bought it all at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Good call. I'll head over to Napa later this afternoon and get some new relays. I'll report back, thanks bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putco Harness - Headlights Won't Shut Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally got around to installing my [Putco harness](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B001P29X4G) to give the headlights a boost. However, I'm running into a strange issue. The headlights simply won't turn off.

I know that the fog wiring on [97+ XJs can cause highbeam issues](http://www.cherokeeforum.com/f67/putco-headlight-wire-harness-install-fail-147992/#post2005100), but I was wondering if anyone has any experience with this harness and this particular issue.

Thanks in advanced! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 07:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3" lift with 30s. Thanks! I would like some 31s on there though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, this was around the Snoqualmie area this morning. Great day to be out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have someone tap the starter while cranking the key. Or, if you're alone, hit the starter somewhat lightly with a hammer, then try cranking. If it starts (or even cranks), replace the starter. Had this same problem awhile ago and thought it was the battery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploring more forest roads and hiking trails in the PNW! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. Extremely helpful. I guess I'll do the t-case drop until I can afford the SYE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 06:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I feel your pain. Been debating this modification myself lately. I'll probably end up doing it myself, and taking an entire week to do it because it's literally the first and only car I've every done any type of work on (aside from oil changes).

But hell, it's why I bought the rig. I wanted to learn how to work on cars. My dad kept our 1991 Ford Ranger running to this day, and I always told myself I'd learn how to do the same.

 I'll just have to pull up my sleeves and get it done

That's the XJ way, man. It fucking sucks sometimes, but you gotta break some bolts and fingers to keep her running smooth. Keep us posted and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 98 XJ Sport - Extended rear driveshaft? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 05:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting some gnarly driveline vibrations on the freeway and I'm trying to alleviate the situation without breaking my wallet. I know I can do a t-case drop (which I already have purchased), but I found an ad on craigslist for a guy selling an extended driveshaft. I believe it's a non-SYE shaft that's 1" longer than my stock one.

Would this work to help those vibrations? Anyone have experience simply extending the driveshaft vs installing an SYE or t-case drop?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gray, natural state of the Oregon Coast - Highway 101 [OC] [2144 x 1256] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 19:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 18:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ack... might be something for the mechanic to do... I'll do some research though. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I'm considering this for my next wrenching day. Is it difficult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gray, natural state of the Oregon Coast - Highway 101 [OC] [2144 x 1256] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 07:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoying the view somewhere off the Pacific Coast Highway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 07:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seafoam, IAC cleaned, Oil change... Ready for the road trip! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 00:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope to get there soon. Going on a road trip next week, hopefully she stays alive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 03:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting this! This has been bothering me. Here's a video of the exact problem I'm having. Just want to confirm that this is what you are referring to as well:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nFffZ36Pj0Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> San Franisco via 101 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm considering taking my wife's vehicle, but I'd be missing the "throw it in the Jeep and go" feeling I was hoping for. However, if I'm super uncomfortable with the state of the Jeep, I won't push it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good. I was thinking of swapping out the alternator, just as a precaution. I'm hesitant, though, as I don't want to make any major changes to the vehicle right before I leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 01:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestions. I'll bring a good amount of tools, spare fluids, and my AAA card for the rest. Will definitely look into the book. Any other podcasts/books you want to recommend, I'm all ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 00:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can think of 4.5 million reasons most people wouldn't "just say no". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there have been times where the size of my nipples and the size of my penis have swapped places

I am going to pocket and use this awesome phrase. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 22:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look! I'll have just ONE peanut butter filled pretzel bite and- they're all gone. Cool, hit TDEE in about 10 minutes there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know one teacher in Federal Way who works through summer. He may not get 3 whole months off, but he definitely gets more time off than me or anyone I work with. That said, I still think teachers are very underpaid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair. I'd take those hours into account in making the comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not 3 months, it's less. However, in the comparison above, if you're going to compare *annual* salaries, it's only fair to compare the number of actual days worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I was trying to figure out in this comparison. The only fair way to compare the two annual salaries is to break them down into work hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these credentials absolutely required for them to do the job? It ~~seems~~ **is** unfair to make teachers pay for anything like that out of pocket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this comparison consider the 3 months of summer that teachers get off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> XJ Road Trip Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning a 2000mi (3220km) road trip in my XJ from WA to CA. My '98 Sport has about 190k miles, fairly well-maintained since I've owned it (about 3 years).

Has anyone taken their XJ on a road trip of similar length? If so, what precautions should I take? Or should I just consider taking a different vehicle?

Recently done:

  * replaced all fluids (tranny and t-case, coolant, oil)
  * brakes
  * water pump, t-stat
  * starter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My knee got injured diving for a ball in a flag football game last Thursday. I think my knee-cap is bruised and it hurts to bend, bear weight on it. So, not only will I NOT be able to play football this week, I won't be able to deadlift or squat.

However, I'm gonna work my calves until I cry to make up for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm lifted about 3.5". She's shorter than I am, so she struggles to climb in. It's no big deal, but a little help wouldn't hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 18:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, what kind of "steps" do you have along the side? Were they hard to install? I'm asking because my wife has a hard time hopping into my XJ, and was thinking of picking up a set of those she can use as a step. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 20:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also the most practical, "real-life" way to apply OOP principles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stereo head unit adapter/mount flimsy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 23:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed a new stereo a couple of years ago and used this adapter to mount it:

http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00029X1O6

The stereo fits, but it wiggles around quite a bit. Sometimes, the antenna will get disconnected because of how flimsy it is. Can anyone offer a better solution? Tips on keeping things stable?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to get this cranberry turkey panini from Petosa's before it closed. I have yet to find another as delicious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, going to the gym is a given. I wake up, go to work, go to the gym, and go home to my wife. It's like a job, you can't just skip a day of work to hang out. Over the past couple of months, friends would often invite me out for a bite or drink at the bar. Most of the time, I respectfully say, "I can't make it, I have to go to the gym."

All of a sudden, I'm the prick who doesn't want to hang out with them. I'm the guy who can't seem to "miss one day at the gym to catch up with friends." Then, when I do find time to hang out with them, and I decline an offer for a drink or fry (watching macros), someone exclaims, "Boooooo, party foul! What's the point of coming out?!?!" Fine, I get it. It's common for a couple of friends to be gainz killers. This isn't new.

However, I got to go on vacation with my friends not too long ago. I'm in the best fucking shape in my life. Like, I am excited to take my shirt off at the pool and show off the work. And when I do, all I hear is, "Man, I sure wish I had your metabolism and genetics..."

I nearly lost my shit. It wasn't my metabolism and genetics! It's the hard work I put in while y'all were drinking beer and eating tater tots every god damn Friday at the bar! Fucking, damn it I need new friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Group of friends with a joint financial goal. Considering opening a joint savings account. Any thoughts/tips/considerations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 22:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings, PF. A close group of friends of mine want to start regularly saving money for a huge trip we plan to take in the next 2 years. Someone suggested starting a joint savings account we could contribute to, earn a bit of interest on, and cash out later. While it sounds simple, I'm wondering if there are "gotchas" we could be missing in this approach.

Has anyone ever tried something like this with friends?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 05:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to Carpinito's instead to prep for yard work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're Jeep might be broken if it isn't leaking oil... /s

haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 18:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the answer OP, just get rid of it. It is hardly noticeable on road and fairly advantageous offroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 19:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two main reasons:

It's right next to my apartment.

It has 4 squat racks. That's more squat racks than two of the 24 Hour Fitnesses within a 10 mile radius, combined.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, this needs to be framed and hung up in every XJers garage with some deep quote about "perseverance" and "struggle"... LOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the story is in the conversation. The story is in the subtleties and interactions between the characters. It's in the way they look at each other and how they say certain things and what's happening in the background. It's not an in-your-face action movie by any means.

Which is why the Godfather II is actually my favorite movie of all time. It's the fall of the Corleone family (which really begins in the first movie) intertwined with its rise. No other movie has gotten me to fall in love with the characters the way the Godfather I and II have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 00:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many "diets" that you can do, but I prefer to keep it as simple as possible, especially at 17... Eat whatever you want, just hit your macros and stay at the deficit you want (700 cals). Sounds like you already have an idea of what to eat, you'll pick up more food ideas as you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what the policies are nowadays, but I was able to bring a suit onboard along with my carry-on and hang it up (there was a special place to hang things). This was for an international flight from Seattle - Germany for a wedding.

If they give you trouble, the best you can do is fold it up and stick it under the seat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This, OP. Track and eat less. Don't try to manipulate using fat-burners, manipulate what you eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the FAQ:

https://www.reddit.com/r/Seattle/comments/25w1k7/list_of_mustsee_summer_eventsfairs_in_seattle_and/
https://www.reddit.com/r/Seattle/comments/26h5ia/things_to_do_in_seattle_for_people_who_have/

As for hikes, I recommend viewing the latest trip reports on WTA: http://www.wta.org/go-hiking/trip-reports </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I want to lose weight and gain some muscle

It seems like fitness is your primary goal. Crossfit will help you achieve your goals faster than MMA.

You'll get many different opinions on this, but my view is that you join an MMA gym to learn how to fight, fitness is just the side-effect.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop humble bragging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 00:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hard was it to install those fogs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm.. which Uniqlo OCBD would you pair with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working out hungover hurts, but is better than getting no workout in. The only thing I'd be worried about is an increased risk of injury due to laziness. If you're unable to keep your form (assuming you are de-loading due to the hangover), then just stay at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 19:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of Charles Tyrwhitt, thanks for the recommendation! I'll check out Banana Republic after work today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of the usual terriyaki chicken breast and brown rice, I'm gonna do fried chicken breast and rice! Nom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how appropriate this is, but I'm going to a bachelor party next weekend and was wondering about "gentleman's" club attire. Any advice/opinions and what to wear to something like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my wife and I were thinking of moving into an affordable apartment in that area while we recover from some financial issues. I wonder what this will do to the rents there. Good to see another company come into Seattle though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out throwback Golden Tate, #81 jersey! -_-

http://imgur.com/WqOjAXZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at the most minimal pre-workout stack to replace my C4. I notice that the C4 gives me this feeling that my muscles are filling up with air (that pump!) and I want a supplement that will provide the same feeling.

Also, is there any other source of a quick shot of caffeine other than pills and coffee that you guys/gals like to use for the "high" that C4 gives?

Thanks /r/fitness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best frugal dress shirts for the money? I'm looking at around $30 to $40. I just purchased a $23 Merona shirt from Target that fits nicely. We'll see how long it holds up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally killed my own personal student loans! Now, we are working on paying off my wife's student loans by our 1 year anniversary in October. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highschool football taught me everything about motivation and discipline, in addition to all that stuff about teamwork. Athletics, to this day, has a huge impact on my health and fitness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 17:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will binge on Taco Del Mar about twice a month, and I'll have a mad stomach ache the next day. But damn if I ever stop binging on my mondo fish burrito!

To answer your question: yes for me. When I eat bad, I physically (and sometimes mentally) feel bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion! I'll probably just do a purple or blue gingham type of shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop telling me you wish you had my metabolism and good genes. What you wish you had is my discipline and dedication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 20:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking about Vegas nightclub attire, yet again! I have some grey (lightish) and navy pants. Looking for two dress shirts I could pair with them that would look nice at various nightclubs in Vegas next week. 

At this point, I'll take absolutely any recommendations at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here looking for this reference! Ah, the days of shareware... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 21:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any thoughts on some swimming trunks for dark-skinned folks? I'm thinking lighter colors? Yellow perhaps?

Also, what are some dress shirt patterns I could wear without a tie that doesn't scream "business"? I would be wearing it to a night event, kind of like a club, but a bit nicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 07:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorites from the Omakase at the main sushi bar. Salmon with sweet, white onion. Red snapper with special plum sauce. I'm no sushi connoisseur, but it's the best sushi I've ever had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salmon and Red Snapper Nigiri at Shiro's Sushi in Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 07:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 17:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that much self control. It isn't that hard to cont- oh shit Gap sale until noon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 06:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've got those awesome desks we can crank up and down. Really nice for staying awake in the office too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I'm going to Vegas in a couple of weeks. Any tips or recommendations on some outfits to wear out at night? I was thinking of doing gray slacks and a white shirt + tie, but I'm open to anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 20:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niiiiiice! Except for the Patriots blanket... I kid, but not really I hate the Patriots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 17:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my buddies who keep telling me to track my workouts on MFP. Stop telling me to track my workouts on MFP. 

No, you did not burn 659 calories doing "General Exercise" for 30 minutes. You're delusional if you think you are. I'll calculate my TDEE on IIFYM.com, track my food, eat at deficit, and continue to look better.

Thanks /r/fitness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~90k

98 Jeep Cherokee XJ

90% of the time, bus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to live on the top of Queen Anne, just up the street from the university. My car got the gas siphoned out of it and the entire side scratched up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice! I like how simple and clean it looks. Good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 22:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dana 44s in front and rear? Dayum... I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 17:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very helpful! Thanks for sharing your process. Usually, I just randomly look up apartments on Craigslist based on the cost of rent. Taking a more methodical approach would probably eliminate some of the annoyances I discover *after* I sign the lease and move into a place... haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. What if I pick just one of the items to build around? How about the grey pants? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see DIS mentioned in here multiple times. I don't completely understand the business or it's long-term strategy, but can someone give me a quick elevator pitch on the business? And the stock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to Vegas for a weekend in April. I'd like to wear a purple button down with some light grey pants. I'd like some kind of vest also. Any recommendations on some ties that would go well? Also, a type of vest that would look nice with the light grey and purple? I'm pretty dark-skinned, if that matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also lost some weight (34W to a 32W). Decided to buy some pants from Old Navy. I'll probably go back and get their shorts as well. Gap is probably my new go-to for jeans and shorts as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 20:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sick of people thinking that their "way" or "method" of dieting is the way I should do it, despite the leaps and bounds of progress I've made over them.

"You should incorporate more [hippy food] instead of [normal food] into your diet."

I'm sorry that I enjoy the taste of rice over quinoa while saving money in the process. It fits my macros, I'm eating it.

"Back squats are bad for you. You should stop doing them."

No, back squats are bad FOR YOU. Just because you have terrible form does not mean I have terrible form.

"A slice of cheesecake won't hurt your progress that much! Come on, you're being a douche!"

To quote Jay Z, "what I eat don't make you shit." I don't want cheesecake, for christ's sake. Just because your fat ass doesn't have any self control doesn't mean I have to give in to temptation. 

Alright, I'm done. Thanks /r/fitness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 20:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alki or the waterfront. I like squidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 19:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow PNW XJer here. I've seen SO many stock XJs just beaming with potential! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always posted in these kind of threads: https://www.t-nation.com/diet-fat-loss/lifters-guide-to-alcohol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 20:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, I can only imagine what this was like. I had a hell of a time replacing my damn water pump for the first time... with all the right tools available... hahaha! Props to you man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah interesting. I didn't know about that rule. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just starting to even remotely care about mobility. I'd like to increase mobility in every part of my body, obviously, but what are the big ones I should focus on while getting started? Which would bring the most benefits to lifting weights (I do a basic-bitch 3x /wk PPL) and flag football?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 18:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To piggyback off of this, when I'm idle after running for awhile (warmed up), my oil pressure sits around 8-10... Is that too low? The "check-engine" light doesn't come on, but I heard the oil pressure should be  15 at idle, hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 21:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man! Nice Jeep! Looks like mine when it was stock. 98 XJ here, givin' a wave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
