<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1203</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 15:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding partying, don't you think it depends on age and family status as well? As I got "older", turning 39 soon, I am not into partying at all, i rather spend the next day with my kids than with a hangover.
Thanks for the comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 15:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) That is funny. How much time do you spend on reddit per day?
Thanks for the comment by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 15:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably yes. But I think at least most people have to prioritize. Thanks for commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 15:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is a good pick! Thanks for commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you! We kind of need all five! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) That is true as well. Which one did you pick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Work, Sleep, Family, Fitness, or Friends: Pick 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 03:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randi Zuckerberg, sister of Mark Zuckerberg, calls this the entrepreneur's dilemma. Basically what she says is that a person can choose only three out of these listed five things, and the other two have to be sacrificed. She says she sacrificed friends and fitness. Does it ring true for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do think of the movie 'Son of Saul'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show Reddit: These are my illustrated designs for life and inspirational quotes from well known people. I appreciate your feedback. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I guess most of us are like that. I have read it somewhere that on Facebook, most people just check others' photos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that is a good point, what is considered a social network? I guess reddit is not one in that sense the question was raised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many hours a week are you on social networks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This study shows why facebook is causing depression for many. What's your intake on this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered how these are created. What keyboard function is this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually interesting that early communications were all pictograms and now the trend is going back to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you can kind of describe that with the current available emojis already. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. When I go shopping, I always use a paper note. Never even considered an app for that. Wonder how successful that app is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never played with it. I will give it a shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) It would be useful when your phone's battery dies you at least have candle light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did you manage to buy any buildings then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that is creepy then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virtual kitties? WTF? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 15:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on what I have heard, even though I never used it, it is an app that can bring good results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
