<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3445</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what my son built for me in his world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 21:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Washington, D.C., police officer was arrested in Annapolis Thursday night after an employee at a downtown restaurant said the officer assaulted him, Annapolis police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 21:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former Hastings police officer was behind bars Friday morning after using a GoFundMe page to raise money for medical bills he didn't have. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 21:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the compliment. 

My 9-year-old said, "I built it, so it isn't fake."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what my son built for me in his world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what my son built for me in his world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX founder Elon Musk tweeted a video Thursday of the company's rocket crashing a day earlier as it attempted to land on an ocean barge in the Atlantic Ocean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the concern; however, I was parked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conclusion: The efficacy of caffeine for maintaining alertness and performance waned across 3+ days of sleep restriction. The extent of this decline as a function of the (possibly interactive) effect of mounting sleep debt and high cognitive load remains to be determined.

http://www.sleepmeeting.org/docs/default-source/default-document-library/sleep-39-as_final.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caffeine has little to no benefit after 3 nights of sleep restriction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally feel you on this. I could take baby steps towards the completion of several things, but then those babies never grow up when I don't take the next step in raising it into something sustainable (the goal). A big issue comes if I aim towards completing a goal so much and give less attention to an already established source of income; then I have to stop my "passion project," and I forget about it until I get my main source of income on track again. By then I'm typically frustrated with the main source of income again, and have to start anew with my passion project. You start a little rusty, and it feels almost like you're starting from scratch. 

This is where rules like keeping your expenses down work real well. Which why I think it's easier at times for kids to really master whatever they want to do before worrying about paying bills with it. Kids can spend practically all their time mastering something if they live with parents who cover housing, clothing, food expenses, etc. But as an adult, as long as you can cover your expenses, you could still accomplish goals that you like working towards. So they key is keeping them down as much as possible and / or learning how to make money to cover your expenses with a very little resource and time requirement. 

The other thing is to also figure out a way to generate revenue from something you like even if you haven't mastered it yet to completely do it like you want to do it. Perhaps by helping other people do what you want to do by teaching them what you know. You'll always find people who know less than you about a certain subject. Teaching is also a great way for you to master your craft, for it helps you learn it quicker.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The driver side view of my Toyota Sienna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.J. Assembly passes bill approving marijuana for PTSD treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey Assembly passes bill approving marijuana for PTSD treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NJ Assembly Passes Bill Allowing Medical Marijuana Use For PTSD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.J. lawmakers vote to allow medical marijuana for PTSD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background:

Little is known of the association between nut consumption, and prostate cancer (PCa) incidence and survivorship.

Methods:

We conducted an incidence analysis and a case-only survival analysis in the Health Professionals Follow-up Study on the associations of nut consumption (updated every 4 years) with PCa diagnosis, and PCa-specific and overall mortality.

Results:

In 26 years, 6810 incident PCa cases were identified from 47299 men. There was no association between nut consumption and being diagnosed with PCa or PCa-specific mortality. However, patients who consumed nuts five or more times per week after diagnosis had a significant 34% lower rate of overall mortality than those who consumed nuts less than once per month (HR=0.66, 95% CI: 0.520.83, P-trend=0.0005).

Conclusions:

There were no statistically significant associations between nut consumption, and PCa incidence or PCa-specific mortality. Frequent nut consumption after diagnosis was associated with significantly reduced overall mortality.

http://www.nature.com/bjc/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/bjc2016181a.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating Nuts Daily Can Reduce Prostate Cancer Death Risk, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oakland PDs history of misconduct  involving African-Americans  made it the subject of federal oversight for 13 years. Wednesday, Stanford researchers released the results of a two-year-long study, confirming that Oakland officers exhibit significant racial biases in their day-to-day work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanford Study Finds Oakland Cops Practicing Racial Profiling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] This quote is starting to help me deal with Something with which I've struggled most of my life... Focusing one thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honda recalls 1M cars in China for air bag problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Birmingham police officer was arrested today after authorities say he used pepper spray on another officer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] The complete guide to never quitting anything again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The complete guide to never quitting anything again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the plan, friend. Get him to do the work that makes the win easy. Thanks for the encouragement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally understand your concern. I would never let him solely game day in and day out, for he'll probably be gaming in my house until he's 50 if I let that happen.

He's "always" gaming during his free time (that's time he gets after homework, chores, exercise, shooting practice, and trick shots are done). If all of the above doesn't get done, then no gaming is allowed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 17:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidently, the researchers weren't part of the sample group of people who bought and smoked the product. If they would have lit up they would have pulled the numbers before the blunt turned into a roach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny; I just a read a few other stories labeling 4/20 as a marijuana's Black Friday. Perhaps *Green Friday*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for viewing. I totally get it, man. Our lesson from this was to try to identify what way of shooting the ball almost worked and make adjustments on power and throwing angles. So for anything in life, I think if you analyze what almost worked, and make a slight adjustment on your next try, you get closer to reaching your objective. I also had him mentally visualize getting the ball in the hoop. I really think that clear focus on the goal also gave him different ideas on how to get it done.

Edit: Just want to say, keep seeing the end result, and you'll get there! Forward! And thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legal Marijuana Sales Hit a Record on 4/20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you; means a lot. He almost gave up a few times, but I managed to convince him to hang in there until he made it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana 4/20 Sales Set Record In Washington, Colorado As Cannabis Retail Surges From Legalization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana sales on 4/20 hit record highs In Colorado, retail sales were up 53% year-over-year, reaching $7.3 million, breaking the previous daily record of $6.1 million set on September 16 In Washington, the $5.5 million in sales on April 20 was double the amount of sales on that day in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legal recreational marijuana works in Colorado and can succeed in N.J.: lawmaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Nicholas Scutari, D-Union, didnt try the product. But hes more convinced than before that New Jersey should legalize pot after experiencing how legalization has positively impacted Colorados economy, tax revenues and crime rates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] After about 50 tries, my 9 year old son (who's always gaming) Made his first basketball trick shot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 9 year old son (who's always gaming) tried 50 times until he got in his first basketball trick shot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 14:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 14:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract

BackgroundCurrent findings on associations between whole grain (WG) intake and mortality are inconsistent and have not been summarized by meta-analysis.

Methods and ResultsWe searched for prospective cohort studies reporting associations between WG intake and mortality from all causes, cardiovascular disease (CVD), and cancer through February 2016 in Medline, Embase, and clinicaltrials.gov, and we further included unpublished results from National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES) III and NHANES 1999 to 2004. Fourteen studies were eligible for analysis, which included 786 076 participants, 97 867 total deaths, 23 957 CVD deaths, and 37 492 cancer deaths. Pooled relative risks comparing extreme WG categories (high versus low) were 0.84 (95% confidence interval [CI], 0.800.88; P0.001; I2=74%; Pheterogeneity0.001) for total mortality, 0.82 (95% CI, 0.790.85; P0.001; I2=0%; Pheterogeneity=0.53) for CVD mortality, and 0.88 (95% CI, 0.830.94; P0.001; I2=54%; Pheterogeneity=0.02) for cancer mortality. Intakes of WG ingredients in dry weight were estimated among studies reporting relative risks for 3 quantitative WG categories, and they were 50 g/d among most study populations. The 2-stage dose-response random-effects meta-analysis showed monotonic associations between WG intake and mortality (Pnonlinearity0.05). For each 16-g/d increase in WG (1 serving per d), relative risks of total, CVD, and cancer mortality were 0.93 (95% CI, 0.920.94; P0.001), 0.91 (95% CI, 0.900.93; P0.001), and 0.95 (95% CI, 0.940.96; P0.001), respectively.

ConclusionsOur meta-analysis demonstrated inverse associations of WG intake with total and cause-specific mortality, and findings were particularly strong and robust for CVD mortality. These findings further support current Dietary Guidelines for Americans, which recommends at least 3 servings per day of WG intake.

http://circ.ahajournals.org/content/133/24/2370.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating more whole grains could help you live longer, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 14:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities Arrest Another Cop in Underage Sex Sting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 01:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In sex sting, police pose as 15-year-old on Craigslist  and nab another cop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 01:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman gets flu shot and then claims she can only walk backwards, develops weird accent, caught fully recovered, then walks sideways, busted as a con </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have performed the first trials of a 'universal cancer vaccine' It's really happening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former co-worker says Orlando gunman was 'unhinged and unstable', went on racist, misogynistic rants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On one occasion, Gilroy said, Mateen told him, "I would just like to kill all those [n-words]" after a conversation between Mateen and a black man. "A few times he mentioned homosexuals and Jewish people," Gilroy said, "but we didn't deal with them quite as often, so it was mostly women and blacks, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orlando Shooter's Father Posted Facebook Video Saying "Only God Can Punish Homosexuality" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-coworker says employer would not fire unhinged Orlando terrorist because he was Muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Citigroup trademarks THANKYOU and sues AT T for thanking clients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens who vape more likely to try regular cigarettes, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vaping teens more apt to move on to regular cigarettes: U.S. study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Results

E-cigarette users and never users were similar on matching factors (gender, ethnicity, grade) and parental education. In adjusted models males were more likely to initiate cigarette use (OR = 1.84; 95% CI: 1.043.26; Table 1). Adolescents who were classified as susceptible to cigarette use were more likely to report e-cigarette use at initial evaluation (OR = 2.48; 95% CI: 1.444.27) and to report cigarette use at follow-up (OR = 3.03; 95% CI: 1.715.39). Having one or more friends who smoked combustible tobacco products also increased the likelihood of e-cigarette use at initial evaluation (OR = 2.61; 95% CI: 1.355.06) and cigarette use at follow-up (OR = 2.58; 95% CI: 1.305.09); having friends who were friendly to cigarette use was associated with e-cigarette use at initial evaluation (OR = 2.13; 95% CI: 1.243.65) but not with cigarette use at follow-up. The median age of participants at initial evaluation was 17.4 years (interquartile range [IQR]: 16.817.9); median age at follow-up was 18.6 years (IQR: 18.319.0 years); median time from initial evaluation to follow-up was 15.6 months (IQR: 12.618.2 months).

TABLE 1
Demographic Characteristics of Participants by E-Cigarette Use at Initial Assessment and by Cigarette Use at Follow-up, N = 298

To assess the potential for selection bias, we compared sociodemographic characteristics of study participants for whom follow-up data were obtained with those lost to follow-up. Participants from whom follow-up data were collected were more likely to have a parent with at least a college education (Supplemental Table 5). No notable differences in gender, ethnicity, grade, or susceptibility to cigarette use were observed between retained participants and those lost to follow up.

Among never e-cigarette users at initial evaluation, 16 (10.5%) reported use of cigarettes at follow-up; among ever e-cigarette users at the initial evaluation, 59 (40.4%) reported use of cigarettes at follow-up (Table 2). The adjusted OR for the association of e-cigarette use with subsequent smoking of combustible cigarettes was 6.17 (95% CI: 3.3011.6). After further adjustment for cigar, pipe, or hookah use at initial evaluation, the association of e-cigarette use with subsequent smoking was slightly attenuated but still statistically significant (OR = 5.48; 95% CI: 2.6911.2). Results did not differ appreciably after additional adjustment for social environment characteristics at initial evaluation (whether others in the home smoked, number of friends who smoked, friends attitudes toward smoking), age at initial evaluation, age at follow-up, or time in months from initial evaluation to follow-up (results not shown). E-cigarette users had 5.49 times (95% CI: 2.6811.2) the odds of initiating cigarette smoking but not having smoked in the past 30 days, and 7.50 times (95% CI: 2.4123.4) the odds of reporting use of cigarettes in the past 30 days at follow-up compared with never e-cigarette users. Estimates were based on 39 (27.1%) initiators and 18 (12.5%) past 30-day cigarette users among e-cigarette users at baseline, compared with 12 (7.9%) initiators and 4 (2.6%) past 30-day cigarette users among never e-cigarette users at baseline; 2 participants reported initiation of smoking but did not report the number of days smoked in the past 30 days (results not tabulated).


Association Between E-Cigarette Use at Initial Assessment in 2014 and Subsequent Cigarette Use at Follow-up in 2015

Among adolescents who were not classified as susceptible to cigarette use at initial evaluation, 36.2% (n = 34) of e-cigarette users and 5.7% (n = 7) of never e-cigarette users reported initiation of cigarettes at follow up (ORnot susceptible = 9.69; 95% CI: 4.0223.4; Table 3). In contrast, among those who were classified as susceptible to smoking at initial evaluation, e-cigarette users were only slightly more likely to initiate cigarette use at follow-up (47.1% v. 32.1%; ORsusceptible = 2.12; 95% CI: 0.79, 5.74; interaction P = .03). We also examined interactions of e-cigarette use at initial evaluation with gender, ethnicity, grade level, time from initial contact to completion of follow-up questionnaire, and use of hookah at initial evaluation. The risk of initiation of cigarette use associated with e-cigarettes did not differ by these characteristics.

Association Between E-Cigarette Use at Initial Assessment in 2014 and Subsequent Cigarette Use at Follow-up in 2015 by Indication of Susceptibility to Smoking at Initial Evaluation

In an analysis restricted to those who reported no use of any combustible tobacco product at initial evaluation, e-cigarette users were also more likely to initiate use of any combustible tobacco product at follow-up (OR = 4.98; 95% CI: 2.3710.4; Table 4) and to initiate use of cigarettes (OR = 4.29; 95% CI: 1.8410.0), hookah (OR = 2.86; 95% CI: 1.216.78), cigars (OR = 4.39; 95% CI: 1.7211.2), and pipes (OR = 8.21; 95% CI: 1.2056.2).

Association Between E-Cigarette Use at Initial Assessment in 2014 and Subsequent Cigarette Use at Follow-up in 2015, Restricted to Never Users of Any Combustible Tobacco Product
http://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/2016/06/10/peds.2016-0379 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens in the United States who use electronic cigarettes are six times more likely to move on to traditional cigarettes compared to kids who never use the devices, a new study reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrests of 3 Grand Isle officers leave troubled department with just 3 to police town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for seeing it the first time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Correctional Officer from Wakulla County was arrested Thursday night after the Department of Corrections says she brought tobacco and marijuana into the county correctional institution. Roath also admitted to some kind of sexual misconduct as well but details on that incident were redacted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wrote and memorized this Eminem "Rap God" Parody a few hours each month since February; here's "Dad God." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most antidepressants don't work for young patients, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 14:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 14:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary
Background
Major depressive disorder is one of the most common mental disorders in children and adolescents. However, whether to use pharmacological interventions in this population and which drug should be preferred are still matters of controversy. Consequently, we aimed to compare and rank antidepressants and placebo for major depressive disorder in young people.

Methods
We did a network meta-analysis to identify both direct and indirect evidence from relevant trials. We searched PubMed, the Cochrane Library, Web of Science, Embase, CINAHL, PsycINFO, LiLACS, regulatory agencies' websites, and international registers for published and unpublished, double-blind randomised controlled trials up to May 31, 2015, for the acute treatment of major depressive disorder in children and adolescents. We included trials of amitriptyline, citalopram, clomipramine, desipramine, duloxetine, escitalopram, fluoxetine, imipramine, mirtazapine, nefazodone, nortriptyline, paroxetine, sertraline, and venlafaxine. Trials recruiting participants with treatment-resistant depression, treatment duration of less than 4 weeks, or an overall sample size of less than ten patients were excluded. We extracted the relevant information from the published reports with a predefined data extraction sheet, and assessed the risk of bias with the Cochrane risk of bias tool. The primary outcomes were efficacy (change in depressive symptoms) and tolerability (discontinuations due to adverse events). We did pair-wise meta-analyses using the random-effects model and then did a random-effects network meta-analysis within a Bayesian framework. We assessed the quality of evidence contributing to each network estimate using the GRADE framework. This study is registered with PROSPERO, number CRD42015016023.

Findings
We deemed 34 trials eligible, including 5260 participants and 14 antidepressant treatments. The quality of evidence was rated as very low in most comparisons. For efficacy, only fluoxetine was statistically significantly more effective than placebo (standardised mean difference 051, 95% credible interval [CrI] 099 to 003). In terms of tolerability, fluoxetine was also better than duloxetine (odds ratio [OR] 031, 95% CrI 013 to 095) and imipramine (023, 004 to 078). Patients given imipramine, venlafaxine, and duloxetine had more discontinuations due to adverse events than did those given placebo (549, 196 to 2086; 319, 101 to 1870; and 280, 120 to 942, respectively). In terms of heterogeneity, the global I2 values were 3321% for efficacy and 0% for tolerability.

Interpretation
When considering the riskbenefit profile of antidepressants in the acute treatment of major depressive disorder, these drugs do not seem to offer a clear advantage for children and adolescents. Fluoxetine is probably the best option to consider when a pharmacological treatment is indicated.

Funding
National Basic Research Program of China (973 Program).

http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16)30385-3/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most antidepressants ineffective in teens, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 14:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a recent report, the International Monetary Fund estimated that the Panama Canal expansion will reduce global maritime shipping costs by $8 billion a year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says he visited the Pentagon to talk about a 'flying metal suit' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says he visited the Pentagon to talk about a 'flying metal suit' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Musicians popular with teens endorse mostly junk food, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 17:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The vast majority of foods and beverages endorsed by Justin Timberlake, Beyonc, Taylor Swift and dozens of other pop musicians are high in calories and low in nutrition, according to a study published in the June issue of the journal Pediatrics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 16:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 16:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract

BACKGROUND: Food and beverage marketing has been associated with childhood obesity. We quantified the number and type of food or beverage brands promoted by music celebrities, assessed the nutritional quality of the products, and examined Teen Choice Award data to assess the celebrities popularity among adolescents.

METHODS: This was a descriptive study. A list of music celebrities associated with the 2013 and 2014 Billboard Hot 100 Chart, which ranks songs according to sales and radio impressions, was compiled. Data on celebrity endorsements were gathered from official company Web sites, YouTube commercials, an advertising database, and media reports. Nutritional quality of foods was assessed according to the Nutrient Profile Index, whereas nonalcoholic beverages were evaluated based on calories from added sugar. Teen Choice Award nominations were used to measure the celebrities popularity among adolescents.

RESULTS: Of the 590 endorsements made by the 163 celebrities in the sample, consumer goods (eg, fragrances, makeup) represented the largest endorsement category (26%), followed by food and beverage (18%) and retail (11%). Sixty-five celebrities were collectively associated with 57 different food and beverage brands owned by 38 parent companies. Of these 65 celebrities, 53 (81.5%) had 1 Teen Choice Award nomination. Forty-nine (71%) of the 69 nonalcoholic beverage references promoted sugar-sweetened beverages. Twenty-one (80.8%) of the 26 endorsed foods were energy dense and nutrient poor. Baauer, will.i.am, Justin Timberlake, Maroon 5, and Britney Spears had the most food and beverage endorsements.

CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that music celebrities who are popular among adolescents endorse energy-dense, nutrient-poor products.

http://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/2016/06/02/peds.2015-3977 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly every food or beverage endorsed by musicians who scored a hit in the Billboard Hot 100 Chart in the years 2013 and 2014 is unhealthy, the study found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 16:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Lampley Cries Over Muhammad Ali Death, Shares Touching Memories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 16:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog with enormous neck wound crawling with maggots is healed and makes epic recovery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 16:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit Police Department - Running Man Challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 15:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy guy tries to attack police with a hatchet and he gets tazed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 15:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Rikers Officers Convicted in Beating of Inmate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 11:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Losing Her Baby, Mom Donates Breast Milk To Her Friend's Adopted Daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 03:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fair Wage Proponent Ted Strickland Promotes Unpaid Positions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 03:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Passes Bill that Allows Medical Marijuana Use at Schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 23:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schools in Colorado will be required to allow medical marijuana after Gov. John Hickenlooper signed Jacks Law on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 23:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roots Ratings: 4.2 Million Watch Finale Of Miniseries Remake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 23:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents elated as Hickenlooper signs pot in schools bill Now, all of Colorado's 177 school districts will allow parents to send medical marijuana with their kids to school. The kids will be able to take those products on school grounds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New bill allows parents to send medical marijuana with their kids to school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I shut my kids up to film a weather lady erroneously telling people to watch Star Trek when Star Wars: The Force Awakens was to start showing the day after. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An off-duty NYPD police officer was accused of punching a 71-year-old woman after the two had an argument about her dog. The woman was transported to an area hospital with minor injuries, and Radionov has been charged with assault, according to ABC7. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HPD clears off-duty officers who shot naked patient in hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this originally on Alous Allo's Google Plus profile: https://plus.google.com/114464919971497431371/posts/intBmCz7gw3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robber Shot With His Own Gun During Struggle With Clerk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When two men decided to rob a McDonalds in eastern France they hadnt expected to come face to face with a table of hungry soldiers from an elite military force. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cited study concluded the following:

**Conclusions and Relevance** Cannabis use for up to 20 years is associated with periodontal disease but is not associated with other physical health problems in early midlife.
http://archpsyc.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2526003 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A long-term study of nearly 1,000 New Zealanders from birth to age 38 has found that people who smoked marijuana for up to 20 years have more gum disease, but otherwise do not show worse physical health than non-smokers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Importance  After major policy changes in the United States, policymakers, health care professionals, and the general public seek information about whether recreational cannabis use is associated with physical health problems later in life.

Objective  To test associations between cannabis use over 20 years and a variety of physical health indexes at early midlife.

Design, Setting, and Participants  Participants belonged to a representative birth cohort of 1037 individuals born in Dunedin, New Zealand, in 1972 and 1973 and followed to age 38 years, with 95% retention (the Dunedin Multidisciplinary Health and Development Study). We tested whether cannabis use from ages 18 to 38 years was associated with physical health at age 38, even after controlling for tobacco use, childhood health, and childhood socioeconomic status. We also tested whether cannabis use from ages 26 to 38 years was associated with within-individual health decline using the same measures of health at both ages.

Exposures  We assessed frequency of cannabis use and cannabis dependence at ages 18, 21, 26, 32, and 38 years.

Main Outcomes and Measures  We obtained laboratory measures of physical health (periodontal health, lung function, systemic inflammation, and metabolic health), as well as self-reported physical health, at ages 26 and 38 years.

Results  The 1037 study participants were 51.6% male (n = 535). Of these, 484 had ever used tobacco daily and 675 had ever used cannabis. Cannabis use was associated with poorer periodontal health at age 38 years and within-individual decline in periodontal health from ages 26 to 38 years. For example, cannabis joint-years from ages 18 to 38 years was associated with poorer periodontal health at age 38 years, even after controlling for tobacco pack-years ( = 0.12; 95% CI, 0.05-0.18; P .001). Additionally, cannabis joint-years from ages 26 to 38 years was associated with poorer periodontal health at age 38 years, even after accounting for periodontal health at age 26 years and tobacco pack-years ( = 0.10; 95% CI, 0.05-0.16; P .001) However, cannabis use was unrelated to other physical health problems. Unlike cannabis use, tobacco use was associated with worse lung function, systemic inflammation, and metabolic health at age 38 years, as well as within-individual decline in health from ages 26 to 38 years.

Conclusions and Relevance  Cannabis use for up to 20 years is associated with periodontal disease but is not associated with other physical health problems in early midlife.

http://archpsyc.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2526003 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle-age people who have smoked marijuana for many years may have a higher risk of developing gum disease, according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An off-duty cop punched a 71-year-old woman in the face during an argument over her dog in Brooklyn, according to police sources and the lady. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An off-duty NYPD police officer was arrested after allegedly punching a 71-year-old neighbor during a dispute over whether she could bring a dog into their Brooklyn apartment building. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Department of Justice announced Monday that South San Francisco-based Genentech Inc. and another drug company have agreed to pay $67 million to settle a federal lawsuit that alleged the two companies made misleading statements about a cancer drug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pharmaceutical companies Genentech and OSI Pharmaceuticals LLC will pay $67 million to resolve allegations they made misleading statements about the effectiveness of lung cancer drug Tarceva, the U.S. Justice Department said on Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French armed robbers hold up McDonalds full of elite police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burj Khalifa, Burj Al Arab and Jumeirah Beach Hotel shot from The Palm in Dubai by Marek Kijevsk [2000x1320] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 02:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer patient charged for medical marijuana use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 02:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix Adds Eddie Murphy To Roster For Fake Documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 02:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Bay casts Britains loneliest dog in Transformers 5 - Director offers film role and a new home to Freya, an epileptic Staffordshire bull terrier who has spent her life in an animal shelter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worlds Biggest Indoor Vertical Farm Near NYC to Use 95% Less Water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elementary school principal facing child porn charges had been reprimanded before. Agents said they found more than 1,100 child porn images on his computer, showing boys as young as 4 years old having sex with adult men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Febrile Seizures After Childhood Vaccines Are Rare, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Importance  Late-term gestation (defined as the 41st week of pregnancy) is associated with increased risk of perinatal health complications. It is not known to what extent late-term gestation is associated with long-term cognitive and physical outcomes. Information about long-term outcomes may influence physician and patient decisions regarding optimal pregnancy length.

Objective  To compare the cognitive and physical outcomes of school-aged children who were born full term or late term.

Design, Setting, and Participants  We analyzed Florida birth certificates from 1994 to 2002 linked to Florida public school records from 1998 to 2013 and found 1 442 590 singleton births with 37 to 41 weeks gestation in the Florida Bureau of Vital Statistics. Of these, 1 153 716 children (80.0%) were subsequently located in Florida public schools. Linear and logistic regression models were used to assess the association of gestational age with cognitive and physical outcomes at school age. Data analysis took place between April 2013 and January 2016.

Exposures  Late-term (born at 41 weeks) vs full-term (born at 39 or 40 weeks) gestation.

Main Outcomes and Measures  There were a number of measures used, including the average Florida Comprehensive Assessment Test mathematics and reading scores at ages 8 through 15 years; whether a child was classified as gifted, defined as a student with superior intellectual development and capable of high performance; poor cognitive outcome, defined as a child scoring in the fifth percentile of test takers or having a disability that exempted him or her from taking the Florida Comprehensive Assessment Test; and Exceptional Student Education placement owing to orthopedic, speech, or sensory impairment or being hospitalbound or homebound.

Results  Of 1 536 482 children born in Florida from singleton births from 1994 to 2002 with complete demographic information, 787 105 (51.2%) were male; 338 894 (22.1%) of mothers were black and 999 684 (65.1%) were married at time of birth, and the mean (SD) age for mothers at time of birth was 27.2 (6.2) years. Late-term infants had 0.7% of an SD (95% CI, 0.001-0.013; P = .02) higher average test scores in elementary and middle school, 2.8% (95% CI, 0.4-5.2; P = .02) higher probability of being gifted, and 3.1% (95% CI, 0.0-6.1; P = .05) reduced probability of poor cognitive outcomes compared with full-term infants. These cognitive benefits appeared strongest for children with disadvantaged family background characteristics. Late-term infants were also 2.1% (95% CI, 0.3 to 4.5; P = .08) more likely to be physically impaired.

Conclusions and Relevance  There appears to be a tradeoff between cognitive and physical outcomes associated with late-term gestation. Children born late-term performed better on 3 measures of school-based cognitive functioning but worse on 1 measure of physical functioning relative to children born full term. Our findings provide longer-run information for expectant parents and physicians who are considering delivery at full term vs late term. These findings are most relevant to uncomplicated, low-risk pregnancies.

http://archpedi.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2527085 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children born in the 41st week of pregnancy - which is considered "late-term" - have better test scores and are more likely to be classified as gifted in elementary and middle school, compared with children born "full-term," that is, at 39 or 40 weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer Drug Prices Highest in U.S., Least Affordable in India, China: Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Pays Highest Prices for Cancer Meds: Study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hostess Brands Voluntarily Recalls Zinger, Ding Dong, Others, Over Possible Peanut Residue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former police officer has been ordered to federal prison for his conviction of lying to investigators in relation to an armored car robbery that occurred in Houston in 2013, announced U.S. Attorney Kenneth Magidson. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former HPD officer sentenced to four years in federal prison. Admitted to lying about his missing service weapon linked to an armored car heist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SF Police Commission OKs body cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fresh Original] Dad God - Rod Squad (Rap God Parody) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 16:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 15:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 17:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiene que ser un arroyo en Barranquilla, o minimo en el costa de Colombia. 

Translation:

Has to be a flooded street in Barranquilla or someplace on the Colombian Atlantic coast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good-hearted man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assume the feeling of fulfilling your wish [Video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 15:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New system for weaving technology into fabric transforms everyday objects, like clothes, into interactive surfaces. Project Jacquard will allow designers and developers to build connected, touch-sensitive textiles into their own products. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 15:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New system for weaving technology into fabric transforms everyday objects, like clothes, into interactive surfaces. Project Jacquard will allow designers and developers to build connected, touch-sensitive textiles into their own products. [May 2015] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 15:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube Fixes Fair Use and Content ID... Kinda #WTFU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not my favorite sport, but watching how these soccer stars greet their fans made my eyes water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 15:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most life-like Star Wars nail art I've seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 year old during a mini debate about whether the death penalty ought to be banned in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably; however, I actually meant I wanted that license plate mechanism, that slides it in and out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 17:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Increasing evidence from laboratory and epidemiologic studies indicates that insufficient sleep may be a risk factor for obesity. Sleep curtailment results in stimulation of hunger and food intake that exceeds the energy cost of extended wakefulness, suggesting the involvement of reward mechanisms. The current study tested the hypothesis that sleep restriction is associated with activation of the endocannabinoid (eCB) system, a key component of hedonic pathways involved in modulating appetite and food intake.

http://www.journalsleep.org/ViewAbstract.aspx?pid=30492 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISO Speed Ratings: 40 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 17:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the remarks. I could see how that may help some children; however, my son loves being on video. We're actually developing a series of his toy unboxings and game plays. 

That said, without the camera up, he didn't even want to shoot the ball. I filmed his first attempts, and noticed he got a little more motivated, but he was still failing, so I thought he might do better without it. I turned it off. As soon as I dropped the phone, he stopped shooting and the first thing he said was, "Is the camera rolling?"

"It is now," I said, as I lifted it and cut it back on. Then he started to try again, and the footage to which I link here is what we got. 

Further, on this other video, I actually got him to do good in school by telling him that I would be filming him when [he got out of school](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ny3gRqIxNgk).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 17:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my 6-year-old who made some shots with a smaller ball earlier in the day. He was done, so he wanted to get back to his Minecraft pad. He lied down in protest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you are coming from. I saw a documentary on Netflix that actually highlighted parents who were obsessed that their children did well at sports. They were verbally and physically abusive with the kids when they didn't perform well. And they forced them to practice like full-time jobs. That said, I'm trying to be real careful to not be like that. Further, I work a lot of hours, so I may not even have the time to be like that. 

My ultimate objective is not that my sons become the next Michael Jordans, I just want them to be more active because as human beings, I think we have to be active to stay healthy. I would be satisfied that they get good enough to like to play basketball or another sport enough that he stays fit. If they get good and go on to play at a collegiate, pro or other good formal level, then I'll support them. 

For instance, I work out 6 days a week myself. My uncle would force me to workout a few times a week when I was nine years old with small weights. I didn't utterly love it at first, for I was lazy. But I have had a love/hate relationship for workouts since that I've rarely lived years of my life without some type of daily workout or sports involvement. And not to brag (which means I'm about to brag), at 40 I am literally stronger than I was at 18, aside from the minor knee pain and muscle pulls that I didn't suffer at that age. Overall, I strongly think that push to get involved with weights at age nine gave me the drive to eat better and be a overall healthy guy for my age. Otherwise, I would have stuck to playing G.I.Joe and Super Mario until the calluses on my thumbs bled (had the calluses but never bled :). 

Thanks for the remarks. Further, I think we're off to a good start, for after this, he told me that being a basketball player was among the other things he wanted to be when he grows up (foot surgeon, military medic, a few others I forgot). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great story. Sounds like your mom loved you so much she didn't want you to get hurt. My mother was overprotective too, who also stopped me from doing more slightly "risky" activities. Great job on overcoming all the chaos around you to still do your thing.

We've also played with smaller balls in the pool where's he's made some shots. But your story reminds me of something Vince Carter said before about using bigger basketballs. If I recall correctly, he said he practiced with a bigger ball than the regulation ball to get better at shooting and dribbling. I may explore trying that to see what it helps produce. Thanks for the thought! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 14:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear that. Hope it helps you become great! And thanks for the kind remarks; I hope to be just as good as your dad.

I've recently had him study a lot of Jordan; and he's digging the story so much he wants to be like Mike, which can't be bad at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 14:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the 6 year old protesting that he wanted to go home to get back to Minecraft :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 16:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought too. It appears as if it's illustrating the effect of the flag flying the other way against the wind. I initially thought it to be confusing and insulting; however, it follows the rules of presentation on vehicles with the canton towards the front: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flag_of_the_United_States#Display_on_vehicles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 15:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An analysis of return on investment can help policy makers support, optimize, and advocate for the expansion of immunization programs in the worlds poorest countries. We assessed the return on investment associated with achieving projected coverage levels for vaccinations to prevent diseases related to ten antigens in ninety-four low- and middle-income countries during 201120, the Decade of Vaccines. We derived these estimates by using costs of vaccines, supply chains, and service delivery and their associated economic benefits. Based on the costs of illnesses averted, we estimated that projected immunizations will yield a net return about 16 times greater than costs over the decade (uncertainty range: 1025). Using a full-income approach, which quantifies the value that people place on living longer and healthier lives, we found that net returns amounted to 44 times the costs (uncertainty range: 2767). Across all antigens, net returns were greater than costs. But to realize the substantial positive return on investment from immunization programs, it is essential that governments and donors provide the requisite investments.

http://content.healthaffairs.org/content/35/2/199.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 16:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [with the left!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pCTfxOrX4k8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never saw him at a game; however, I hated him when he beat up my hometown Knicks over and over again when I saw him live on TV. I had to grow out of being such a bias Knick fan years later to realize he is indeed the GOAT; and I was lucky enough to witness some of the best physical feats performed by perhaps any human being ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 16:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure that's true really. Netflix really caters to the part of me that wouldn't have as much to do. They've got some crazy good documentaries that I would think closely targets my middle-age approaching demo. Netflix also has a lot of those movies that I wanted but didn't have the time to see. And movies that I saw which I wouldn't mind leaving on in the background while I'm doing something else, like the Bourne flicks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 16:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it though? Sometimes what you need to do to be happy doesn't produce immediate happiness, but isn't the end result supposed to be a happy situation? 

Like I work all day, so I could pay my rent and be happy in a home, with warm clean food for me and my family. I wouldn't be that happy if I was homeless and hungry. I guess that's not the be all and end all of happiness, but doesn't that constitute the start?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 16:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I'm a little older than you, and I liked that Unicorn Island trailer. It's a social media success story. I don't think anything like that has been portrayed as a full-length feature yet. I wouldn't mind taking a look on a f-off Saturday. It would have to be good from the start though; otherwise, I'll cut it off in the first few minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though common sense suggests that positive thinking shelters people from depression, the four studies reported here showed that this intuition needs to be qualified: Positive thinking in the form of fantasies about the future did indeed relate to decreased symptoms of depression when measured concurrently; however, positive fantasies predicted more depressive symptoms when measured longitudinally. The pattern of results was observed for different indicators of fantasies and depression, in adults and in schoolchildren, and for periods of up to 7 months (Studies 14). In college students, low academic success partially mediated the predictive relation between positive fantasies and symptoms of depression (Study 4). Results add to existing research on the problematic effects of positive fantasies on performance by suggesting that indulging in positive fantasies predicts problems in mental health.

http://pss.sagepub.com/content/early/2016/01/14/0956797615620783.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new rule prohibiting it reads:

*Athletes will be disqualified for evidence of CED (Caffeine Enhancing Drugs) in their blood specimens.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 20:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Endurance athletes commonly ingest caffeine as a means to enhance training intensity and competitive performance. A widely-used source of caffeine is coffee, however conflicting evidence exists regarding the efficacy of coffee in improving endurance performance. In this context, the aims of this evidence-based review were three-fold: 1) to evaluate the effects of pre-exercise coffee on endurance performance, 2) to evaluate the effects of coffee on perceived exertion during endurance performance, and 3) to translate the research into usable information for athletes to make an informed decision regarding the intake of caffeine via coffee as a potential ergogenic aid. Searches of three major databases were performed using terms caffeine, and coffee, or coffee-caffeine, and endurance, or aerobic. Included studies (n=9) evaluated the effects of caffeinated coffee on human subjects, provided the caffeine dose administered, administered caffeine 45 minutes before testing, and included a measure of endurance performance (e.g., time trial). Significant improvements in endurance performance were observed in five of nine studies, which were on average 24.2% over controls for time to exhaustion trials, and 3.1% for time to completion trials. Three of six studies found that coffee reduced perceived exertion during performance measures significantly more than control conditions (p0.05). Based on the reviewed studies there is moderate evidence supporting the use of coffee as an ergogenic aid to improve performance in endurance cycling and running. Coffee providing 3-8.1mg/kg (1.36-3.68mg/lb) of caffeine may be used as a safe alternative to anhydrous caffeine to improve endurance performance.

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/26568580 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 14:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background Premature cardiac contractions are associated with increased morbidity and mortality. Though experts associate premature atrial contractions (PACs) and premature ventricular contractions (PVCs) with caffeine, there are no data to support this relationship in the general population. As certain caffeinated products may have cardiovascular benefits, recommendations against them may be detrimental.

http://jaha.ahajournals.org/content/5/1/e002503.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 17:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the charge should be tampering with evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 15:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/430ez2/old_man_reacts_to_hearing_music_from_his_era/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
