<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5873</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I believe he did.

- Dr. Zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude your fat friend, Lucy, was the drunk driver!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't do it. Let them take you out! Then you'll only be remembered as an awesome guitar player that was murdered. You could be as famous as Tupac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never lie to Tio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever woken up handcuffed to a bed and thought How the hell did I end up here?

Of course you have, this is Reddit and you are all sick fucks. The way in which my situation differs is that at the time I truly did not know how I ended up handcuffed to a bed. Only after a few more punches landed did I start to recall my circumstances and not until years later (right now, in fact) did my memory fully come to the forefront of my mind. I am getting ahead of myself, though, so let me make one disclaimer before I move on to a story of my youth. This is not your typical NoSleep horror. No, it was a personal horror that will live with me for the rest of my life.

--------------------

Cold, freezing cold. It drenched me, stuck to me, invading my body. A 5-gallon bucket now empty of the frigid water it contained now coated me and the bed I woke up on. I tried to escape the liquid but my restraints held me in place. Something even colder than the water was clasped tightly to my ankles and wrists. Once I could blink away the water flowing down my face I began taking in my surroundings:

Handcuffed to a dirty bed in a dim room with a menacing man sneering at my predicament.

He replaced the bucket in his hand with a wide leather belt and I think his sneering became more sneerful somehow. Have you ever been whipped with a belt? I mean really whipped? I still have the scars to prove how much it sucks. This moment is where I received the first scar.

**whooooosh, slllaaaapppppp**

My body jerked away but of course there was nowhere to go and the leather made solid contact across my chest. His arm pulled back and came down again, lower this time, across my ribs. Again and again. Crisscrossing my torso leaving a large red welt and thin trickles of blood behind. As far as I can remember he hadnt even said a word yet. I do remember him speaking after the belt came across my cheek and nose. Blood gushed out and down my lips and into my mouth. 

Why you tryna play me, boy?

I sputtered and gagged on the amount of blood rushing into my mouth, fear plastered on my face.

I said why you tryna play me?!

The belt came down across my upper thigh and wrapped inwards. My eyes bulged and I choked on spit and blood as I gasped for air. I tried to curl up, tried to hide the pain, extinguish it with the fetal position. My wrists and ankles were becoming raw from the jerking motions I was making. 

You think I dont know? You think you can lie to me?

I finally found my voice. It was quite small. Lie? It was all I could muster. One word. I received another caress of the belt for that one word.

You must think I am fucking stupid, eh? I told you to beat that fag up and put him in the hospital.

My mind rewound like an old VHS tape that had been watched too many times  only bits and pieces were visible and coherent. 

*My fist went forward and across, connecting lightly with my friends face. I hit him in the gut once, twice, then pushed him down. Kneeling down over him I grabbed his wallet and whispered Just play along, meet me in an hour. One last shove into the dirt and I walked off*

Another lashing across my thigh brought me out of my reverie and into the painful present. 

I knocked his ass to the ground and took his wallet, Tio. I even gave you the wallet.

You think you can lie to me and get away with it? I got people watching my initiates, dumbass! My crew said you hit him like a little girl.

*Alhandro rounds the corner and warily looks around the back of the gas station. My head peeks up to see him and I usher him over. Handing him the money in his wallet I explain everything. Tio needed me to prove myself, put a friend in the hospital. He picked you because you are queer, man, I am sorry. Alhandro just nods, takes the cash and leaves.*

Yea, you starting to remember now you little bitch? You stupid pussy. I told you to put him in the hospital and rob his ass, not tickle his face and give me an empty wallet.

This time the belt was turned around. The buckle came down on my knee and pain exploded throughout my body. The swelling was almost immediate and soon I couldnt see my foot over it. It was about this time when I noticed my brother down the hall. I only saw him for a second and then he was gone but it jogged another memory. 

*I walked into the game room a bit unsure but trying to seem confident. It was my first time in there  only the high up members had access. Someone pulled out a chair and I sat. Tio, my brother, two other dudes, and I all sat around a poker table. Tio started to deal cards and talk to me. I dont know what he was saying but maybe something about congratulations or asking me if I played cards. After two hands something hit me in the back of the head  I woke up on the bed*

No one fucking lies to me, man. I show you what liars get.

He walked out, then. I am not sure if he was taking a break or going to get something worse than the belt. What I do know is that my brother came in and took off my cuffs. He told me how to get out through the back and to never come back. I hobbled out the back and made it to the first building I could, a library. 

-----------------

Looking back it was probably the safest fucking place I could have ever went to. That leads me to now. I did end up making it out of that awful city and stayed with some cousins in Vegas for a while working construction. I am not sure why all of this came flooding back to the forefront of my mind. Maybe it was the belt I put on this morning for work but then again I put one on every day for work. Maybe it was my cousin telling me about my brother trying to reach out to me for the first time in a decade. 

What I do know is I finally remembered something  I wasnt the only one being tested that day. My brother was the one who got me in to that gang. My brother was there playing cards. My brother was there watching me take the worst beating of my life. What I have realized is that my brother was the one who snitched me out, followed me and told Tio I didnt bust up Alhandro enough. 

He might have saved my life but he was the one who endangered it in the first place. I dont think Ill be taking a call from him any time soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think you can't find it anymore? Decommissioned in favor of our facility. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That you'll find out in due time. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your question answers itself, my friend. If he had said "turn to page 394" I'd have understood but "page 394" means a great deal of things to me due to the vast amount of information I have at my mental disposal. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human Centipede </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone is may be running the show still. Keep your eyes open, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True but it would be really easily proven with video recording.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your FB is covered in MS Paint dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all Patients are interesting or groundbreaking in their abilities. To be honest most were complete failures in a scientific sense and some were simply Dr. Feldman exacting revenge for others doubting his work.

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr Feldman was an interesting man, and brilliant. He was not known for sensitivities, however. He was very much devoid of emotion except at the most extreme of times and therefore believed his Patients to be as well. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh most certainly! We'll be in touch. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it is in the past I suppose you could consider it completely harmless now that it has all already transpired. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 39 pages or so thus far. There are over 100 terabytes of data here at Site 2 so be thankful I am as sparing as I am. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahem, brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanksgiving with Dr. Feldman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Chapter 1** | [1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/) | [2]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/) | [3]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/) | [4]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/) | [5]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/) | [6]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/) | [7]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/) | [8]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/) | [9]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/) | [10]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/) | [11]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u0d4q/site_2/) | [12]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u7lf7/patient_314_final/)

**Chapter 2** | [13](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u9s1m/hide_seek_with_dr_feldman/) | [14](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5vt6ud/patient_zero_origins/) | [15](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5w0734/thanksgiving_with_dr_feldman/) | [16](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wotm6/patient_11/) | [17](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x4373/patient_98_the_surgeon/) | [18](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5y1fk7/patient_314_has_a_name/) | [19](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yhiy6/patient_314_has_a_name_part_2/)

-----------

09/01/1985 - 08:31:15

FROM: Richard.F.Talbot@51.gov

TO: J.Feldman@MWPW.gov

SUBJECT: Entity Transfers

Good morning, Dr. Feldman,

Id like to thank you on behalf of the United States Military for your exemplary service and dedication to your work and this great country. Based on the most recent logs received we believe that your research far and away exceeds the expectations initially placed on your facility. As a result of this we will be transporting two entities to your facility to help further your cause. The attached documents will outline the precautions needed with housing and testing of your two new Patients. Henry Finebar is already on a flight out to assess your facility and send a report back to me on what you will need. In addition a barracks will be built in order to house a Regiment. These men will be available for whatever needs you may have in addition to security. 

Please continue providing weekly reports directly to me. Once Henry builds the report for your facility we will have construction crews out immediately to get you up and running quickly. I would expect your new Patients within the month. Once again, thank you and congratulations on your recent successes. God Bless America.

General Talbot

-------------

ATTACHMENT 1: SUBJECT A

**Description:** Humanoid in shape. One hundred and eleven centimeters in height, one hundred and eleven pounds. Skin color is a matte grey that absorbs light. Subject A has no reflection nor casts a shadow. Each hand ends with three fingers and a thumb, however, each finger has far more dexterity. Subject A is capable of bending each finger in any direction and can carry out two tasks per hand in comparison to a human. Feet are similar in nature.

**Abilities:** Subject A has incredible strength, quickness, and agility. Adept at blending in to its surroundings, although it does not change in color or appearance. When motionless it simply fades away from vision. 

**Conclusions:** Based on its adaptability and apparent need to vanish into its surroundings it is determined that Subject A is most likely in the middle of the food chain in its place of origin. The terrain is either extremely mountainous or densely forested and bleak in color.

**Precautions:** Subject A does not blend well with the color red  therefore its holding cell should be colored as such, as well as any transportation devices used to move it back and forth. It should be noted that a color change is advised at least on a semi-annual basis. Subject A could become accustomed to a new environment and begin blending properly with red. Alternate between reds, yellows, and oranges. Subject A has strength equivalent to a fully grown gorilla and quickness rivaling a mongoose. Ensure all forms of containment can withstand 100,000 psi and has a set of two doors, an inner and an outer. 

----------------

ATTACHMENT 2: SUBJECT B

**Description:** Slightly smaller in size than a giant squid, but similar in all regards externally. Approximately six meters long and three hundred and twenty pounds. Blue in color. The beak is larger and extremely powerful. Two were found, one dead from impact.

**Abilities:** Subject B is highly intelligent. It has its own language and learned English within three months of captivity, although it is difficult to understand due to the difference in anatomy, it is intelligible. Aside from its intelligence it does not need to be in water to survive.

**Dissection:** The brain is roughly the same size as a human brain and each section proportionate to ours as well. There are no lungs or other unknown internal organs so its skin must be similar to that of an amphibian. It should be noted that each individual sucker has tiny barbs that emit poison from a sac at the base of each attack tentacle. Testing has confirmed that there are two different poisons. One is an aphrodisiac and the other a sedative.

**Conclusions:** In the water, Subject B is an extremely dangerous and formidable foe, most likely at the very top of its food chain. The intelligence and power that it possesses alone make it deadly but the addition of the poisons make it a truly remarkable predator. It is possible that it uses the poisons solely for mating but that seems unlikely. Its place of origin is clearly similar to ours based on its amphibious nature. 

**Precautions:** DO NOT PLACE IN WATER. On land it is much more slow and cumbersome, although still fierce and formidable. Subject B does not like electricity. Excessive use will result in permanent cognitive damage, just as with humans. Keep temperature at a constant sixty degrees Fahrenheit to ensure longevity.

-----------------

 09/09/1985  14:21:55

FROM: Henry.U.Finebar@51.gov

TO: Richard.F.Talbot@51.gov

SUBJECT: Mt. Whitney facility assessment

Staffing  Understaffed, however with only one Patient that is to be expected. Suggesting two Companies of troops stationed initially, scaling up to the full Regiment by year five.

Security  Adequate, but outdated. A full revamp will need to take place if the site will be ready for Phase 2. Suggesting a second, emergency exit installed and blast doors on each entrance. Handprint, voice, and retinal scans at each entrance as well as internally for restricted areas. A flood system and shock system will need to be installed in case of site failure, as well as charges on each floor. Expand the no-fly zone.

Accessibility  There is only a gravel path currently. We will need to install roads, a helipad, and high-speed rail for Patient transport. In addition to the barracks the area will need outposts and fences installed to keep hikers and campers far enough away.

Data/IT Infrastructure  Very basic server room connecting a few desktop computers. With the extent of research that will soon be happening we will need a similar setup to Site 51. This is not my expertise so an expert should be sent to assess.

As a side note I believe a second site should be built in case of emergency evacuation of Site 1.

Cost  Total cost will range from $300 million to $900 million

------------------

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Dr. Feldman Personal Log

*11/28/1985  2:53PM*

Forgive me for not making a log sooner. The system has been down or intermittent for some time due to all the construction and changes being made here. Patient 2 and Patient 3 have just arrived and are in their new homes! I always knew but now it is confirmed! Life outside of this planet  wow! And I, Jacob Feldman, get to test and experiment these marvelous creatures for the betterment of humanity. 

I cant wait to see if Patient Zero can absorb their information the same way he can Earthly beings. Of course, I have to figure out how to scale back his power first. Dont want to absorb everything and lose one of the most precious test subjects in the history of the world! What a day, what a day. Today truly is a day of thanksgiving. So much to do before dinner with the troops.

-------------------

[History 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wotm6/patient_11/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best comment I've seen all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure hope your grandma knows Rambo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this one will stay up. Good luck, OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is not staying in our house any more, that is for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of what you or I believe in, OP MIGHT. I was merely seeking out information that may or may not help OP cope with his difficult situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let us know if/when you get in contact or any updates you might have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a reasonable question to ask. In a world of hypothetical situations every possibility is a good possibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please continue to keep us informed. I was just reading about this very subject so I am incredibly interested in what you find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only were the Plague Doctors the spreaders of the Plague but also possibly from the future, communicating with cell phones or walkie talkies of some sort. If not the future possibly another planet or even alternate reality. 

The question is, why? Did they come to try and wipe out the human race out of cruelty or in order to stop a greater evil that would come at a later date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea you need to get a hold of her, if not just to explain but to make sure she is safe. She could get mixed up in this as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap, I have an Uncle Tom. He has always been the nice one, the one to take us out to dinner and wanting to visit our daughter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you going to try to contact Lucy and see what is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, do you believe in God? If so, do you believe that your plight will end when He finally sends His Son back to this Earth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that feeling of helplessness and complete confusion. I promise there is always a way. Do NOT give up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hide your kids, hide your wife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been farting all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty soon they will be sporting boners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to find out more! Drink protein mixes, it will help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient Zero - Origins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Chapter 1** | [1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/) | [2]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/) | [3]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/) | [4]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/) | [5]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/) | [6]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/) | [7]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/) | [8]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/) | [9]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/) | [10]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/) | [11]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u0d4q/site_2/) | [12]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u7lf7/patient_314_final/)

**Chapter 2** | [13](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u9s1m/hide_seek_with_dr_feldman/) | [14](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5vt6ud/patient_zero_origins/) | [15](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5w0734/thanksgiving_with_dr_feldman/) | [16](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wotm6/patient_11/) | [17](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x4373/patient_98_the_surgeon/) | [18](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5y1fk7/patient_314_has_a_name/) | [19](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yhiy6/patient_314_has_a_name_part_2/)

-----------

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Dr. Feldman Personal Log

*5/18/1985  7:30AM*

Today a new chapter is opened  our research will make massive strides forward. My colleague and friend, Irithmus Thar, has kindly volunteered to be our first human test subject. As much as we have gained in the five years experimenting with the local flora and fauna we will gain in weeks or even days with Patient Zero. That is, if my hypothesis is correct. Irithmus has this amazing talent for absorbing knowledge. It seems as though he needs to read a book once to commit it to memory in its entirety. I began questioning how this could be when we started to work together more closely on the human potential. He had no books, no library of any kind, never took notes or recorded conversations or lectures. Somehow, though, he retain all he took in without the slightest error to it. 

Of course, there are physiological explanations for this, disorders that could cause it as well, but usually result in a loss of function in some other fashion. Without any apparent losses I can only speculate that this is a singularity unto Irithmus himself and must be examined in a more secluded and contained environment. Today our journey into his mind begins.

-------------------

*5/18/1985  8:00AM* 

Experiment One  logging

**Dr.** - Good morning my friend. I pray you are feeling well.

**Zero** - What have you done, Jacob? Where did you take me?

**Dr.** - This is where real science takes place. You wanted to study the human potential, lets study it!

**Zero** - You dont know what you are doing. You cant just take people, Jacob. This isnt you.

**Dr.** - Oh, I do and I can. On the table next to you is a book. Please pick it up and being reading. 

**Zero** - I am not in the mood for reading, Jacob. Let me out! 

Patient Zero approaches the observation window and begins pounding on the glass. The shock collar affixed to his neck is activated, sending him crashing to the floor.

**Dr.** - The observation glass is rated to withstand an angry bear. The collar around your neck can be turned up high enough to kill such a bear instantaneously. Please do not disobey my orders again. Now pick up the book, Zero. 

**Zero** - Zero? [He gingerly makes his way to book and picks it up. A small after-tremor from the shock shakes his body.] 

**Dr.** - Now begin reading.

As Patient Zero turns the pages they become a blank, off-white page.

**Dr.** - Just as I thought. What did page twenty eight explain?

**Zero** - The chemical reactions in the brain that dictate short-term, long-term, and ultralong-term memories.

**Dr.** - In your professional opinion, would you say that you only create ultralong-term memory?

**Zero** - Yes.

Experiment One complete.

--------------------

*6/24/1985  7:21PM*

Dr. Feldman Personal Log

I love being right. After weeks of work I finally replicated Zeroes ability to extract and retain information and have begun collecting his memories. I love this digital age. Once digitized we can then implant the memories back into Patient Zero. On second thought maybe I should only give him some memories back. I suppose depending on what we need him for he could be given information and have things taken away at any time. Yes, that would make the most sense.

I have begun to experiment on myself to see if I can start forcing memories into becoming ultralong-term. That must make me Patient One. [chuckles to himself] Of course Ill never be on the other side of the observation window. Hmm what was I talking about? My memory does seems to be a bit off since the experiments. Would ultralong-term memories even be desired without a fast enough recall? Patient Zero never seems to hesitate when bringing forth information. There must be more to his ability  instant recall, perhaps. Oh good, something new to test.

--------------

*6/25/1985  6:15AM*

Experiment Two  logging

Breakfast delivered.

**Dr.** - Good morning, Zero. I am excited for the results of todays testing. Are you?

Zero eats his food silently. Four orderlies walk in with an exam table loaded with equipment.

**Dr.** - Once you are done eating these fine gentlemen are going to hook you up so that we can track your recall ability. Does that sound good?

Patient Zero continues eating in silence. Once completed Zero is ushered to the table and strapped in. Electrodes are placed in various locations on his body, predominately on the head. Patient Zero is given an encyclopedia. 

**Dr.** - Please read the book. When you are finished I will ask you questions regarding the information in that book.

Patient Zero reads through the book in twenty seven minutes. Each page takes approximately half a second to be understood.

**Dr.** - Page one hundred seventy one, paragraph three.

**Zero** - These specialized plants employ a variety of mechanisms to capture prey, ranging from the passive pitfall traps of pitcher plants to the adhesive leaves of sundews and butterworts to the snap traps of Venus flytraps and aquatic bladderworts. Most carnivorous plants attract and digest insects and other invertebrates, but some large pitcher plants have been known to digest frogs, rodents, and other vertebrates.

**Dr.** - Page nineteen, paragraph one.

**Zero** - Just prior to the beginning of the Neoproterozoic, Earth experienced a period of continental suturing that organized all of the major landmasses into the huge supercontinent of Rodinia. Rodinia was fully assembled by one billion years ago and rivaled Pangea (a supercontinent that formed later during the Permian Period) in size. Before the beginning of the Cambrian, Rodinia split in half, resulting in the creation of the Pacific Ocean west of what would become North America. By the middle and later parts of the Cambrian, rifting had sent the paleocontinents of Laurentia (made up of present-day North America and Greenland), Baltica (made up of present-day Western Europe and Scandinavia), and Siberia on their separate ways. In addition, a supercontinent called Gondwana formed, which was made up of what would become Australia, Antarctica, India, Africa, and South America.

**Dr.** - Page nine hundred and two, paragraph four.

**Zero** - Black Panther Party, original name Black Panther Party for Self-Defense, African American revolutionary party, founded in 1966 in Oakland, California, by Huey Newton and Bobby Seale. The partys original purpose was to patrol African American neighbourhoods to protect residents from acts of police brutality. The Panthers eventually developed into a Marxist revolutionary group that called for the arming of all African Americans, the exemption of African Americans from the draft and from all sanctions of so-called white America, the release of all African Americans from jail, and the payment of compensation to African Americans for centuries of exploitation by white Americans. At its peak in the late 1960s, Panther membership exceeded 2,000, and the organization operated chapters in several major American cities.

--This continued for two more hours--

**Dr.** - Excellent. Thank you Zero. Lunch will be served soon. 

Experiment Two complete.

--------------------

[History 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5w0734/thanksgiving_with_dr_feldman/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I love gravy. Turkey gravy though, not baby gravy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy named Squirrel that lives down the street. Dude is a weirdo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sorry that you lost your friend. Do yourself and the "dog" a favor and put it down. Something got to it and I wouldn't want to see what it becomes. You definitely don't want to lose your hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much better than I AM Legend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet she had a nice pair of lungs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hasn't everybody? It felt so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, want some dice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you're a genius! My best buddy is our DM and I'm sure he'll help me out. Hell, he'll probably make it fun somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it works that way. I've already tripped and fallen a few times from failed rolls. Any action I take requires a roll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything is Fun, Everything is a Toy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont recall the first time I felt that warm, flowing sensation between my legs. I must have been young because I always seem to remember knowing about it. I just cant pinpoint the first time. I do, however, remember my first orgasm. 

We had just moved into a new home and I had my own bathroom for the first time in my short life. The first thing I did when I was all unpacked was take a nice, hot shower in my own personal bathroom. Steam filled the room quickly and soon I was covered in soapy bubbles. The best part was how the shower head could be taken off of the wall and move around. No longer would I need to bend over or hike up a leg to get all the soap off. I could just aim the water exactly where I needed it! Soon enough I found out *exactly* where I needed it. My parents water bill probably increased quite a bit that month.

Id call that my Awakening. From there I began to experiment. A Sharpie was my first toy. I have never told anyone about this or even asked questions relating to it out of embarrassment so I dont know if I progressed faster than most girls or if I was just another normal teenage girl. One Sharpie led to two. Sharpies led to hair brush handles. Brush handles let to carrots and cucumbers.

Each stage in my adventures thrilled me more than the next. The thrill just didnt last very long. I had to find something new, something bigger or better. Something to bring me back to that first night in my shower. 

-----------------------------

Friends gossip and some of my friends were talking about what they did with their boyfriends. It sounded like a lot of fun and maybe, just maybe, it would fill the void I kept searching for. I am not the most beautiful girl or anything but Ive noticed a few passing glances here and there. One of those glances came from a tall, muscular boy a grade or two above me. He was *gorgeous* and pretty popular as well, which made his glances all the better. Id get wet just thinking about it!

Within a week he was mine and I was his. I didnt know how to go about these things with a boy but he seemed to know a lot. It is different with a boy. Better. Maybe it is because I dont know what he is thinking so I am kept guessing. When it is just me I already know what I am going to do. The only bad side of it is how short he lasts. Doesnt he know I want it all the time? If I could have him inside me every minute of the day I would!

Our first time together was amazing for about a minute. I begged and pleaded for more and after a while he obliged. I guess boys and girls are very different because he started getting really tired while I was just getting started. I was wide awake when he passed out next to me. It was still nice and hard, glistening with what we had engaged in, beckoning me over. I played with it a little and before I knew it I had cut it off and pushed it back inside. It felt sooooo good and warm  but only for a few seconds. Boys are so stupid. He was screaming and bleeding all over but that didnt last too long. It took much longer to clean up than it did to have sex. 

So after that I gave up on boys. They were too much work for such little reward, you know? I began to experiment again and soon found out that I enjoy a little pain. If I added some pain even one Sharpie felt good again! I was so excited! I found this website that sold all kinds of fun things and used my babysitting money to buy it all. Clamps and tassels and oils and things that move and shake and wiggle. My eyes were bigger than my you know, because one of the things I ordered was almost the size of my arm!

Of course all of these fun things only lasted a little while. Once I try something I cant go back, you know? Always forward. I really want to try the huge one but I think it is more like a joke or something because there is no way it would fit, right?

-------------------------

Well the joke was on them because after just a few snips I was able to get it to fit and it feels so good! I just had to make like two or three little cuts so that I could open up a little more, you know? And all the blood makes it so easy to move back and forth. When I say it is big, I mean HUGE. I have to stand up and kind of squat onto it. 

So that brings me to right now. I am starting to think there is something kind of wrong with me, you know? Because even though that felt great for a few days now it is just so boring. So I was over at my friends house and she has this cool plant thing that kind of looks like the right shape and stuff, right? It is about a foot long which isnt all that much but it is really fat! So I stole it and took it home. At first it really hurt, I think all the spines maybe, but then it was better and better and better. But I wont stop bleeding and now the plant is missing all of its spines and I think they are inside. How do I get them out? Please help me because I want to try it again as soon as I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Hrann crouched warily, peeking around the corner. The guards back is turned  Hrann draws back his longbow in a quiet, fluid motion.*

DM: Roll a D20 to see if your attack hits.

Crack^clack^clatter^tink^tink^tink

Player: 18!

**THWAK** *The arrow sinks deep into the thick musculature of the guards shoulder, momentum spinning him around to see directly into your eyes. With a roar he rushes you with broadsword drawn.*

DM: Roll a D20 for your reflex save. Dont forget your bonuses this time.

Crack^clack^clatter^tink^tink^tink

Player: Um, 14 with the bonuses. 

*The guards blade whistles by you, slicing only through air. Hrann slams his bow into the throat of the guard and draws a dagger.*

Crack^clack^clatter^tink^tink^tink

Player: Nat 20, hoo ya!

*Caught by surprise at the swiftness of the attack, the guard stumbles backward leaving his neck exposed just enough for Hranns blade to find it. Blood rushes forth as his life rushes away.*

DM: Alright friends, that is it for today. We will pick back up tomorrow at 6PM, alright?

Player 1: Yea bro, good stuff. See you tomorrow.

Player 2: Never miss it.

Player 3: Might be a bit late, my turn to make dinner cause mom is working.

DM: Alright no worries.

----------------

What a great session, right!? I actually killed that guard! Let me explain. I **never** do anything right in this campaign. I am a rogue. I am supposed to be sneaky, snipe people with arrows, steal things, that kind of stuff. The last time I tried to be sneaky I failed my roll so bad Hrann ended up alerting the entire camp to our presence instead of just the guard on duty. We had to run our butts off just to stay alive. 

I picked a rogue because I cant do those kind of things in real life either, you know? My mom says it sounds like an elephant when I walk around the house no matter how hard I try. I am actually banned from this cool antique store at the mall because the last time I was there I tripped and knocked over a massive display of plates and cups and stuff. I dont think my mom had to pay for anything but she was so embarrassed. I think it was her favorite store and now she cant go there anymore because of me. 

You can imagine my chagrin when Hrann couldnt do any of those things, just like me. If anyone else was Hrann he would be so awesome! But no, his stats are awful (because I rolled them) and he fails every check. Call me desperate or foolish but I had had enough so I went online to order a new set of dice. After about three hours of searching (yes, it is a very important decision) I came across a set that caught my eye in a different way than all the others. This one felt right, like it was calling to me across the internet. Even better was the price. Some dude was selling the whole set for $4, free shipping.

Id check the mail every day after school to see if my special package had come and finally, after three days it did. That was today. As soon as I saw the metallic shimmer-paper I knew my set of dice were inside and my fortune was going to change. Hrann would be the back-stabbing ghost he was meant to be. That snippet of the session at the top was pretty much the way the whole two hours went. I didnt miss a single attempt. Not one! 

Once I left I was feeling such a high. I raced down the street to my house and ran upstairs to my room where I had my own campaign that I was working on. I usually test scenarios out myself with a few mock characters to see how the balance works out. You never want your campaign too hard or too easy. I must have lost track of time because pretty soon it was completely dark out and my stomach was growling badly. As I got up to go get some food downstairs I tossed the D20  16. Sweet, a successful roll for food! 

Once I made it down to get some food I realized I had to choose what kind of food. I dont know why but I couldnt make a choice. I felt like the D20 was calling to me from upstairs. I ran up to get it and rolled: 1-10 would be leftover pizza, 11-20 would be a roast beef sandwich. *4* Pizza it is. 

That was four hours ago. Things have gotten progressively worse  like every roll takes a little bit more of my ability to choose for myself. I tried to trick it by rolling for the same thing a few times until I got the result I wanted but now it is rolling by itself. I can feel my body being tugged in directions to do something or think something but I dont know why until I get there.

I just pissed myself. I dont know how to break out of this trance, spell, curse? 

I rolled to see I could post this and it agreed.

--------------------

**UPDATE**

Based on some advice given I managed to make it through the night and meet up with my best friend who is our campaign DM. We got his parents approval for him to stay over at my place for a few nights for a "long campaign". Hopefully in that time we can find a way to nullify the D20.

It is really weird not having an inner monologue and I forget sometimes which I usually pay for dearly. Fortunately Tim, my best friend, it really understanding and wouldn't make fun of me for anything. We get made fun of enough from other people for playing D and D, you know? 

I think I can pass this on to someone else but the problem is who do I pass it to? I would have such a guilty conscious knowing what kind of evil I was giving someone. 

Any more advice would be very welcome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm so confused. Are there better plants to use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What could a gardener do that I can't? Are gardeners not supposed to be girls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow you are so nice! Thank you for the advice! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please don't yell. I just wanted to feel good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some in there. I can feel it if I try to stand up or walk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a trick? I tried to keep it firm but it just deflated like a stupid balloon so I threw it away with the rest of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please don't go. I need your help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um yea at first but I stuffed a hand towel there to stop it and now it seems to be ok?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no no I can't go to a doctor. My parents would find out about all of my toys and take them all away. I need to fix this before they get home. Please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never trusted mirrors in the first place. They always make me look fat and wrinkly around the eyes. Pft. Fuck mirrors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good a girl! Could you maybe give me some advice, girl to girl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any advice? I have taken a few out with tweasers but some are like really in there so I can't reach them. I tried once but I think they dug in deeper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patient 316 confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One-Punch Man: Origin Story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy's dog shits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one hole I wouldn't be venturing in... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so, too. He was a smart guy so I'm sure he will be fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes of course. I am sorry if I wasn't clear about that. I guess it was glossed over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's it, CL is banned on all devices!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that end scene in Jumanji when they scream at the parents to not go on the vacation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh is right!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any kids?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to lie, I'm going to miss the food trucks. I'll need to find the good ones again in my new town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words. It feels good to be together again, that is for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, it ain't Philly, that is for sure. He loves his Philly movies. It took place in Kansas City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least the writing would be better and it would be funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she is a sleepwalker Tom should have known about it and warned you both about it before hand. He didn't seem to know so I believe this is much worse than just sleepwalking. Keep us updated and don't go off alone with her. Be safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure I could have done more but I was concentrated on my own family at the time. I took them to the NBC station so it should be pretty hard to hush hush them, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always know the full extent of a contract before you sign it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be amazed what you are capable of once thrown into the situation. I have actually applied for some security jobs now based on this that I never would have thought to look at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately there was very little hand-to-hand combat so it looked a lot more realistic ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every father has a little Liam in him now and again. Daughters first date? Liam shows up. First time one of your kid goes missing, even for a second, Liam shows up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I had no idea it was him until after I shot him. The only person I knew visually was the receptionist but since they worked together I assumed the man with her in the factory was Brian. If it wasn't, oh well. One less bad guy around. The police confirmed it was him at the scene, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would do the same, would you not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just doing my fatherly duty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks. I actually pawned it since it was a work laptop but your offer is very kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never buy a mattress off of Craigslist - Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5uf78g/never_buy_a_mattress_off_of_craigslist/) | [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5umhqn/never_buy_a_mattress_off_of_craigslist_2/) \ [Related](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5v4wrk/ill_never_go_downtown_again/)

My wife went from chains to cuffs within minutes. We were stuffed into the back of a squad car and the sirens started up. Twenty minutes later we were on the outskirts of town at a park on the river that no one ever goes to due to the smell. The office opened the door and let us out. He led us about a hundred yards away from the car and told us to face the river on our knees. My wife was balling her eyes out, pleading for our lives. 

*I aint gonna kill ya, just need to look like it, alright? Now shut up and listen.*

So we did. Turns out this cop was new to the area, two weeks to be exact, and noticed a lot of weird, off-the-record stuff going on. When he was transferred he was told to take some drug that is exploding out on the streets so he faked it. He didnt know what it was but he figured it was some kind of weird mind crap because the Chief would give people orders no one should ever accept but no one asked any questions. They just did whatever he said. Anyway the police have been keeping this human trafficking stuff hush-hush because it is how they are testing the drug or getting it out on the streets or something. The cop was told to take us out here and pop us since I was causing all this trouble talking about kidnapping and stuff online, bringing unnecessary attention to Downtown. The last thing he tells us is that this will hurt our ears and to fall down and never come back to the city.

**BANG BANG BANG BANG**

I flopped forward like a dying fish and laid face-down on loose gravel and mud. I heard a thud and hoped my wife had done the same. I whispered softly to lie still until we could no longer hear the car. A few minutes passed before I ventured to flip over and found a small key nearby. The key unlocked the cuffs holding my wrists together and I leaned over to undo my wifes. She was trembling on the cold ground and I pulled her into my arms. 

*Its going to be OK, now. Youre safe with me now, babe.*

She stared back at me with eyes that had seen far too much. I am not sure how long we sat there staring or how long we cried, but eventually she broke the silence.

*They took her. Our baby. They took her.*

*Who? Where did they take her, hunnie?*

She started to cry again but it didnt last long. She was spent. It would be the last time we cried until this whole thing was over. She explained what had happened and how Brian and the receptionist used the storage facility to move people and drugs. They lured people up there with all kinds of Craigslist ads, sometimes to steal the person, sometimes to spread the drug. She said the mattresses would be filled with the vials and sent out all over the city. Some of the people they stole were given the drug, some were sold off and some were used as slave labor. She wasnt harmed or abused in any way, just treated harshly but she didnt know what happened to our little girl. I promised her Id find our daughter and bring her back and we would get out of this forsaken city.

It isnt easy leaving Downtown if you are in a position like us  no money, nowhere to go. But I knew our lives depended on it. 

---------------------

I still had all of my gear in the car and since I had parked it off the beaten path I hoped it was still there. Obviously I couldnt contact the police for help and I didnt have many friends to begin with, let alone trust now that all of this had happened, so I was on my own. I told my wife Id be back as soon as I could with the car and Id take her to the next city over and get her into a motel while I figured things out. 

It took me a few hours to make it back to my car but I was in luck because not only was my car still there but it hadnt been broken into yet or thrown up on blocks to steal the tires and rims so all my gear was still in it and it ran. My wife was sitting in the same place I left her, throwing rocks into the slow-moving river. I went as far as I could go before filling up the gas tank. While I was there I pulled out the limit for cash on the card and gave it to my wife for food and clothes and then drove another half a tank of gas away before pulling into a pretty nice looking motel. It was one of those extended-stay places with a little kitchen and living room and a nice hot breakfast each morning. The nice thing about being dead is that no one can come after you when you dont pay your credit card bill. 

We made love that night like it was our honeymoon, or like it was the last time wed ever see each other. I am not sure if there is a difference, honestly. That morning, full from a nice breakfast, I went to a pawn shop and picked up a heavy-duty Taser and a decent rifle. It wasnt as nice as the one that was taken from me at the factory but it would do. I made my way back to the hotel, pulled out whatever money I could from the ATM and then we headed the opposite direction. I didnt know for sure but in case we were followed or my credit cards were tracked I didnt want to take any chances. I only used cash from that point on and went about four hours in the other direction to a different extended stay motel. This one was just as clean as the last and I thought it would make due until I could find our daughter. My wife promised she would stay indoors as much as possible and only use cash when she needed food. We tested out the bed before I left. 

I made a new e-mail and kept checking Craigslist all day to see if I could find any ads like the ones they used so I can try and meet up with someone for information. I responded to a few but so far nothing back from them. I waited until late into the night before putting a few more cameras around the storage facility. Since the cops were a part of this whole thing I figured they wouldnt shut down operations. Once everything was set up I retired to my car to watch footage and browse the Deep Web for anything about infants. I couldnt imagine what they would want a child for and I was somewhat thankful for that. Trying to imagine all the things that could be happening would bring any father to his knees. 

----------------------

I must have passed out because I woke up to warm sunlight on my face and my laptop and phone clutched tightly in my hands. Both were dead. Fortunately I had a car charger for my phone so I was able to get that going again but I didnt have anything for the laptop. I must have left it at the house. Without the footage I could only hope to get lucky with a hit on some of those ads. 

Not too far from where I was parked was an amazing smelling food truck so I went over and grabbed something to eat  breakfast burritos with homemade salsa. So good. Halfway through the bulging tortilla I got a buzz  someone responded to my ad inquiry. This one was for a single-sized mattress. I was guessing that maybe the size of the mattress was code for something, maybe age. After several more e-mails and much convincing I was able to get the meeting place to a local Wal-Mart parking lot. With the Taser in my pocket I waited for the van to pull up.

Have you ever used a Taser before? It is so satisfying. When the gentleman was showing me the mattress I jabbed the Taser right into his crotch and let it rip. The look on his face was priceless. After a bit of interrogation in the spacious cargo area of the van he gave me enough information to believe my little girl was alive and unharmed. My main concerns was whether or not she was given the drug or if she would have eaten at all during our time apart. She is a pretty sensitive girl and a picky eater. Apparently they dont usually take kids but if they do they raise them and sell them as child brides at an early age.

*You are going to go to wherever my daughter is and you are going to bring her back to me. If you dont Ill find you, your family, everyone you ever cared about, understand?*

I took my new friends wallet as insurance. At least I would have his address if anything went south. I could have guessed where we were going. After a few minutes he parked the van up front at the receptionist office and went into a side door. Peeking through the windshield from the back of the van I could make out a few kids faces and hear shrill cries for mommy. My gut was wrenching around  I couldnt leave them. 

As promised my daughter came out in this bastards arms and he opened up the back of the van. The look on her face when she saw me was magical. She squirmed and leapt out of his arms and crawled over to me faster than Id ever seen. 

*How many kids are in there?*

*Um, like five, man I dont know. Please, I got your daughter.*

*Who is here right now? Who is watching them kids?*

*Just the new receptionist, man. Come on, man, I did what you asked.*

*Bring them all out.* I finished my finish with a crackle of the Taser. *Bring them out and then we are done, ok?*

He did as I asked, although it took an agonizingly long time. At first I thought he screwed me and was about to hop out of the van when the door opened and a range of kids came out, all old enough to walk. The new receptionist was yelling at the guy but he just slammed the door on her and opened up the van. The kids piled in with me and my daughter and we were off. About three blocks down I told the guy to get out.

I drove off into the heart of Downtown to the news station headquarters. I knew the police wouldnt help me but maybe if I dropped a bunch of grimy, starved kids at a news desk claiming they were kidnapped Id get a little attention. Of course they thought I was crazy but the state of the kids gave them enough pause to look into some things. I didnt wait around, but I felt like I at least gave the kids some chance, some hope. I trashed the van (they did horrible things with it!) and buckled my little girl into her car seat. 

----------------------

I am posting this from a Starbucks in a hopefully far-enough-away location to never be bothered again. I watch the news to see if anything came of those kids but nothing, yet. Ive tried contacting other agencies to look into the police there but maybe this is the best way, posting here. Maybe with enough attention it can create some change.

My daughter has gained back most of the weight she lost and doesnt seem to be affected at all by the ordeal. Only time will tell. Jobs are hard to come by but we are making ends meet. All we wanted was a nice mattress but my family is safe, that is all that really matters. Sometimes you just have to be happy with what you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is so commonplace now it is scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was privileged enough to have two tin cans with some string. I think they held the sound a little better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've known quite a few Melissa's in my day. I wish they had known Courtney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be careful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martha is crazy. I bet she learned some stuff in the joint, right? But for real I gotta save Mikey. Dude is my best friend, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it isn't that easy, ya know? You gotta have money to move and a place to go, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She loved you very much. What a wonderful gift she gave and even better advice. Please never make that trade, unless you are in the same position she was in: old age, a long well lived life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need more info in order to help. But yea I'd suggest contacting the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck. Something doesn't want you messing about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, are you satisfied? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was too poor for walkie talkies. I used to be jealous of all the kids that had them. Now I am quite content. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'll never go Downtown again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Related](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5uf78g/never_buy_a_mattress_off_of_craigslist/)

Have you ever felt like you were suddenly a part of something bigger? In the midst of your standard routine, carrying out mundane tasks that take no effort to complete, but now surrounded by unfamiliar people and places with no recollection of how you ended up there? Id like to share one such time with you now.

u/maddmikeyt and I were cruising through downtown in his ride doing the norm. Leaned back, speakers blocking out the outside world, taking in the skyline via sunglass-darkened vision. Pretty soon I didnt recognize some of the buildings that we were passing and popped the seat up to check out where we were at. 

*Yo, Mikeyboy where we headed my man?*

*Ah shit you gotta ruin the surprise? Just lean back and take it in, son. Well be done real quick.*

So I did. After another few turns we slowed to a stop under the 169. You know how there are those artists that risk their life to tag hard, out of reach places for notoriety? This had to be one of them because the entire underside of the overpass was covered, like it was actually constructed out of tag signs and bubble letters. I wasnt paying much attention to what Mikey was up to because I was lost in all that tag, trying to figure out where it began and where it ended. I was snapped out of my revere when Mikeys door snapped open and he got his ass dragged out of the car.

*Hey, yo, what gives son? Mikey, what you got us in?* I stepped out of the car and into a confrontation I didnt really want any part of. It was Mikey and I and some real tweaked out looking fools four deep.

To me: *Relax, my boy I got this, we cool.* 

To them: *Look I said I got fifty so just cut it and well be off aight?*

Tweaker king: *Nah man this is new, pure, stuff. You dont cut this. I told you it was an even hundy so cough it up.*

Mikey looked over at me in a way every best friend can understand. His eyes, expression, everything about him except his wallet said Ill pay you back, I swear. I pulled out two twenties and handed it over.

*Thats all I got so unless you got ten more*

Tweaker king snatched up it and tossed Mikey a small glass vial. *First time user discount.*

Him and his druggie friends were gone before I could sit my ass back down in the car. I was shaking my head in frustration and anger.

*Look, Mikey, you know I dont*

He cut me off: *Yo, yo I know, Im sorry. This is that new stuff people are talking about. I had to try this man. Ill pay you back man. Im good for it. I got that job at the Store now ya know?*

Yea, I knew. Making more money selling out the back of it than he did working the cash register up front. He promised he would get clean, whatever. 

**WHAM**

Two skinny arms ending in thin, scarred hands came crashing down on the hood of Mikeys car. We snapped our heads up to see who the hell was acting up. Tweaker King was back looking pissed off and high on something. Mikey was turning the key in the ignition when the dude came around the hood to grab at him. Two perfect handprints were pressed into the hood.

*You GOTTA be kidding me with this phony money, man. Pay up, DOUBLE!*

Mikey mashed his foot down on the gas, ripping away from the grip of Tweaker King and losing some shirt in the process. We tore out of there at top speed, looking like a movie car chase where the tires screech and the car leans hard to one side, hub caps flying off of the wheels. After rounding the corner I could hear another engine light up. Great.

*My man, why you gotta stiff em? Fake bills?*

*I didnt think he would notice. I got stiffed by the same bill so I tried to get it back by snatching some product I could resell. Dont be mad alright? Ill lose those fools and then Ill drop you off.*

*You know I cant get mixed up in this stuff, Mikey. I am clean, been clean a long time. My girl will kill me if get busted. Shell walk.*

We stopped talking so he could focus on driving. This was Downtown. Traffic was thick, even at this time of night, so weaving in and out was not easy. Tweaker King was in some riced out white Honda that hurt my ears and he caught up quick. They can really tune those things, you know? He came right at us, mashing his bumper into ours and we both lost control. Mikey spun one way, Tweaker spun the other. I am not sure how but one of their tires popped. It may have just been bad tread or maybe debris on the road, but we were free either way.

Mikey get the car turn around and we started to make our way back out of there but that crazy dude fired up the Honda and came at us, blown tire and all. We could hear sirens closing in so we tried to play it cool. Tread was going everywhere and sparks starting shooting up from the rim when a cop pulled alongside him. I was too busy looking in the side mirror to notice another cop was right in front of us. Mikey slammed on the brakes and put his hands out the window. 

A short time later we are all on the curb wearing cuffs with the cops searching our cars. Tweaker King is looking amazingly calm for a drug dealer. I know his trunk is loaded. Mikey is freaking out next to me and I was just pissed. I was trying to make myself something else, you know? Get out of all of this stuff.

*If I make it out of this you aint gonna hear from me again, my man. Dragging me down and shit. Done with this..*

Mikey just hung his head. 

*I see you boys have been recreating.* The cop is holding up the vial Mikey just bought. *Its a good thing I was on the call. Other guys might not be so easy on you causing all this ruckus. But I am feeling generous today.*

Tweaker King had this big dumb grin on his face and held his hands out. The cop walked over and pulled out his key, removing the cuffs and whispered something. Tweaker King went to work on switching out his tire and eventually drove off. What the

*I am going to give you boys a choice. You can go to jail or you can take this [holding up the vial] and start selling it to your friends. There is only enough for one so who is it going to be?*

Mikey looked like he was about to crap himself. No way was I going to take that stuff. I didnt even know what it was. Slowly Mikey reached out his cuffed hands. The vial dropped into his cupped hands and I swear I could see it moving around like it was alive. I know liquid kind of looks like that anyway but this was different. It wasnt normal. 

*Mikey, dont man.*

Too late. 

The cop removed our cuffs and whispered something to Mikey, then got in his car and drove off. 

*Yo, man what did he say?*

*He told me to kill you once he left.*

Mikey took a step toward me and I saw something in his eyes that told me he was being serious. I ran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who drug others and rape them are bad, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was two daughters trying to extend their family line. The only way to make that happen was to get him virtually blackout drunk. 

The children of this incest became two of the worst nations which were later destroyed by God. 

I can't see anyway that this is trying to promote a good thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick Google search gives the answer: Maggie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, we are on the run. If I ever get a chance I'll make a new post - If we find my daughter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have me confused with someone else :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pencils have erasers for a reason. Keyboards have Backspace. Write your own life. Don't let this book define you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he is fat and stinky, so.. you know. It's ok to kill him, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me so thankful I am not a woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We rent so I couldn't install a system. The owner didn't want "holes in the walls" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People were coming and going for the hour or so we were there. It would have been pretty easy to slip something on without us noticing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely. Brian wasn't one of the two men that were caught in the van so he is still out there and the receptionist wasn't there when the police went back to the facility after the arrests. If I can find them I might be able to find my family! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to think of something to say, but nothing wants to come out. I am sorry, Jay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They scanned it or something to do just that but I haven't heard anything back about it matching anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope you didn't eat *our Richie*, the window-jumper. Haven't heard from him in awhile and I was expecting an update. Please don't be our Richie.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
