<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2527</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> his faction might not be on the best terms with Geralt

Thats a mild way to put it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom asks for my help with technical things for three reasons

1. I know about those things and can explain them so that she understands

2. I have the nerves of a cow. I can stay calm even if she doesn't get it

3. I know when I can just say *"chill the fuck out, I got this"* when I know better and she knows it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really need to do some other side questing after this quest too. There are 2 or 3 areas I haven't even entered yet
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay good. I have already romanced Josephine and was wondering about companion quests or such. I'm a perfectionist so I always worry I'm going to miss something important </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC real witcher medallion reacts to all danger while Fringilla's reacted only to magic and monsters? Not sure, its been a while since I read Lady of the Lake last time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 16:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fringilla's mediallion wasn't as magical as a real Witcher medallion but it did react to monsters on some degree. I was happy when in the end Ciri gave him a real wolf school medallion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to get a tricone hat before you do actual face reveal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 09:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family guy is definetly not for everyone. You need certain kind of sense of humour to enjoy it. Especially if you're easily offended by darker humour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each on their own. I doubt I could eat piece of that without feeling sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And fudge

Tbh that cake sounds pretty disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. -32C today and 4 hours and 40 minutes of daylight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finnish and my parents live in the woods (30 kilometers to the closest town) and we had alot of animals around. Mooses, Lynx, foxes even occasional bear and wolf. Well one of our neighbours (who lived around 1km away) had a habit of throwing leftover food out at side of a field and a fox would go and eat it and it became customed to human precence.

Well one night my mum came from work and the fox was sitting at the corner of our house (no idea why) and my mother tried to shoo it away with a broom stick. Well the fox didn't think nothing of it and when my mom started to inside the fox tried to follow her.

Now we wouldn't get close to the fox because we had no idea if he had any diseases or lice or something like that. Also we had a cat and a dog inside and if they had seen the fox a whole hell would have broken loose.

Tl;dr: A neighbour threw leftover food outside, fox ate it and thought all humans give food and tried to come inside our house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Met Your Father spin-off - Family guy did it first </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a rule in /r/AskReddit and preferred way to post in reddiquette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO when she locked Barney and Robin I'm the room she was being a good friend. She knew that if they only were friends with benefits it would crash and burn and most likely end their friendship. Even thought they eventually did crash and burn, at least they got to be in a real relationship and had some good times.

Also Lily isn't only bad friend in the group. Tbh Marshall and Barney are the only ones. Ted makes everything about himself and his problems, lily is selfish and manipulative, Robin is also very selfish and doesn't really care about the group. first she sleeps with 2 of the 3 guys in the group, basically brakes boths heart, leaves her best friend after divorcing one of the guys. And I just imagine that her and Ted's relationship did not last after the shows ending. 

But this is a sitcom. The characters are made extreme versions of real life people in the sake of comedy, just take a closer look at any sitcom characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess these are supposed to be lined together on a shelf or on a table. Not too bad as an idea but execution, not so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the first time I read the books and found out that Emhyr was Ciri's dad it was real *What the fuuuuck* moment. Especially since [Spoiler](/s"Emhyrs plan was to have a kid with Ciri so he could get Cintras people on his side") --- spoiler about the last book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents have a cat that is basicly mute (only "growls" and meows in extremely rare occasions. Only heard him meow once in 4 years) and it is fun to watch him when he wants to go outside or wants food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 09:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The girl in the fireplace is my favourite too! It kinda shows the more human side of the 10th doctor. How he got bit heartbroken when he didn't get to travel with her after all. I think 10th is more emotional and human than any other of the new doctors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish that was possible. I'm pretty much in "I can't get a job because I dont have experience and I can't get experience because I can't get a job" situation. I did 2 interships during my studies, one was in a top agency in my area and other in a printing house. I guess I can't get much more guidance. 

I guess there is very little of what I can do. There are 9 graphic designer positions open in the country I live and 4 of those are for developers. And all but 1 is at least 500km away.

Also damn I wish that jobs would inform that I am not suitable applicant or that I didnt get the job. Wating is so annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the second one was much of a cliffhanger either. We knew Sherlock was alive so it was just a question about how he will come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 09:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I agree, I was just making a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddammit Jon, come up with your own stuff once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Brombadil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit torn. His character is alright, kinda silly on the surface but still very mysterious. But I can't stand the part of the book. I find it very unnecessary and tedious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, many people disagree but I think they did the right choise to exclude Bombadil. Even though I think they were bit too serious time to time, Bombadil would have been too much.

Also people would have complained him being bit Deus Ex Machina, just kinda randomly appearing to save the hobbits twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, thats an unfortunet spoiler since it gets revealed in the last book... Its kinda major reveal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q903TTTqEEQ Less famous song about Delilah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only played for around 6 hours but so far i really like it. The freerunning and combat took bit of time to get used to but now it feels much more fun. Also Paris is beautiful. The side activities are great and co-op is lot of fun. 

You're right, Ubisoft should take Unity and improve some aspects and they could make AC great again but I fear that they wont since Unity got such a bad rep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 06:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that proves my point, she is most definetly not a dude in a wig. I still think her character is going to be important later on in the season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just love the character customization in Unity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I like that they added possibility to do different kinds of character builds to the game](http://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/179415084210478898/3FE7C2C32CC0C13F729ED3C27EC873F61B1E6B1C/?interpolation=lanczos-none output-format=jpeg output-quality=95 fit=inside|1024:576 composite-to%3D%2A%2C%2A%7C1024%3A576 background-color=black) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civ V was the perfect game for that. I remember when I first got it and me and my friend started playing for the first time. So many times we said "okay one more turn and then to sleep" and we ended up playing for 5 hours. First "one more turn" happened around 3 hour mark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? There arent any subreddits. I know I can filter out nsfw content but how would I filter out advice animals? Or sob stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kbelwagen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Prometheus school of running away from things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was she really wearing a wig? I watched that scene again and to me it doesn't look like one. More like she was just nervous and scratching the back of her hair or something. It doesn't really move. 

I could be wrong though

~~EDIT: But she is going to be some shady character. Especially since they didn't credit her~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I watch game of thrones. But I still find it creepy when people secretly photographs celebrities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spoiler tag shows okay for me. And yeah, I like the Black Flags version of the Creed too. Thats one reason I wish there was more focus on it earlier on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing that the dev's didnt realize how popular BF would be after AC3 got such a bad rep after release. BF's popularity was pretty much suprise to everyone, I remember before it was released people were already proclaiming AC series dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No dont get me wrong, Black Flag is the most fresh game since the first one but I think they could have made more games for Edward since Black Flag has kinda little focus on the assassins until the later of the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is that it plays alot different than the previous games. I've played the first game and the Ezio trilogy and both had the focus on the Creed and assassinations while Black Flag has more focus on character developement and pirating. Its not bad, but for some reason it doesn't feel right to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love his character because of that but I feel like I'm playing an origin story. I wish they had made more games for Edward. The Creed is much more mysterious in this game than in others I've played before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye, but Ezio had 3 games while Edward only has one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been playing Black Flag and there is one thing that bothers me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I want to say that this game is awesome. The combat is fun, game world is gorgeous, characters are interesting and the boat combat and basic pirating is lots of fun. Only thing I dont like about the game is that it doesn't *feel* like an Assassin's creed game. Towns are fairly small so parkour isn't that much fun and I'm 14 hours in (around 30%) and the Assassin's Creed is only a small side plot. Edward is just a pirate who happens to wear the outfit of dead assassin and has some assassin friends. I just got my diving bell and found out that [James Kidd is a chick](#s "James Kidd is a chick"). And I'm still not an actual assassin. 

But overall its great game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 13:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like that would be even possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least in reddit you can filter them out. I never have advice animals or boobs in my frontpage of reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 09:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to get one of those but I just can't justify using almost 50 on a cup. Its a great for a gift though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creep shots, boobs, advice animals, overused memes, Bill Nye... Imgur frontpage in a nutshell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 09:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You finally arrived, but our records don't show from h'where."

-Imperial soldier in Seyda Neen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You never should have come here"

-Bandit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/superbowl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said in another reply, I'm not really big person on social media so I guess this is just one of those things I dont get and never will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ofc there is no harm but I just dont see the other side of it either. Then again I'm not really big person on social media so this might be one of those things I dont get and never will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, its my opinion (and judging from the downvotes its a unpopular one) 

I get that we do pointless things for fun but I just dont see the fun in this. Its like version of those things people do for awarness (like the ice bucket thing) except there is no cause </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty bad prank. I mean I see a female friend post picture of avocado online I dont think nothing of it. 

Part of the fun is that the person you are messing around with realizes that he/she is being messed around with which doesn't happen .

[Reminds me of this](http://i3.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/000/738/025/db0.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what's the point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remeber when I was like 14 and saw girls doing this type of stuff but when women 20+ do this I just dont get it. It doesn't make any sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fact: Bears eat beets.

Bears.

Beets.

Battlestar Galactica. 

EDIT: Spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thats what its called! I love this type if lettering but I never knew whats it called
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in that case I need to learn to draw! 

I've actually done Lithography myself before, it was real pain in the ass to carve the plates. But I really love this type of design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any guides on the basic forms of the typography? Or should I just start copying these via hand and then start making my own? (I can't really draw) Also what is this type called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tips on how to go on learning this type of typography? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 12:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kilian has amazing sense of humour. Kinda similiar to mine which probably is why I like watching him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 08:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would totally wear a smart "watch" the size of a pip-boy. Mini computer on your hand would be kinda good idea, altought nerdy as hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 08:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I didn't realise that the husky was supposed to have a beard until I read it on the text. If you want to make it look like it has a beard, you should make more detailed illustration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This is my second account, here is funny randum picture of my shoe. Please give me karma" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tj7TV7QAmi0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 11:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I dont think this is supposed to be while walking, more like when you lift your feet on a feet rest or something. And usually then your feet would either be on top of each other or bit apart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 11:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephanie of House Something or Other, first of her name  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How big were the crews in 18th/19th century sailing ships/clippers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 21:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean those things were *huge*. Cutty Sark had 32,000 sq ft sail, 3 masts and it was 85 meters long. I'd imagine that types of ships would need alot of people to maintain and sail them but there is only so many people you can fit in ships like that for several months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 10:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me thieves guild had much more interesting characters. DB always felt like Astrid and Cicero are all that matter and everyone else is filler NPC and companions questline was so short that I never actually got to know the characters. They met me, I cleared one dungeon and suddenly I'm part of their inner circle. At least with thieves guild you had to do guests to regain the foothold in holds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 07:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choosing between Nick and Cait is the hardest decicion in the game. One one hand I love 40's film noir movies so Nick is awesome character, but on the other hand I really love Caits accent and staring down her arse (altought then we dont move so fast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded the mod that allows you have dogmeat with other followers and I think it was in the mod description that this was supposed to be in the game so all followers already "like" when you stimpak dogmeat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the part where [Spoiler](/s "Ciri is riding to the farm where Geralt and Dandelion are staying after she ran from Yennefer?") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats too bad to hear. What was so bad about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 100% the first and second game. I played the third for few hours but it was pretty laggy on my last pc (I pirated it to test it out, good thing I did since I couldn't run it) and I might get back into it now that I got it free from ubi30. Altought the setting of AC3 doesn't really interest me. I'm thinking about getting brotherhood and revelations from steam sale since I've heard the Ezio trilogy is quite good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its kinda like Wind Waker? I bought Black Flag since most seem to think that its better as a game (I've fallen off the AC wagon since I've only played the first games) I will probably play Unity later though. Buy it from some sail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do yourself a favor and do. It is definetly one of my all time favorite comedy shows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually didn't play AC3 pretty far. Mainly because my pc couldn't run it back when I first tried it. Is the historical aspect in Black Flag in big role in the game? From what I've seen it looks like its just pirates and not some certain historical events </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This helped alot. One thing I'm bit worried about black flag is being "stuck" in the ship. I like open world and freedom in games and I'm worried that in black flag there is going to be lot of small areas to explore and most of my time is spent on a ship. Especially if it turns out that I dont enjoy the sailing.

 I'm also interested in pirates as setting. And that the main character is a pirate instead of just an assassin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your honest opinion on Unity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 10:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But its common in f2p games. Little inconviniences (I'm 80% sure I wrote that wrong) like this are skipped with micro transactions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If eso was f2p it would probably have mpre microtransactions. Like when researching weapons and armor 

"Pay $3.99 to finish instantly" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there's one song that decerves re-recording, its Grinne Mhaol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, that song is near perfect as it is. Only thing missing is female background vocals. The song is basicly begging for female vocals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont worry, that fuck face was the good kind \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not with that additude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally unupvotable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 10:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you know, like super mario run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like my teachers said, good thing about ideas is that they dont have copyrights :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I lose all my souls because I keep dying trying to recover them \_()_/

But I guess I need to give it another try, I really want to get into Souls games so I was hoping souls 2 would have smoother and more "user friendly" controls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> QUICK, THE MODS ARE ASLEEP, WISH THEM A GOOD NIGHT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Amazing* work! I might just steal this idea, I love travel posters. I have the NASA exoplanet travel posters on my wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finnish, this is what it looks like here around 6 months  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 13:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh in that case he must have also played souls 1 too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 13:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, might give it another chance. I chose Pyro because my former roomate told its good class, he played ds2 though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 12:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I made it to the gargoyles. I played pyromancer but also tried to play thief. One problem to me was that I had no idea how to make builds so I think my character was kinda weak. It was fairly frustrating that the game didnt give much info on this. I like I play myself and not use online guides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 10:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I watch this online? I've seen some clips and it looks like a show I would enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used one for _two years_ before switching to android. I was amazed by the fact that there is actual multitasking on android, while on windows if you switched from website to spotify (for example) and returned on the website you had to reload the website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started using snapchat and I got to say I almost ditched it because I found the UI/UX unpleasant. For example the emojis that represent the "relationship" you have with your friends makes no damn sense. I'm always asking my little sister what they mean. 

Also I find it weird that people call snapchat a social media. I always thought it as messagin app and I use it like one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
