<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4589</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry Farage was a commodities trader. Same difference - his job was to nefariously trade other people's stuff about, without actually creating anything real. Like his father, he didn't dedicate his life to public service, he dedicated his career purely to his own self-interest. It clearly says that his dad was an alcoholic that abandoned his children. Maybe corrupt wasn't the best way of phrasing it and maybe I was being insensitive to the struggles of growing up with a single parent - I will retract that tiny detail from my argument if you want me to. Still though, OP was pretty insensitive  in mentioning how Miliband's dad was a Marxist and in neglecting the more pertinent fact that has actually impacted Ed's perspective more that both his parents were holocaust survivors. James O'Brein dug into the dodgy deals Farage did on that car-crash interview on LBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent quite a bit of time and thought on that post. If you're going to downvote it, at least make a counterargument to the point I was getting across. 



Source on Nigel Farage: http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-20543513

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would you prefer? Nigel Farage - public school educated, followed his daddies footsteps as a corrupt stockbroker? David Cameron - I don't even think I have to go there, he's descended from royalty. Natalie Bennett - Australian journalist, never had a real job outside of journalism and politics?

Maybe you'd like some perfect rags to riches type to be contending, whose perspective is so distorted because he just presumes that everyone has the capability of him. He'd big up his background so much that he'd refuse to see any of his own flaws. He'd have no guilt-induced moral duty to be in politics - having not benefited from a system that privileges the already privileged. He would have no impulse to keep up with the changing dynamic of British society. He would be way more out of touch than the people we have already got. Moreso to be as exceptional as he is and to be able to enter a very closed, nepotistic political circle he would literally have to be a psychopath - completely unrepresentative of the British public at large. 

Maybe you'd like to survey all 60million of us and find the most average person out there - lets say he earns 27,000 as an IT consultant, he went to a polytechnic and comes from Birmingham. Would he be able to speak on behalf of a Pakistani cleaner from Leeds or a nurse in London or a business owner in Glasgow? One of the beauties of British society is that there is no 'average', we will never have a Hugo Chavez type that unites absolutely all of us. More so, would he have any idea about how to understand all the people around him that came from or climbed up a closed net of politicos? Would he have to capacity deal with any of the stresses or tasks of being in charge of one of the most powerful countries in the world?  I live in the states at the moment and I can see these types in congress, they have no idea how anything works so they delegate most of their decisions to advisers that aren't accountable to the public and are trying to climb the greasy pole without a sense of public duty.

I think being snarky about where our leaders came from is pointless. I'm a Labourite but I think my fellow party members are making a cheap jibe by criticizing Cameron for being born into wealth - he didn't choose his circumstances of his birth. Yes, there's a structural problem in parliament - it's too white, too male, too middle-class, too many people that have only worked in politics before and too many people that only got there through connections. We need to make some structural changes that might be painful in the short term - including all women/bme/working class shortlists. You're not going to change the essential reality of our system by electing a leader that defies the norm. If anything, you're going to obscure the fact that Cameron, Miliband, Clegg, Farage, Bennett ARE representative of the majority of our elites and we have a problem that needs to be changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It would be so much easier if snow was black </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 18:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snow is terrible. It causes sunburn by reflecting light into your face. If snow was black not only would it absorb light but also heat and it would melt quicker. Also we would be socialized to think that black water is not disgusting to drink so it would be ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Sartrian radical freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 17:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red is associated with socialism and militancy, pink seems more reasonable, social-democratic, approachable. They could have used that [weird union jack](http://www.globalpost.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/gp3_small_article/labour_conference_manchester_united_kingdom_september_29_2012.jpg) but that's meant for blue collar workers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 04:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the issue - if there were problems with a local school I may visit the school governers - if they couldn't help because there was some kind of external problem I'd go to my council. Where I'm from, we have a unitary authority meaning that all local power is vested in a single body; when I lived down south there was a city council and a county council and nobody could tell you which had which powers. In some places there are parish councils that deal with micro issues. 

If the issue was larger, I'd go to my MP at his surgery - he's a feckless idiot though - which means a petition is probably the best thing. Some schools exist outside of the control of the local authority, in which case I'd have to contact the national government minister for education directly. Some issues pertaining, for example to regulations can only be sorted out at a supranational level so I spose Id have to go to my MEP (whose name I don't even know). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 03:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a large part of the reason he supported equal marriage was so he could justify tax cuts to married couples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 18:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labour on foreign policy, economy, democracy. Lib Dem on Education and Europe. Green on Immigration. Tory on welfare (fuck that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 17:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He used to have some good scoops and he wasn't tied to the westminster circle back during the Blair/Brown premierships. Since he got a column with the Sun he's been doing his best to do suck up to Murdoch. The HSBC mandating Tory policy has been the biggest scandal as of late, but all he can talk about is Labour funding. He's meant to be the biggest online investigative reporter in UK Politics -- which prove why internet journalism is no substitute for real journalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 02:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People that read the FT need to know the news without a bullshit filter because they'll be making investment decisions based on the stories that happen that day.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 01:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Funded by Owen Jones's pet think tank

Here's a more recent poll that puts Labour on the far-left, the Conservatives and UKIP on the far-right and the British public on the center/centre-left https://yougov.co.uk/news/2014/07/23/britains-changing-political-spectrum/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A free-market conservative has just admitted that the corporations are subverting the press in modern Britain.  

He's always been an extremely liberal conservative. He was a massive supporter of David Cameron, he's wrote ant-israel books and as late as last week he wrote a piece in the speccie arguing that Ed Miliband was a great opposition leader. He's basically the opposite of Nick Cohen if that means anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FT, the Times of London, Reuters and the Economist are just as top notch in terms of news sources. Edit: I think The Private Eye is fantastic for investigative journalism too and The Spectator is a magazine favorite on the centre-right



 It's worth noting as well how people actually consume news.  

[This](http://www.gallup.com/poll/163412/americans-main-source-news.aspx) gallup poll gives a pretty good picture of national news consumption in the US. Television accounts for 55% of news consumptions over there; they don't have the same broadcasting regulations that we do so national news comes through sensationalists like CNN or unashamedly partisan channels like MSNBC and Fox. Internet sites comes next - which is obviously far more advertising driven and entirely unregulated; judging from the stuff my freinds post on facebook these are sites like the drugde report and breitbart that make Guido Fawkes look liberal. A bulk of this will be tweets sumarising stories or comments on the page rather than the stories themselves too. Print comes next - and, aside from the new york times, the publications you mentioned aren't even there - the bulk of consumption will come from gossip magazines and tabloids. Finally - talk radio makes up 5% of consumption and in the states this is basically right-wing crap that truckers listen to like  - Glenn Beck, Rush Limbaugh and even Alex Jones.

In the UK things are on the decline and we have some big popular outlets like the Daily Mail and the Sun and some people even get their news from things like the Lad Bible on Facebook. Still though, the BBC makes up for the vast majority on news consumption over here - and although it has its flaws, you only need look at the way american redditors talk about it to see how much better it is than 99% of what you get in the states. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because its possible to gauge the opinions of the population I'm a meaningful way? This is the general public that wants lower taxes and higher spending - drug legalization and the death penalty - Britain to be a 'great power' on the international stage without getting involved with foreign aid, humanitarian intervention or European alliances. If there was a major demand for an economic revolution, there would be a mass exodus right now - but political involvement has barely changed in England at least. If anything, the political spectrum has shifted way to the right - Enoch Powell is no longer toxic, the issue of the day isn't whether we should enter the Euro but whether we should leave the EU and the public are set to vote for a kind of austerity we've never seen before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because that's the global consensus. If we lived in the 60s we'd have two corporatism parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 05:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting an argument, but that was one of the best responses I've ever had on reddit. 

If this particular group is neglected - why is it that every speech on the economy or benefits has men at work in a construction factory in the background? Why is it that the Cameron's entire programme is about drastic action on complicated social and diplomatic issues - EU referendum, benefit cap, tougher on criminals, action to stop terrorism etc? Why is it that Miliband is forced to match Cameron on all of this, posing with The Sun and emphasising   perfunctory bullshit about soldiers or football clubs? Why is it that so much column space has been dedicated to 'white van conservatism', 'blue collar labour', 'working-class UKIP' etc?


The same thing happens in the states - stars and stripes covered truckers and farmers are given top spot in political adverts and every politician has a backstory about castrating hogs or working as a mechanic. 

It's stupid - these people don't claim a monopoly on the salt of the earth; IT consultants, window cleaners and quantitative surveyors play a big role but scarcely get mentioned. Nor do immigrants that actually do crappy graft work get much of a say in the political process. 

I think the concerns that you mentioned tend to be based on emotive reflects - daily mail headlines rather than actual knowhow. There's no way to argue with these positions - they have everything to do with individual identity and nothing to do with that's best for society. I'm sick of all this pandering; the world has changed are there's nothing you can do about it apart from suck it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 04:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quite happy with Labour as an inclusive, Liberal party. I don't think that nationalistic middle aged, white tradesmen are representative of the truly afflicted members of society or a major voting bloc with anything constructive to say. 

I'm glad that one of our governing parties makes decisions based on facts and evidence and not socialist ideology . I'm happy that Labour isn't afraid to reach out to people who wouldn't traditionally vote Labour. I acknowledge the reality of the image-centred newscycle and the importance of networking with the 'liberal elite' in politics. 

This is the world we live in now. You can't blame it one Kinnock or Blair, it's a reality that social democratic parties are facing in every single democratic country in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 03:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're saying that the only thing that matters in politics is the budget. That's categorically wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference in planned spending between Labour and the Tories is the biggest it has been since 1992. The Conservatives want to cut capital spending and Labour don't. The Conservatives want to cut the schools budget and Labour don't. The Conservatives are hand tied in that they can't raise taxes, while Labour are proposing a whole bunch of populist measures to make up for the deficit. 

The only conceivable way you could say that the two main parties are the same is by pulling out some situtationist arguments about how everything in society is merely a representation about what has been or something. This is literally the biggest election since the Thatcher years - and it's likely that we will see more than one party in power this may anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I have no idea what that has to do with economics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If France gets over herself and stops associating neoliberalism with us Anglo-Saxons bastards, she could easily become the biggest economy in Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto on the fraternity point. It was so weird being demeaned while pledging but I think it was worth it for my sex life alone haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 19:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me how much progress this government has made in those two areas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 19:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The libs have an almost identical prospectus to Labour. When polled the majority of lib demand members say they would prefer a Labour coalition to a Tory coalition. It's pretty obvious that the next government will either by a coalition of the right or a lib-lab deal with rogue left parties working with them on a confidence and supply basis - so yeah, you should vote liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much everyone - I have to put on my best american accent when ordering coffee to avoid the inevitable "where are you from? "No, but where in Britain?" "Manchester is near london, right? I went through Heathrow once..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've probably been to somewhere like LA or NYC where it's pretty common to have foreigners around. Where I'm from 90% of people haven't traveled outside of a handful of neighboring states in their entire lives. The obsession is real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brits who have lived in America: do you think your personality has changed for the worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 07:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I've been studying in New England since August last year and it seems like every single conversation I have is about being British. We all know how obsessed yanks get "oh my gaawd your accent is so sophisticated [even though I'm a manc with a mr beanish twang]" "have you seen Dr Who before - I have a scalf!" and it's easy to take well to the attention. Our frames of reference are completely different - I have absolutely no interest in any american sport and congressional politics seems to bore. So there's little you can actually talk about apart from how different America is to the UK. Without being a lapdog, it's easy to take to the very positive archetypes they have for us. They're absolutely obsessed with us and its pretty hard to avoid the conversation. Literally every conversation starts with "where are you from" and a brief explanation of how Britain is different to America. 

All this forced introspection - and the fact that it's so easy to fall back talking about what it's like to be British makes me feel as if I'm become more myopic, self-obsessed, narcissistic. I'm hoping I won't be an absolute backwards baseball cap-wearing prick when I come back that has literally nothing to talk about. Do any expats feel like this is the case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 05:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the field has strongly pursued the use of statistics and making rigorous mathematical models that are empirically testable

Maybe for micro economics, but at the end of the day you can can make statistics about anything - but the number of extraneous variables in the entire global economy (varying from the voting behaviour of cypriots to the weather in new hampshire) just make things too complicate to calculate. 

 mathematical models that are empirically testable

No they aren't. Academics can't just, say stimulate the construction industry on demand, you need politicians to do that. Sure, you can make models that looks very similar to economies, but ultimately thats like creating a 3D simulation of a rat to conduct lab tests - completely pointless and unnatural. As much as you want to dress up economics with statistics, it's catagorically a  *social science* and that means it's about human motivation and behaviour, which is impossible to fully understand no matter how advanced human technology becomes. 

 Non-state-socialist academics actually know that they cannot predict the market (otherwise there'd be no need for a market). I don't expect them to predict how the markets go. I expect them to make predictions from models that simplify markets. The map is not the territory, and their models of markets are not the market.

Right - so you're saying we actually can predict markets. Why then has nobody found a model to completely rig the stock market with 99.99999% certainty? Why are economies so sensistive to external shocks if governments could hire people to tell them exactly the way things are going? Why is it that several completely opposing schools exist and nobody can say with certainty which is the 'correct' school. 

Honestly, it seems like you're pretending to be 'above' non-mainstream ideas by dismissing any kind of unauthodoxy and asks us to listen to 'the experts' instead. Well listen - they're just as flawed, just as corrupt and need just as much scrutiny as the rest of us. Dressing someone up in a labcoat and telling everyone that they know more about the public than the public themselves and that they have somehow found a monopoly on meaning is a totalitarian idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 04:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said that Steve Keen has written extensively about it - and he has. Economics is known as the 'dysmal science'; to expect academics to predict how the markets go would be like asking historians to predict the future. I recommend you watch the Matt Damon documentary 'Inside Job', it shows how senior figures in the monetarist world were paid off in the pre-crises years to support failing policies and institutions. The facade that economics is a science leads us to trust charlatans that, against the grandiosity of the world finanical system know as little as we do about how everything works. 

Besides all this, it's a CIF video - its not meant to be dry, it's meant to inform and provoke. Expecting the guy to cite everything would be like expecting a regular CIF article to come with MLA-style references at the bottom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 23:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The literal translation of democracy is people-power. The queen has no real power to do anything constructive - instead she ties us as a nation and as people. Her office acts an anchor - without a popular and traditional head of state, we would lose a sense of who we are and why we  should sacrafice for greater good of the British state. 


I'd also like to contribute a thought I've had: the queen gifts us with knowing that no, not everyone has a fair chance of making it to the top of society. While Americans pride themselves and define themselves by their republicanism, they're blind to the lack of opportunity that exists in their country. Having a monarchy led to class-conciousness in britian, which is turn led to an innate distrust of power (look at prime ministers questions or the way business leaders are grilled in select committees) and a polity willing fight for its own interests. By contrast, Americans became so welded to the idea of the 'american dream', leaders were able to manipulate this naivety to crush socialist movements and push for the interests of a wealthy elite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 22:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was printed by the state and it is regulated by the state. By all means, mega corporations are free to use other forms of payment but since they choose to 'promise to pay the on demand' in the pound sterling, they have to play by the rules we as a society decide upon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but RT is so transparently Kremlin propaganda it's hard to get anything useful from it. The BBC isn't like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 15:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but if you think you're getting anything other than infotainment from RT you're wrong. It's literally Kremlinist propaganda - it prides itself as being the left wing version of fox news and it deliberately focuses it's stories so the west looks bad and Russia looks good. Aljazeera are much better but their middle east coverage tends to have biases - toward the quatari emirit, towards palestine, towards regimes unfavorable to quatar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 15:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's objectively wrong. You can't just make assertions like that with no basis in facts. The BBC is not beholden to any interests. I live in America and people regularly tell me how the BBC is the most accurate source of information - more so than the NYT with its political neutrality and more than NPR with its international perspective. I have had communications directors on Capitol Hill tell me the BBC is the first place they go to. Fox News is infotainment, CNN is so heavily slanted to conflict and sensationalism it's just hard to discern anything while the Pravda was literally state propaganda in a backwards, totalitarian regime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 04:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if you're serious or not because online commenters have been known to say things like this
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 00:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily - some taxes, like the VAT are downright regressive and likely to hit the poorest members of society the most. Taxes on the minimum wage can actually incentivise people to stay on benefits. Extremely high income taxes bring in less revenue - compare tax returns under Callaghan vs the later years if Thatcher - and this means less money for hospitals, schools etc. Right now taxes are chronically low and reductions aren't going to help the poor/middle class as much as other interventions, but theoretically there can be moral arguments for lower taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 21:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has there ever been a government  both socially liberal and economically conservative? ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ridiculous title. She was saying that it's worth turning up to the ballot station anyway just to spoil a vote if nobody on the paper represents your interests. You're framing it as if she's trying to disenfranchise the young when she was making a good argument for Political involvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 18:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we came 6th on the [Climate Change Performance Index](http://www.caneurope.org/resources/latest-publications/ccpi) this year which is bloody good considering the fact that our English speaking cousins: Ireland, New Zealand, America and Australia came 10th, 43rd, 44th and 60th respectively in the advanced-industrial world.  The Climate Change Act (hat tip to Ed Miliband for the [crazy work](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LB34vXKL5w0) he put into it) legally obliges us to cut emissions 34% by 2020 and 80% by 2050 - if the rest of the world meets that we might just be able to handle global warming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't the same be said for terrorism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 22:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good idea - revolutionary even, just imagine how capitalism would change if people didn't have to go to shitty jobs at poverty pay to live. 

I think the biggest thing that people neglect is that welfare only works if there's a good amount of public support for it. The changes to the tax code and the benefits system this government have made are among their most popular policies. Brits see social security in a very negative way 'how's it fair that some layabout can take MY hard-earned money'. Nobody political party can change that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's the hypocrisy - greens are the biggest advocates of criminalising hate speech and overturning the principles of the judicial system in the name of social justice - but for them joining ISIS is perfectly fine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but my tenancy agreement in my halls of residence means that they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 20:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an expat in new hampshire  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
