<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject419</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 22:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps changing it up, have 90 damage and 95 accuracy or 95 damage and 85 accuracy, kind of making trade offs for higher hits, if less often </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the tick thing just as limiting as Java when it comes to mechanics?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artisan workshop armour is a 5 minute thing dno if good for Ironman though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High level pvm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically my question to you is where does max / high level pvm go from here? We have t90 weapons and armour for everything, will jagex make higher tiers? Or are we doomed to forever have the same weapons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 13:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few, iv been doing about 5 to 10 QUESTS a day lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fashionscape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 10:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm new to this fashionscape thing but since I got 6 keepsake keys and just got sunglasses I was wandering if anyone could suggest me a nice fashionscape including the glasses please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit and runescape basically  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 19:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I get rid of the perk?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Concerns about eve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the first thing I did when invention was released was put the talking perk on my drygores mace. I am now concerned because it's just trying to be kinky and it's boring, not even humorous. Why couldn't it be more like the magic sword from the colour of magic or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 01:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got banned from /food for calling a mod a fascist pig  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 23:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? The guide looked a lot longer than 3, I just assumed they got harder as the series progressed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 23:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv done it now, thank fuck. It wouldn't have been so bad if I hadn't got halfway through years ago. And now there's a 4th I have to do apparently. That will probably be the last quest I do lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done it. I hate puzzles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ten out of ten would buy max good idea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elemental workshop 3... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I started this quest years ago, I cannot remember what I did or how far I got. My quest log says

 iv managed to lower a section of puzzle, giving me access to a new puzzle piece. Iv managed to lower another section of the puzzle I now have access to a really tall puzzle piece. 

Can anyone point me to a guide and where I am at? Iv been doing puzzles but nothing is happening. Getting stressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New quests I love, fate of the gods is my favourite quest ever,the only quest iv had voice acting and music on for the whole time. Absolutely amazing. However, the old quests I find tedious and irritating and not enjoyable. Having to do the older QUESTS to do the new quests just puts me off and makes me say I hate questing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tactical wank works for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right sorry, I hope you don't think I was talking bad about what you do or anything, I just didn't look at the screen or comments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the latest one on YouTube, I may have exaggerated the time frame but the bit that I listened to was mostly batman vs superman and technical difficulties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shower sex is the fucking worst thing ever. I'd rather not have sex than try have shower sex. I fucking hate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 15:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried listening to this but for like an hour it was just technical difficulties.... Is this normal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Runescape podcasts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 14:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv recently just got really back into runescape and I'm wanting a podcast I can listen to whilst playing rather than just afk and Netflix, I want to be more active in the game lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 21:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is halberd good at Abby demons?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a temporary fix to this, I can't remember what it is though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 13:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry? I don't understand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 09:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not all bad mate, my birthdays have been forgotten since I was 13. It doesn't matter though, it's just another day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all I did, and for my 21st. It can suck but it also means I could do what I wanted to do, mainly eat pizza drink pop and playv games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to add, both would be augmented so the torva degradation would be irrelevant too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nex vs gwd2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I was just looking at the new armour, specifically the melee armour, and noticed it's pretty much the same stats as torva, except no health or prayer bonus. So, other than monetary constraints, why would anyone use the zaros stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought chronicle was this, was immensely disappointed when I downloaded the beta. I can't wait for it, I love idle games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gizmos on tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 21:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible to put a gizmo on my crystal hatchet that is in my tool belt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 04:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was guna be an idle gam for  Mobile devices, I'm SURE I read that somewhere. Am I wrong?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So putting genocide on Both weapons would be useless?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about if duel wielding? Do perks stack?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 19:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy having my hair did, that's generally thought of as a woman thing. Plus I have a pony tail  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 21:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably fishing before cooking. Or mining before smithing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That name was like a time machine for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 15:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. Ignorance sucks ass  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 15:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens when I run out of charge and try using the gear?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 13:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not trying to train it, I'm just putting augmentors on the things I can cos why not? I'm not guna destroy them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to make it so we can augment lucky gear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 10:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lucky bandos chest plate and just tried augmenting it and turns out you can't. Is it possible to make it so you can? I have a literal 1.5m cash stack so can't afford to buy a new one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 23:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, I'm doing salamanders until I get 27 then I shall be training passively and siphoning. Think iv got more or less the gist now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 22:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy things from GE?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 21:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so I am going to be training my melee from 90 att and str to 99 via slayer. I have drygores and bandos armour. Can I augment these and get invention ezp from them without destroying anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Invention through pvm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, so I'm just coming back since invention came out, think I have 12 or 14 before getting fed up and leaving. So, now I'm back I keep hearing of training invention through pvm and i was wandering how exactly? Sorry, I know this has probably been explained lots of times but I can't see the woods for the trees </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 13:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much info ty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 13:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh? How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 09:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except, at least in my country, you can't fly with a bottle of liquid that isn't clear. So no go friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My reversal is tomorrow... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 14:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my ileostomy reversal is tomorrow and if I had the ability, I would be shitting my pants. All I remember from getting the ileostomy is so much pain and suffering and everything else and I'm terrified and I need someone who has been through to tell me what it's actually like please. Please help me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 20:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it? I think your doing it wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 00:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the garen skin about an hour ago so that works  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glutony by far  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 00:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queen! There's the live aid thing or whatever and that other that I can't remember the name of  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a dinosaur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv never been in a subway cos I'm scared of the ordering system, so, how the fuck do I just get a sammich? I don't like wet or green shit, I just like meat and perhaps cheese  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 16:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually laughed at this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 14:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My penis is the only weapon I need and that stays in my pants until needed. My phone lives in my right pants pocket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 14:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that thing in bottom right that everyone seems to have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 02:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just starting 07, iv played rs over team years but recently bored of rs3. My question is is there anywhere I might find a rundown of the things that are different to when it was 07 and from rs3?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 00:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It stays on even with the SFX off, I can't figure out how to shut it up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 22:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hover what someone else is, think it's good when 3veryone does it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 22:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see, what kind of knot is that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one is krepo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only time I get main is if main support or secondary mid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a few things I feel. This leads me to believe iv had a lot of shite sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 15:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wing it. I never studied and got good grades  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 12:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use more toilet paper with my ostomy than I ever did before...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love kindred  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Report"

League community in a nutshell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What item?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the UK, should probably have mentioned that

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the UK, should probably have mentioned that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I used to be a labourer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 15:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I used to labour for a plumber but had to stop when I became ill. He has since retired. I'm going to be coming back to the working world in about September time and I was wandering how I might go about becoming a plumber? Working as a labourer was honestly the best time of my life and I think it's what I want to do with my life. 

Edit: I live in the UK, didn't think to mention that, and I'm 22 if it matters  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 09:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way of things I'm afraid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 09:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mid is most popular so will be hardest to get basically  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are gizmos tradable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 08:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically I was wandering if you made a gizmo with hella good perks if you could sell it, as well as the augmenters I think they are called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 00:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only weigh 11 stone so I'm a skinny fuck that plays it all week, then travels at weekends essentially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 23:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an adult living on disability at my mothers, where dies that put me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. Is there a tldr by any chance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for my ignorance, but what the general gist of kalista hecarim mordekaiser and thresh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting a curve to be honest not a table  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 15:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just how I play it. My most played champ and how I like it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 00:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think cs has something to do with it too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 23:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rush devourer, farm alot, gank at 6. Go for ad and remember you w gives loads of as, doubles when you block a spell with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how to play vayne, I only jungle. I play a lot of nocturne ekko and elise. All very strong. Rengar is strong. Elise is a little more mechanically difficult than the rest and I play nice as an on hit Max attack speed assassin. Ekko or elise when my team is lacking ap, I play both off tank ap. R3ngar just ult double q a squishy and they dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her kit makes it incredibly easy to kite, so yes, while she is squishy and will get blown up if you run in head first, played right it doesn't even matter. Plus her ult makes her essentially immortal for like 3 seconds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 21:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kindred is ridiculous right now, and not often banned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 21:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what elo is either. It's all a bit confusing. Winning good losing bad right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 21:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a MMR?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 21:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended in b5. 7 win 3 loss, good kda n most games. I don't get it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lamb one looks good, wolf's left eye and lower half looks a little wonky. All in all a good do! I like the style. Hope you don't mind the honesty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I still lose 9 put of 10 games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 15:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do they have to do with him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 14:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ban Lee if anyone wants to play him. B5 lifer here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 00:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know he's next on the list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 00:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 15:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nocturne devourer blue one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 19:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people in England drive "stick shift" as you call it, and we all manage to text and phone while driving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 12:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ashe tutorial then kogmaw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 11:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened yesterday?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 11:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1yth and 14th of Jan? Where can I watch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is the next competitive season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 11:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the entirety of world's and absolutely loved it. So I was wandering when the next similar thing is and where I could watch it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warwick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Levelled all skills over 71 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 12:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By levelling up my Thieving skill, I achieved at least level 71 in all skills.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Levelled up Thieving. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 12:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I levelled my Thieving skill, I am now level 71.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 20:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for episode order. Then again, I saw them in a stupid order, something like 5 2 1 3 6 4 7 and I love it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultralight for winter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 19:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi iv just got my pack together for a weekend away this weekend, expecting a lot of rain, we are flooded, possibly even snow and a lot of wind. My problem lies in weight. My winter bag is excellent for keeping me warm, but is huge and weighs a ton. So, any suggestions on how to lighten my lode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 18:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to sound so fucking chipper you obnoxious twat. Pretentious fascist pig. Oink oink bitch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 13:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little bit, its a double yolker!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look what I found! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 13:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vango nyx 200 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 21:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone ever used a vango nyx 200? Iv just seen them on a website for a outdoorsy shop as I'm looking for a new tent and it sees pretty good for the price, but feel it may be too good to be true. So, any opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tenner says this is from chip shop not home made  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 01:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive my ignorance, but what makes this stuff so good? Is the white bit fat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 22:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this spoiled too, and it did perhaps ruin the film, purely because of thinking I bet it happens here all the way through. But, I was still right at the edge of my seat and in tears, and it was still incredibly moving and amazing and everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a chart somewhere using fruit as reference I believe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
