<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4602</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we give Counterparts some love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 02:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is often my go to anti-depression album. It's both dark and heavy to get the anger out, but still very positive. It's this, Test For Echo, and Vapor Trails that have got me through many lonely nights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell me you aren't in love with him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 02:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "As relaxed as a Greyhound on the first day of summer" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Face Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 06:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I'm going to give hugely controversial statement and say that this is probably in my top 3 songs from Presto on. It's so happy and always makes me feel good when it pops up on shuffle. Such a shame that they didn't play it live as I can totally imagine a huge fireworks pop at the transition to the chorus and a lot of cool light and pyrotechnic work. Would've fit beautifully in the Clockwork Angels tour with the strings, but I digress.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/Ywa3BMpUhsQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Please date me :}" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 01:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Roll The Bones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 13:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you to /u/IISycHll for filling in for me yesterday.

This song is *amazing* live and so much fun on bass. The wordplay is complex and this is over all an amazing spin on such a cliche subject.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/YoE1SrWWyNA)

[Counterparts (I think) tour](https://youtu.be/oV9yUvNp6z0)

[Rush In Rio](https://youtu.be/v9P6SFp_BFE)

[R30 tour](https://youtu.be/cqW4QFGBDkY)

[R40 tour](https://youtu.be/kZmK4PKrJ60) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Dreamline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 20:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really pumped for this section! This album is stupid underrated and it's recently become one of my favorites!

This song sounds like it'd be great live which is a huge part of this album. Presto feels like it's only intended for the album while this album feels like the songs were pretty much crafted to be done live. This is no exclusion

The bass has a very unique and interesting part and that guitar solo is classic!

The meaning is very true and beautifully written.

 We're only immortal for a limited time.

I view it as Anthem Part 2. Live the life you want to live, go as far and do as much as you can.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/Xtt0MUB93Ms)

[Roll The Bones tour](https://youtu.be/nxzGbFdl_mw)

[Counterparts tour](https://youtu.be/rYkUre8FWIQ)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/XhYuYxRlDRY)

___
On a side note, I'm bummed that I had to leave the R40 stream super early last night. It was almost 10 and I had barely slept the night before. I'm super upset that I bailed so early. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAILY DISCUSSION - If they were to do a reunion show and you got to choose one song, what would you pick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd choose Harold The Barrel. It's so underrated and they've either barely or never played it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R40 stream live RIGHT NOW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the stream link](http://sync-video.com/r/rfddWd8n)

In about 5 minutes, one year ago, Rush hit the stage in Tulsa for the R40 tour. Just now I thought that it'd be cool to watch a bootleg from the Tulsa show together. I've started a room (link above) where we can watch this video at the same time.

Until 8:30pm in Tulsa (9:30pm NY time) I'll have a fan's alternate version of R40 playing. You can join the stream free, there's a chat there, just enter the username you want (preferably the same as the sub) and just hang out until we begin R40! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're in Michigan, I'm sure you'll agree this is the album of the day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 21:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Presto recap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 14:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This album is actually really good despite what I've hears in the past. The only kind of weak song on it (in my opinion) is Scars and that song is even bearable.

But what do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAILY DISCUSSION - Favorite song on each album/of each member's solo work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 20:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is a bit harder, it's asking you to choose one favorite song from each album. I'll use your answers to make some cool statistics!

___
From Genesis To Revelations: I've only listened to it once and I can say I don't really like any of it enough to have a favorite.

Trespass: The Knife

Nursery Cryme: The Musical Box

Foxtrot: Supper's Ready

Selling England By The Pound: MOONLIGHT KNIGHT!

The Lamb Lies Down On Broadway: The Colony Of Slippermen

A Trick Of The Tail: Entangled

Wind And Wuthering: Afterglow

...And Then There Were Three: Undertow

Duke: Duchess

Abacab: Dodo, Lurker

Genesis: Home By The Sea

Invisible Touch: Domino

We Can't Dance: No Son Of Mine

Calling All Stations: Calling All Stations

Peter's solo work: Signal To Noise

Phil's solo work: The Roof Is Leaking

Mike's solo work: The Living Years

Steve's solo work: Icarus Ascending

Tony's solo work: From The Undertow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May The 4th Be With You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Available Light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 15:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song is awesome! There isn't much I've never said about this song so I'll keep this short and sweet.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/cKHp2tgYYxc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAILY DISCUSSION - Favorite album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 13:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the logical choice for the first post. At the time thus was posted, what would you say is your favorite Genesis and non-Genesis album?

___
***Genesis album=Selling England By The Pound***

Especially Moonlight Knight and The Cinema Show+Aisle Of Plenty. Its bookends are classic and the 3 big songs are phenomenal!

***Non-Genesis album=The Human Equation by Ayreon***

Any Dream Theater fans here need to hear this. James LaBrie does some vocals on it and is great as always. There are some very Genesis inspired sections, but it's just great overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Hand Over Fist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 14:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this song. It's often hated, but I think it's great. Sure it's a bit cheesy, but I like cheesy. The verse is awesome and the chorus is catchy.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/MKUOMtq0NQw)

[Music Video (I think, at school can't check)](https://youtu.be/547O5uJh8SE)

___
Presto ranking:

1. Red Tide
2. Available Light
3. The Pass
4. Superconductor
5. Show Don't Tell
6. Presto
7. ***Hand Over Fist***
8. Chain Lightning
9. Anagram
10. War Paint
11. Scars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you guys be interested in a daily discussion thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub could definitely use a boost in material, and when I started the daily discussion thread on /r/Rush it certainly helped there and now on a slow day we get maybe 2 or 3 posts. Would you like me to bring that idea here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The subreddit album is going to take a little bit longer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was depending on two people to mix it, one is now out of town for the next week and the other didn't respond. So now I get to mix it. We can either mix it or just compile it into a zip, label it, and post it. I'd like it mixed which I may be able to do this week, but that'll mean you'll have to wait another week. So what do you guys think?

We could *also* redo the track voting in a better format than I did cause I kind of messed up with that. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the loser in your high school? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a real world easter egg that needs light shed on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I waited 2 hours but it was worth it for all 5! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 08:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Games with similarities to these 5 games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are my top 5 games of all time:

1. Dark Souls 2 - I like the exploration, secrets, and difficulty in this. It's hard, but not impossible. With enough determination you can definitely do it. The combat is a bit clunky, but the variety of attacks and the rolling helps make up for it. The lack of forgiveness is amazing and is something that's been seldom explored since the original Zelda on NES.

2. Silent Hill 2 - I play this game purely for the puzzles and story. Everything about those two aspects is phenomenal. Is anybody here familiar with The Lamb Lies Down On Broadway, the album by Genesis? If so, this is the game version of that. Atmospheric with loads of plot and symbolism for people to explore for years to come. Plus the challenging puzzles are loads of fun.

3. Wind Waker - I love the large open world with so many places to explore plus the combat is fantastic! The plot isn't too much to talk about, but it does have a nice spin to make it more believable rather than "save the princess you just met". The puzzles are fun, the characters are very entertaining, and the art style is beautiful and fills me with joy.

4. Katamari Demacy - Not much to say, it just makes me happy. Cute music, cute graphics, an original idea (if you forget about Snake). It's just fun.

5. Portal - If you haven't caught a trend, I love puzzles and atmosphere. If a game has two of those things then I'm all set to go. Funny characters, an enjoyable plot, and great gameplay is all I need.

Consoles I have are PS2, Xbox 360, Wii, and 3DS.

I've also played Bethesda games as an FYI, so I know those fit right up my alley. Just thought I'd mention that. But I've only played some of Skyrim and Fallout 3, enough to feel content </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Red Tide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 16:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still sick but I'll still make these posts because I feel horrible not doing so.

This song is my favorite on Presto hands down. The only thing that brings it down is its not full. This is what prevents Presto from being a top 5 album in my eyes. It's just too flat.

But flatness doesn't bother me in this song because every second is perfect! I'm excited to hear everyone's opinions on this.

___
[Remastered version](https://youtu.be/c_fvqxrXWAk)

[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/gO8W0qEmMPQ)

___
My Presto ranking:

1. ***Red Tide***
2. ?
3. The Pass
4. Superconductor
5. Show Don't Tell
6. Presto
7. ?
8. Chain Lightning
9. Anagram
10. War Paint
11. Scars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a new player, how easy is it with offline mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 01:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that it's best to help people with bosses to get souls as well as full health without an effigy, but because I don't want to pay to play online (I'm on xbox) I'm stuck offline. Is this going to get tough?

I'm 3 hours in and have a decent handle on what I'm doing. Only 22 deaths so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ku Klux KLand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you bootlegged TA Live the old fashioned way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 21:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that I mean audio only. I'm planning on doing it for the Detroit show when I go just so I can have it as a thing for memories as well as to have a live recording of it. But have any of you done it before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a fan edit of Trilogy of Error? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the episode where the day plays out focusing on Homer, Lisa, and Bart (in that order) with each of their storylines intertwining. I was curious as to if there was a fan cut where all the events are in chronological order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Anagram </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 13:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sick today, but this is a pretty good song. Sorry about the short post.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/MBfV5bDKorM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's considered their best album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard people say Californication, but I honestly love Stadium Arcadium more. It just seems like one good song after the other. I specifically like Jupiter.

Other than SA, I really like I'm With You as that's when I started listening thanks to a friend and Raindance Maggie, but I never really got into them until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New fan, what's considered their best album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've hear Californication, but I honestly love Stadium Arcadium more. It just seems like one good song after the other. I specifically like Jupiter.

Other than SA, I really like I'm With You as that's when I started listening thanks to a friend and Raindance Maggie, but I never really got *into* them until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent over half of the school day looking for evidence of the Massey Hall bootleg. This is a Google doc of my findings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How was your childhood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 00:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My top 10 Coheed songs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 21:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been listening for roughly two months now, and I've got a top 10 list for them and I want your thoughts on it.

1. 2113 (favorite)
2. The Willing Well (full)
3. IKSOAE:3
4. The Hound
5. Mother Superior
6. No World For Tomorrow
7. Island
8. World Of Lines
9. Sentry The Defiant
10. Welcome Home (listened to it to much) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Superconductor Superconductor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 15:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my favorites. It's cheesy, goofy, but fun. Not much else to say.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/D_YCoQrq0WU)

[Music Video](https://youtu.be/XcYP5XP0Rlk)

[Roll The Bones tour](https://youtu.be/ThZ9vUAFRYQ)

___
Presto ranking:

1. ?
2. ?
3. The Pass
4. ***Superconductor***
5. Show Don't Tell
6. Presto
7. ?
8. Chain Lightning
9. ?
10. War Paint
11. Scars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Presto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 13:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love love love this song! It reminds me of summer because I listened to it constantly then. This would've fit perfectly on R40 but whatever. It's just a beautiful song.

Don't ask me, I'm just improvising.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/V-HKrpIJO0s)

[Time Machine tour](https://youtu.be/Tcsb8SClvgI)

___
My Presto ranking:

1. ?
2. ?
3. The Pass
4. ?
5. Show Don't Tell
6. ***Presto***
7. ?
8. Chain Lightning
9. ?
10. War Paint
11. Scars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Scars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 15:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an alright song. I like the synth bass line. It reminds me a bit of Red Lenses honestly, but it's nowhere near as good. I used to love this but now I think it's one of the weakest on Presto.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/lOKiWdC0k98)

[Presto tour](https://youtu.be/99P7uxHDpEc)

___
Presto ranking:

1. ?
2. ?
3. The Pass
4. ?
5. Show Don't Tell
6. ?
7. ?
8. Chain Lightning
9. ?
10. War Paint
11. ***Scars*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My family got a cat off the streets and into our home. It was going great, but she's been bullying one of our others, please help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have three cats. Emmy, Luna, and Faythe (the newest). Emmy we rescued from a very bad household, Luna we fostered and then got, and Faythe who we adopted. Faythe was a neighborhood cat and she immediately clung to me. Originally we were only going to take her in for the winter, but she got very attached to me and vice versa.

Now, she and Luna get along beautifully. They'll play constantly and then lay together sometimes when they aren't. However, Faythe has been attacking Emmy who was declawed by her previous owners. Because of this, she can't defend herself. And Faythe has been attacking her. Maybe it's playing, maybe not, I don't know, but it has Emmy horrified. She lays on one couch, hisses at Luna (they got along beautifully before) and hisses and growls at Faythe. I've ended up having to feed her on the chair. She won't get up to use the litter box so she goes on a couch or chair or, (until she wasn't allowed in it anymore) my parent's room.

My parents have only tried separating them, but that won't work. They say they're at a loss but I don't think they've even tried much of anything! Please, what can I do to make her stop. It may be too late, they already have a friend who may be interested.

She's a sweetheart. She'll curl up in bed with me, purrs like a lawnmower, and is a beautiful cat. Is there anything I can do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A greyhound in the grass marks the first day of summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 17:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - War Paint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 13:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song is an...it's an interesting little ditty. I listened to this song a lot when I first got into Rush. It's not great, but it's the inspiration I needed to loose weight along with The Pass, Marathon, and others.

The line that stands out to me is obviously "The mirror always lies." I've used it to help friends with self esteem issues as well as to help my own self esteem. It doesn't have the best writing of any Rush song, in fact it isn't as good as 90% of them, but still. It's alright.

The instrumentation isn't much to write home about either.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/TvLos5-pDtY)

[Presto tour](https://youtu.be/sCsBeJB59LE)

___
Presto ranking:

1. ?
2. ?
3. The Pass
4. ?
5. Show Don't Tell
6. ?
7. ?
8. Chain Lightning
9. ?
10. ***War Paint***
11. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any teens want to talk about Rush? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being 15, it's hell on earth trying to find others around my age to talk about Rush or (thanks to my interests) anyone to talk about anything. Let me know if you're around 15 (preferably 13-18) and, I dunno, maybe we could make a Skype group/kik group/whatever.

Ghost of an edit: no personal info will be shared, don't worry. Felt I should clarify that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Pass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 14:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, this song. Seriously, I owe my life to this song. When I was in a super deep depression last year, this song is part of what helped me keep going. I'm sure plenty of people are the same way.

The lyrics are a masterpiece, the instrumentation is beautiful and haunting, and the climax of the song "No hero in your tragedy, no daring in your expense, no salutes to your surrender, nothing noble in your fate. Christ what have you done?" is like a punch in the gut.

Another little thing I love is the sweeping synths. They're so pretty.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/qTHJv3SAMBY)

[Presto tour](https://youtu.be/Nebn_BW28dw)

[Vapor Trails tour](https://youtu.be/aWCVxx2QIls)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/vjDskdgXztU)

___
My Presto ranking:

1. ?
2. ?
3. The Pass
4. ?
5. Show Don't Tell
6. ?
7. ?
8. Chain Lightning
9. ?
10. ?
11. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geddy Lee circa 1980s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone want to jam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 15 year old bass player and I just want to jam with someone, specifically around the Okemos/Haslett area. My main inspiration is Rush, but I'm also inspired by a variety of bands including Yes, The National, Genesis, Green Day, Muse, and more.

This will probably not get any responses. But I figured I'd just put it out there in case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite fact about ants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Chain Lightning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the verse of this song. Kind of reminds me of Money For Nothing. At least Weird Al's cover, cause that's all I know. The chord changes are really cool and everything blends really well. The lyrics are also awesome.

By the way, I didn't post yesterday due to daylong testing at school and me fully forming my opinion on Presto. Spoiler: I like it.

***That's niiicce***

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/kuqSjKgq3Sk)

[Remastered version](https://youtu.be/Xe9KdJXnKSQ)

[Cover band](https://youtu.be/2caiNu-Oy7U)

[Drum cover](https://youtu.be/zXq-u-4swz4)

___
My Presto ranking is coming tomorrow. Sorry, school's been busy as hell and I lost my last draft of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE #2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 01:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, this has been a crazy time! Our list for this update is:

* Subs
* Wiki
* EP

___
***SUBS***

We now have 500 subs! I'm so happy about this. Thank you all so much for joining, it's really fucking rad of all of you. I would like to say, however, we're doing something extra special for 1,000 subs that will

#blow your fucking mind.

So be sure to spread the word of the sub so we can hit that goal and surprise you with that amazingness that's still brewing.

___
***Wiki***

Our glorious mod /u/Condensor worked super hard to make a super rad [wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/TWRP/wiki/index) that contains tour dates, discography (all that wasn't lost in the Great Space Laser War of 2011 at least), lyrics, and much much more. Go check it out if you haven't. It kicks ass!

___
***New EP***

I feel it's necessary to tell you that they have an EP coming out on April 23th of 2016 (hey, that's *this year*)! It's called Guardians Of The Zone and contains these songs:

1. Time To Shine
2. Rock N Roll Best Friends
3. Makin' a Move
4. The No Pants Dance (feat. Ninja Sex Party)
5. Business Tips
6. Groove Crusaders

Makin A Move is up on their bandcamp, so check that out too!

___

Once again, thanks so much for subbing. I'm pumped for this upcoming 1000 sub thing, and I'm pumped that we even made it *this far*.

Rock on, /r/TWRP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (At 7:40) This guy lists the Rush discography with years in under 30 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 21:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Show Don't Tell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 14:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song is actually kind of proggy. The bass is *AMAZING*. Honestly, it's probably one of the coolest songs they've made.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/jFNaq1x6mqk)

[Presto tour](https://youtu.be/--OPPqaqx7g)

[Counterparts tour](https://youtu.be/eV5Y9ym0q2w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oktopus - Eyes Open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 04:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oktopus - Eyes Open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 04:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rush fan starter pack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [JOKE] Rush fan starter kit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 23:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Hold Your Fire recap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 00:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This album. This fucking album. If I weren't into heavier stuff at this moment, it may be in my top 3, but this week that's kind of jumped out of there. I think there's a lot of underrated gems, but this isn't their most underrated album in my eyes. That's Roll The Bones.

___
New ranking (personal):

1. Lock And Key
2. Force Ten
3. Prime Mover
4. Mission
5. Time Stand Still
6. High Water
7. Tai Shan
8. Turn The Page
9. Open Secrets
10. Second Nature

But really, everything from 5-9 are tied for #5.

___
Album ranking (personal):

1. Clockwork Angels
2. Caress Of Steel
3. Hemispheres
4. Signals
5. A Farewell To Kings
6. Permanent Waves
7. Moving Pictures
8. Power Windows
9. Grace Under Pressure
10. Presto
11. ***Hold Your Fire***
12. ?
13. 2112
14. ?
15. ?
16. ?
17. ?
18. ?
19. Fly By Night
20. ?
21. Rush
22. ?
23. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do the rewards for My Nintendo change monthly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 16:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody want to mix the subreddit album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 02:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've started it but am really not proud of how it sounds, and want this product to be top notch quality. I know that we have some talented folks on here who can make a beautiful mix. I was wondering if anybody wanted to do that and make it sound awesome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a sub to get friends on Miitomo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 21:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started and have no friends who have it. Is there a sub to exchange QR codes or whatever is needed to add friends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - High Water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 16:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is THE most underrated song of the album, hands down. I'd even dare to say it's ***the most*** underrated Rush song of all time. The synths are beautiful in it, and when he says "The water takes me home" I get chills down my spine. So beautiful!

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/o3iQNLA8oJo)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Garden reduced me to tears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 03:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again. I almost can't listen to that song, it's like an emotional punch to the gut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Tai Shan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 18:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this song, a lot don't. This will be an interesting post.

I think the lyrics are cheesy as all hell, but the instrumentation is too beautiful to hate.

___
[Lyrics](don't bother) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Turn The Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fear for tomorrow and Wednesday, but I think we can all agree that this song is a classic!

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/E1qgn7KSPgo)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/r5gH8ehjm5I)

[HYF tour bootleg](https://youtu.be/qiywWlA25Lg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SUBREDDIT ALBUM: Tracklist, cover, and mixing begins! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the voting was through upvotes. I didn't want to mention it because I wanted it to be genuine, and /u/sonickarma's tracklist one. Here it is:

___

Disc 1:

1. Metropolis Part 1
2. Breaking All Illusions
3. Trail Of Tears
4. Space-Dye Vest
5. A Change Of Seasons
6. Finally Free
Total run time: 76:56

Disc 2:

1. The Glass Prison
2. The Best Of Times
3. Sacrificed Sons
4. The Dark Eternal Night
5. The Looking Glass
6. The Ytse Jam
7. In The Name Of God
8. Our New World

Total run time: 75:43


___
I love this list so much, great work! Now while I'm getting into mixing, I need to ask for you talented artists on /r/DreamTheater to make the most *kickass* art you can! I'm really looking forward to seeing this part.

I'm gonna admit, I'm becoming a bit nervous with this result. If you guys want, we can redo this in the summer when I have more time to plan. I just don't want to put out something of subpar quality.

As for the mixing, I'm just gonna make it flow. When finished, I'll put up a flac and mp3 version with the album art so both audiophiles and people who are more concerned about storage space can listen.

You've all been doing great work and I'm interested to see how this turns out!

Cheers!

EDIT: Fixed the tracklist so it includes all albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What bass is used on Good Apollo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 21:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it's metallic sound. Like a Fender Jazz but clangier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oktopus's second album came out today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 16:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, here we are. We're at the end of the line. It's been an amazing year, but now that we've reached the end of the listen through, I have an announcement to make.

I'm no longer mod. I fulfilled my purpose on this sub (the listen through) so there's no reason for me to be here. In fact, I'm probably just going to chuck this Reddit account overall. So a tear-filled cheers

___
Anyway, The Garden. Wow. A journey from Garden Road to The Garden. I believe this song is a masterpiece. Truly. The strings and just...I can't today.

___
Instead of linking, let's go through a little best of.

How about the time /u/Arctos889 said that Tai Shan was his favorite song and reached the WORLD RECORD of -999999 downvotes? We broke Reddit with that!

Or how about the Dog Years thread where literally nobody posted? That was funny.

Oh! And when /u/berkmarhighschool made a really intriguing argument about Working Them Angles being about Communism? Classic!

My personal favorite is when /u/KieranX, /u/Mattou, and /u/Hokie23aa came together to try and take down our listen through BUT WE DIDN'T LET THEM, DID WE?

#***DID WE?***

___
**A**nyway guys, it's been quite the adventure with you! **P**lease continue this sub log into the future, and know you'll always be in my heart. **R**eally, **I** mean it. **L**ike...really.

**F**reewill, **O**ne little victory, **O**pen secrets, **L**a villa **S**trangiato. i will always remember this

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 08:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a very pretty song. Honestly, I'm very out of it as it's 2:35 am and I'm having a lot of issues sleeping. I can't wait to see all of your comments on this! I think this is a very dividing song, but I may be wrong.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/nlUhIXZnFYw)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/hVXMTNKIEak)

[Snakes And Arrows tour](https://youtu.be/tMBMsy4TzkI)

[A great full band cover](https://youtu.be/Zc473sbFZYk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory: it is what is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking at the lyrics of "it" when I realized there were 32 descriptions of it. Who helped Rael through the Chamber of **32** doors? Lilywhite Lilth. The song named after her is the twelfth on the album. The twelfth description is "It is the jigsaw".

it is the puzzle.

This makes a bit of sense I think.

* "The puzzle's only knock and knowall (no wall, there's no true answer), but I like it"

* When you eat right through the puzzle (when you explore it, when you find everything there is to find), you'll see everything alive (you'll see pointless details important)

* Any rock can be made to roll if you [spend enough time on the puzzle] 

* "The puzzle is purple haze" Hendrix often gave various answers to the meaning of Purple Haze

And most important:

* The puzzle is both the chicken and the egg

I think that last one means that the puzzle is boh John (the chicken, the mature and developed one) and Rael (the one in the cocoon, waiting for birth). The key to the puzzle isn't it, it's who Rael and John represent. That means it's just Rael. The answer to the puzzle is that John and Rael combined. If you didn't know, John is the good side of Rael, at least that's widely believed. If John and Rael combined that means Rael's good now.

The key to the puzzle is that Rael's journey is over...I think. I'm confused now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Lock And Key </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 14:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy. This is on my list of top 10 Rush songs for sure. It's an absolute masterpiece. The lyrics, the little piano hurried in the verse, the proggy bits, the use of clicky synths, the guitar during "on the price of being free" in the chorus and also during "so we keep it under lock and key...lock and key...", it's just. GAH!

This is a great one to bike/run to, and the intro to the live version is great. I wish they did this for R40. This is easily my favorite on the album. It's haunting and just amazing. I seriously cannot express how much I like this.

Also that guitar solo is a classic. This is a song that's easy to airdrum and headbang to and impossible to not.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/y8cTl8y3SKo)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/1IvcppD9vgI)

[Music video](https://youtu.be/MLGgzN8Kd7Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teramaze Working On New Album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 16:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Prime Mover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 15:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely adore this song. It's easily one of the best on this album. The synth part mixed with the jumpy bass line makes it just beautiful as well as the optimistic lyrics. This is also a good example of a cool guitar part on this album.

 Anything can happen

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/kHUfEyakl7E)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/O49F8pB8bH4)

[Drum cover](https://youtu.be/6MLS_wrUeSI)

[Bass cover](https://youtu.be/ZRw6IlaS4xM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guitar pedal mimics the sound of a Mellotron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what Winery Dogs songs do you guys want to see at MP's birthday bash? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 19:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be okay with literally anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Second Nature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 14:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is, by far, not my favorite song on HYF. I don't know why, I've just never got into it all that much. It's alright, but just not on par with the rest of the album.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/ZGwGR1BltFo)

[Bass cover](https://youtu.be/s866xu0T-_k) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another dream setlist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 07:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is molded from the T4E tour setlist.

___
1. The Spirit of Radio
2. Working Them Angels
3. Lessons
4. Animate
5. Kid Gloves
6. Neurotica
7. Red Barchetta
8. High Water
9. Limbo
10. The Trees
11. Secret Touch
12. Cold Fire
13. Closer to the Heart
14. Hemispheres (complete)

**Intermission**

15. Dreamline
16. Far Cry
17. Carnies
18. Roll the Bones
19. Hope
20. Halo Effect
21. Leave That Thing Alone/Drum Solo/Red Lenses (medley)
22. Limelight
23. Natural Science
24. Force Ten
25. Emotion Detector
26. Countdown

**Encore**

27. Tom Sawyer
28. Beneath, Between, And Behind
29. Working Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a fun idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 03:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #EDIT:

***THIS POST HAS NOW BEEN CLOSED FROM SUBMISSIONS. FOR THOSE WHO PARTICIPATED, THANK YOU SO MUCH. I NOW HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO. :)***

Let's make another subreddit album, but this time, instead of being Rush songs, it's songs by other artists that we like. What I need *you* to do is to leave a song or two that you really like that's by another artist (only one song per artist please) and, if we get enough results, I'll make a poll at the end of the week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teramaze - Trapeze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 00:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By the end of the day, I will be 100% caught up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...well at least with the podcast. I'm gonna listen to the audio book too, but that's over 10 hours!

I just finished the actual podcast (minus the bonus episodes) and bought every live episode a few minutes ago. Plus I saw them on their murder mystery tour and will see them in a few weeks.

After nearly three years of listening to Night Vale I'm so glad to be caught up again for the first time in over a year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could this classify as Prog? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 17:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HAPPY EASTER! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 07:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know what the hell this is (Okemos area) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 23:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiment: Some songs can be perfectly combined </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 18:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This started when I realized that Cold Fire was remarkably similar to Red Tide. I combined it, and it worked PERFECTLY. This made me curious, and I brainstormed what other songs sound a like. I came up with this list and decided that I would test them.

1. In The Mood vs. I Think I'm Going Bald - This one went pretty well. It's the same basic chords I think.
2. Bastille Day vs. Headlong Flight
3. Freewill vs. Caravan
4. A Passage To Bangkok vs. BU2B
5. Ghost Rider vs. Secret Touch
6. Scars vs. Seven Cities Of Gold
7. Heresy vs. You Bet Your Life
8. Cinderella Man vs. Wish Them Well
9. Red Tide vs. Cold Fire

I'll test these out and put the results up on Dropbox so we can maybe have a sick combination album!

Do you guys have any other similar songs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SUBREDDIT ALBUM - Songs announced/tracklist challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week we had some tough picks, and a lot of people didn't even vote due to their favorite songs not making it. However, we did get 141 responses, so that's cool. The songs (in order of album, 2 for each, 1 epic) are:

___
* A Change Of Seasons
* The Ytse Jam
* Afterlife
* Metropolis
* Learning To Live
* Space-Dye Vest
* The Mirror
* Trial Of Tears
* Peruvian Skies
* Finally Free
* Home
* The Glass Prison
* Blind Faith
* In The Name Of God
* Vacant+Stream Of Consciousness
* Sacrificed Sons
* Panic Attack
* Ministry Of Lost Souls
* The Dark Eternal Night
* The Shattered Fortress
* The Best Of Times
* Breaking All Illusions
* Bridges In The Sky
* The Enemy Inside
* The Looking Glass
* Three Days
* A New Beginning
* The Path That Divides
* Our New World

___
So, I guess you guys chose these...

Anyway, what we're doing now is the track list challenge. Pretty much, you just organize it how you want and then next Saturday we vote! The only rule is that it'll be 2 "discs".

Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Open Secrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 13:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this song is criminally underrated. Well, maybe not underrated, but very rarely discussed. It's a really beautiful song with a classic chorus. My biggest issue with this song is it was NEVER PLAYED LIVE! ***HOW?***

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/ypwtq1ShnHI)

[A tribute band playing it live](https://youtu.be/MBGdnXtT6Og)

[A bass cover](https://youtu.be/7KyNK4DSW7E) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever read A Step From Heaven? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 13:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading it in school (9th grade) and it's boring as all hell. I'm struggling to get through it because *nothing happens*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Portnoy Plans 50th Birthday Set on 2017 Cruise to the Edge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think are the angriest/most aggressive DT songs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much all of ToT honestly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Time Stand Still </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 15:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a pretty good song. Not their best, but definitely not their worst. This was my jam last summer. The video is probably the best thing they've ever done and really showed off their ability to play perfectly while flying in a studio, over a lake, really anywhere.

___
[The masterpiece of a video](https://youtu.be/dMSFqXGZ5TQ)

[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/t0YwbAmCwz8)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/OhT4r2p56b0)

[Roll The Bones tour](https://youtu.be/Pu40t7nFsDk)

[Counterparts tour](https://youtu.be/5DukUbT6UMw)

[Time Machine tour](https://youtu.be/z-nnkbDpRHc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of the upcoming 2113 book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 02:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's got 16 or so short stories by various authors that are based around Rush songs, including a 2112 follow up by KJA and the stories that inspired Roll The Bones and Red Barchetta.

I for one am pumped for this. I'm just about to finish Clockwork Lives after reading Clockwork Angels very quickly and have preordered both the book and sample booklet that I hope to get soon. However, looking at the comments on some Rush news sites it looks like others don't share my excitement...it looks like nobody else does. Please tell me I'm not alone in this. PLEASE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some more albums/bands for me to check out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 17:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a lengthy read coming up, but eh.

Elements I love in progress:

* As a bass player, the Rickenbacker sound greatly pleases me and is always a plus
* Metal and instrumentals, but no strong screaming
* I'm weak for concept albums
* Long songs too
* As long as it doesn't have screaming, I'll probably be able to get into it

I'm a huge fan of Rush, Dream Theater, Genesis, and Pink Floyd. My top two current favorites of theirs are:

Rush: Clockwork Angels and A Farewell To Kings (although Hold Your Fire may be tied for second).

Dream Theater: Systematic Chaos (I've had ITPoE and TDEN on repeat today) and SFAM

Genesis: Selling England By The Pound (specifically The Cinema Show) and The Lamb Lies Down On Broadway (complex story telling is a plus)

Pink Floyd: Meddle (I saw a tribute band on Saturday and they did a fucking AMAZING version of Echoes, I seriously almost cried of sheer joy after it) and Animals.

___
As for other prog, this is what I've been listening to over the past few months:

* Her Halo by Teramaze (lesser known, but fucking amazing)
* Tarkus by ELP (I have it on at this second)
* Thick As A Brick by Jethro Tull (listened to this for the first time last night, fucking great, awesome drumming)
* SF Sorrow by The Pretty Things (I listened to this for the first time today too, and it's absolutely wonderful)
* Tommy by The Who (I've returned to this recently, but I was ***in love*** with this album/movie when I was little)
* The Mountain by Haken (This album is a classic, my favorite song is either Atlas Stone or Cockroach King)
* Every album by Coheed And Cambria (I saw these guys recently and that's what largely started my fandom, Good Apollo is probably my favorite album because of The Willing Well)
* Liquid Tension Experiment by LTE (I love the instrumentals and DT, so this is perfect)
* Lateralis by Tool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some great upcoming prog releases? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 17:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about Haken and that Teramaze is in production with their new album, but what are some upcoming prog albums that you're pumped for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Force Ten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 14:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a pretty damn good start for Hold Your Fire. Personally, this is one of my favorite albums and I'm pumped to get into the later bits.

I love the synths here. So awesome.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/hZG3FvjAtJE)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/8AFy7piA8UQ)

[R30 tour](https://youtu.be/xkC11WyY7J4)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/fufng_oC410)

___
Pre listen through personal ranking:

1. Lock And Key
2. Turn The Page
3. Mission
4. Time Stand Still
5. Tai Shan (sorry)
6. Open Secrets
7. Force Ten
8. Prime Mover
9. High Water
10. Second Nature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH #2 - Top 3 Picks and Final Choosing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 01:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***EDIT: I don't know why I keep calling it Listen Through. Sorry.***


If you don't want to read my bullshit and just want to vote, head [here](http://goo.gl/forms/QtRvvLNZme).

Anyway, these results were interesting, disappointing, and slightly predictable. The thing that pissed me off the most is that Outcry wasn't chosen. I love you guys, but come ON! That's an amazing song, and yet more people picked *Sacrificed Sons* over it?

Anyway, coming soon will be the 2 songs from each album that will appear on this subreddit album, and the setlist contest where you can comment the setlist you'd like it to have, and then we'll make a vote for it.

That's going to be from this Friday to next Friday and then I'm on spring break and will have time to mix it while the cover art contest goes on.

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Power Windows review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 13:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what'd you guys think?

Here's my new ranking 

1. Emotion Detector
2. Grand Designs
3. Territories
4. Manhattan Project
5. Marathon
6. Middletown Dreams
7. Mystic Rhythms
8. The Big Money

I truly love them all.

___
Personal discography ranking:

1. ?
2. Caress Of Steel
3. Signals
4. ?
5. A Farewell To Kings
6. Permanent Waves
7. Moving Pictures
8. **Power Windows**
9. Grace Under Pressure
10. ?
11. ?
12. Hemispheres
13. 2112
14. ?
15. ?
16. ?
17. ?
18. Fly By Night
19. ?
20. ?
21. Rush
22. ?
23. ?

___
The demos were interesting. It was odd to hear unfinished versions of these songs. I wish we had more demos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Mystic Rhythms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really sorry, but I'm both in school and have gotten no sleep. Can somebody please do my linking today? Super sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something kickass I just noticed in Mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 11:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got remastered versions of Rush to A Show Of Hands on my phone.

Geddy doubling Neil's little Xylophone type bit

Badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISCUSSION - On the topic of R40 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 22:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure we were all at least somewhat satisfied with the R40 set. But I'm curious, what are a couple songs that *you* wanted them to play that they didn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of Rush references I found in the Clockwork Angels book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished the Clockwork Angels novelization and I absolutely loved it. In fact, I just bought Clockwork Lives and am about 40-50 pages in. This is great because I'm not a huge reader.

Anyway, here's a list of Rush songs I found referenced in the book:

___

How It Is

We Hold On

Cold Fire

The Stars Look Down

Time Stand Still

Hope

Red Barchetta ("laughing out loud")

Bravado

Subdivisions ("sprawling on the fringes of the city")

Prime Mover

Dog Years

Chemistry ("a change of synergy")

Mystic Rhythms

The Big Money ("Bi-i-i-iig money!")

Peaceable Kingdom ("Justice against The Hanged Man")

Stick It Out

Roll The Bones

Presto

Chain Lightning

Lock And Key ("no one wanted to make a terrible choice on the price of being free")

Freewill ("he would choose freewill")

Driven

Red Lenses

Animate

Faithless ("I don't have faith in faith")

Natural Science

Double Agent ("Where would he rather be? Anywhere but here.")

One Little Victory

Tom Sawyer ("mean stride")

Spindrift

Far Cry

Ceiling Unlimited ("looking glass")

2112 (Discovery)

The Way The Wind Blows

Fly By Night

Dreamline

Turn The Page

Between The Sun And Moon

Mission ("exotic and strange")

Limelight ("long awaited friend")

The Enemy Within ("experience to extremes")

Resist

Force Ten ("tough times demand tough hearts")

Malignant Narcissism

Cut To The Chase

Crossroads

In The End

Grace Under Pressure (the album)

War Paint ("we see what we want to see") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Emotion Detector </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 01:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love this song. It's so underrated, but it's one of the best, if not the best on this album!

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/V4gG4F5z4OI)

[Demo](https://youtu.be/EJCvC9Xl-Kw)

[A nice fan made acoustic cover](https://youtu.be/ZgmyVPCMlnc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SUBREDDIT ALBUM - The first round of voting! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 00:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about time we get this goddamn thing off the ground, don't you think? :)

After the original front-runner of the subreddit album has seemingly abandoned this project, I've decided to take it under my wing. So you guys/girls may be a bit confused. Here's my schedule:

___
3/18: First round of track voting

3/22: Second round of track voting

3/25: Songs announced and tracklist contest begins

4/1: Tracklist is chosen, artwork contest begins, and I begin mixing

4/8: Mixing will be done, the artwork will be **Chosen**, and the album will be released as a zip file onto the subreddit

___
So we've got a little less than a month to go on this. If you feel like I should alter the schedule, please let me know and I'll considre it.

Without further ado, [here's the link to vote!](http://goo.gl/forms/dhmJTafZm8)

Be sure to select only 3 for each album and 1 for the epics question (the first one).

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R40 Live is now on iTunes video! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 00:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About the subreddit album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 20:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hasn't gone anywhere in months. With my spring break in a week, I'd love to take it up and organize and mix it myself. Would you guys like that? If so, I'll put a pull up tonight to vote for favorite tracks from each album. The top 3 for each album will be put in another poll, and the top 2 from each one will make it to the subreddit album. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome Dream Theater/Winery Dog fans! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 19:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I'm very excited to see how this sub grows. If you guys have any requests, questions, or ideas, please let us know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A request to Skyrim modders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started playing Skyrim again, and I realized (along with many others I'm sure) how awesome an Astonishing mod would be. Even it it were just Heaven's Cove, it'd be bad ass. Can anybody who knows how to mod Skyrim make this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Middletown Dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 13:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dreams flow across the heartland, feeding on the fire.

I always have thought of this as Subdivisions part 2. About chasing your dreams, leaving a normal life behind. Very similar to the story of Clockwork Angels.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/7t4SaJxu7SQ)

[Demo](https://youtu.be/AthRv__R_Lw)

[Power Windows tour](https://youtu.be/jvAfVeb6ZfQ)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/FtQ2yGJmXnI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Territories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 13:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In every place with a name, we play the same territorial game"

This is a common quote whenever I'm in a discussion about countries going to war for expansion.

It's a cool song. I love the goofyness in the line, "Better people! Better food! And better *b*e*eer*!" And then the chorus is just beautiful.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/RvM387NJTYg)

[Demo](https://youtu.be/yNddv53KROQ)

[Power Windows tour](https://youtu.be/ZFvnRP6v1rU)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/_OMBal69Odg)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/90lseLri1oo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Marathon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 13:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great song to run to and just an overall motivational tune. I love the lyrics and the synths on it.

[Demo](https://youtu.be/RJoCX83cjgw)

[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/MUcdRLn3bgM)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/rP58U_R3gK0)

[Time Machine Tour](https://youtu.be/9em3ff7hxw8)

[Cool bass cover](https://youtu.be/ANFWnh3P4NI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help finding a better remastered version of the self titled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the sectors versions on my phone for every album from Rush to A Show Of Hands because I love their mix and my friend's dad has got it back when it came out.

The issue is, now that I got a good sounding, 100% surround version of the first album, I hear the original track they recorded over very well in my left ear.

Is there a good remastered version that fixes this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This would've been a great cover for Under The Covers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of doing the, frankly overplayed, Misunderstanding, they could've done I Can't Dance by the same band. Dan's voice would've been perfect for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Manhattan Project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 15:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great one about...the Manhattan Project. I like the different feel to the demo.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/HTkicdO_64w)

[A music video that I made for it](https://youtu.be/BO_8YcYpDDk)

[Demo](https://youtu.be/I5syDQXxMM8)

[Hold Your Fire(?) tour](https://youtu.be/-7RaDUn7W84)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/6Swtx3phmrM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Grand Designs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 17:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I'm stuck in loading screens in Skyrim, I figured I'd make today's post! Here's a very underrated song, but not the most underrated on the album!

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/NkTfybI2ofE)

[Demo](https://youtu.be/6Vrdug6syMY)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/mIRTfQc3raY)

___
And now my fucking game crashed. Great.

___
Pre listen through ranking:

1. The Big Money
2. Manhattan Project
3. Grand Designs
4. Middletown Dreams
5. Territories
6. Mystic Rhythms
7. Marathon
8. Emotion Detector </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing Civ when... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 21:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REMINDER: If you post any pre-Device footage/audio, it will break Rule 3 and may result in a temporary ban or permanent ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to recent discussions on this sub, we feel that this needs to be restated just in case.

Edit: I'm going to resticky this as a fair warning. The band themselves requested to not have these posted and we are not going to disobey them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Peter Gabriel were to do two Genesis songs on this upcoming tour, what would you want him to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 17:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I feel like an encore of The Lamb Lies Down On Broadway followed by The Light Dies Down On Broadway.

It'd be beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Big Demo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 21:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Big Money Demo](https://youtu.be/05jVO29DDjY)

I think this version is too bare without And Richard's collaboration with the synths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Big Money goes AROUND THE WOOORRLD!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 15:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I'd like to start this off by saying that, for Power Windows, there will be two Listen Through posts a day. The first for the studio album and the second for the demo version.**

Okay, I'm sorry. This is my favorite song on Power Windows. I first heard it when I was barely getting into Rush. I watched the Clockwork Angels Live DVD and fell in love with this song. On my family's trip to Florida last spring, I had it on repeat along with Manhattan Project. It kind of reminds me of 80s Genesis which was my favorite band when I was little (I'm still only 15, so I'm not old at all). Specifically Land Of Confusion.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/-KqKMJmvk4s)

[Music Video](https://youtu.be/WQgu0MpnKq8)

[Power Windows tour](https://youtu.be/it3unMrUDpk)

[Hold Your Fire tour](https://youtu.be/zsskd9LCp_Y)

[Vapor Trails tour](https://youtu.be/MA77MZPK68Q)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/4VMbUzsXP78)

___
Pre listen through ranking:

1. The Big Money
2. Manhattan Project
3. Grand Designs
4. Middletown Dreams
5. Territories
6. Mystic Rhythms
7. Marathon
8. Emotion Detector

This hurts, because I love every song on the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ANY POSTS ABOUT AN ANNOUNCEMENT OF NEIL'S RETIREMENT FROM HERE ON OUT WILL BE REMOVED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 03:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will be treated as spam. We've known this since prior to R40, this is absolutely nothing new. I'm sorry, I try to keep posts open, but this is something that's just too ridiculous to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWRP AMA on the Game Grumps subreddit tomorrow at 4pm est! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've just received a message from TWRP themselves that they will be doing an AMA tomorrow at 4pm Eastern on /r/Game Grumps. So here's a little advanced announcement for you guys.

We (both TWRP and the mods) are very happy with how this sub is growing, and it's all because of you guys/gals.

You all fucking rock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Grace Under Pressure overall review/What I've been listening to </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, so now we're done with Grace Under Pressure. Where do you guys/girls (lol jk) place this in your temporary ranking of their discography? Here's mine (my top 10 are all tied tbh):

1. Hold Your Fire
2. Clockwork Angels
3. Counterparts
4. A Farewell To Kings
5. Hemispheres
6. Moving Pictures
7. Caress Of Steel
8. Permanent Waves
9. Signals
10. 2112
11. Presto
12. Roll The Bones
13. Power Windows
14. ***Grace Under Pressure***
15. Snakes And Arrows
16. Vapor Trails
17. Fly By Night
18. Test For Echo
19. Feedback
20. Rush

___
My new ranking for this album:

1. Kid Gloves
2. Between The Wheels
3. Red Sector A
4. The Enemy Within
5. The Body Electric
6. Afterimage
7. Red Lenses
8. Distant Early Warning

___
What I've been listening to:

Here's a few songs that I've recently had on repeat that *aren't* Rush!

[The Willing Well part 1 by Coheed And Cambria (to start you off)](https://youtu.be/3kyr_pmnDXQ)

[Five Years by David Bowie](https://youtu.be/yYwpnG-rkHI)

[Your Love covered by Ninja Sex Party](https://youtu.be/dtr6LSo-8FQ)

[Nights On Broadway by The Beegees](https://youtu.be/bqlbFA0qOoA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Between The Wheels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I start, do you like Daft Punk and indie music? Do you just want to hear something new? If so, come to /r/TWRP where I'm running a second listen through for *their* discography! You won't be sorry!

Anyway, here's another fucking amazing song. What else is there to say? So much fun to sing, and was one of two songs to greatly help me through my recent depression.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/zOgz8kM1VDg)

[Grace Under Pressure tour](https://youtu.be/AfgM1cZ6Cnc)

[Snakes And Arrows tour](https://youtu.be/QtXo7aYC2nY)

[R30 tour](https://youtu.be/U5-1W3wvsF4)

[R40 tour](https://youtu.be/HYUGDr2t-UY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Prelude </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the first listen through post! We'll be going through an album a day in a similar vain to what I've been doing in /r/Rush. Once this wraps up, I'll do another thing like I did in /r/Rush, which is a daily discussion post where it's something related to either twrp or the community that would for a great discussion.

Today's song is on the first TWRP album known to exist (as discussion on prior releases is prohibited by the FBI on account of it being too fucking amazing), and it starts it off, obviously. It's The Device Prelude! It's a neat little track that, in the style of a prelude, gives a great sneak peak at the album without spoiling the best bits!

___
[The song](https://youtu.be/j5CKFyff4i4)

[A Mario Paint version](https://youtu.be/aLGzI1J6ppY)

___
I'd like to mention, this is my first time listening to their discography as well. I'll be adding any live videos containing the song (this one's live version comes with tomorrows song as they're packaged into one nice bundle).

So what do you think of the prelude to The Device, TWRP, and the listen through? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early versions of lyrics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 03:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started reading Traveling Music by Neil Peart and it opens up with the lyrics for a demo of Workin Them Angels. Does anybody know if more lyrics like this exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Red Lenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 14:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i see red. it hurts my head.

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/0Wdn4OPZTX8)

[Grace Under Pressure tour](https://youtu.be/aqcwpTpGPBo)

___
My ranking:

1. Kid Gloves
2. The Enemy Within
3. The Body Electric
4. **Between The Wheels**
5. Red Sector A
6. **Red Lenses**
7. Afterimage
8. Distant Early Warning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will a VOD be available on twitch right when the stream ends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 03:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on my way back from a family outing and a will watch it if it's up right after. I'll be up till 7am roughly if I do so, but oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was used for the intro of Lock And Key live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 03:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanna know for a project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Kid Gloves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 00:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song is easily in my top ten Rush songs. I absolutely adore it ever since the first time I heard it while my family was vacationing in Florida. I was praying that this would be played in R40 and was distraught when they just played DEW. Such a bummer, I'd kill to see this live.

[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/TA0nyFR8krU)

[Grace Under Pressure tour](https://youtu.be/h3uam9fY_pc)

___
My Rankings:

1. **Kid Gloves**
2. The Enemy Within
3. The Body Electric
4. ?
5. Red Sector A
6. Afterimage
7. ?
8. Distant Early Warning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAMA 88 year old man who has had a hell of a life, AMA (details in post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #He's left now. I'll put this up again when I go visit him next month.

**EDIT: I'll be posting answers now**

**EDIT 2: I'm recording his answers and will upload it later tonight. There's some interesting things in this.**

Hey, I'm the Grandson and my grandpa is supposed to be here in a few hours. I've always been amazed at his life story, and thought it would be fun to share it with you and have you guys ask him questions so hopefully we can both learn new things.

Here's a basic rundown of his life:

* His family (not w/ him) moved to the US from what's now Croatia
* Grew up in a depression era Michigan UP mining town
* Was amazing at basketball (still has newspaper clippings)
* His dad died when he was 14(?) and he had to *wake up the postman* to call for an ambulance, walked back when he got no answer and was told "Come back with help or don't come back at all"
* His uncle had a bar (iirc)
* He worked on an iron oar freighter at the age of 18 and was promoted to be some people's boss
* Went to work in the Navy right before WW2 ended
* Met my grandma who was 13 years younger when he was in his 40s(?)
* Moved to Gaylord, MI to work as a teacher and a driver's ed instructor
* While there he had 4 children
* Was moved to a small town in central Michigan to be a superintendent where he lives to this day
* Has 10 grandchildren among those 4 kids (three had two, one had four)
* Is in great health and almost 90
* Has a brother still alive, but who has Alzheimer's

A couple stories:

* Once he took a trip to Las Vegas with someone (I can't remember who), and lost all of his money. He ended up having to call a friend for a loan to pay for gas on the way home. There's way more, but I forgot.

* He went to his first rock concert maybe...ten years ago. He saw Scorpions with my dad and his brother in California. The drummer gave him his stick and then my Grandpa turned to a girl behind him and gave it to her

Today we're actually going to a Croatian festival, so I have an hour and a half long car ride with him, but he isn't coming for another hour. I figured it'd be good to get questions in early so I know if people are interested.

Edit: He'll be here soon, so I hope that more comes. The two so far are great though.

Edit 2: I'm currently in the car with him. I'll start asking questions soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a beautiful cover of Madrigal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/2PEh1VNz6dc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The stoner version of the Super Bowl would have the same name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 10:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I'm making my own prog rock ranking system, what album should I base it on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 2 ideas:

* Images And Words (including the song ACoS as was originally intended)
* In The Court Of The Crimson King

Which would be best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Body Electric </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a fun bass song! Based on a George Lucas movie and a Twilight Zone episode by Ray Bradbury, this song is kick ass.

[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/1dW8wEQbAXU)

[Grace Under Pressure tour](https://youtu.be/9fqXV8sbgyE)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/YpMJDj4pXNM)

___
My ranking
___

1. ?
2. The Enemy Within
3. **The Body Electric**
4. ?
5. Red Sector A
6. Afterimage
7. ?
8. Distant Early Warning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What albums do you have on your phone/mp3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 06:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have:

* Rush through A Show Of Hands (all studio and live albums) as their remastered Sectors versions
* Presto FLAC
* Roll The Bones through Clockwork Angels as MP3s (no live albums here)
* Vapor Trails Remix MP3
* Hold Your Fire tour bootleg (soundboard)
* Roll The Bones tour bootleg (damn good audience I think)

The bootlegs are A Desperate Voice and Mirrors respectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They've come so far in two years! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 06:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Progressive Rock tropes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 21:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a personal project, but I need a list of as many Prog Rock tropes as possible. So far I have these:

* Long Songs (7 minutes)
* A solo longer than 1 minute
* Multiple solos in one song
* Tracks that flow into one another
* Instrumental songs
* A concept
* Dissonance
* Sound bites (quotes from TV, movies, etc)
* Sound effects
* Obscure instruments (stuff other than the typical guitar, bass, drums, keyboards, and vocals)
* Odd time signatures
* Changing time signatures
* Key changes
* Polyrhythms
* A Rickenbacker bass
* A Hammond organ
* A singer with a high voice
* An orchestra or brass section
* Heavy use of synthesizers/keyboards
* Complex musical parts
* Different genres within one song
* Vocal harmonies

Got anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Under The Covers be available from the CD Baby pre-order at midnight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WEEKLY SUBREDDIT UPDATE #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 21:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we have a few announcements to make. I'll split it into sections so it's nicer to read.
___
Section list:

1. 100 subs!
2. Rules
3. Flairs
4. Future plans
5. Under The Covers

___
**#1: 100 SUBS!**

I'm so pumped to see that this is getting off the ground! Hopefully we'll get even more as the next two days go by and hopefully also in the following weeks thanks to Under The Covers. But no matter what, thank you all for joining.
___
**#2: Rules**

We've added some rules that *will be enforced.* While moderating is our job, we'll also try to be understanding. I hope that you all know that how you react after getting in trouble (see also: a temporary ban if your offense is bad enough) can effect the length of the ban.

But don't worry, we won't be just tossing around bans. We'll take action as we see is required after some conversation.
___
**#3: Flairs**

Something we're trying to come up with is flairs. /u/TWRPband will be receiving some badass flair, but we want to make sure you guys/gals have something too. Ideas we have so far are the album covers and the masks, but we want your suggestions too! Drop them here in the comments and we'll consider them!
___
**#4: Future plans**

Now, we've got some pretty cool plans for this sub in the future. One that I can't quite tell you about cause it's still up in the air, and another that I can.

The one that I can is that we'll be making a weekly or monthly post every Sunday or the last day of each month depending on which one we end up doing.
___
**#5: Under The Covers**

As you all know, Ninja Sex Party's new album is being released in just *two days*! It will feature TWRP alongside NSP with cover albums. I'm giving you a warning now:

#IF YOU LINK TO A LEAK OR ANY ILLEGAL DOWNLOAD, THE POST WILL BE REMOVED. REPEATED ACTION WILL RESULT IN A TEMPORARY BAN.

Links to *official* YouTube videos will be allowed, but non-official videos featuring just the music and nothing else will be removed. This is where I have to put my foot down. I won't say that I've never got stuff from the open seas, but I don't want it posted here. Unofficial YouTube videos featuring only the audio and cover art is a huge pet peeve of mine. No bans will be issued from this, but I will remove them.
___
Thank you all, once again, for joining!
___
**EDIT**

We also have the Wiki up. It's a work in progress, but go check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come join /r/TWRP! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 18:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shameless self promotion!

/r/TWRP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think of my ticket stubs? (Missing shows in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something nice Jason White sent 10(?) year old me... [Story in comments] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Enemy Within </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 02:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great song. I love the baseline and the meaning. It really needed to be done live more. Honestly, it took me a while to get into, but now it's one of my favorites.
___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/lBZ2qDIbDUQ)

[Grace Under Pressure tour](https://youtu.be/I06T6M6R0Cc)

[An eerily similar song by Coheed and Cambria](https://youtu.be/fgb5ATrZocA)
___
My ranking:

1. ?
2. **The Enemy Within**
3. ?
4. ?
5. Red Sector A
6. Afterimage
7. ?
8. Distant Early Warning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWRP live at MagFest (ft. Ninja Sex Party) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 21:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What bands do you like that we wouldn't expect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like bands like Genesis (Peter Gabriel era especially, I drove 8 hours to see the officially licensed tribute band do a version of the Selling England tour), Rush (every era), Dream Theater, King Crimson, Haken, Yes, Emerson Lake and Palmer, and Queensryche.

Obvious ones include Green Day, Panic At The Disco, Coheed and Cambria (my favorite of the obvious category), and Iron Maiden (stated by Gerard as one of his main influences), and a bit of The Misfits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would your dream setlist be for a reunion show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 21:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next year marks a 15th anniversary of Bullets and this year marks a 10th anniversary of Black Parade. These are arguably two of their most important albums as well as two of their best (in my top 5 for sure). So if they came back and you had to make them a setlist, what would yours look like?

For me it would be:

*Intro: Look Alive, Sunshine*

1. Na Na Na (Na ^8)
2. I'm Not Okay (I Promise)
3. To The End
4. Kiss The Ring
5. Desolation Row
6. I Never Told You What I Do For A Living
7. Sleep
8. House Of Wolves
9. Mama
10. Ambulance
11. Heaven Help Us
12. Early Sunsets Over Monroeville (with Demolition Lovers's intro)
13. Hang Em High
14. Helena
15. The Ghost Of You
16. Interlude/The Jetset Life Is Gonna Kill You

*Tape: Jet-Star And The Kobra Kid/Traffic Report*

17. Party Poison
18. Cubicles
19. Welcome To The Black Parade
20. Disenchanted (with the chorus from Shut Up And Play)
21. Famous Last Words
22. The Kids From Yesterday

Encore:

*Intro tape: Goodnight Dr. Death*

22. Vampire Money
23. Fake Your Death

Encore 2:

24. Blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Geometry] How to solve for x, y, and z in similar right triangles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 18:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've payed attention in class, tried homework, and looked online. Help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SCENARIO: Coheed is doing a one off show in your area and you can submit a setlist. What is your list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 14:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Red Sector A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 14:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a dark song with one of my favorite live moments.

 I hear the sound of gunfire at the prison gates

 #***BANG***

So haunting. I'll be honest, I do miss a baseline in here, but it's cool.
___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/RoXFVb1VVJA)

[A really good fan video (Band Of Brothers Spoilers)](https://youtu.be/CzXDi_f9PUY)

[Grace Under Pressure tour](https://youtu.be/8ivnvKIu4mg)

[Snakes And Arrows tour](https://youtu.be/3YpmqeAgEA0)

[Clockwork Angels tour](https://youtu.be/3QmZAvZjpsE)

[***BONUS!*** An old Rush themed cartoon](https://youtu.be/DVZ5cKHHuhw)
___
My ranking:

1. ?
2. ?
3. ?
4. ?
5. **Red Sector A**
6. Afterimage
7. ?
8. Distant Early Warning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
