<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 08:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you bothered to find this to reply to. Hope you're enjoying the DLC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 04:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me a kid, but that Cheese flavoured Korean instant noodle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather trust GPS directions than what taxi drivers claim is the fastest route. And you can dispute charges on Uber if your driver takes a longer route than needed. You can't do that with a normal taxi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only gotten middle age drivers so far. There was an Ah Beng who drove fantastically in a Toyota Estima though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea. Maybe years of driving have led them to lose all dexterity in their heels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 18:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than Uber being cheaper for me, one reason I choose to take Uber over taxis is because Uber drivers know how to drive smoothly and properly, unlike almost 100% of taxi drivers who use the accelerator pedal in an on-off fashion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 17:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's gorgeous. And I'm Chinese. Good marketing research done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 17:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll check out the Honor 5X. I'm not sure if it's available here. I'm quite sure the Moto X 2nd Gen isn't here though. I've also read that its camera quality isn't that good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 05:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's slightly above my budget and not readily available here. Is there a similar used phone at the same price level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After having had poor experiences with Xiaomi, I don't think I'm ready for another Chinese branded phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds promising! I don't mind another 20 HPs added to my S80 D2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 05:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will there ever be a Polestar tune for the D2 engine? It'll be hilarious to see what kinds of power and torque improvements are possible from a 1.6L engine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 20:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great but I'm worried about the warranty. Is it just a rebrand of some Chinese phone? Usually only Chinese phones have dual-SIM slots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap and Good Android phone for use as In-Car DVR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 10:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm based in Singapore and am looking for a cheap (US$200) Android phone to replace the current XiaoMi Redmi 2 for use in my car as a Digital Video Recorder. I currently record using Background Video Recorder 2 and also simultaneously use Torque Pro to record OBD2 logs from a connected bluetooth OBD2 reader. 

The current phone is crashing randomly and lags at recording video. In addition, the GPS doesn't work when recording video, a bug that XiaoMi refuses to acknowledge or fix despite numerous reports from different users. As such, I am looking to replace that heap of junk. 

I would prefer an Android phone with a newish version of Android (5.0+), expandable storage, support for ExFAT (important) or basically writing of video files 4GB, minimum 30FPS 1080p video recording (60 FPS preferred, constant frame rate even better). Optical image stabilization would be amazing to have but not necessary. Battery life must also be reasonably good to last at least 1.5h of recording videos between charges. Is this too much to ask for in a low-end phone?

I don't mind recommendations for used phones. Please, pick an Android for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 20:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did 650km and spent almost 50 in tolls in one day. About 7 hours of driving at 4000rpm in a rental city car with no cruise control. Shouldn't have done that in hindsight as I live in a tiny country and have never driven more than 100km in a day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 17:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this in London. Naughty...
http://imgur.com/fURzJZw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steering wheel (left-right, top to bottom): Retarder - | Retarder + | Interior look left | Interior look right | Horn | Reset interior camera. Shifter Y Button: Ignition | Shifter X Button: Cruise Control | Shifter B Button: Cruise Control Resume | Shifter A Button: Parking Brake | D-Pad Up: Light Mode | D-Pad Right: Wipers | D-Pad Left: Dashboard Info Mode | D-Pad Down | Toggle High Beams | Red Button 1: Shifter Toggle Range | Red Button 2: Shifter Toggle Splitter | Red Button 3: Cruise Control Lower Speed | Red Button 4: Cruise Control Higher Speed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 11:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing stands out most, how is the maid being paid $1000 a month? My maid is paid $650 a month and I thought that was higher than average.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 11:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's particularly infuriating during rush hour and you see a whole line of cars stuck behind one road hogger. Drivers here should learn to keep left. Especially van and pick-up drivers who stay on the 2nd lane all the way to overtake bigger trucks. I was so impressed when I drove in France; they were extremely adamant about keeping right after overtaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 08:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't hog the right-most lane. Move over when you're not overtaking. Check for blind spots. Look ahead and anticipate. Be careful around motorcycles. Try not to overtake on the left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 08:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For best fuel economy shift at 1500rpm. For max power shift at 1900rpm. Max torque is always between 1000-1400rpm but max power is achieved at around 1800-2000rpm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 05:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF. "This is far more than the usage in other cities with comparable standards of living".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's surprising to me that Singapore has a comparable standard of living to Tallinn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My black beauties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 07:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 07:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are DCTs so jerky? And every time I let off the gas at any speed and go back on it, the revs jump up a bit before settling down again. Traditional automatics don't do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 07:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be the only one here that says SingTel isn't that bad. I've been using SingTel fibre (300Mbps now) since the day it was launched and it's been very reliable. Even when there were problems, there's nothing a reboot won't fix. I get a new upgraded router too whenever I recontract so that's nice too. Anyway I don't have much choice in telcos since my Dad watches BPL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live in a condo. My neighbour downstairs smokes and it's really quite terrible. The smoke smells like those contraband Chinese cigarettes that I've come across in China going for about 15 a pack. But that seemed to have stopped recently. Maybe they moved out or my loud complains have been heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 03:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0-100km/h in 12.8s... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stock Mercedes-Benz Actros (featuring new wheels) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 17:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice stock Scania Streamline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 17:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 17:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they will. Existing buses won't be scrapped until the end of their serviceable lifespan. It's just that new orders in the future will probably consist of one of those concept buses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 14:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think based on the concept buses shown it's either MAN or ADL for future double-deckers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 07:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. But honestly the red isn't that good either. The London red looks better. But I guess people want a special colour for Singapore. Green's weird, so I guess that stands out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 07:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted red. That green to me isn't as classy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been driving automatic cars, but had the chance to drive a manual Ford Ka when I rented one in France. The only automatic car was like 3 classes up in price. While it was fun and all, it was really tiring and stressful in traffic. I had the constant pressure of not stalling and looking like an idiot. I think it was quite lucky of me not to get honked at by Parisian taxis when I finally did stall. I think automatics are better for daily driving, it's just that much smoother, unless it's a dry-clutch DCT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that building. I didn't even know its name until you mentioned it. I hope you enjoyed your time in Singapore. 

Diesel here is still much cheaper than gas, it's usually half the price or less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 16:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diesels are quite rare here in Singapore too. It's only really offered by Volvo, Renault, Jaguar and Citroen and Peugeot here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 07:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup managed to do 3.9. My local site says 3.9 too. The D2 was the only diesel version offered here in addition to the T5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 05:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just select the D2 option here: https://www.media.volvocars.com/global/en-gb/models/s80/2015/specifications </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 04:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's in US MPGs. UK MPG is around 70. I'm using 3.9L/100km to do the calculations. That's the official EU economy rating and is indeed achievable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it's sufficient. I've only tried up to 130km/h though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it's normal. That's what you get when you use such a high pressure turbo on a 1.6L Diesel engine. 0-100km/h in 12.8s, with a dual-clutch transmission! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No turbo hiss for me, just loads of turbo lag. Nothing, nothing, 32psi of turbo, sudden surge, redline at 4000rpm, and back to nothing again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That T6 though. Worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 16:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The long term average since I collected the car 1 year ago is 42 MPG. I can only get 60 MPG when I drive to my university. 

And for fun, there's always the C30 T5, although 0-100km/h in 7.6s isn't that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 14:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I figured I should upload some photos of a right-hand drive Volvo which is quite rare on Reddit. Obligatory IKEA shot too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 14:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is something SCS isn't showing you about the next DLC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My eco cruiser, only 115 hp but 60 US MPG! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 12:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 07:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys just don't get the hint. You won't be needing a mod to see those in the game soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 06:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I'm saying you won't be needing a mod to get those nuts in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 04:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need a custom mod for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I know where it came from. I just felt that it might be rude to harass Merc UK when they're already in ETS2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is MercedesTruckUK in there? That's got nothing to do with ATS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 15:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DLC will be worth it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only my S80 had that kind of power... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 07:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they book more of those polluting old lorries and buses. It's quite a disgrace and an eyesore for a developed country to have so many old clattering vehicles stinking up wherever they go on the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 07:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww no Ludicrous Mode. And I wonder how scheduled maintenance works for him? Ship to HK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 03:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess this is true. They can't promote car usage at all, so they can't promote electric cars. It's really sad when you think of what could have been, and see how we're entirely missing out on the potential. I drive a diesel car for fuel economy but I'll be glad to switch to electric anytime if it was available to help with reducing emissions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still a while to wait then. I always thought that Singapore being so small would be the perfect place for large scale electric car deployment. I envisioned a future where other countries look to us in awe and admiration of our high adoption rates and low pollution. It's really quite silly that we still put electric vehicles on RD plates and don't have proper orders for hybrid buses yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After so much trouble he had to go through, I hope he got the P90D. Methinks that the government's reluctance to go electric for cars has to do with Singapore being so reliant on oil refining and exports.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 18:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps I'm weird. I actually think the Panamera looks good. Can't stand cars like the Lambo Aventador or that hideous Sesto Elemento. Too many straight lines and jagged edges. To be radical is one thing, but Lambos are taking things too far. Even the Huracan looks strange to me with that angular front.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 17:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contrary to popular opinion, I think the Chiron looks absolutely stunning. The Veyron wasn't bad either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is the loads are different in nature. For example I was running what I thought was a stable overclock, it did very well in Aida64 and things like Asus Realbench. But just running GTA V for 2 minutes caused the computer to crash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want cheaper homes and cheaper maids or not? Haven't we all agreed that those things are more important than the welfare of maids and those construction workers? I understand your concerns but our construction industry mainly relies on exploiting cheap labour. Until you can get people to fork out condo prices for HDBs I don't think we can do much to improve those workers' lives without affecting property prices. And for maids, I can't really give an opinion since my maid gets every Sunday off and lots of her friends do too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 18:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? AFAIK, the game only connects to WoT when you have account details stored in your profile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 15:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 1941 Right-hand drive Ford Mercury Convertible that was assembled in Singapore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like luxury vehicles too, especially luxury vehicles with great performance and comfort. Something like the MB S600 or the Rolls Royce Ghost. Too many car manufacturers are trying to make everyday models sporty by having suspensions that are too stiff and ruining the ride. Why is it so difficult to buy cars that roll in corners and wafts over bumps like those American land yachts in the '80s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wished I had remote start here in tropical sunny Singapore so that the car can be cooled down before I get in. On bad days the interior can exceed 60 degrees C. Never seen a car with that feature here though. Are there such things as pre-coolers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolls Royce Phantom EWB - 12 cylinders
Range Rover LWB SVR - 8 cylinders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 06:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe try editing the profile and removing the login details, then saving those changes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 05:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it silly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 04:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't like the closure of the CBD area to cars. Roads are for cars. I paid so much COE and road tax, I should be able to drive there if I want. Same goes to those stupid marathons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 10:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who thinks the new Civic looks absolutely hideous from the front? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 11:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm worried if traffic accident related traffic jams will incur charges for road users. It's unfair if there's a build-up of traffic due to accidents (which is especially common along PIE) and the driver has to pay for it. 

I'm also not very enthusiastic about the possibility of speeding fines from the GPS-tracked speeds. 90km/h on TPE is really quite ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how this compares to a Phantom in terms of sheer comfort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 12:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speeding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 02:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well cars are a luxury here so they're ridiculously priced. We just accept it as a part of life. Can't let our dreams die because they're a little harder to attain. Perhaps a good deal might come by. I got my S80 for quite a good price. I understand that the XC90 starts at around the same price as the S80 in many markets but the S80 I got was 40% cheaper than an XC90.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 02:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm it shouldn't wobble even at 0. Maybe swaying from side to side but not wobbling. Perhaps there's some unstable changes in some physics mod.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singapore consumes 10.4118 gallons of oil per day per capita... That's even greater than Qatar or the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 16:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it but I'm wondering how much it'll cost here in Singapore, if it does get imported. It should be more than an XC90 so that means $350,000+, which is almost S Class money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 12:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. Thank you for the information. The dealer's not been very useful though. Multiple fixes but the problem seems to recur every 2 months or so. Hasn't been two months since the last service, so don't really know if the last fix worked as yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 08:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trailer stability at 0 as anything more than that means lowering the COG artificially. For me, braking intensity at the centre seems to be the most realistic. I've looked at some braking videos on YouTube and apparently a 30t Volvo can brake from 80-0 in less than 40m or so, which is what I've tried to replicate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 06:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already did 4 times. First two times couldn't identify any issue but changed the ECU. Third time they changed the closing velocity module and the last time they changed some part of the ESP system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute. I have an S80 D2 with the exact same problems which I've experienced for more than 5 times but it's not part of the recall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 03:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really frustrating for me because I have to download around 200MB of updates almost everyday for beta-testing purposes. In comparison, NVIDIA drivers are around 300+MB and they never take more than 20 seconds to finish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow download on Steam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 300Mbps Fibre internet service but Steam is downloading everything really slowly. Usually around 200KB/s with drops to like 20KB/s. I've tried my local server (Singapore), Malaysia, Indonesia and many others but all of them are extremely slow. Any ideas what's happening here? I have no problems with anything else other than Steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 09:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forza on the PC would be awesome! To date, there are only a few driving sims out there but none of them have enough road cars. I don't care about racing spec cars, I want to drive a family saloon on the Nurburgring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 09:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should post this in the SCS forums. Or let the CEO know. Maybe you'll be a valuable beta-tester if you can help improve the gearbox simulation in ATS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rental left hand drive Ford Ka. I'm from a RHD country so that's pretty interesting to me. Also it's a manual. That's rare as hell where I'm from too. Other than that, it's extremely slow and noisy, gets terrible fuel economy and struggles to even hit 130km/h. I think one of the most genuinely scary and stupid moments in my life was reaching 175km/h downhill in that tiny car. Comfortable car for that class though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 03:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the newer videos now are from the leaked version. It's quite sad that such a thing has happened to such a hard-working team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 02:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure this isn't intended behaviour. I've never encountered this since the 1st day of testing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 02:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quite sure it isn't. Testers will try to show off the game in a good light and this isn't one of those glamorous shots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 18:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey isn't it great that you downloaded the leaked version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 11:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll probably get you to go for a few specialist appointments. I was PES D for almost a year before they decided to enlist me with a temp E9L9.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 GTX 970s. It's still not perfectly smooth in populated areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [From 11:00UTC] New gameplay videos (Peterbilt 579   Kenworth T680) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 09:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [American Truck Simulator Gameplay - Kenworth T680 Las Vegas - San Francisco (pre-release beta):](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mh76qvpqMEI)

[American Truck Simulator Gameplay - Peterbilt 579 Reno - Barstow (pre-release beta):](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5xw4CMQ1uvw)

[American Truck Simulator - Kenworth T680 Customization (pre-release beta):](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LRQrnY1yjQU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [From 11:00UTC] New gameplay videos (Peterbilt 579   Kenworth T680) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 09:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [American Truck Simulator Gameplay - Kenworth T680 Las Vegas - San Francisco (pre-release beta):](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mh76qvpqMEI)

[American Truck Simulator Gameplay - Peterbilt 579 Reno - Barstow (pre-release beta):](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5xw4CMQ1uvw)

[American Truck Simulator - Kenworth T680 Customization (pre-release beta):](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LRQrnY1yjQU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ain't happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 03:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get your hopes up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 02:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it's similar. Some trucks may have more options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 04:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people and then there are cunts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 09:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still diverting and merging, but only slightly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 14:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 06:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's what you get when you have many people playing the game. OMSI 2 is absolutely terribly optimised but you don't hear many people complaining because it's a very niche genre and not many play it. People have to remember ETS2 was released like 3 years ago and it's still going strong with more than 20+ patches. Which other developer does this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 14:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're saying I'm a troll I'm not. Just come back at the right time tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Viewable from 22 Jan 11:00 UTC] American Truck Simulator - Peterbilt 579 Customization (pre-release beta) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 12:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The information embargo for American Truck Simulator lifts on 22 Jan at 11:00 UTC. Each tester is allowed to release a short video and so here's mine showing off the customization options for the Peterbilt 579! I hope you guys are as excited as I am for the release of ATS!

[Video link!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mOsDOT0zUGU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
