<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a gf in college who was absolutely terrified of ET. She said her cousins used to chase her with this doll when she was little. The fear was real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Value edition. Wow. Way to stick it to the students, America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, socialized medicine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been the problem with the Christian-right for 40 years. They call liberals intolerant and controlling, but it's like they're saying "stop being intolerant of our intolerance." It's a vicious circle that shouldn't be allowed to continue, but here we are with Donald Trump playing into their fears and hatred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Nobel Prize winner to human rights threat.  
Good job, America. Good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the way she goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, the United States is the bestest, most free, rich, peaceful, educated, did I mention free? country on the planet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thought has crossed my mind more than a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely with what you're saying, Republicans will probably back him because the controversy of an impeachment could destroy their party when they were lucky to have won this Presidential election and both houses of Congress anyway. I'll always wonder how the Dems not only lost the Presidency, but didn't gain both houses. I mean, I know why. We ran a weak candidate. But the opportunity was there.  
No, I think the Republicans will fall right in line and back their President while speaking out in his favor as little as possible.  
But, if there was an impeachment, it's best that he gets impeached by his own party (given they have majority in every house and will have the Supreme Court). It keeps the Dems from taking all the blame and possibly dividing the country further. Make no mistake though, a Trump impeachment would require the Republican party to fall on it's own sword, and I don't see that happening. If it did though, it would be the most patriotic act by a group of Americans in 100+ years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That 20%. That's where our houses are. Found em, guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Republican's minds, they all served and earned Metal of Honors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All we have to do is all get rich, then we can all enjoy the fruits of the Trump Presidency. No big deal. Just get rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think I get what you mean. It means you don't want to just not do those jobs for those companies, it means you don't' ever want to do that specific type of work ever again. I'm with you. Been a financial adviser, marketing director, resturaunt manager, operations manager, truck driving fleet manager, coffee shop employee, and I don't want to do any of those things again ever. I did them, it was what it was, but it'd be nice if there was more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just an absolute tragedy that Beau Biden passed away for the obvious reasons. Joe Biden would have probably won the Presidency against Donald Trump, and might have been the perfect middleground for Hillary and Bernie supporters. The potential for a continuation of the Obama years was there, but lost. I'll always wonder what could have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially since it's the same cloud over and over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcissism. It's a real thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you never played Mario Kart 64, the best Mario Kart game ever made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can't hear you, I cant hear you, la la la la la la." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're going to learn a lot about gaslighting over the next 4 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Pence is a true and total sociopath. We throw that label around a little too liberally sometimes, and narcissism too. I disagree with Pence on so many issues, especially his stances that abortion should be outlawed and creationism taught in schools, and maybe he has an absurdly over-inflated ego because of the position he holds now, and the position he's held as an upperclassman his whole life, but I don't know if he's a full blown sociopath. He'll push for legislation I don't agree with, and he might even get some things passed I wouldn't like, but he'll never get Roe V Wade overturned even with a conservative Supreme Court, not without a major fight from the rest of the country. And he'll never get creationism and prayer to become a public school requirement.  
Trump though, he really is a narcissist. And he very well might be a sociopath too. He needs approval, he can't take criticism, and he has the means (now more than ever) to take revenge on anyone on the planet he feels has disrespected him. And yeah, he has illustrated very clearly that he has little more than an elementary level understanding of our legislative process, country history, or understanding of current global affairs. That is dangerous. Pence would sting, but Trump could blow the whole fucking thing up in months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like when conservatives at up the story that Obama was born in Kenya, or how Hillary and Obama intentionally let Benghazi happen? Like that kind of fake news? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can compare this situation, Trump being our President, to anything we want, but we've never seen anything like this before in the United States or in the 21st century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you know what it's like to be the fat guy in New Balance tennis shoes at the front of a line in a popular night club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would kicking a tree stump kill a horse? Did he break his leg and y'all had to put him down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to my parents and grandparents. They're convinced every founder was a Christian, and we were founded on the principles of Christianity. TBH, I'm pretty sure they think every founder was an Evangelical Christian and they were trying to found a Christian nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a good example of what we saw in the Dare Program (80s/90s), here's [Helen Hunt Jumping out a window on Crank (aka Meth)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rEpyLzHeozY).  
I remember this video being shown to us in 1996. Even in the 6th grade we all thought it was bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's official: US election systems designated as critical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, they can investigate themselves. They'd never do anything unethical like give favorable treatment to a criminal just  because they were a police officer on the same of some symbolic blue line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drop dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *checks outside*  
Well, it's not too hot to walk my dog, but my hand is fucking cold now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hail hydra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the media attacking Putin? The President-elect said the media would reward Putin greatly if he hacked some e-mails. This makes no sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but In Utero went 5 times platinum. Would you say Nevermind was a failure because Thriller sold 46 million? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wallflowers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 minutes on WebMD and everyone will think they're either psychotic, narcissistic, bipolar, or have cancer. Get to a real doctor if you have concerns.  
edit: a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac? You're here too? Oh, god damnit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you realize how many times when your back was turned the wrestlers have hit each other with chairs, tables, and bats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We threw rocks at trains, but only on Christmas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makita, Milwaukee and Hitachi's professional lines are great. Hilti or one of  those 3  are generally considered the best quality and most durable I think, just depends on what you need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just DeWalt. Porter Cable used to make some great power tools. Now they're full of plastic garbage from B D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 12:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dee Snider is that 50 year old guy who's spent the last 30 years talking about how cool he was in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my boss let me leave work at 2:30 every day, I'd be willing to do 1-3 hours of work at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing with South Park. I enjoyed the season-long storylines for a season, but it'd be nice to see them hit what is current every week again, or just go off the radar once in a while and do something ridiculous like the Awesome-O episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And at the end of the day, these are the people who's data decides if you can get a home loan or not, regardless of your current financial standing. Go America. Go Freedom and the right to pursue happiness. But fuck is that pursuit exhausting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't really call Bartolo Colon elite....at all. But he is entertaining and somewhat effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note to self: No cheap, light-weight wal-mart furniture for the baby's room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi Arabia. Our ally in peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a weird feeling listening to Coheed and Cambria too. There was some good music in the early 2000s, despite all the crap. Same with every period I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. She pushed for it for years. She's just very pragmatic in her older age. She chooses smaller, winable battles most of the time. But she'd sign it if she could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mariah Carey gets blasted by Dick" would be a good clickbait title once this gets reposted 1000 times. I'm just sayin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frittata. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably use the phrase "mouth breathing dummy" at least once every week to refer to someone, and least 2-3 times a week during the NFL season. It's a great non-profanity insult. Thanks, Ruxin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Stars and Bars](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5uBVWH6onvE), but that's not his fault. It was just a shit movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Teenagers don't listen to radio stations anymore. Not the way they did, anyway. Just when there's no XM stereo or iphone/android/ipod device plugged into the car stereo (and would be pretty unusual). Most of the time if there's none of that, they'll just pull their phones out and make/watch videos, take photos, browse  social media, or just listen to music on their phones without the car stereo. I'd bet most teenagers can't name a single FM radio station in their area. NPR is still a thing though. A lot of teenagers and 20-somethings listen to that. They just get it on their smartphones/tablets/laptops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe next time she's on vacation she shouldn't schedule a work activity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 06:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bashing hipsters is so 2009. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *In a big way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was like watching Clinton lose to Trump, despite all projections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least one of those two is really hoping Australia legalizes same-sex marriage. I'm leaning towards thinking they both want it, and have a major communication issue in their relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be a good opportunity for the 3D-printed organ market. There will also be fewer people needing organs since they won't be getting maimed in car accidents. If this is the one of the traditional auto industry's best arguments against self-driving cars, it's a weak argumement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 08:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't call your mom a bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 08:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell her until she gets back. Don't have ceiling fans around birds.  
source: did the same thing to my sisters bird by mistake. I was 9 though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is the type of behavior Donald Trump was referring to when he said Putin was a stronger leader than President Obama, I'll take our "weak" leader all day long and twice on Sundays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [But being a mother is the hardest job in the world!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hitc8haEu_g) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney is no Potsie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
