<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9815</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  said Javier Bracamonte, the Astros bullpen catcher, who interpreted for Gurriel in an interview. 

Bracamonte does everything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Houston Astros fans are less optimistic than the Phillies... I don't know if that says we are a depressed bunch or that the Phillies phans are delusional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a break from it again. I keep getting to the end of Part 1? But now I feel like I'm really missing something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly how it made me feel: These people are crazy... I should train for an Ultra! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4K for Devo through 2IP? Yes please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it can be both right? There were protests after his Muslim ban at JFK and other airports because of the action and because it was seen as a despotic ruling that unfairly targeted a religion/ethnic group. The woman's march was in response to both misogynistic statements (among other things) and perceived legislation that will negatively impact woman's health.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yeah sure. I'm just saying you *could* say that. You could also argue Palin was palatable because she wasn't the boss, but boss's second hand. But I think it's hard to verify those kinds of feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but then you could say largely because she's a woman and there might be a shred of truth in that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of historical examples of Trump, I think the best comparison is likely James Buchanan for his plurality victory, denouncement of the opposition party stating the Republicans were dangerous and geographical with bias against the South, and general political attitude. He was President prior to the Civil War but also represented views that were increasingly seen as out of date and challenged by more progressive parts of the country (slavery, Fugitive Slave Act, Dred Scott happened during his term as well). I've only encountered him peripherally in my reading so far (through biographies of Jackson and Lincoln, and White Rage by Professor Carol Anderson) but a lot of it seems to fit the Trump model </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend told me this too! I feel like I'm missing something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been stuck in a conundrum if I'm running slowly because that's just where I'm at or if it has to do with my effort. 155 spm seems slow based off everything I've read but I have to consciously focus on my form to get runs that avg 160+. (I honestly can't even imagine doing 180) 

I just want to be able to fully understand cadence so I can work on it. This is very helpful though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I deleted "childhood high school" cause it seemed like a weird phrase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve, Correa, and probably Bregman or Springer. None of our pitchers seem that versatile, but Keuchel is a perennial gold glover and snags ground balls hit to him with some pizzazz  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone recommend a definitive article on running cadence? Or does cadence correlate to effort? I have the general idea that I should be doing about 160 pm but I either am still fuzzy on what cadence really means or I just don't get the why. I'd been doing my runs in the 155 pm range but can keep my cadence up if I spend my run just focusing on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe someone else can speak to this with more general knowledge but I'm about 190 and 5'11" so just about similar build. Last year I ran 500 miles. I did a HM in November and averaged a 10:30 min/mile (I fell off towards the end). I'm now seeing my per mile average creep steadily down but it's definitely time in and work. I would recommend picking a HM training plan and sticking to it religiously. I always skip the speed work, which probably doesn't help me improve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your pace and longest distance run?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just two long ones this week 

**Team of Rivals, by Doris Kearns Goodwin** Which looks at Lincoln's presidency and surrounding himself with his political and ideological rivals. Is Salmon P. Chase one of the most cruel names a parent has given a child? Yep. 

**2666 by Roberto Bolano** Starting this for the 5th time. I don't get the appeal, but I really want to get through it. I just don't care for the first part with the mysterious German writer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First long run of the year: 8 miles. The new town is steeper than I'm used so I'm still trying to get better at going uphill (and my quads are taking a beating going down). Also found a sweet trail behind my wife's high school with a great view.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only problem with yur buds is that the plastic attachments lose their grip over time. And then I lose them/theyre useless without the molds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the more interesting thing but it seems like both parties do it. So the only way I imagine it ends is if the judiciary gets a chance to rule on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may or may not be competing with you but it was 70 degrees two days ago and is low of 19 tonight. America is all over the place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I misremembered the details but it allows me to logically work through this. The Executive Memo specifically mentioned harboring in cases where USCIS is not aware of the immigrants presence, so Anne Frank not church sanctuaries known to the media et al. And I imagine providing services to persons without status isn't illegal because status isn't a requirement for receiving status ie federal law does not require La Raza to ask or provide documentation status when they do health services or general service. And someone can correct me here but I believe Immigration Law is Administrative Law and thus subject to the Executive Branch's enforcement. So would probably not have been illegal at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if you're receiving legal aid it means you are in court. And having representation is def not illegal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's an argument which should be made in court. But as of right now this isn't technically illegal and I don't think will stir up controversy except in the same way the house judiciary committee used Benghazi to assassinate Clintons character. The GAO at least seems less like political posturing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies if I missed the announcement from the DOJ but I think until we see Legislation or the DOJ actively pursuing an investigation rather than just opinion pieces by bias-leaning newspapers we can't really say that it'll amount to anything. This is also an interesting not legally corrupt vs. it should be corrupt we just haven't legislated it or ruled on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly does La Raza do that constitutes illegal activity. Here's my guess: It sounds like the NCLR does similar work as to what my organization does ie provide immigration relief to immigrants in removal or deportation proceedings. During our staff meeting we had a segment about the legality of providing services to undocumented immigrants because apparently immigration law suggests that any service provided that allows the undocumented immigrant to remain in the United States is in violation of the law unless USCIS knows about the immigrant. It's still being discussed how this will be implemented.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the best one so far because it attempted to remain more in line with factual journalism. It appears as if there might have been grant reporting style requirements for recipients of the funds, which I would be interested in seeing. I've worked for non-profits that provided these exact services that are covered here BUT there was always a million reporting requirements whereas the opinion here is that they might not have been heavily regulated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> while I think this is a really interesting situation I don't think it's going to be controversial. As evidenced by most of these pieces being "opinion" and the fact that it didn't gain much traction from last year from the Wall Street Journal. Would the DOJ make it an issue now in order to cut off the ability from future Presidents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like a weird and unique occurrence. Some clarification I'd like

* It sounds like other presidents have done this in the past. To what extent did Obama expand the power? 
* If corporations were given incentive to donate the money to non-profit organizations rather than to the DOJ and consumers, how is this different than tax breaks? 

* What exactly is the uproar, that the DOJ was used to direct corporations to give to specific non-profits that may or may not have had left leaning progressive policies? Is this a problem if the money is distributed equitably? 
* Ie is this largely political or should we be concerned about this money going to non-profits versus going to the Treasury? 

Additionally this is my big take away here:
 Both the Government Accountability Office and Congressional Research Service have concluded that the settlement agreements do not violate Congress power of the purse. But others disagree.

At least at the moment this isn't seen as an illegal procedure and any controversy that erupts can only result in future thinking legislation or judicial action to rule on the constitutionality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An opinion piece. Which means that at least currently what was being done was within the accepted legal framework of our nation and if it isn't it needs to be sent to the judicial branch. I get that this might be an important issue to be outraged about, but it looks like Executive Overreach which a) hasn't been legislated and b) has not been thus far taken to court. So how is this at all relevant to Trump's empty talk and Democrats pushing back against his suspect appointments as political posturing or actual concern?

Edit: Would also like to point out that I'm not calling the Wall Street Journal fake news as I am re appropriating the term as used by Trump to discuss an opinion piece that you posted. I can recognize that opinion pieces support viewpoints which I might disagree with but aren't necessarily fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not necessarily interested in discussing T_D talking points. And unfortunately or fortunately for myself I only know that Brock's monetary influence into politics is suspect just like Trump appointing his billionaire friends with little to no experience as cabinet positions. It's broken all round, but it doesn't mean I can't criticize Trump. Which you completely ignore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checking in and Morton's stat line looks pretty good. But I'm sad about Rodgers, I hyped him so much that his performance so far is just a huge disappointment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to that being behind a paywall I couldn't read it but I did look up the author. And I'm not one to engage in "fake news/biased media" but it looks like Kimberly Strassel might be that http://mediamatters.org/people/kimberley-strassel

Also I think we were talking about the Trump administration. A) Obama's performance is irrelevant to Trump's and B) I think unfortunately it will become easier to ignore Obama's faults because of how poorly Trump is doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right well from a fiscally conservative stand point I don't think additional tax breaks should be given to those who might not necessarily need them. But I guess that could be a difference in opinion here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big story is Democrats using the GOP strategy to block suspect appointments like when McConnell did that to Obama's judicial appointments http://www.politico.com/story/2016/01/obama-nominations-blocked-senate-judges-217589

Sessions was largely suspect even before this Russian fiasco.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semantically I said higher income brackets not only the top singular bracket. I should not have used only because I'm sure it will minimally effect lower income earners, but most analysis has suggested that will be marginal/not effective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  However, the largest benefits will go to relatively affluent dual-income families using paid child care," said Alan Cole, an economist with the Tax Foundation.

https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2017-02-23/ivanka-trump-is-pushing-her-500-billion-child-care-plan-on-hill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity is there a reason you keep misspelling Schumer's name? It's right there in the same link you've posted multiple times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just putting things together are you suggesting that Schumer's actual thought out response there was just posturing? It's not like they targeted every department, or did so without reason. They were asking for proper vetting. You know the thing that could've avoided this Sessions mess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like a Trump strategy to lay blame on the Dems without actually proposing anything. Even Ivankas billion dollar Family Leave only affects a higher bracket income earning family and isn't really in line with Democratic values.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are  you running the Hudson Valley? I just moved to the LoHud and I've started thinking about where good spots for exploring would be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) Trying to keep filling in my City Strides for my wife's small hometown. I'm at 12% after a week of runs. Maybe picking early hours to knock off the sidewalk less highways. 

b) I'll be at 17 after tonight's commute run. I don't know if I want to push close to 30 by Sunday or stick closer to 20-25. 

c) baseball is back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * I'm cold. It's cold. East Coast winter is erratic and unpleasant. 
* Hopefully getting in an 8-10 miler. 
* Is audio feedback too obvious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she try to schedule a concert in MMP and the Astros got sassy again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tienes algunos que puedes recomendar? Necesito mejorar mi espaol para mi trabajo nuevo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the writing. Alexander Chee could easily be my favorite writer IF I cared at all for the subject. I discovered him from an essay in the best Non fiction essays of 2016 and loved it. Queen of the Night is a period piece that I didn't connect with. But I finished it with no strain so I would definitely recommend it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then you'd be leaving out Oprah. (I hope running celebrities doesn't become a thing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen a single instance of you using theory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was more so going for reductio ad absurdem there since it sounds like you're discussing the Pell Grant program which supports low income students who are not financially able to attend university? Because otherwise student loans are largely private loans. And by that extension that you are referring to government-subsidized education for low income individuals removing that assistance will result in a reduction of low income participants in university settings. 

So I think civics might be a semantic or generational term because I did not learn civics in high school but I did take Government in high school. But it seems that the denotation of civics is the participation and rights of citizens within a governmental entity. Unless I'm mistaken the United States government is a representative democracy in which policy is created according to the mandate of the people. But also who cares about any of that, you stated that my opinion was irrelevant and I explained the meta aspects of debate, I don't think I have to mention that I could easily run for office and if a representative sample of people agree with my opinions I could make them into law. And even that is irrelevant because we are discussing from a layman's perspective the effectiveness of immigration policy and the morality of accepting refugees. If you wanted to offer a counter argument we could keep going, but it seems like you ran out of things to say and resorted to personal criticism. Which is fine. But it's boring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laws are the codified personal beliefs of a large group of people. People enter into debates based off their personal belief system, so mine and yours are as equally irrelevant and relevant in any conversation unless one of us is an expert and it refers to non-ethical/moral questions. 

What even are you talking about with the student loan program? Are you suggesting only higher income individuals should have access to university education? 

You don't believe that someone doesn't want to spend 20 some billion dollars on an ecological disaster that will prove relatively ineffective while ignoring the fact that Drug violence and economic instability is driven by American demand for illicit substances? Sounds like something the MSM is ignoring. 

"Sounds like something I can't provide proof for so I'm going to blame the media" and support the President using confirmation bias to rile up his agitated base.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so yeah I'm also for Comprehensive Immigration Reform because our current immigration system is extremely backlogged and gives incentive to illegal immigration. The pathway to legal immigration includes provisions for self supportive immigrants and sponsors to vouch for the financial stability of immigrants. We were arguing about the merit of accepting low income immigrants or refugees. 

"victimizes our people" is hyperbolic nonsense. The presence of Trump supporters post them shooting those Indian Men in the face victimizing me, please deport Trump supporters preemptively and without further investigation or discrepancy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which isn't a thing and is already part of our process. which is why I think Trump is using the ignorance of the populace to racial code the immigration system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right I misspoke about SNAP, but it looks like SNAP representation is based off of likelihood of poverty which is higher for blacks and Latinos. I could argue for systemic reasons, but I'm sure that's an argument for why we shouldn't accept more Latinos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to my own personal beliefs about we should treat immigrants I also don't want my government spending tax dollars on ineffective procedures and telephone hotline balms. All of my questions were hypothetically posed to try to figure out how this isn't just a complete waste of money. Like a border wall. If both sides recognize that x is a problem why is it effective to propose y solution that is ineffective and then not budge on that solution?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure and how do they confirm that Juan Persona is real and that I felt threatened by him? Will they direct me to an appropriate line if I want to make a report against John Smith because he victimized me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought asking for sources was just proving ignorance of the subject matter and avoiding arguments? Here's a couple: [HuffPost](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2015/02/28/food-stamp-demographics_n_6771938.html) and then here is [Forbes](https://www.forbes.com/sites/bethhoffman/2013/09/23/who-receives-food-stamps-and-why-it-is-critical-to-continue-their-support/#2612d5ec5e49)

I said Trump's merit based immigration reform is stupid because we already have merit based immigration reform to a large extent and he's using America's ignorance of the process to demonize or scapegoat a particular group. Which is rather xenophobic (not rayciss) policy imo. 

Care to share with me how Mexico is raising ideological purists hell bent on destroying American values? Or Guatemala, El Salvador, Nicaragua? Yeah you can't. And in reference to our the destabilized Middle East, that the Obama administration helped to further unrest after the Bush administration decided to try its hand at nation building, does personal responsibility only apply to people you don't like or is it actually part of your moral code and you're just ignoring it because these refugees from Syria are a little too brown?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really thought Peacock would eke out 3 innings after that terrible 1st.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve is like the king of the bobble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man r/mariners always have so many AMAs. Where's my Jake Marisnick AMA r/Astros?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has Pettis lost his windmill identity? It's ST why is he being cautious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peacock's feather are ruffled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that'll push young Springer to the bench.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm. Peacock out of options he could be this years Straily or Woj. Cut or traded after Spring Training. Who will be our 2017 Kratz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been limited to radio so far, so I haven't had a chance to check out the Root team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad former Toronto mayor Robert Ford was able to get it together enough to do Astros radio broadcasts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will be bloated in an obvious way that shows how pointless this method is. But I agree with you I think it will let violent bigots use this shit for justification. Per White Rage which I read this month, after the lynching of a black man in a small community, the responses was "Don't you know Buchanan is president?" I feel we are in similar times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's merit based immigration reform is entirely code for reduction of refugees, asylum cases, and anyone with a humanitarian interest in immigrating and anyone who makes the "not immediately on the dole" argument is ignoring the fact that our current immigration model requires you to pledge that you will not become a burden to the state and be financially sponsored by a US citizen who becomes responsible for you. 

Additionally the white American born demographic disproportionately benefits from and takes advantage of welfare services relative to overall population breakdown. So I'm not sure why this welfare queen myth keeps chugging. 

And again low income, or financially insecure immigrants, do not de facto become a burden or provide zero contributions. If you, and Trump, want to frame the conversation as ending humanitarian reasons for immigration, then go ahead, but pretending that it's because these people are useless is deflecting the responsibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yeah that's why my question is how do you verify and monitor each call? I'm not advocating for it per se, just trying to figure out how it's not easily manipulated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming that Garmin's VO2 race predictions are wildly speculative right? According to mine I should be running a 23:10 5k. I've topped out at 28 mins or so, so far. But I also have been worried I'm not pushing myself hard enough lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if you're a Dem you hope that the other shoe will eventually drop and you try to make the DNC hacking by the Russians connection even harder. This isn't just oh Trump said he would warm on Russia, this is Russia is ideologically opposed to the American way and we need to investigate their influence in our elections (which tbh sounds very Cold War/Red Scary) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schumer just called for his resignation. I was very against Sessions as Attorney General, and just like everyone else he was confirmed along party lines. I take that anything that goes wrong for the GOP will just result in the Dems trying to amplify the problem to the press/public and politically posture as look at the Trump administrations violations blah blah blah and the GOP cover up to swing future voters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was previously subcontracted by CPS to provide services for families. Which was bad dealing with them but manageable. Now I'm just a case manager as part of a legal team and they're case practice is terrible (so far) and they shut down completely with even a minimal mention of "legal" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Complaint**  Working in conjunction with Child Protective Services is a nightmare. I was speechless during a conversation with a supervisor yesterday when she asked me to disclose irrelevant and confidential information. 

**Confession**  Still really loving my new job one month in. Despite the crazy. 

**Complaint** I hate not living in the city. Sidewalks and shared roads need to become more common! 

**Confession/Uncomplaint** I've been running more despite it being more inconvenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yesterday it was high of 60 and moist here but tomorrow it's going to be low 30s and snowy. I just want some consistency from my winter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as a form of protest rendering the hotline useless through a coordinated effort to report all violent crimes or somehow fabricate information in an obvious way could produce the same result as Trumps media survey. It becomes unreliable in any incarnation and confirms nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I'm not going to completely ignore systemic inequality in our system just yet but yeah aptitude can take you far and isn't limited to the wealthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reread Roadwork by Richard Bachman (Stephen King) a lot because Bert is probably the most relate-able character he's every written  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Runtastic has training plans that do this but you have to become a yearly member </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  who won't contribute to our society in any way and will just sit around collecting welfare and reproducing just to be able to tell ourselves that we're good people.

I guess at this point it does become a matter of opinion but that's misguided and wrong. just because you are low income does not mean you can't contribute to society whether you are documented or undocumented. That's just reviving Reagan era welfare queen lies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah I think that's taking it out of context. the last CIRA was what Gang of Eight right? and the GOP backed out because they wanted to use it as a pivot in the general election with Marco or whomever. Then the one before that was with GWII and it fell by the side because of 9/11 and fear mongering that terrorists were coming across our southern border (they weren't). People want CIRA; it's up to politicians to prioritize that rather than outdated enforcement policies. And that's what Democrats, progressives etc don't support. Congress needs to get to work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant moreso those visas that are available for purchase for $100,000 and the exorbitant cost that sometimes comes with filing. You can also make humanitarian arguments for accepting lower income individuals or, the fact that these types of immigrants are already providing low wage labor that we need in America that native borns are not willing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I recall correctly this is still being litigated as in whether or not you can be deported without due process or if legal proceedings need to occur. I think that's the maelstrom we are building up to, explicitly defining what is guaranteed to non-citizens in the United States. 

Supreme Court has also created a test for free speech in which they can determine what is harmful and inciteful (shouting fire in a movie theater is always the example) and what isn't. But that doesn't really apply to political parties or presidents. 

The obvious solution would have been to change our sodomy laws long ago. But some would rather kick the can. Now Trump wants to enforce laws and is called a homophobe. That's the entire debate, our immigration laws have always been somewhat xenophobic and wax and wane depending on the economic climate to scapegoat the low-skilled labor force (c.f. The Chinese Exclusion Act). Which Mark Twain felt was racist despite it being current law. The point is I don't think, well it's established law, should free us from criticism. Conservatives make the same argument for why Roe v. Wade is bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably replying to the wrong person here in terms of communicating the message but I just want to add that Hannah Arendt's Eichmann in Jerusalem also provides some insight into why it's important to nip things in the bud ie evil is banal; and though Eichmann was simply following orders, it doesn't make his actions any less reprehensible. I've also always been struck my Eichmann's reasoning of to not follow orders would have been suicide/career ending because he literally took the wait   see approach despite having some misgivings for fear of personal disenfranchisement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "a few looks", "assholes exist in this world"

but can be inflamed to commit murder like in the Kansas City situation with legal immigrants Srinivas Kuchibhotla, and Alok Madasani </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a dumb example. Think of it this way, the immigration system is so convoluted that you have to have money to get in. You can either buy your way in or be from a desirable country without a back log. If you're from Mexico or Latin America (or China or the Philippines) you can fill out the test but there's no promise it'll be graded. 

Additionally if you try to do independent research yourself (cross the border illegally) you will probably be raped, taking advantage of, and there's a chance you'll die. And then if you make it people will immediately discredit everything you do because you broke the law and "cheated  the system" which is already designed to make it more difficult for you than the other person having their test graded right away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will this be enforced and how will calls be verified? How is this any different than simply calling ICE and ratting out your undocumented neighbor whom you hate? What's to stop immigration advocates from clogging the line with false reports or reports against American citizens like with Mike Pence PP donations. What's the practical defensible point of VOICE? Why not just invest in mental health in more places if people feel victimized so often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you read the studies that I posted, or even just simply the Scientific American article, diversity of race, socioeconomic background, religion etc contributes to a diversity and promulgation of ideas that homogeneity doesn't. Diversity of "ideas" is a subjective standard that can't necessarily be considered for admission to schools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm jealous of your setup there. the town I moved to is more of the older less planned out type. I'm skeptical of that main road between divisions though and would be apprehensive/anxious running through there after commuting home if no sidewalks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm not sure what the logic is. Surely it's safer and easier to fast now than it was when the practice was first implemented. I have a lot of respect for people who fast during Ramadan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep Catholic fasting rules. Plus no meat on Fridays and Ash Wednesday. I get my info from my more devout wife. Growing up we just did no meat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ash Wednesday is all I can think of but modern fasting is two half meals and one full meal. (Unless I remember incorrectly)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could be it. Handler is good at giving hope and then dashing it. I guess I just don't buy it knowing that Montgomery is a part of the VFD and seemingly unaware of the Veiled Facial Disguises and Various Finery Disguises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I would suggest you remove the articles that lean towards "white people are uncomfortable with diversity" to make your point. Because it really undercuts your argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Individual self selection does not equate to diversity is bad especially from a non peer reviewed study.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just picking on a couple of these but it looks like white people are uncomfortable with the introduction of diversity. Want to try distilling your point instead of spamming me with studies and articles for racial purity and homogenization?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most studies show that what matters is unique perspective and approach to problem solving. In addition to the benefit gained by working with others of perceived difference. My problem with morals and values is that there is less of an objective support for what that means and it too easily falls into the Make America Great Again purview of defining America as having a specific value set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That scene at the movie theater was the worst. I'm contrasting that with the flipped canoe conversation and thinking it was just sloppy writing or an attempt to be a little mysterious. The herpatological spy but seemed more for Olaf than for Montgomery and the children  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diversity introduces differing perspective and challenges people to work harder to both meet a unique perspective/argument and respond to it. The SA article pointed out that if you prep a Democrat by saying heres a Democrat who disagrees with you vs heres a Republican who disagrees with you, the Dem will prep harder to work with against the Republican. Its in the links, its the rationale the Supreme Court uses to determine affirmative action cases with higher education like Grutter v Bollinger, UT Austin v. Fisher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not overly familiar with these city's to also do your side of the argument by filling in the one word responses you're making but im going to suggest that has to do with religious extremism on both sides whereas a secular America wouldn't necessarily have that problem yeah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep heres a Scientific American article on the impact of diversity [here](https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/how-diversity-makes-us-smarter/) and a longer study by the US Commision of [Civil Rights](http://www.usccr.gov/pubs/112806diversity.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incidentally when is diversity bad?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Race. Socioeconomic background. Religion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it was because he accepted the Medicaid expansion and it was a big success in Kentucky 

Edit: Kansas to Kentucky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean maybe small sample size but diversity and integration lead to higher individual school performance and deeper empathy for others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back coal! Manufacturing jobs are down! Immigrants are rapists! Etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean besides increase private prisons? His rhetoric is an issue but his solutions are also shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had some hope after that leaked conversation about comprehensive immigration reform but its just more republican bs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Points for whomever got him to stay so on script. Seems like just a rehash of events  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have these speeches always been so masturbatory. Not everything needs a standing ovation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresno Grizzlies unveil bobble heads for 2017 season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best bobble heads in the minors https://instagram.com/p/BREUTKogvSO/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you're being slightly hyperbolic by attributing a poorly planned survey to the entire field of Urban Planning being a quote unquote. I'm jealous of your arrangement though. I just moved from Brooklyn to a suburb and sidewalks end unexpectedly, switch sides, streets are narrow and curving in such a way that I have to be extremely certain a speeding car isn't coming. It's a nightmare trying to find a route.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without a solid Ace on the staff it's a little hard to swallow a good 5th starter like Fiers. He's being tasked with scraping up a win more often than he should be. I'm with you on him being solid at 5, but I get why people are frustrated with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's dehydration? Since there's most likely more space between your last drink of water since you're asleep than evening runs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Per Strava:


* 68.9 miles
* 1,264 ft
* Nope. But I'm starting to see more consistent 9 min/mi for my 5k
* Nope. Signed up for two HM though
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah my only disclaimer for the book is that (at least for me) it feels very made up. But I mean I guess it depends on if super fantastic long distance running Native Americans who live isolated in canyons and are faster than any trained athlete in ultra running and wear huaraches and survive mostly on corn sounds fantastical. It's easily internet searchable though. The Barkley Marathons was intense and great! I feel like someday I might make the stupid decision to do an Ultra because of things like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more into bears you could maybe pick up and carry around Brown Spectacled Bear, Sun Bear, Trash Panda etc rather than bears that could maul me. 

*This is also vaguely sounds like a We Bare Bears reference but none of them are black bears so I must be trying too hard to place it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck with the marathon! I did my first half in November. I'm signed up for two more halfs this year. I'm working my way slowly to a full. Born to Run is definitely a feel good/people were meant to run naturally story if that's what you're looking for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counterpoint Astros Bo Porter put Tony Sipp in LF for an at bat and then chaos ensued when he tried to move him back to the mound  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sipp on pace to strike out every batter he faces. 

Edit: Welp not worth the contract extension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Springer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
