<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3642</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ouroboros (horror) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 15:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ouroboros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 15:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calories in, calories out.

I used the dremel saw I stole from work to cut off the first knuckle of my left pinky. The bosses had to know I took the thing but I doubt they even cared. Whats a $100 tool to a company thats worth millions? Besides, they were getting rid of me, and thats what their priority was. Maybe theyll take it out of the last check they said theyd mail. 

Despite what I thought, it wasnt easy to pull the bone out of the finger chunk. So, I peeled off the nail and then cut the remainder of the piece open with the dremel and took the bone out the messy way. I didnt think much as I popped the fingertip in my mouth and chewed for what felt like an hour before the meat broke down enough for me to comfortably swallow. I tried to figure out how many calories were in the finger segment while also working to determine how my caloric needs have changed now that my body mass had decreased by that little bit. I dont know why I wasted so many years cutting when I couldve done the smart thing by cutting *off*.

My adrenaline was off the chart for the rest of the day and I could barely sleep. I was brimming with excitement; Id actually found a way to beat the system. Why do we need food when we *are* food? This elation was crushed when I stepped on the scale the following morning and saw the familiar, disgusting number: 82 pounds. I punched myself and clawed at my face as I stared at the scarred, bloated atrocity that smirked at me in the mirror. Much too much of me. Far too much. 

I bent the remainder of my left pinky backward and twisted. The mirror-me kept smiling. I twisted and twisted the finger until it was connected to my hand by a tiny, tight rope of skin before pulling the broken digit completely off. I walked into the kitchen and turned on the stoves electric burner and pressed the stump onto the coils. No more bleeding. Back in the bathroom, I took an antibiotic and an Oxy I had left over from my back surgery last year. I didnt want to get too sick to continue or be in too much pain and lose my nerve. I gazed in the mirror while I chewed the cooling flesh off the bone.

Did you know its surprisingly easy to find someone on Craigslist who will perform surgery for the promise of cash? We met in my garage. He inspected the place for cameras, closed the garage door, and slammed the hatchet into my left wrist. I fingered my collarbones and traced the craggy topography of my ribcage as he swore, realizing hed only broken the bones without severing my hand. All the while Id retreated into my head, watching the scene unfold from above. I felt the thud as the blade hit me and the dull popping as he carved away. The Oxy did a really good job masking most of the pain. To be honest, I was a little disappointed.

My Craigslist surgeon looked mildly haunted by what hed done, so as soon as he seared the wound shut with the torch, he ran out. Hed be back soon enough, though. I sat in the garage and stared at the stump where my hand used to be. It smelled like the time mom burned pork chops and almost set the kitchen on fire. My severed hand sat on the table like a flaccid relative of Thing from The Addams Family. Picking it up, I was a little surprised by how heavy it felt. You never really think about the individual parts of your body having weight. Still, I was encouraged. This was an immediate loss of at least a pound or two. 

I gnawed at the sinewy knuckle areas and fought through a dizzy spell. Orange juice helped get my vision to stop spinning. Whether it was blood loss or excitement didnt matter much. Things were finally going in the right direction.

A week later, I contacted my Craigslist surgeon again. I didnt have any more cash, but he agreed to do what I wanted in exchange for a couple of the Oxy pills. I had at least 20 more in one bottle and an unopened bottle of 30 stashed in my bedroom, so hed be happy for a while. Besides, we were almost done. I was almost done.

My surgeon said the next part would probably kill me. I agreed. He got to work. The pills didnt do much to dull the pain this time. The feeling of a saw going through a femur right near the hipbone is a hard thing to describe. Even harder is the sensation one experiences the moment ones femoral artery is severed. Its like the world starts melting and going gray at the same time. Luckily, my surgeon had the torch ready and seared the gushing artery shut before finishing the amputation. When dropped the saw, the first thing I did was try to wiggle my toes. It felt like I was wiggling them just fine. Strange. I threw down another few antibiotics and painkillers.

Before the surgeon left, I demanded that he help me to the bathroom scale. It was hard to balance on one leg and get a proper reading on the scale, but when it finally registered, I was triumphant. 68lbs. The dizziness came back quickly and I yelled to the surgeon who was about to leave. We were going to finish this. It didnt take long for him to agree to take off my other leg in exchange for more pills. Cut cut, burn burn. He carried me back to the scale where I teetered on my lopsided stumps. 59lbs. Then he brought me to my bed. 

So here I am. My right arm works fine; I dont think I want to get rid of that. Its probably the only part of me I find useful these days. I figure I have another couple weeks of antibiotics left. Theyre next to me under the pillow. I tucked my severed legs under the comforter. Over the next few days, Ill nip at them whenever Im hungry. My guess is the hunger pains will become less intense once my body realizes it doesnt have as much to fuel. Until then, Ill just keep taking little bites. Minimal intake, just like Im used to. Just like what keeps me comfortably in control.

www.unsettlingstories.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wife, the Artist [Halloween 2015] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jen and I love Halloween. We go all-out when decorating our house and yard. The neighborhood kids love to see what we put up every year and even their parents are impressed by the scale and sophistication of the decorations we use. We dont just give out candy, we invite the trick-or-treaters into our home to see our setup. Pumpkins, spiders, skeletons, ghosts - you name it, weve got it. Our local newspaper even did a feature on us last year. A Safe and Spooky Spot for Local Kids. It wasnt much more than a fluff piece, but it felt good to have our work celebrated.

A project Jens been working on over the last fifteen or so years is her Halloween Town of Horrors. Its the centerpiece of our trick-or-treat trip around the house. The town takes up our whole dining room table and its a darker take on those big Christmas villages people like put out in December. The architecture is very Tim Burton-esque; lots of strange looking buildings, exaggerated colors, and blood splatters, while the townsfolk lurk in the shadows like little purple zombies and space aliens. As the years have gone by, Jens taken her Halloween town from a couple small buildings to the sprawling, populous nightmare-scape it is today.

This year, Halloween came and went. We had a blast. Jens Halloween town was a huge hit. Even adults from around the neighborhood came over to take a look. Jen loved the attention; she wanted to be an artist growing up, but, sadly, it wouldnt pay the bills. As we cleaned the house, Jen picked up one of the townsfolk dolls. Its clothing had a little tear that needed to be fixed. Sighing good-naturedly, she gathered the rest of them into their box. I love those dolls; their aesthetic works beautifully with the town Jen puts them in. They range in size from a raisin to a lemon; some have distinguishable features, others dont. It takes a while for her to make each one - between 2 and 5 months - but her effort always yields a product thats perfect for Halloween. Until she can carry one to term, we both agree they shouldnt go to waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fertility Treatments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 15:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alternative Medicine (horror) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 17:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fertility Treatments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 17:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They told me when I was pretty young that Id never be able to have a baby. And that was that. No therapy, no consolation, no nothing. I was given the knowledge and left to my own devices to deal with it. They wouldnt have to see me crying at night. Every night. For years and years. I kept it all under wraps, despite hating myself inside. Hating my failure. Hating my parts that didnt work. Hating the jealousy I felt for the women who had that gift and squandered it. I needed to try something. Anything.

It didnt take long before I was ordering fertility drugs online. Clomiphene. GnRH. Diethylstilbestrol. I took them all. Then I had to get sperm. That wasnt too difficult to obtain. A quick few ads on Craigslist, a couple pictures sent back and forth, and a meet up. An hour later, Id have a condom full of what I needed.

I gave the drugs a week to kick in before doing anything else. They made me dizzy and nauseous. Small price to pay, I guess. For the next part, I had to inject the sperm into myself. I had to try lots of spots; I was aiming for where I thought ovaries would be. I figured an ectopic pregnancy was still a pregnancy. And maybe the doctors could fix it if I was lucky enough to encounter that problem in the first place. 

The needles were long and fat and the contents were cold from the refrigerator. In that week, Id been with 30 men. My body ached and my self-esteem was gone, but theyd given me what I required. I injected myself with all of it over the course of the day. My belly was a hole-filled, leaky wreck by the time I was done. And the medication had me dizzier than Id ever been. Its even hard to type this out through the brain fog. But its all going to be worth it when this works. When this works, Im going to have a beautiful baby of my own. One who will be loved. One who wont be told he cant follow his dreams just because hes a boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alternative Medicine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 15:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *June 29, 2015*

Bills been complaining about the cut on his leg. He wont go to the doctor and I dont blame him. He doesnt need a smug college boy in a white coat telling him he cant be working on the house at his age. Back in my day, I remember mom telling us that fly babies ate up all the bad skin and whatnot from a cut thats gone bad. Ill see what Bills got to say about it later.

*June 30, 2015*

Didnt take too long to get Bill on board. Hes always told me Im the smart one of the family. I got him sitting out on the porch with his leg propped up on a stool. That cuts a nasty thing. Goes from the little joint under his knee all the way around to that tendon in his heel. Bills a toughy, though. Hardly complains at all, thanks to the bourbon. I guess we just have to wait and see if those flies will come do their thing.

*July 1, 2015*

What a scorcher today. Bills sweating up a storm and his leg looks bad. A couple flies landed on it but then took right off so I took a little molasses and rubbed it around the cut. And you know what? That did the trick! Before we knew it, there were ten or so of the little guys on the cut at a time. Bill told me they tickled but I told him to man up and let them make their babies in peace. He did.

*July 2, 2015*

Im glad Bill chose to sleep in the chair on the porch. We didnt want to disturb any of the progress we were making. When I looked at the cut in the morning, it was real red. Lots redder than the day before. I told him that meant it was healing. He nodded and had some breakfast bourbon. In the afternoon we started to see some white gunk leaking out of the cut. It smelled pretty bad. From what I remember mom telling me, that always happens before it starts getting better. Bill was glad to hear it.

*July 3, 2015*

Boy oh boy does Bills leg stink. I think he might be running a little fever, too. A fevers the bodys way of fighting an infection, so its good hes got his own body working with the fly babies. Speaking of those, we can see the little buggers wiggling inside that cut. Theyre real small but theyre definitely there. I make fun of Bill and call him a momma and he tells me to shut up and we laugh. I made sure to make him an extra big dinner so he could have his strength and keep fighting the good fight. 

*July 4, 2015*

Happy Independence Day! Wish it was a happier one for Bill. He had a real hard time getting to the restroom with his leg as swollen as its gotten. He left a trail of those white worms as he walked. I asked if he was Hansel or Gretel. He didnt get it. I shouldnt poke fun at the poor man. But it doesnt feel like his fever has gotten much higher so weve got that going for us. Tomorrow Im going to peek around inside the cut. Better get Bill some extra bourbon because its gonna hurt.

*July 5, 2015*

My poor Bill had a bad fall in the middle of the night when he had get up to go pee. I didnt even hear him and only found out in the morning when I saw some blood and fly babies on the floor near the bathroom. Well, that, and he wouldnt get out of bed. Took some convincing for me to get him to show me what he hurt. That tendon in his heel that was already a little cut up just snapped and rolled up like a window shade. He couldnt move his foot at all and had to hop all the way back. Dont know what it says about me that I couldnt hear him hopping and grunting. Guess Im getting old.

*July 6, 2015*

I got Bills leg all splinted up as best I could. He really hooted and hollered when I tried to pull that tendon back into place. We agreed I should just give up and let it heal on its own. Some good news, though - the fly babies are looking great. There might be a thousand of the little guys in there and some even grew up and started laying their own eggs. The itching is bothering Bill real bad and he said hes got a hell of a sore throat. Im trying to make all his favorite dinners to help keep his mind off it.

*July 7, 2015*

Bills leg is swollen up real bad and the sheets on the bed are starting to get wet with whatevers coming out of the cut. Doesnt smell right either. I took as many of the fly babies out as I could reach and poured some rubbing alcohol in the cut. Boy I thought he hollered yesterday! I thought hed break all the kitchen china all the way from the bedroom with the way he yelled. Hes got some bad lumps on the sides of his neck. On top of all this, my poor Bills gotta deal with a cold. When it rains, it pours, I guess.

*July 8, 2015*

Bills fever is high. I asked if he wanted me to call the doctor and he would have none of it. I feel stupid for asking.

*July 9, 2015*

The smell coming off Bills leg woke me up at sunrise. I opened up all the windows and tried to air the place out. It was hard for Bill to wake up. Hes fighting that cold with everything hes got. Hes always been a fighter. A little cut and a cold wont keep my man down. Theres a lot of flies in the house lately. I figure theyre from the babies in his leg. To be honest, theyre just becoming part of the background. Ambiance, I think they call it. 

*July 14, 2015*

I havent written for a while because Bill passed away the other night. It mustve been his heart. Id been worrying about how his ticker would hold up against all the other stuff. Wasnt an issue for years, though. I guess it doesnt matter. I still go to bed with him every night. I dont want him to be alone anymore than hed want me to be. Plus, and I know Im a big weirdo for thinking this, but I dont want all those baby flies to be without their momma. Bill didnt like being called that, but we both knew it was true. The little babies are all over his mouth and nose and eyes. Maybe other spots too but I dont want to look and make Bill blush. The girls in heavenll make fun of him for a while if they saw him blush. No, Im content with watching him the way he is. Big Momma Bill. You know, I always wanted to be a grandma. 

www.unsettlingstories.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIFW I just ate a big meal and I'm trying to initiate sex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 20:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snapshot of a New Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 00:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel happiness. Elation. Old Me experienced misery. He was stationary, stagnant, and sad; a shuffling personification of malaise. But Old Me ended earlier today. Peer into my eyes and watch as hes devoured.

In the late afternoon afternoon, I strolled through our small-town markets and malls, restaurants and theaters, touching all I could. Its amazing how oblivious people can be. Back home, a few hours later, local news reports started coming in.

Biological Mystery. Impossible Pregnancies. Plague.

Each headline fed my reinforcement mechanisms. Elation begat ebullience. Ebullience begat euphoria. I am the Infestor of Wombs.

I wandered, undetected, through blockades and cordons and walls. When I chose to be seen, they flocked to me; women walked, girls skipped, infants crawled. Old Me peeked out from behind my eyes, only to retreat, sobbing.

Gravid bellies seethed from the impatience of the lives-to-be and threatened to tear their mothers in half. I walked from home to home, invisible again, stroking the hair and skin of my surrogates, watching them smile contentedly during this brief respite from pain. Soon after, they all gave birth.

Scores Dead. Devastating Deliveries. Stillbirth Epidemic.


My Little Girl crawled to my home as I slept and was waiting on my doorstep the next morning. I bathed Her tiny body and removed the remainder of Her umbilical cord. She stared at me with Her radiant eyes as I poured warm water over Her skin. Extinguish the stars, She whispered, smiling. I kissed the top of her head. I am the Father of Joy.

Joy grew as I fed Her throughout the day. Old Me was nearly gone; his presence only manifested as prickles down my spine as Joy raced through Her childhood and adolescence and peaked as a young woman over a period of hours. Joy told me She was ready and I followed Her into the basement.

She stood in the center of the dirt floor, beaming at me with adoration. I am the Gaze of Beasts, She breathed. I heard a ripping sound as the corners of Her mouth tore to Her ears. Her teeth cracked and splintered and fell to the floor. Fingernails peeled off and fluttered to the ground like dead moths. Old Me shuddered and exhaled his dying breath. Joy was still for a moment, but then She began to change. I watched in awe as Her flesh sagged and split and the pores of Her skin gave birth to the eyes of Black God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snapshot of a New Man (horror) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 20:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snapshot of a New Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 20:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The following excerpt has been released by Wikileaks following over a year of refusals by the United States Government to provide answers about the US military action in the town of Clearview, Maryland. The action is reported to have killed nearly 400 people, all US citizens or legal immigrants. This attack was unprecedented, illegal, and has been vehemently denied, despite overwhelming evidence of a massacre. It is hoped that this bit of information can bring to light some of what occurred in Clearview and help end the mystery of the attack on US citizens by their own government.*

**January 9, 2016**

I feel happiness. Elation. Old Me experienced misery. He was stationary, stagnant, and sad; a shuffling personification of malaise. But Old Me ended earlier today. Peer into my eyes and watch as hes devoured. 

In the late afternoon afternoon, I strolled through our small-town markets and malls, restaurants and theaters, touching all I could. Its amazing how oblivious people can be. Back home, a few hours later, local news reports started coming in. 

Biological Mystery. Impossible Pregnancies. Plague. 

Each headline fed my reinforcement mechanisms. Elation begat ebullience. Ebullience begat euphoria. I am the Infestor of Wombs.

I wandered, undetected, through blockades and cordons and walls. When I chose to be seen, they flocked to me; women walked, girls skipped, infants crawled. Old Me peeked out from behind my eyes, only to retreat, sobbing.

Gravid bellies seethed from the impatience of the lives-to-be and threatened to tear their mothers in half. I walked from home to home, invisible again, stroking the hair and skin of my surrogates, watching them smile contentedly during this brief respite from pain. Soon after, they all gave birth.

Scores Dead. Devastating Deliveries. Stillbirth Epidemic.

**January 10, 2016**

My Little Girl crawled to my home as I slept and was waiting on my doorstep the next morning. I bathed Her tiny body and removed the remainder of Her umbilical cord. She stared at me with Her radiant eyes as I poured warm water over Her skin. Extinguish the stars, She whispered, smiling. I kissed the top of her head. I am the Father of Joy.

Joy grew as I fed Her throughout the day. Old Me was nearly gone; his presence only manifested as prickles down my spine as Joy raced through Her childhood and adolescence and peaked as a young woman over a period of hours. Joy told me She was ready and I followed Her into the basement.

She stood in the center of the dirt floor, beaming at me with adoration. I am the Gaze of Beasts, She breathed. I heard a ripping sound as the corners of Her mouth tore to Her ears. One by one, Her teeth dropped to the floor. Fingernails peeled off and fluttered to the ground like dead dragonflies. Old Me shuddered and exhaled his dying breath. Joy was still for a moment, but then She began to change. I watched in awe as Her flesh sagged and split and the pores of Her skin gave birth to the eyes of Black God.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body Cast (horror) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body Cast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 16:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My therapist suggested I write this out. I guess reliving that night and putting my experiences on paper will help me get over the trauma. 

A few years ago, I was in a motorcycle wreck. Broke my left tibia and fibula, shattered my right patella, got a greenstick fracture of my left femur, multiple fractures in my pelvis, breaks in almost all my ribs, and two broken collarbones. I was immobilized from the shoulders down by a heavy body cast. They told me I was lucky.

My wife, Violet, was supportive and nurturing. She never once complained about having to care for me. She cooked all my meals, kept me company, and emptied my bedpan without grimacing. About two weeks into my convalescence, Jenna called us, bawling, because her college roommate died. Vi had to leave immediately and be there for her. Vis sister, Kathy, was going to take care of me.

When I woke up the following morning, Vi was off to get Jenna. Kathy was there, cheerfully making breakfast and talking up a storm as she helped me with my more embarrassing biological needs. Like her sister, she never made me feel ashamed. She left around 11 that night and told me shed be back at dawn. 

I like to sleep with the TV on. For some reason, I find it comforting. Id drifted off while the game was finishing and only woke up when I felt something thud against the cast on my chest. In the flickering light of the television, I saw a huntsman spider staring back at me. She was bigger than most of the ones Id seen around here; maybe the length of a rugby ball. My breath caught in my throat and every muscle in my body fired in an attempt to push the thing off me. I couldnt move. 

I started yelling at the spider, hoping it might scare her away. She wasnt frightened. She turned around, exposing her abdomen to me, and I gasped. Her back and belly were covered in babies. They rippled like windblown fur as they moved over their mothers body. The huntsman turned back toward me and walked closer to my face.

Before then, Id never thought about spiders having a scent. This one did. It smelled like wet dirt, sort of like how outside smells after a rainstorm. The smell intensified as its long legs reached my face. I squeezed my mouth and eyes shut. Its prickly legs advanced, first to my lower lip, then my nose, my eyelids, and finally my forehead. Its leg-span stretched from ear-to-ear, hairline to chin. Its thick, heavy body ran from my chin to right between my eyes. And it stayed there.

I tried to hold my breath. To say I was horrified was an understatement. I wished I was dead. I prayed to be dead. My prayers went unanswered as it walked a little higher, letting its abdomen brush against my nose.

I sneezed.

The huntsman immediately buried its fangs into my forehead as her babies streamed from her abdomen onto my face. I shrieked. Tiny spiders crawled over my cheeks, squirmed through my beard, and hid in my eyelashes. I thrashed my head back and forth in an attempt to get them off me. The mother moved onto the pillow by my right ear and bit my cheek. It felt like a wasp sting. Then she ran over my shoulder and pushed herself through the tiny opening of the cast by my armpit.

At this point, I was screaming uncontrollably. A sea of baby arachnids explored my nostrils, hair, and were starting to find my ears. I felt a tendon or ligament or something snap as I thrashed, sending white-hot pain through my neck. Trying to move my head after that was excruciating. 

As the babies dispersed throughout my face and head, the mother explored under the cast. To this day, I have no idea how she was able to compress herself to fit underneath the thing. She wandered over my chest to my stomach and down to my groin. She exited the cast by the hole nearby, only to move back inside by my legs. She stopped at the underside of my knee. And thats where she stayed.

When Kathy arrived in the morning, Id somehow fallen asleep. I guess the exhaustion brought on by the horror Id experienced forced my body to shut down even though my mind was still soaked in terror. Oblivious to the events of the night before, Kathy shook me awake. I started screaming again. I felt the huntsman behind my knee. She mustve been sleeping, too, and was startled awake by my yelling. She bit my leg over and over as Kathy tried to calm me down and tried to get me to fill her in on what was happening.

By the time I was able to tell her, she looked like she was about to faint. Id always considered myself somewhat of an arachnophobe, but Kathys fear of them was light years beyond my own. She called emergency services, and they sent a couple guys who were able to coax the thing out and kill her. In the end, it was anticlimactic. 

Vi came home with Jenna later in the day and Kathy and I told her about my night. Neither of them were able to listen to the details. A family of arachnophobes. Time went by and my broken bones knitted together and healed, and eventually I was back on my motorcycle. Every night, though, I dream about the huntsman staring at me. I feel her young streaming across my face and up my nose and around the gaps of my teeth. Whenever theres a quiet moment, I hear them scratching at my eardrums, and Id swear that every time I clean my ears, Im pulling out eggs.

www.unsettlingstories.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you hear the one about having oral sex with an Indian guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 16:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever drink a glass of saliva? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 16:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Schrdinger couldn't prove the cat was dead or alive, why is the box I put mine in starting to smell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 16:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a 34 year-old toddler. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 03:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I hear Netflix might be producing new episodes of Gilmore Girls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 00:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I have a serious comment in a thread and you guys come in and say, "Hey, I have you tagged as 'likes sea creatures up his cock!'" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 23:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I use Johnson's baby shampoo when I masturbate, will it help me stop crying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 17:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to load a crate (from /r/woahdude) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 02:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU when I had my first sex dream in years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 01:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened early Monday morning. I rarely have erotic dreams anymore. I used to have them a lot when I was 15 or so, but 20 years later I'm usually dreaming about food or flying or something. However, during that brief, pre-dawn moment, I was 15 again.

All I remember is that I was performing oral sex on a beautiful woman. The hottest aspect of the dream was how she smelled. It was so intense and animalistic; never before had I experienced such a pheromonal head-rush from a dream alone.

Toward the end of the dream, I remember I was rubbing my hand against her crotch over and over and then sniffing it. It was then I woke up and realized what I'd been doing: I had been rubbing the area between my balls and my legs with my hands and then sniffing them as I dreamed.

TL;DR: I should shower before bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rhinoceros licking elephant semen from the vagina of another rhinoceros. For lack of a better title. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 21:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Tom and Jerry fans here? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm working on my technique for jerking off two guys at once but I keep getting interrupted by a fly buzzing around me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 19:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He found a baby bat rolling around on his deck (via /r/aww) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 14:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, I successfully grossed myself out. Enjoy. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 19:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never been to a Reddit meet-up, but if they play out like this one did, I'll become a regular. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 18:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something about toenails brings out the worst in me. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't believe I forgot to post this. Here's "Sockets" - enjoy! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did a 24 hour sous vide on big piece of chuck steak. Tasted like prime rib. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 20:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chewing hair and tasting history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 17:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/subject3642: A place to read fun, life-affirming stories about romance, creativity, and snowballing termite queen innards. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 15:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the hypercorrecting owl say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 20:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the hypercorrecting owl say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 19:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cam Newton or Tyrod Taylor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 15:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I apologize to any lions who may find this offensive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 16:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Normanogenesis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 15:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Norman gazed across the structureless void; a formless vacuum of unbounded cosmic nothingness. He looked down at his watch. It was far too dark to see the position of its hands. Sighing, Norman pressed the button to illuminate its face. Blackness, still.

Norman drifted for countless subjective eons, his frustration growing. The Indiglo button on his watch had long since eroded away under the cumulative stress of unquantifiable presses. He remembered how the watch face looked when lit up: bright, welcoming. Informative. But now it was gone.

He put the watch to his ear. It still ticked. With his arm back at his side, he realized he could still hear the faint ticking. There was no other sound. The steady ticking persisted without end for another colossal epoch. During that period, Norman began to devise his own sense of time. It worked. Finally, he could start planning.

Norman floated along. He couldnt tell if he was moving at incredible speed through billions of spatial dimensions or simply stuck, motionless, in zero. It didnt matter. As the watch ticked in the void, he plotted and schemed.

The void felt different to Norman when he was ready to put his plan into action. It appeared the same, but the sensation he perceived was no longer one of emptiness, but one of ripeness - of gravidity. The feeling gave him hope; the hope all great minds have when their creations are to be unveiled.

Norman embraced the void from all sides. He felt it rush in to fill him; an avalanche of nothingness somehow given shape and weight and form through his perception of it alone. It was then, he knew, he could manipulate this cosmos of nothingness. It was now his clay, and he was the sculptor.

Power flowed through Norman as he sculpted nothingness into form. Always on the verge of being overwhelmed, but somehow managing to hold on, Norman wept with joy. Through his tears, through the sobs which convulsed through his body, Norman closed his eyes and whispered, Let there be light. The power of the void left him, and all was still. 

Norman gazed across the structureless void; a formless vacuum of unbounded cosmic nothingness. He looked down at his watch. It was far too dark to see the position of its hands. Sighing, Norman pressed the button to illuminate its face. And there was light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A different kind of doctor. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 15:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marriage material. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 18:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that on September 11, 1973, the government of Chilean president Salvador Allende was overthrown by a military coup led by Augusto Pinochet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 14:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Kayjay25 describes why he considers fellatio an art form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 15:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Bernie Sanders and a Kentucky clerk won't let me marry my fianc, Richard Dawkins. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 16:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of melon can't run off and get married? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 16:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cantaloupe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We get it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 14:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See that girl / watch that scene / eating a termite queen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A couple makes love atop the carcass of a decomposing whale. Welcome to /r/subject3642, new subscribers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 02:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yesterday I was drinking out of a straw during lunch and last night it woke me up and whispered in my ear, "why'd you stop?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many Neil deGrasse Tyson quotes do I have to memorize before I become a real scientist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Albert Einstein's parents name him that knowing he'd be a world-famous scientist or did they just get lucky? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 18:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This bot is fucking great! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 04:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a cool idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My writing process: "Hey, that's pretty cool - I wonder if a guy would shove it up his cock." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 02:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They can't all be winners. (I had big hopes for this one.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did we make the ISS as big as Jupiter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife is leaving me because I punched my son for being a misogynist. Is it wrong to defend women against someone who crassly claims they going to study a broad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are limericks about foot-binding in bad taste? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those with poor dental hygiene need love too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 20:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who says, "Bugs, you stole my hearing aids?! You're despicable!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 18:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deafy Duck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who says, "Phlbbbbtfffbllph I NEED TO SAVE THE WORLD IN LESS THAN 24 HOURS phlbbbbtthhphhbbl" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 03:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queefer Sutherland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What He Told Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 19:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We knew there was something wrong with him. Something about the way he was sitting. Wed given him a wide berth; the smell alone warranted that. But beyond that, there was a disconcerting amount of tension in the man. I knew I wasnt the only one worried about the potential for violence he signaled. 

Peristaltic ripples of dread pulsed through my gut when the train slowed to a crawl. Another service outage. The train stopped completely, accompanied by the automated message indicating a technical issue and an assurance that we would be moving again soon. At least the lights stayed on this time.

Nervous smalltalk ebbed and flowed. Wed stopped in a bad place. The emergency exits were unobstructed, but they led to a cement wall. The tunnel was excruciatingly narrow and felt claustrophobic, even within the relative roominess of our subway car. We were in the first car of the train. At the front was the locked compartment housing the conductor and her controls, and the rear led to small gap separating our car from the next one in line. The man sat in the corner seats closest to that exit.

We grew quiet as the mans breathing became loud enough to hear over the din of conversation. Sweat poured off bald head and neck and disappeared into the fabric of his heavy woolen coat. The bituminous matte of his skin was in stark contrast with the high-gloss white wall behind him. He looked like a shadow. We all stared at him.

A collective groan rose from the passengers when he stood up and dropped his coat on the floor. He stood in place, starting at the wall. He was naked - his body a frightening combination of scar tissue and slabs of muscle. The nauseating scent of ammonia washed across the train car like a chemical spill. My eyes teared up and I was at least twenty feet away. I couldnt imagine how bad it was for those half that distance. I saw people take cell phones out of their pockets, presumably to call 911, but none of them had success. I figured we were in a tunnel under the river. No service. Everyone backed away as far as they were able while still trying to respect the personal space of those around them. I fumbled around in my purse for a minute and felt a bit of relief for the first time since boarding the train. To say I was grateful for my sisters gift of a little keychain pepper spray was an understatement.

The relief didnt last. The people nearest the man were the first to cry out when he bent down to pull a knife from his discarded coat. Now we began to panic. There was nowhere we could go. Within ten seconds of seeing the knife, those closest to the emergency exit windows had pulled them from their panes only to realize there was about six inches of clearance between the car and the wall. 

The parts I want most to forget are those I remember with the greatest clarity. 

His knife was short and thick. Probably four or five inches long with a wooden handle. It didnt look particularly sharp. It cut well, though, as we all saw, when he sat back down and started carving into the skin on his legs. Everyone was yelling or screaming or shouting. Some yelled at the man, who didnt even look up, while others simply expressed their horror in whichever way suited their individual personality. I caught myself repeating, oh fuck, oh fuck, with progressively-increasing volume before I noticed a little boy next to me whose expression begged for the sight of a calm and collected adult who could tell him things were going to be okay.

Then someone tried to be a hero. A guy in baggy khakis and a sleeveless t-shirt. He approached the man, bobbing and weaving like a boxer. When he went for the knife, the man grabbed his shirt with freakish power and pulled him to the floor. I saw the hero hit his head hard on the handrail on the way down. Dazed, he struggled to get up. The man pushed the knife into the back of the heros neck. He didnt move after that.

Now my fellow passengers were on the verge of hysteria. Some of the bigger guys were pounding on the door of the conductors cabin and yelling at her to open up. She was yelling something back but I dont know what. When I redirected my attention to the crazy man, who Id only taken my eyes off for about five seconds, he was standing again. Long strips of black flesh hung from his thighs. Hed sliced strips from his groin to his knees, exposing the muscles underneath. In slow motion, I watched them twitch as he advanced toward us.

The first person he grabbed was a middle-aged woman. His large left hand grabbed her lower jaw; thumb under her chin and fingers in her mouth. She shrieked around his fingers in a higher pitch than anyone else in the car. She bit down. I remember how his blood darkened her teeth and dribbled out of her mouth. He didnt flinch. He adjusted her neck so she was staring into his eyes. He stared for a few seconds. Then he swung the knife into the top of her head, killing her instantly. He let her drop to the floor, her teeth still clamped around his fingers, tearing off the skin as she fell.

Two more women died the same way. In our panic, wed begun pushing and shoving one another to get away from the man. None of us were brave enough to run by him and try to get to the other car. The stronger ones of us were the victors here, pushing the smaller, weaker passengers at the man as they worked to get further from him.

A tall, heavy businessman stood between me and the murderer. I knew what was coming. I braced myself to no avail. He picked me up and threw me at the man, my 100 pound frame being no obstacle in the businessmans quest to run away.

The man grabbed me before I could crash to the ground in front of him. I closed my eyes and screamed, knowing I was about to die. I felt him wrench my chin and jaw and I vomited around his gore-caked fingers as they pushed down my throat. I waited for the knife to fall.

But it didnt. His breath, humid with putrescence, replaced the omnipresent odor of ammonia. My eyes opened to the sight of his face a mere six inches from my own. He stared at me with a rapt intensity Id only seen from cats about to pounce on their prey. I struggled against his grip, but he was incomprehensibly strong. I scratched and kicked at him, aiming my blows at his face and groin. He still held on.

The next thing I knew, I was on the floor. His left hand still remained in my mouth while I felt his right pushing up my skirt and tearing my underwear off with one violent pull. Then he was inside me. I screamed in protest and agony only to hear the sounds gurgle around his long fingers lodged in my throat. I prayed for him to kill me. Every thrust of his hips made me feel like my bones were shattering under his weight. After a while, I gave up struggling. I stared into his eyes and sobbed as he gazed at me. Then he was done.  

He slowly pulled his fingers out of my mouth, causing me to choke and cough. His entire weight was on top of me. The screaming in the background was just white noise at that point. I gasped, trying to fill my lungs under the pressure of his mass. When he rose up on his knees and raised his blade, I knew the sweet, unobstructed breath I took would be my last. Again, though, I was wrong. He sliced through the carotid artery on the right side of his neck. Hot blood splashed onto my face and puddled inside my gasping mouth. Letting the knife fall to the floor, his enormous hands moved up and grasped my head. 

The last things I ever saw were his long, chipped thumbnails pushing in toward my eyes. In the blinding whiteness that followed - in the piercing silence that overtook the cacophony of screams, one clear voice broke through. Extinguish the stars, it told me. I drifted into a void of unconsciousness.

My coma lasted for seven months. Im in the hospital. Blind. Dictating my story into a word processor. The last couple weeks of being awake have been terrifying; every sound I hear still causes me to spin my head and try to look at the source. Im still not admitting to myself that those days are over. 

What the man said to me resonates throughout every waking moment of my new life. I try to pick it apart in my head in a vain attempt to find some meaning in it. Of course, theres nothing. Extinguish the stars, I murmur to myself, running my trembling hands over my belly. As if in response, I feel the baby kick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A brief and loving relationship between two women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 16:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I come in peace. Sorta. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Thfffft." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 500 subscribers? How the fuck do I keep 500 people happy? What do I write that'll be new and interesting for my readers who've already seen my most vile creations? I'll have to do something that'll shock even them... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iia stared at his laptop screen with disbelief. Five hundred readers. Five. Hundred. He sat back. The smile on his face was one of pride, but, internally, he worried. What do I do next?, he asked himself. Ive done it all; leg gum, the eye fairy, Melanie, Maude, things up cocks, things left to congeal, but what can I do thats new?

Grumbling under his breath, Iia stood up from the couch and walked over to the kitchen. Hed just been to the store. Whole Foods. Pricey, yes, but conveniently nearby. He opened the refrigerator. Many components and potential food items, but nothing snackable. The clock on the stove read 5:01. His girlfriend wouldnt be home until late. Long after dinner. He wondered what he could do to fill all that time. 

With a groan, Iia hauled the 15 cast iron pan from the cabinet beneath the granite countertop. He was sore. Leg day was only two days ago, plus hed reaggravated an old hip injury. He felt as if two decades had been added to his three. Bro, do you even lift?, he joked to himself, as he plopped the pan onto the stovetop and turned the flame to medium-high.

As the pan heated, Iia freed a package of spicy Italian sausage from the confines of their natural casings. They were from a local company and had quickly become his favorite. Lots of fennel. 

He crumbled the sausage meat into small, coin-sized chunks. By the time he was done, the pan was hot and ready. He drizzled a small amount of extra-virgin olive oil onto the iron surface and immediately followed it with the sausage. The sizzling sound was a pleasant harbinger of the porcine aroma that would soon follow. As the fat rendered, he began chopping some garlic. About four cloves. He liked to make them thin; a larger surface area meant more flavor got infused into the end product. 

Time passed as Iia stirred the sausage around, making sure it was golden brown and delicious. Once that critical status was achieved, he removed about 95% of the meat from the pan with a slotted spoon. The remaining pieces spat and sizzled in the fat left by their colleagues. Iia cranked the heat to high. The blue flame under the pan grew like a gravitationally-contained supernova. The sizzling sound increased. 

Reaching over, Iia plucked the tube of tomato paste from the countertop. He squeezed in about four tablespoons of the scarlet substance and stirred rapidly, gritting his teeth as oil splattered on his bare forearm. As the paste browned, he threw in the little medallions of chopped garlic. The timing of this part was crucial: the remaining sausage in the pan was about a minute from burning. The tomato paste would be charred in less than twenty seconds. The garlic had to get cooked in that time period.

Iia watched the garlic slices with the rapt intensity of an epidemiologist working to identify an infection vector. With only seconds to spare, he emptied half a bottle of Sauvignon Blanc into the pan. Steam exploded from the surface, followed by a bright flame. Iia was prepared for this. He calmly covered the pan and watched as the flame quickly died out. Uncovering it, he stirred the mixture, making sure to scrape all the bits of sausage and caramelized tomato paste from the bottom of the pan. Once he was satisfied with the deglazing, he reincorporated the sausage meat hed put aside.

By now, the concoction was finally starting to look like a sauce. It would still have to reduce for about forty minutes on low heat, though. And that was fine. There was still one major part to work on.

One other item Iia had purchased from the store was a small plastic package of heirloom grape tomatoes. They were beautiful; yellow, red, orange, and purple. His favorites. With great care and a very sharp knife, he halved the lycopersicum gems and arranged them, cut-side up, on a baking sheet. They were then drizzled with extra virgin olive oil, coarse sea salt, cracked black pepper, and a chiffonade of basil fresh from his cousins garden. All this time, the oven had been preheating to 400 degrees. It was ready for the tomatoes to be deep inside.

Iia pushed the baking sheet into the hot body of the oven. It accepted it without complaint. He set a timer for 25 minutes. Now, the only thing left to do was get a pot ready for the pasta.

Growing up in an Italian-American family, Iia had particular love for pasta. All kinds, really. This dish, however, called for something special. Something with a good chew that could hold up against the firmness of the fennel-packed sausage. And that pasta was cavatelli. 

Iia brought a pot of water to a rolling boil. The timer had just gone off and the roasted tomatoes were resting on the unoccupied burner space next to the still-reducing, but nearly-finished, sauce. He salted the water generously; hed always had the best results when the water was as salty as the Mediterranean. Into the water went the cavatelli. Theyd only take a couple minutes. 

He watched as the little pieces bobbed in the turbulence of the cooking process. Once they floated to the top, he moved them directly into the cast iron pot housing the sausage sauce. Iia turned up the heat on the sauce again. It was now thick, the wine having reduced and emulsified with the rendered sausage fat. He stirred the pasta and sauce gently, letting the cavatelli soak up as much of the liquid as possible. He poured in half a ladle-full of the water from the pasta pot; the salty, starchy fluid would help flavor and bind the sauce to the cavatelli.

Satisfied with the cooking process, Iia added the roasted grape tomatoes. Their bright, sweet acidity would be a perfect compliment to the fatty unctuousness of the sausage sauce. He stirred them in gently so they didnt break. 

Iia took his favorite pasta bowl from the cabinet on the left of the sink. It was a pale gray-blue. It reminded him of the ocean on a cloudy day. A few scoops of the pasta went in. He took a fork and brought his dinner to the couch. He refreshed his subreddit. Still five hundred subscribers. No one had left as he cooked. No one came to the conclusion he was a weirdo hack in that period of time. That had to mean something.

He chewed the pasta with satisfaction. It was delicious. Some of the best hed made in a long time. It took him about ten minutes to finish the bowl. By then, he was getting full. He glanced at the television. The Pioneer Woman was just starting. Perfect. With a contented sigh, he put down his fork. As he watched Ree Drummond, he thought about his future. His future as a student. As a writer. As a life partner. The last one made him so happy. Theyd recently been talking about getting a kitten. A fluffy gray one with little ears. Her name would be Hugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The time I was lucky enough to get inspired by /u/AWildSketchAppeared. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 13:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sebastian the crab from The Little Mermaid is known to change song lyrics to accommodate shifting circumstances. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 18:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melanie and the slugs, as requested. (NSFW/NSFL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any of you like dinosaurs when you were kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 18:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm also an amateur art critic. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does a code-switching trilingual Russian say when he wants to increase his bovine supply? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 14:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ms cow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Believe it or not, this extremely short story might be my favorite one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of experts are saying we'll eventually have to start eating bugs if we want to properly feed our growing world population. I'm way ahead of 'em. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's been a really, really long day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome, new subscribers! Here's a story about a Spring-Winter romance. (Very NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 13:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The time I wondered how many hummingbirds I could fit in my mouth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much rain has fallen in Texas? (x-post /r/mildlyinteresting) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two words: Leg. Gum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 03:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot interracial erotica, subject3642 style. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comfort Food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 20:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife lost her battle with bone cancer a year ago. I have no one. 

Ive worked from home for the last six months. My employer has been sympathetic and accommodating after everything that happened. Too many workplaces neglect and end up getting rid of disabled employees. I guess I should feel valued. 

Breakfast was mac and cheese left over from the night before. I hadnt made enough for my breakfast to be even remotely satisfying. Stock prices and quantitative analytics spilled from my computer monitors as I tried to concentrate on work. My eyes kept drifting over to the picture of me and Brynn on our wedding day. I have no attention span when Im hungry.

I groaned as I lifted myself into a standing position. My knees were shot. I made my way over to the kitchen pantry and got a bag of chips and a bottle of soda. Coughing as I trundled across the office over to my desk, Id already opened the chips and was pushing them into my mouth. As I walked by and saw my reflection in the glossy murk of my hibernating television, I could swear I saw Brynn standing by my side. When I blinked, she was gone. Just like a year ago.

By lunchtime I was just finishing the chips and the bottle of soda. I was ravenous. My concentration had improved somewhat as I ate, and I made a few good trades that got my company some cash and me a nice commission or two. But it was noon. The market volume was drying up as everyone went to lunch. Id start working again around two and go hard until closing bell. Until then, I had to eat something. Anything.

The pizza delivery guy always brings me extra stuff because Im a generous tipper. At this point in my career, I earn more money than I know what to do with, so why not spread it around? I ordered two large Sicilian pizzas, some mozzarella sticks, garlic knots, and chicken alfredo. The delivery guy brought me a pint of ice cream and a cannoli. He got a $100 tip. I think my interaction with him is some of the only person-to-person contact I have nowadays.

I sat in front of the TV as I ate. I didnt bother to turn it on. When I looked up after finishing my first pizza, Brynns reflection was watching me. Her body was distorted by the curved surface of the television. She was shorter. Heavier looking. Compressed. She moved her arms as if to embrace me. I squeezed my eyes shut and tried to regain my composure. I had to be hallucinating.

The lids of my eyes lifted to the sight of her face inches from mine. My scream reverberated throughout my cavernous office space. Before Id finished my yell, shed wrapped her arms around me and nestled her head against my shoulder. Everything went white.

All I can remember from that moment was blissful warmth and closeness. I can only describe it as reexperiencing the minute I knew I was in love with her, along with all the associated tactile sensations of the most intimate embrace Id ever felt. The experience couldnt have lasted more than two seconds.

When it was over, it was as if every organ had been ripped from my body and Id been left to exsanguinate on the floor. A feeling of overwhelming emptiness swept over me like an atomic inferno. My mourning period following Brynns death was nothing compared to this. I was a bottomless pit of despair and loneliness.

The expanse of my lunch was still spread in front of me. Mindlessly, I began eating. Every swallow felt like an eyedropper of water attempting to refill an evaporated oceanscape. But it was progress. I ate until nothing was left. My stomach ached, protesting the amount of food it had been forced to accommodate in such a short period of time. But the hunger remained. The emptiness remained. And it taunted me.

I tried to get on with my day. Work was out of the question. There wasnt much food in my house, so Id started drinking soda. I definitely had enough of that. One of my closets had countless three-liter bottles of the generic brand I preferred over the popular ones. Id gone through two of them before I started feeling lightheaded. I couldnt begin to imagine what this was doing to my already-unhealthy blood sugar. That was the least of my concerns. 

Around 8pm I walked out of my house for the first time in almost a month. Everything had been delivered to me over that period of time. Hoping there was still gas in my X5, I clambered up into the drivers seat. I was shocked at how much bigger Id gotten since I last drove and felt my only moment of relief all day when I discovered the seat could go back another few inches. The car started with no effort and I began driving to the store. I was in no condition to drive. My vision kept blurring and despite the tremendous pain of emptiness I felt, I desperately wanted to go to sleep. I managed to keep my composure, however, and made it to my destination.

Even with the handicap tags on my truck, the short walk from it to the store felt like torture. I was wheezing by the time Id taken my cart and started pushing it around the front of the store. There was no way Id use one of the motorized scooters they provide. I dont have much pride left, but I still have enough to keep walking until I simply cant anymore. 

I bought whatever was closest to the doors and the cash registers. I didnt care what. I had a bagboy help me load up my car with the three carriages-worth of food Id purchased. The gratitude I felt for him and his colleague as they pushed and emptied the carts was immeasurable and I emptied my wallet of cash to thank them. I went home.

My entire trip was spent eating. When I got back I turned off the car and sat in the dark, illuminated only by the dim light of my garage. I frantically worked to tear away wrapping and packaging. Sleeves of crackers disappeared down my throat. Partially-frozen TV dinners of meatloaf and mashed potatoes followed. I sobbed as I pushed it all into my mouth, hacking and coughing crumbs onto my steering wheel and dashboard. Only when my stomach pain was nearly unbearable did my feeling of emptiness dip to a level where I had the strength to get out of the garage.

It took nearly an hour to empty my car of the colossal amount of food Id purchased. I crashed onto my couch, gasping for air as stars twirled before my eyes. A few minutes later, after Id regained some semblance of wherewithal, I felt an acute pain in my right shoulder. When I reached around with my left hand to investigate, I yelped as I sliced into my index finger. Some asshole had left a juice glass on the arm of the couch and it had fallen off onto the cushion. That same asshole recently fell onto that couch without looking and shattered the glass with his shoulder.

I went into the bathroom. A familiar, morbidly-obese man greeted me in my full-length mirror. I turned to look at the damage to my shoulder. Chunks of glass were embedded in my shirt and skin underneath. Despite my disgust with myself and the pain in my shoulder and stomach and finger, I felt slightly better and less empty. Sighing, I pulled off my shirt and felt shards of glass detach from my shoulder and plink onto the ground.

The feeling of emptiness reemerged like the head of a hydra. I began to cry. I stared into the mirror at my shirtless self, watching the blood trickle from my shoulder in thin rivulets which were stopped by the absorbent waistband of my sweatpants. I wrapped my arms around my body in desperation. The cheap facsimile of an embrace only served to make me sob harder. I released the hold and started plucking the remaining glass from my shoulder. Each removed shard made the feeling of empty loneliness intensify. The feeling became overwhelming when I pulled out the last piece. I stared at the shard through my tears with curiosity. Then, without a hint of critical thought, I pushed the shard back into my shoulder. A tiny fraction of my emptiness evaporated. A fraction comparable to an entire stomach-full of food.

Time seemed to freeze as I methodically broke the larger shards of glass Id removed from my shoulder into hairpin-sized needles. I carefully plunged them into my skin. By the time Id finished with the glass, there was a semicircle of crystalline splinters decorating my upper arm. Warmth radiated out from the shards and suffused through the surrounding skin. The pain was miniscule compared to the emptiness the glass had helped eliminate. 

With more energy than Id been able to muster since my experience with my wifes apparition this afternoon, I hurried to my office to find my stapler. I assumed I was losing my mind. A healthy person doesnt see his dead wife. A healthy person doesnt ameliorate emptiness through food and glass. But what I felt was real to me. It was as real as the floor on which I stood and as real as the air filling my lungs as I gasped with the tiny pinpricks of relief I felt as each staple entered my arm. I emptied the stapler into myself, refilled it four times, and was left looking for something new to use.

I went to the garage and over to Brynns work area. She would frame pictures and paintings for her friends and family and even set up an Etsy shop before her diagnosis. Everything was right where shed left it. 

An hour went by as I pushed tiny, sharp framing nails into my other arm. These hurt much more than the glass or the staples. I arranged them in a tight, sleeve-like grid. Pain radiated throughout the limb, but I persisted. A few times, when I blinked, I saw Brynn.

Right now, its the morning after the events Ive described. I havent slept. My night was spent finding ways to fill that void inside me. Up to this point, Ive been successful. Every part of me hurts, though. Everything, from the top of my head to the bottoms of my feet, is covered; punctured and impaled in some way. Most of it is broken glass from the various glasses and china sets in the kitchen. Some of it is from my wifes old sewing box. Each of my fingertips have long pins originating right underneath the nail and terminating somewhere up toward the knuckles in my hands. Its hard to type with straight fingers. 

Im standing at my computer desk because my back and buttocks are caked with broken glass and the pain is too intense when I sit down. Even though the bottoms of my feet are equally encrusted, I have less sensation in them because of my underlying medical conditions. When I walk, I can feel the thicker and longer chunks of glass carving at the bone. 

The part I find most difficult to deal with are the series of thumbtacks in my soft palate. They are constantly causing me agonizing discomfort and they itch just as much as they hurt. I cant help but to trace my tongue around them which just draws my attention to their presence even more.

The constant, caustic undulations of searing pain are only tempered by brief, infinitesimally-soft brushes of warmth. I know its my wife trying to touch me again. But the feeling of emptiness within me is still there, albeit far less intense than yesterday. Ignoring it just makes it worse. I have to keep going, but I dont have any space left. I know what Im going to do next, and probably finally, and thats okay. 

In a few minutes, Ill be slashing open my belly and thighs and arms and stuffing them with the entire pantrys-worth of our splintered wedding china. I cant live with this feeling of emptiness. If doing this is what it takes to give me some relief and peace of mind and body, its what needs to happen. I have the knife honed and ready. As I write this, I know with 100% certainty Im not in my right mind. Ive long since stopped caring. And with that, Im going to go now. Whether or not this plan works, at the end of it all, I might have the opportunity to be with Brynn again. That's worth more than anything in this life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's the TL;DR for this little bit of alternative history I wrote: "If you go back in time to the 1680s, puke strawberries into the mouths of Pilgrims. They'd pay you." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I get a lot of people mentioning "The Ant Story" in my private messages. So, here's the ant story. NSFW. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/subject3642 - I like to write stories. Some of them are funny and gross. Some of them are sci-fi or horror. Feel free to check them out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I write stories. Lots of them are funny and gross. Some of them are sci-fi and horror. Feel free to check them out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 01:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend's reaction when we're fooling around and I whisper, "I want you to show me your sexy birth canal." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy mother of fuck, over 100 people subscribe to my sub?! I'd like to share with you the most disgusting thing I've ever written. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 23:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the picture that inspired it. The title was, "Had to clean up pelican vomit. Safe to assume he has stomach worms."](https://i.imgur.com/Jlqzq.jpg)

Ted had a secret he kept from those close to him. He was so worried they wouldn't understand; that they'd think him odd or ill. Luckily, in this time of great online interconnection, he could find sympathetic, or sometimes even supportive, friends. I was one of those friends.

I'm a veterinary ornithologist. Birds are my business. You got a sick bird? I'll make it a healthy bird. Sparrow or albatross, egret or jackdaw, i'll fix 'em all. After meeting a particularly ill pelican, I remembered Ted.

It seemed like I hadn't even finished hanging up the phone before I heard a frantic knock on my door. I let Ted in, and he was in prime form. By prime form, I mean he was shirtless and had a raging erection pushing out the front of his Dockers like a battering ram. Apparently he was ready.

I introduced him to the sick pelican. "Pelican, Ted. Ted, pelican." Ted curtseyed, the pelican projectile vomited. The projectile hit Ted in the chest like a peanut butter javelin and stuck to the copious hair on his torso. Ted looked down and instantly confirmed to himself that I hadn't been exaggerating.

The vomit was easily 65% worms in total mass. They writhed in their sticky confines and looped through his chest hair like eels swimming through a kelp forest. Ted gingerly plucked one from his chest and sucked the vomit from it as if removing sauce from a piece of bucatini. He growled with delight.

I stood back and watched, fascinated. The pelican, which was somehow still alive, also watched, more wormy vomit dribbling from its gullet in a steady stream. Ted was now nude. One by one, he was lining up the worms and pushing them into his urethra. Due to the upward tilt of his erection, I could see them swimming up his vas deferens before disappearing, I presume, into either his bladder or prostate. Either way, they wouldn't be getting out until he wanted them out.

Ted continued, silently. Once the worms were all out of his chest hair, he moved to the pelican. He carefully picked it up, obviously not wanting to harm the bird, and tilted it upside down and let it drain its stomach contents into his mouth. "Just like a mother bird feeding her baby," I thought. As an ornithologist, I found this to be beautiful. One species fulfilling the needs of another. Once the pelican ran dry, Ted slowly placed it back down on its makeshift nest.

Ted thanked me and left. I started to clean the floor, replaying the events in my head with curiosity and awe. "What a world we live in!" I thought. The pelican retched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In case any of you wonder how I live, this is a direct quote from my beautiful, sweet girlfriend: "Having a bubbly butt makes me salty." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a 33 year old 8th grader. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 23:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any sci-fi fans interested in seeing something like this get developed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 13:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Im documenting a rough recollection of the events I helped set in motion. After that Ill try to keep track of whats going on now as long as Im able to.*

What happened after the simultaneous eruptions of Eyjafjallajkull and Kalta last month indicated what were internally calling a miscalculation of capability. Patterns were detected by satellites studying the ash trapped in the gales of the upper atmosphere. Cellular automata. Fractals. Polyhedra. Patterns which formed and collapsed at random intervals and lingered for a few seconds before transforming into something new or dissolving into windblown chaos. 

The survey drones we sent up didnt disturb the patterns when they were encountered. The shapes waxed and waned as the surveyors deployed instruments, took measurements, and beamed back data. There were strong electrical fields within the patterns. The fields were dynamic; each pattern shift was accompanied by a change in the current. Each repeated pattern had the same charge as its previous iteration with less than a nanovolt of variation.

After a few days, the ash clouds should have dissipated far more than they had. By then, the general public knew something strange was happening in the atmosphere. There were three main sectors, all in the northern Atlantic area, with high concentrations of stratospheric ash. Those areas became packed with all types of aircraft: surveyor drones, picoturbines, personal camsquitos, and every other flying device that curious people sent over to watch what was happening from their homes, offices, and labs.

On the 9th of April, the ash clouds started to descend. Over a period of about two hours, the ash moved from the stratosphere to 150 meters above the North Atlantic. The three zones then coalesced into a shapeless, dark gray mass about 300km northwest of the coast of Scotland. It remained there, motionless. 

At that point, everyone was watching. Theories bounced off claims and got synthesized into proclamations. All of them were wrong, of course, since our small research team hadnt said anything to anyone. We were afraid of what was occurring, but we were more afraid of what might happen to us if we admitted responsibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's funded by the Qatari royal family... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW when I tell my girlfriend "hold on!" but it's too late. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 02:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let me guess: it's worse than Hitler? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sepultura - Ratamahatta [metal/tribal] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 03:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I might be a horrible person, but at least I love Disney movies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 02:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are men and women essentially the same or is there a vas deferens between us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 17:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wore shorts to work today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 15:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the first day of 2015 that I've worn them. Well, aside from my few trips to the gym. I haven't gone there enough lately. My legs are a little cold but I have a space-heater under my desk so things are okay. My office is getting a little toasty, though. I have a small patch of eczema on my calf that will probably get a little better now that I don't have long pants rubbing it all the time.

The girl at Dunkin' Donuts must have had lotion on her hand when she put the top on my coffee because it smells like lotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If all ships are female, shouldn't the bow be called a curtsey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 20:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a decrease in air pollution is responsible for heavier babies being born in Beijing, should the United States increase air pollution to fight the obesity epidemic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 15:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And by "unpopular opinion," I mean "obviously the most popular opinion on Reddit." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 20:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the next card to come out determines my sexual orientation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 21:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The third part of "Sockets" that was deleted by /r/nosleep mods because it was considered "torture porn." I can't say I blame them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 23:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good afternoon, readers! My name is Rudolph Baylor. I am composing and submitting this narrative of last nights events from my, and our, friend Iias Reddit account for reasons I will momentarily reveal. For the sake of full disclosure, I must admit I am the man with whom Iia has been working. 

Now that we are on the same page, I will provide a bit of personal backstory heretofore unknown to you all. 

As I mentioned above, I am Rudolph Baylor. Im 52 years old. In what now seems like a past life, I was a day-trader who made quite a bit of money in the forex markets during the early growing-pains of the Euro adoption. Im by no means a King Midas, but Ill just say Ive been quite fortunate. 

One of the problems with making enough money in a few years to last ones lifetime is trying to fill the following years with purpose. I ended up doing what many, many people have done when searching for purpose: I trawled the Internet. Most of this trawling was to kill time. I make no effort to hide that fact. As a man uninterested in the hedonia that drives others to seek social and sexual interactions, I sought intellectual stimulation on the World Wide Web. 

Between 2002 and 2011, I read hundreds of thousands of journals, followed the rise and fall of popular online fora, and became a prolific contributor to Wikipedia. If this sounds like a boring life, you may compliment yourself on having good analytical instincts. The problem was, my options were (and are) limited. 
Some of you may have gathered, based on Iias accounts of our time together, that I have a superhuman ability to ignore pain. Unfortunately, there is nothing superhuman about it. Congenital analgesia carries great risks - not only to my physical well-being, but to my pride; not being able to feel pain means not being able to feel the pressure of my bladder or bowels. I make timed trips to the restroom every day to prevent an accident. Leaving the controlled environment of my home carries more unpredictability than I wish to endure. You can imagine how difficult my school years were; especially when the only physical sensations I seem to be able to feel involves tickling.

Ive digressed. In an effort to make this biographical tirade short, I will endeavor to get, as they say, to the point. The latter portion of my Internet research time became highly specialized as I developed a strong interest in herpetology - specifically gecko lizards. Those wishing for an explanation as to why those animals resonated so deeply within me will come away disappointed. Anyones guess is as good as mine. The best I can come up with is that it is simply a manifestation of body dysmorphia resultant from my experiences as a child with my medical condition.

My self-diagnosis of body dysmorphia led me to research the condition and seek out biographical accounts of other sufferers. The vast majority of those accounts were from victims of eating disorders, and, more recently, from transgender individuals. Very few people claimed to experience a feeling of belonging to another species. The few I did encounter, mostly on websites such as Tumblr and Reddit, labeled themselves as x-kin, with the x representing the animal with which they identified. Therefore, in the parlance of our times, I guess I am a geckokin.

Assuming Id only be happy once I at least attempted to become that which I felt so close to, I placed the Craigslist ad, met Iia, and everything went basically according to the two stories that preceded this one. 

Now, as for why this is being posted from Iias account, the answer is very simple: I followed him home, knocked him out, and have tied him to his kitchen table. 

Why am I telling you all of this? For those asking that question, good for you! From one inquisitive mind to another, I appreciate your investigative drive. Im telling you all of this to raise awareness of what happens when someone with a severe mental disturbance has no choice but to act on his urges. If I were to admit my geckokin nature to a professional, all it would lead to would be an attempt to treat my condition rather than help me embrace who I really am. I know who I am; or, at least who I will be. Its unfortunate for Iia that he needs to experience what Im certain will be a great level of discomfort, but all great leaps forward in societal progress have their casualties. On some level, Im sure he will understand.

Its fortunate that Iia doesnt have neighbors nearby. He just wont stop screaming. How he managed to find an apartment building thats in such horrendous disrepair astounds me; one would think that being one of the only tenants in a building that has 70-something apartments would be an indication to avoid signing a lease. Still, I wont pretend to understand the rationale behind his decisions. Im sure he didnt understand why I asked him to do what he did to me.

Such a busy night ahead of us! The next phase of my transformation is more dangerous than the work Iia did on me and I wouldnt trust anyone other than myself to do it. Still, I need to practice on at least one other person so I dont get it wrong and really hurt myself in the process. So far, Im working to get Iias transformation up where mine is. Id already taken out all but two of his teeth. As he said in his first story, those molars are a bitch.

I got the last one in the upper right-hand quadrant with the hammer. I warned him that his sobbing would make him aspirate some of the bone chips. Did he listen? No. In his blubbering, he inhaled a couple shards of tooth and I had to wait a half hour until he stopped coughing them up. The molar on the bottom was a wisdom tooth. Iia has a really big mouth. His wisdoms came in with room to spare. I remembered the success he had with standing on the chair and pulling mine out, so I got up on the table, grabbed the tooth with the pliers, squeezed as hard as I could, and pulled.

I must have been squeezing too hard. The pliers crunched through the tooth and gripped the root and when I pulled, only the root came out. It sounded pretty awful, a bit like crumbling a styrofoam coffee cup. Iia screamed and screamed. I used the edge of the pliers to shave down the gum line around the shattered tooth and knocked away the remaining bone. I took advantage of his wide-mouthed howling and hammered two of the same type of metal tooth-pins hed installed into my mouth yesterday. They broke through the bottom of the bleeding sockets in his gums and secured themselves deep within his jaw. I had to knock him unconscious again to do the rest.

Once the new teeth were in and Iia was coming to, staring at me in wide-eyed horror as realized he wasnt waking up from a run-of-the-mill nightmare, I realized Id forgotten the chisel to do his nose and ears. The only silverware he had was plastic. No real knives. Who doesnt have knives? I sighed in annoyance. Then I realized I had the right tools with me all along! Id been so busy focusing on my next moves that Id neglected the new teeth given to me just yesterday. 

I bit Iias nose as hard as I could. I felt the cartilage crush as the tiny needles lining my gums broke through. The pins anchoring the teeth to my jaw held, Im happy to note, and I pulled back sharply. The nose came with me. I was very surprised by how good a job I did when I estimated how far the pins needed to be to ensure proper adhesion. 

The holes in Iias face gurgled with blood as he worked to breathe through them. I knocked him out again, untied him, turned him over on his stomach, and restrained him. Ugly, flatulent sounds filled the room as the blood that had accumulated inside his sinus cavity got pushed out through the nose holes. I bit off his ears.

Now Iia and I had achieved the same level of our gecko transformation. I found two straws in his cabinet and inserted them into his nose holes. Air traveled freely through them, so I untied him, removed his clothing, turned him again onto his back, and restrained him. It was time to work on the aforementioned dangerous part of the transformation.

Geckos have cloacas. Put as simply as needed, they eliminate all their waste from one hole. I assume that the easiest way to replicate this would be to route ones urethra through the colon and allow all waste to be expelled through the anus. While this is an entirely makeshift cloaca, Im not deluded enough to believe there is a better way for me to accomplish such a thing at my nearly nonexistent level of medical knowledge.

To my dismay, upon inspecting Iia, I discovered Id overestimated the size of an adult penis. Id always known mine was larger than average and I knew that would make it easier to properly route what needed to be routed. Iias penis, however, was less than a quarter of the size of my own. It stuck out from his pubis like a pink, fleshy lightswitch. Some of it I attribute to his terror and some to his recent loss of blood, but the unfortunate truth is that Iias member is woefully undersized. The look on his face when he regained consciousness and saw me holding and inspecting his penis would have been funny if I wasnt so concerned about whether or not I could get this to work. I really, really needed a knife.

Rummaging through Iias drawers, I found a vegetable peeler. The blade turned out to be very sharp. I grazed my forearm with it and happily discovered the edge was keen enough to remove hair. I truly sympathized for Iia at this moment. I didnt want to strike him in the head again, as I didnt want to contribute to any lasting brain damage should he live through his whole process. So, I chose to leave him awake as I ran the peeler up and down his penis, removing thin strips of skin. 

Much like the sound of my voice changed when my own nose was removed, so too had Iias. The few actual words he exclaimed sounded filtered through a very bad head cold. His screams, however, were mostly unaffected. These screams continued after Id finished peeling when he saw that I held the thin cord of his urethra. I felt quite a bit of relief when I found it could stretch further than Iias tiny penis had suggested.

Iia passed out from exhaustion or shock moments later. Right now, Im taking the time to finish this account of my evening and research the best way to approach the colon and begin the urethral routing. I will likely update you all with another story tomorrow to let everyone know how the last few bits of the process fared. Arent we lucky that these stories are considered fictional? Ill wait and work here worry-free. Enjoy Friday, everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>    ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ Upvote this if ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ you are a beautiful strong Redditor ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ who dont need no DMCA takedowns ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~    </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A music video starring a fat South Korean singer/rapper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 17:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Najeneun ttasaroun inganjeogin yeoja
Keopi hanjanui yeoyureul aneun pumgyeok inneun yeoja
Bami omyeon simjangi tteugeowojineun yeoja
Geureon banjeon inneun yeoja

Naneun sanai
Najeneun neomankeum ttasaroun geureon sanai
Keopi sikgido jeone wonsyat ttaerineun sanai
Bami omyeon simjangi teojyeobeorineun sanai
Geureon sanai

Areumdawo sarangseureowo
Geurae neo hey geurae baro neo hey

Areumdawo sarangseureowo
Geurae neo hey geurae baro neo hey

Jigeumbuteo gal dekkaji gabolkka

Oppa Gangnam Style
Gangnam Style

Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style
Gangnam Style

Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style

Eh, sexy lady
Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style

Eh, sexy lady
Op, op, op, op
Eh-eh-eh, eh-eh-eh

Jeongsukhae boijiman nol ttaen noneun yeoja
Ittaeda sipeumyeon mukkeotdeon meori puneun yeoja
Garyeotjiman wenmanhan nochulboda yahan yeoja
Geureon gamgakjeogin yeoja

Naneun sanai
Jeomjanha boijiman nol ttaen noneun sanai
Ttaega doemyeon wanjeon michyeobeorineun sanai
Geunyukboda sasangi ultungbultunghan sanai
Geureon sanai

Areumdawo sarangseureowo
Geurae neo, hey, geurae baro neo, hey

Areumdawo sarangseureowo
Geurae neo, hey, geurae baro neo, hey

Jigeumbuteo gal dekkaji gabolkka

Oppa Gangnam Style
Gangnam Style

Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style
Gangnam Style

Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style

Eh, sexy lady
Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style

Eh, sexy lady
Op, op, op, op
Eh-eh-eh, eh-eh-eh

Ttwineun nom geu wie naneun nom
Baby, baby
Naneun mwol jom aneun nom

Ttwineun nom geu wie naneun nom
Baby, baby
Naneun mwol jom aneun nom
You know what I'm saying

Oppa Gangnam Style
Eh-eh-eh, eh-eh-eh
Eh, sexy lady
Op, op, op, op
Oppa Gangnam Style

Eh, sexy lady
Op, op, op, op
Eh-eh-eh, eh-eh-eh

Oppa Gangnam Style

Oppa is Gangnam style
Gangnam style

A girl who is warm and humanly during the day
A classy girl who know how to enjoy the freedom of a cup of coffee
A girl whose heart gets hotter when night comes
A girl with that kind of twist

Im a guy
A guy who is as warm as you during the day
A guy who one-shots his coffee before it even cools down
A guy whose heart bursts when night comes
That kind of guy

Beautiful, loveable
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey
Beautiful, loveable
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey
Now lets go until the end

Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style
Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style
Oppa is Gangnam style

Eh- Sexy Lady, Oppa is Gangnam style
Eh- Sexy Lady oh oh oh oh

A girl who looks quiet but plays when she plays
A girl who puts her hair down when the right time comes
A girl who covers herself but is more sexy than a girl who bares it all
A sensable girl like that

Im a guy
A guy who seems calm but plays when he plays
A guy who goes completely crazy when the right time comes
A guy who has bulging ideas rather than muscles
That kind of guy

Beautiful, loveable
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey
Beautiful, loveable
Yes you, hey, yes you, hey
Now lets go until the end

Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style
Oppa is Gangnam style, Gangnam style
Oppa is Gangnam style

Eh- Sexy Lady, Oppa is Gangnam style
Eh- Sexy Lady oh oh oh oh

On top of the running man is the flying man, baby baby
Im a man who knows a thing or two
On top of the running man is the flying man, baby baby
Im a man who knows a thing or two

You know what Im saying
Oppa is Gangnam style

Eh- Sexy Lady, Oppa is Gangnam style
Eh- Sexy Lady oh oh oh oh

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That one time I truly worried I might have Aspergers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 17:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A relationship involving love, compassion, and skin tags. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 12:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the moderators on WTF sent me a message and said this story had been reported to the mods more than anything he'd ever seen. I wonder why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 00:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home sweet home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 00:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If all roads lead to Rome, how do I leave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 00:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know about the anti-climax, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 18:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your uncle's really good at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/subject3642. No posts, no activity. The mod is inactive and has no karma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M'ssiah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the first animal to answer a question was asked, "How do you like your memes?" to which it replied, "Dank." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 00:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumbwaiter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our new house was an old house. We spent tons of money on renovations and upgrades before we could live there. The basement was particularly heinous. After a while, it started coming around and was looking less like the pit of despair from when we bought it and more like the man-cave I dreamed of. Once everything was done, we finally moved in. 

One of the kids was poking around in her closet the other day and discovered an old dumbwaiter. I had no idea we had one of those. It led down into the basement, but apparently the compartment had been bricked up before we even moved in. When setting up my man-cave down there, I just plastered over the brick like any of the other walls.

During one of the worst snowstorms I can remember, we were all bored in the house. The two girls were playing in their room and my wife and I were trying to read in the dim light coming in from outside. The power had gone out about three hours earlier. Living in the middle of nowhere has its aesthetic perks but its definitely a tradeoff in the luxuries department. The kids were using the dumbwaiter, as always, sending one of their dolls down, making up a little story together, and then rescuing their doll when they pulled it back up from the bowels of the house. I heard a little bump when the kids accidentally bottomed it out in the basement. Then they pulled it back up.

The the youngest one screamed. I didnt even flinch. Theyre 4 and 7. Theyre always screaming. But then her sister started in. And they didnt stop. My wife and I ran upstairs and the girls were backed up against the far side of the wall wailing and crying. I tried to ask them what was wrong but they were inconsolable. The older one pointed at the closet. I went inside and looked. Inside the dumbwaiter compartment was their pet hamster, only really, really messed up. Its eyes were expelled from their sockets and all its guts were pushed out its backside in gristly tangles of rodent offal. 

My wife was trying to comfort the girls and theyd at least stopped screaming. They kept saying they never put the hamster in the elevator (thats what they called it) and he never left his cage. We didnt bother to chastise them for lying at that point - they were obviously too upset. My mind was elsewhere, though. I was trying to figure out what the hell happened to that hamster. It was inside the compartment, so it couldnt have gotten crushed underneath when the dumbwaiter hit the bottom. It almost looked like the poor thing got put in a vice and was squeezed to death.

We let the kids sleep in our room that night. The power was still out. My thoughts kept going to that hamster. There had to be a reason for it. I tiptoed out of the room, stepping over the kids sleeping bags, and went to their closet. I quietly worked the dumbwaiter up and down. On the third trip down, I felt the rope shudder when I accidentally struck the bottom. I hoped I didnt wake anyone up. I carefully pulled it back up. I thought it had gotten caught on something; it was heavier than it should have been.

I gradually got it back to the top without making any more noise and locked the handle and opened the door. The empty eye sockets of my youngest daughter gaped at me as she tumbled out of the dumbwaiter, her entrails sliding out after her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's an air conditioner outside my window. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 17:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not on because it's still winter. It'll probably get used once it starts warming up; likely late May or early June. Sometimes we have a streak of really warm days in May but the building owners don't turn on the AC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIFW I'm peeing and I can hear my upstairs neighbor peeing at the same time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It looks like /u/subject3642 leaves his account signed in on his home computer, so hi everyone! If Iia was the one posting this, maybe he'd have called it "Sockets 3." I prefer the title "A New Perspective;" it sounds much more mature. I hope you all find it enjoyable and enlightening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 20:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Further Alterations (A continuation of "Sockets") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's what happened last time.
](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/2x8hdv/sockets/)

A little over a week after I submitted my story about spiders and pulling teeth, I received a message in my Reddit inbox. [Heres the link.](http://i.imgur.com/ul6zCWi.png)

After I read it, I experienced an entirely new sensation: I shivered with horror and nearly came in my pants. $250,000 is a TON of fucking money. No more college loans, no more 1983 Camry, no more 300 square foot apartment. All Id have to do is meet up with that lunatic again. Well - more than just meet up. I had a feeling Id be earning every cent of that 250k.

I replied to him and he quickly wrote back. I was to meet him the next morning at the same house.

I got there at 8:00. He greeted me at the door, his smile showing off his perfectly passable dentures. He hadnt aged much over the four years since wed last met. He was still thin and beautifully dressed and looked very healthy. I was so happy when he pointed to the fridge and told me there was more of my favorite beer inside. Before we went into the basement, I grabbed a Burton Baton and started nursing. 

The basement had a layout very similar to the last time. I almost cried with relief when I saw there wasnt anything resembling a shoebox full of spiders underneath the gray cloth covering what I assumed were more tools for the job. The man sat down in the same chair. It had some bloodstains on it from our previous encounter.

Pulling out my teeth was the first step in my transformation into a gecko lizard, he confidently claimed. This time I just came right out and asked, what the fuck are you talking about? I wasnt going to be as passive as I was last time. If the teeth-pulling was completely crazy, then this was another fucking dimension of nuts.

Geckos have very different dental structures than humans, the man said. Their teeth are much smaller and very sharp. I thought about shaving mine down but they just wouldnt be the same. Their faciocranial structure is vastly unlike our own, too, as Im sure youve noticed. Today we will be working on all those things, plus another if we have time.

He pulled back the cloth and revealed the familiar hammer and pliers. Accompanying them this time was a chisel, a carving knife, and a series of what looked like double-sided metal thumbtacks, each with a long pin on one side and a set of six shorter pins on the other.

Those are my new teeth, the man informed me. You will be putting them in the old sockets. All your money is in that big duffel bag next to the fridge upstairs. He took out his dentures and grinned at me with his pink gums. You can begin.

I sighed with deep resignation, turned around, and walked upstairs. Abita Turbodog, Foothills Sexual Chocolate, and Brooklyn Lager came back down with me. All the money had been there, too. Fuck.

When I got back, the man was patiently reclining in the dentists chair with his mouth agape. I peered inside. Perfectly clean holes peered back at me, reminding me of the work Id done those years ago. I picked up one of the pins and tentatively touched it inside the socket. The man brushed my arm away and said, the long side of those pins need to go deep so they dont fall out. He leaned back again and opened his mouth.

I drained my Turbodog while he spoke that last sentence. Sexual Chocolate time. After a few sips, I picked up the pin and hammer. I poked the tip into one of the bottom sockets in the front of his mouth and pushed. I felt it break the skin but didnt go far. At all. Fuck. I pushed a lot harder. I heard a little bit of a crunch and the tip disappeared about three more centimeters in. I still had about two inches to go. I guess it was hammer time.

I started tapping in the pin with the gingerness of an artist trying to tap in a hook to display a wall painting. The man smacked my leg and grunted what sounded like come on! with unveiled irritation. I slammed the hammer down, plunging the pin into his jawbone. It stuck and it didnt budge when I tried to wiggle it. Blood seeped from around the edges. 

Keep going, the man told me. I did.

Id jammed all the pins into his jaw without much of a problem save for one of the ones near the back. I was slightly off balance and the strong hammer blow caused the pin to go down on an angle and it erupted out the side his gums and jawbone. Splinters of bone and what looked like a white loop of nerve pushed out of the wound. I pulled the bone shrapnel away with the pliers and did my best to twist the nerve back into its home. Then I levered out the pin and nailed it in properly. Through the hole where Id made my mistake, I could see Id put the tip right through the nerve. The man didnt even twitch.

So, the new teeth were in. They looked truly bizarre; tiny, sharp metal spikes lining puffy, bloody gum tissue. My Sexual Chocolate was long gone. I opened the Brooklyn Lager and chugged the thing. Then I went upstairs to get more. Holy fuck Lagunitas Hop Stoopid.

The piney-tasting beer had an astringent quality that seemed to help wash away some of the dirtiness I felt. I fondled the 250k in the duffel bag and retreated back to the basement with the whole 4 pack. When I got there he was naked. Fuck.

Geckos dont have noses like us, he told me. Please remove mine. He handed me the hammer and chisel. The chisel was brand new and had a 3 edge like a razorblade. I really, really didnt want to do this.

He sat upright and I touched the edge of the chisel to the bridge of his nose right near the forehead. The skin broke immediately. That edge was really fucking sharp. I didnt even take the time to gather my thoughts. I brought the hammer down on the chisel as hard as I could. The nose sheared off his face with the ease of pulling rubber cement off the flap of an envelope. Blood poured out of the wound. The cartilage was completely severed; the remains of the organ hung loosely on what were the outer edges of his nostrils. I just grabbed it and yanked it off. The fucking guy looked bored.

Ears now, he said, his voice pitched differently and having a flu-like timbre. I repeated the nose move with his ears. Those came off even easier. 
The man now looked like something youd see as evidence in a war crime deposition. Except for the fact that now he wouldnt stop smiling. He jumped up from the chair and disappeared around the corner by the furnace and yelled dont forget to take your money!"

I dont know why I followed him. What good could have possibly have come of it? When I turned the corner, I saw an enormous glass tank. The man was inside, crouching on a rock. His hands were full of spiders and scorpions. More skittered around the bottom of the tank, which I should probably be calling a terrarium. Handful after handful disappeared into his mouth. His jaws worked and worked and I heard the sickening crunch as the arachnids turned to pulp in his spiked mouth. He swallowed everything he chewed and brown juice ran down his neck and chest. He walked up to the glass and looked at me. Next time we finish, he said, his mouth stuffed with writhing legs and pincers.

I nodded, trudged upstairs, took the duffel bag, and went home. Im sure Ill hear from him again once hes healed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a medical caretaker for a depressed man named Huey. For the last three years, I've lived with him and tended to whatever needs he might have - needs that have grown more numerous as time went by. He used to be a day-trader who made a pretty good amount of money with some unique trading strategies. It's not like he was rich or anything, but he made more than enough to keep me employed and to satisfy his addiction. As much as I wanted to help with that addiction, it was the one thing I wasn't allowed to address. All I could do was tend to him and try to minimize the harm as best I could. I knew the time would come when I'd just have to stand back and watch, helpless.

Huey awoke to the dull white noise that signified his eventual transcendence. He rolled out of bed; quite literally, as his girth had ballooned over the last nine years to a hair under 500lbs. His knees and ankles were terrifically swollen. The ligaments and joints had undergone immense stress because of his weight gain. Had today come a year later, there would have been a chance that he wouldn't have been able to walk.

But walk he did, into his kitchen. From the window, he saw a brownish-black mass outside. The mayflies had finally arrived. They had arrived in numbers that even he had refused to hope for. Here they were, though. In the flesh. And they would soon be in his.

Huey was a compulsive ingester. He needed to feel full - his body constantly felt like a gaping maw and his life had been spent trying, but ultimately failing, to relieve the physical feeling of emptiness. But today, this would end. He recognized how his failures had been the result of his small, pitifully-average mouth. To fill a hole quickly, the opening had to be larger. And the more openings there were, the faster it could go.

Huey stripped naked and stepped out into his front yard. He carried a large chef's knife. He opened his mouth as wide as he could while inhaling deeply. Flies filled his mouth and he chewed and swallowed. To him, it felt like an eyedropper attempting to fill an ocean. He was ready. First, he opened the corners of his mouth with his blade, creating a ghastly rictus that exposed his entire dental system. His mouth could achieve a much wider position now, and the flies filled it in greater numbers.

Next, he took the tip of the blade and began to unhinge his lower mandible. This took work, and Huey was no surgeon. This didn't matter much to him. The longer he took, the thicker the cloud of mayflies around him grew. They took to his wounds, laying their eggs, and doing whatever else mayflies did. Huey continued inhaling the flies into his gut as he carved, and he was finally successful in the removal of his lower jaw. His tongue lolled out obscenely and was instantly coated in the writhing mass of insects.

Encouraged, he continued. He made more and more cuts into his body, first shallow, then, once the flies began to accumulate, he went deeper. He decided to begin flaying his skin; the insects seemed to be attracted to his subcutaneous fat. Each one that landed on him and contributed its mass to his own gave him an infinitesimal sensation of fullness that had alluded him for so long. A tiny success was still a success. Huey, finally, was on the right track.

Minutes passed as he continued his excoriation. A passerby would see a pool of blood surrounding bits of skin on the ground, seething with flies, and above it all stood a morbidly obese, human-shaped figure completely covered by the swarming creatures.

With his external organs essentially removed and exposed to the flies, he began to work deeper. He opened his gut, spilling his viscera and allowing thousands of insects to fill him. I saw his strength waning and he fell backwards. Flies covered him, inside and out, and Huey's life slipped away. His final moments, however, must have been blissful. The emptiness had been chipped away. It wasn't complete, but it was something he could be proud of. And for the first time in his life, I think he was happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teeny-Tiny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctors asked me to tell my story so other girls like me could read it and learn from my mistakes because Ill be dead soon. That makes me pretty sad to think about. I dont want other girls to be sick like I am. I guess they wont be sick exactly like me, because that would be crazy, but maybe they can read this so they wont make the bad decisions I made.

When I was little, Mom used to hold me and say stuff like, Oh Katie, you fit so perfectly on my lap! Youre so teeny-tiny! I loved it. Shed keep me warm and hug me and I felt so great. Id always go to Mom if I felt sad or scared and shed just scoop me up, saying whats wrong, my teeny-tiny girl? and Id tell her what was making me upset and shed always always always make it all better.

The most vivid memory I have was the day I turned 10. It wasnt of my party, which I vaguely remember being great, it wasnt the presents, some of which I still have, but it was when Mom had me in her lap that night and had tears in her eyes and said to Dad, Katies getting to be a big girl, huh? I dont remember what my dad said, but there was no denying it: I wasnt her teeny-tiny girl anymore. 

At 10 years old, I was about 410, maybe 100 pounds. I was growing fast. Both my parents are tall. I remember being scared. The scale kept going up, and by the time I was 11 I was 52, 120 pounds and I started getting boobs. At that point, when I was sad, mom would hug me tight and say the right things, but it all felt different. She never cradled me. She never had me in her lap. I felt cold and lonely even though I was never really cold or lonely. I just wanted to be closer to her like I was when I was little. So I decided to get little again.

Mom started to notice when I pushed around my food on the plate, trying to pile it up on one side to make it look like I ate more than I really did. Youre a growing girl, she said, kindly but firmly. You need to eat. I couldnt leave the table until I was done. 

That night after dinner, I remember lying on my back on the bed, staring at the ceiling and feeling the food in my stomach. Moms words youre a growing girl echoed in my mind and I felt so sick that I ran into the bathroom and threw up. I was really glad I had my own bathroom so they couldnt hear me puking. After I was done, I felt so much better. Lighter and smaller, even.

Mom was so happy to see me eating normally again. She had worried aloud that I might be getting the flu, so seeing me chowing down like my old self pushed those worries right out of her head. What she didnt see was how I went to bed afterward and while the bathwater ran I was throwing it all up. I did this every day for years.

One of the sad truths about throwing up your meals is that you dont lose all that much weight. I actually gained more. Sure, Id get rid of what Id eaten, but probably twice a week Id be lying in bed, wide awake, fingering my collar bones, hip bones, and ribs, and obsessing over food. Something inside me would snap, and Id run to the fridge or the cabinets and eat until I felt like I was bursting. Then, exhausted, Id go back upstairs and pass out on my bed. Calorie-for-calorie, after those twice-weekly binges I was eating more than I would if I was healthy. Except I really, really wasnt healthy. And nobody knew.

All this built up to the last few months after I graduated high school. I was 511, 175lbs. 17 years old. There was absolutely nothing I hated more than my body. I was constantly lonely and wanted to try to take my mind off it all. I decided to get a job. When I told Mom I found a position at a place that recycles old medical gear, she was really proud of me for taking the initiative. It was bittersweet; I knew she was starting to see me as an adult. Not her teeny-tiny girl. I felt like a complete and utter failure.

The recycling place where I worked dismantled big machines that hospitals used and sold the parts. I was the receptionist. I took phone calls and helped set up deliveries. The people I worked with were really nice and after a few weeks they gave me a key so I could get there early and have their coffee ready and their work orders printed out. That night, after everyone had left, I went back there and let myself in. I still feel bad about breaking their trust.

A couple days earlier my coworkers were bringing in an old machine. They all were wearing heavy gloves and had on breathing gear like scuba divers. When they were done, I asked what it was. Apparently it was something hospitals use to give radiation therapy to cancer patients. I didnt know too much about that, so when I got home I went on Wikipedia and did a lot of research and then I got my idea.

When I let myself in that night, the place was empty. I made a beeline for where they had that radiation therapy machine and I investigated it. Most of it was completely dismantled. What I was looking for was conveniently labeled and brightly marked in a massive lead container. It took me a while to get the cover off. Leads so heavy! But after I did, I saw a round metal part that looked like a wheel. I picked it up, rotated the mechanism, and it opened a little window in the front. A faint blue light was inside. I held it up to my eye and looked in. Nothing but that light. I thought it was probably what I was looking for.

I brought the object home with me and locked the door of my bedroom. I worked to pry the thing open with a screwdriver but it seemed locked from the inside. Eventually I got frustrated and I turned the wheel again to open the window and pushed my screwdriver into the blue light stuff and tried scooping it out. It turned out to be pretty soft. A lot of it broke as I poked it with the screwdriver, and when I turned the wheel upside down, it tumbled out onto my desk. Now I could see how pretty it was. It was like chunks of glowing blue clay and sand. I gathered it up as best I could and put it away, save for the little bit I was going to use tonight.

One of the things Id read about radiation therapy was that it made the poor people with cancer really skinny. They just totally lost their appetites. I couldnt believe it was true. Id always had such a big appetite. I kept telling myself that I need to be really careful when I take this stuff because if I get too much of the radiation I could get cancer myself. I took a pinch of the blue stuff, put it in my mouth, and swallowed it with a gulp of water. It felt warm going down even though the water was cold. Since Id gotten home from the recycling place Id been pretty warm, in fact. Cozy. Like a little puppy under a blanket.

That night I woke up sweating worse than Id ever sweated in my life. The bed was totally soaked. Gross. I figured weight loss was weight loss. Water weight wasnt really what I wanted, but it was better than nothing. I took a shower and changed the sheets and went back to bed. My stomach ached a little.

When I woke up the next morning, my stomach hurt and I threw up a couple times. But, I wasnt even remotely hungry. That alone made the pain in my tummy pretty much go away. I didnt need to eat! Mom asked if I was bringing leftovers to work from last nights dinner and I lied and said we were going to get a pizza. I hate lying to Mom, but I didnt want her to worry. There was no need to tell her I wasnt hungry. At work, theyd finished disassembling the machine and started sending it out to wherever they send those things. Id been really careful to put the canister back exactly as I left it. No one checked to see if the little wheel was still there.

The next few days were uneventful, aside from my stomach ache getting worse and having to puke once or twice. Id barely eaten anything since I started taking the radiation medicine. Whenever I got woozy from lack of food I ate an apple or a fat-free yogurt and I was fine. I was still sweating a lot. When I got on the scale, it said 168.

After a week of eating nearly nothing and faithfully taking my radiation medicine nightly, my stomach ache got really, really bad. Id stopped throwing up, but this time it felt like I needed to go to the bathroom. I went, and it was awful. There was so much - I was shocked. Id apparently eaten and kept down more than I thought. It was agony coming out, too. I got on the scale after, though, and that helped me feel a lot better. 161.

Over the next couple days, one or two people told me how pretty I looked. They asked me if I lost weight and I said yeah, maybe a few pounds. I beamed. Over my whole adolescence Id done nothing but get bigger. Now, finally, I was shrinking and on the way to teeny-tiny. I didnt feel too great, though. My tummy was constantly having me run to the bathroom and it still hurt afterwards. I figured I was getting rid of all the extra fat. 158.

I was in the shower about 10 days after I started taking the medicine and I was horrified to see some of my hair coming out. That was bad. Really, really, really bad. I stopped washing it immediately and let just the water rinse away the remainder of the shampoo. I got out of the shower and took like an hour blow drying my hair because I was too scared to use a towel that might pull more out. When the mirror was unfogged and my hair was dry, I checked to see how noticeable it was. There was a good-sized patch of bare, red scalp about 2 wide above my left ear. I pushed the hair around it down to cover the patch. Some more fell out. It had to be a nutritional deficiency from all the meals Id been missing. I put on my Titans hat and got dressed. When I brushed my teeth I noticed a little blood in the sink. I made a note to get some multivitamins after work.

I didnt shower the next day because when I woke up that morning, there was more hair on my pillow. My scalp was getting pretty visible. It looked prickly and raw but it didnt hurt. Since I was off work I stayed at home and looked online for all the nutritional deficiencies that might cause my hair to fall out and my gums to bleed. Most of the ones were covered by my multivitamin, so I tripled the amount I took just to be on the safe side. I had to go to the bathroom five times during the 15 hours I was awake. By the last time I was incredibly light-headed and so thirsty. I weighed myself before I started downing water and my radiation medicine. 150. The medicine had helped me lose 25 pounds in less than two weeks. 

Mom hugged me the next morning before I went to work. She ran her hands up and down my back and she remarked about how skinny Id gotten. Then, she said it: remember when I used to call you my teeny-tiny girl? I miss those days but I love you just as much as a grown up. Then she let me go. Pain, nausea, and despair washed over me. All of a sudden, my lightheadedness came back with a vengeance and I stumbled and fell on the kitchen floor. My hat fell off. With my head spinning, I vaguely remember Mom gasping, Katie what happened to your hair?! before I violently threw up on the floor and myself. It was all blood. I passed out to the sound of Mom screaming.

I dont know how much time went by at the hospital. I wasnt completely unconscious, but all I remember up until recently when they used drugs to wake me up were images of doctors in the same scuba gear as the guys at work and saying weird words like caesium chloride and sloughed and gray that didnt mean the color. 

Today, I cant move or talk and Im writing this using a cool keyboard that can pick out letters using the movements of my remaining eye. Like I said in the beginning, Ill be dead soon. Im not too fun to look at anymore. My hairs gone. And my lower jaw. And my skin. The nice doctors are giving me medication that helps me manage the pain and keep me alert. They asked if they could do tests and experiments on me to help understand what ingestion of the radiation medicine does to the human body. Apparently there was a man in Japan a few years ago named Hiroshi Ouchi who got a similar level of exposure and the same stuff happened to him. They said it would help other people in the future if they could compare our two cases. Of course I let them. 

I cant eat food anymore. My esophagus got cooked away. Same with my stomach. The doctors are keeping me hydrated with a tube in my butt. I dont really like to think about it. I guess all the excitement I get as I wait here is when they weigh me every six hours to see if Im able to retain the fluids they give me or if it all seeps out into the sheets. They hoist me onto a pad and a little machine voice says a number. This morning it said 72. The next time it was 69. 

Mom and Dad have to wear those scuba suits when they come visit. Moms always crying because shes not allowed to touch me. Dad just stares. Right before I started writing this, Mom bent down and started whispering to me some of the stuff I remember her saying when I was small. I closed my eye and imagined being warm and safe on her lap. I love you, my teeny-tiny girl, she sobbed. I would have smiled if I had a mouth.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sockets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 15:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dollar signs floated through my vision when I answered that Craigslist ad a couple years ago. The ad wanted a male companion for 6 hours. No sex, nothing illegal, and, get this: it paid $10,000. Who wouldnt jump at 10k? 

We met at his house. His handshake was firm. He seemed solidly middle-class; modest home, basic decor, nothing ostentatious. A suburban bachelor pad. After our hellos, he asked if Id like something to drink. His fridge was stocked with microbrews. Good stuff! I grabbed a Dogfish Head 90 and he guided me to the basement. Thats where well be working, he said.

The basement was sparsely furnished. Most prominent was what looked like an old dentists chair with a table next to it. The table was covered in a gray cloth. The man handed me an envelope hed been carrying. $5000. You can have the rest when were finished, he told me. Itll only be a few hours. 

He sat in the chair. With a smile, he gave me my instructions: I want you to pull out all my teeth. As he spoke, he pulled the cloth away. Underneath was a pair of gardening gloves, pliers, a ballpeen hammer, and a shoebox. I processed the last 5 seconds for a good 30. Pull his teeth out? I asked him and he confirmed that what Id heard was, in fact, accurate. No more questions, now, he ordered, just do whatever you need to do to get them out. With that, sat back in the chair and opened his mouth.

Im not, and never have been, a fucking dentist. But, there he was. His mouth was wide open, exposing brilliantly white, healthy teeth. His gums were a soft pink and his tongue seemed to be patiently waiting on the floor of his mouth. I fingered the money in the envelope and chugged the remainder of my beer. You can run upstairs and get another one if you want, he told me. 

I ran upstairs, as suggested. Staring at the dozens of beers, I tried to gather my thoughts. Long story short: I said fuck it, grabbed as many as I could carry, and trudged back down into the basement. After cracking open a bottle of Rasputin imperial stout, I approached the man, his mouth still open, and tentatively pressed on one of his front teeth. It was smooth and firmly anchored in his jaw. I sighed and put on the gloves.

The feeling that came over me was one of resignation. I knew I was going to do what he asked, and I figured I could always leave with the 5k if it got any weirder. I picked up the pliers, which looked brand new and shiny, and gripped the front tooth Id poked. Applying careful pressure, I gently pulled back. It didnt budge. The man exhaled softly though his nose and his eyes rolled. My next pull was fierce and quick. The tooth bent toward me with an audible crunching sound. Blood seeped from behind it. Still, it was lodged in his gums. Muttering under my breath, I squeezed the pliers as hard as I could and pulled with all my weight.

The tooth came out and I fell on my ass. Still holding the pliers, I stared at what Id done. There was the tooth, white and gleaming, with an ugly, short root jutting from the top. I got up and looked at the man. Blood oozed from the hole in his gums. He sat, calmly, arms crossed in apparent impatience. I loosened my grip on the pliers and let the tooth fall on the concrete floor. 

The remaining top front teeth went easily enough now that I had an idea of what kind of work had to be put in. Never once did the man make a sound aside from small changes in his breathing when my hands were blocking his mouth. The blood was beginning to be a factor. It limited my grip and I frequently had to ask him to spit it out. He just swallowed. After the top six teeth were gone, I was presented with a problem. Molars. I drank a Lagunitas Lil Somethin' Somethin'.

I decided to wait on those and go with the bottom row. The leverage was easier with them. I could put the pliers straight down on the tooth and yank back and downward. Those six went quickly. Again, the problem. Molars. I drank a Fat Tire ale.

I took the hammer and asked him to clench his remaining teeth together. Then, I pulled back his cheek as far as it would go without breaking the skin. I tapped the molars with the hammer. He sighed in annoyance. I swung. Teeth exploded in shards of enamel into his mouth. I took the pliers and yanked out what was left dangling. I repeated this on the other side. Then, all that were left were the wisdom teeth.

The hammer trick worked on the top ones. The bottom ones, though, were a bitch. I stood on the chair, reached in with the pliers, squeezed, and pulled. They came out with the sound of a shrub being ripped out of the ground. And then I was done.

The man grinned at me; his mouth a crater-filled wreck. He drooled blood from the corners of his mouth. Reaching into his jacket pocket, he pulled out the other envelope and handed it to me. I thanked him and backed away. As I was counting it out, he reached into the shoebox that was on the table. When he opened it, my spine immediately started tingling. 

The box was filled with spiders. From the look of them, they were brown recluses. They skittered up his forearm and he clenched a handful of them in his fist. Then he stuffed them in his mouth. I could see his jaw working as if he was chewing - which was now impossible because of the status of his teeth. He beckoned for me to come closer. Id finished counting; he hadnt shorted me. I moved forward maybe an inch. I like their little legs in the sockets, he choked out. They tickle.

I ran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I conduct a double-slit experiment if my wife is adamantly against a threesome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most discomfort you can cause a reader to feel in just two sentences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 02:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife sent me to the store to get some Progresso, but I accidentally brought home Regresso. She keeps getting younger and I think I'm now a criminal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I cast a line in any part of the ocean and expect to catch a fish in a reasonable amount of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 00:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first thing I thought of when I saw the picture of the dick that had to be surgically reduced in size so the owner could have sex. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know we're supposed to breastfeed my son, but he already finished them and my wife only had the two. Does that mean he's ready for formula? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 18:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of a </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 17:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overheard in the inner-city high school where I work. Double fucking negatives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 14:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine months from this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 18:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Puckett   The Union Gap - Young Girl [60's Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been off Reddit for 6 hours and now I'm lost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 13:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michel Foucault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 21:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 21:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ping-pong balls and mousetraps (from /r/gifs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 15:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitumen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 17:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't regret what I did, despite the fact I'm now transformed. I'd always wanted to be a dinosaur.

I strode out onto the hot tar. In my mind's eye, I could see my nude body - a beautiful contrast of white skin on ebony bitumen. The surface was hot. Scalding. The soles of my feet were immediately engulfed in searing pain. They'd blister, but I didn't mind. What I had ahead of me would be far more damaging.

Dinosaurs were so beautiful. How huge they were! How powerful! I stomped my scorched feet into the tar, feeling the substance rise up between my toes. I clenched them, the sensitive skin in between getting covered. I roared.

Now, I could act out my means of communion with the beasts. I pressed my body into the tar. Chest down. Face down. I burned. I ground my face into the road, opened my mouth, and bit as hard as I possibly could. The majority of my front teeth loosened immediately. I bit even harder, using the leverage of my head on the ground to force my chin into the act. My teeth gave up. I knew they'd be found by paleontologists someday. I was so happy for their future excitement.

My raw gums were coated in tar. My arms, chest, stomach, genitals, thighs, and feet were coated in tar. Rolling over, I covered the rest of myself. My gaping mouth gouted blood through the substance that was hardening on my lips. My back and buttocks, now burned and covered, completed my transformation. All that was left was the inside.
Handful after handful of the pitch disappeared down my throat. My internal temperature caused it to cool significantly, blocking my esophagus. I gasped for breath, a rictus of pleasure etched upon my face. My friends died this way so long ago. Now I'd be one with them. I closed my eyes and waited.

I cried when I realized I was getting pulled out and taken away. I saw my reflection in the mirrored sunglasses of the EMT - a blackened face with a red hole for a mouth. They couldn't take the bitumen off without excoriating me down to the muscle. I was peeled; now I'm pink and itchy. My fingernails don't grow anymore. Sometimes I poke my tongue up into the holes where my teeth used to be. Knowing they're still out there makes me happy. I let out a little, happy roar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical feminist, Jennifer Lawrence, wants this picture removed from the internet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 15:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karma Akbar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 14:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIFW I'm home alone listening to The Cure while seriously thinking Kierkegaard's "The Sickness Unto Death" might be the best book title of all time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 03:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my mom (who's a bird, btw) asks me if I want another helping of worms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm Jesus of Nazareth and I meet a dude named Bartimaeus while hanging out near Jericho. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 18:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm browsing the online sex offender registry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 04:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The majority of Congress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 19:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow, they kill one of the most hated human beings on Earth. How controversial and hilarious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 21:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been working on gaining weight for football tryouts and I'm drinking enormous quantities of deuterium to help, but I'm just getting a progressively-worse headache. Is my football helmet defective? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 20:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's freezing in my house so I went get something to eat so I'd warm up and I end up eating ice cream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 20:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M]'lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 19:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M'ssiah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 19:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe I shouldn't try to make them out of Pepto Bismol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 19:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flopflopflopflopflop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 15:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M(internal)RW I'm working my ass off on a time-sensitive task and my boss is frantically calling my line saying he needs help, and when I run to his office, I find out it's because he wants me to check his lottery tickets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 14:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you swear you invented or thought up on your own, only to see/hear it from someone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autechre - Second Bad Vilbel [Electronic] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 02:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my girlfriend farts and I turn to her in horror and ask, "period fart?" and she says, "No. Chipotle period fart." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 03:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I think Satan talks to my GI tract when I eat spicy food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 02:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I'm walking around a sex-toy store. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIFW I'm peeing and I can hear my upstairs neighbor peeing at the same time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 00:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "No, hahaha I really like penis-shaped chopsticks!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my horse won't stop galloping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 17:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone should start a furniture store called the Ottoman Empire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 21:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The president must get sick of hearing the National Anthem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 02:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend's reaction when we're fooling around and I jokingly whisper in her ear, "I want to give your birth canal the ol' lickaroo." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 21:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These next few are dedicated to you, England. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 21:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new sinkhole on my property. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 16:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A horribly burned man who lost his nose and lips. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A wiring closet from the worst nightmare of an IT worker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 00:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there's something wrong with a duck's feathers, does it have down syndrome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 20:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I've only been attracted to women for my entire life and then I see a shirtless picture of Rob Gronkowski. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend's reaction when she's having a conversation with me while I'm in the shower and she looks down and notices I'm smiling because I'm peeing on the shower's glass door. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine months from now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's good to be a boss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 02:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I accidentally submit a text post instead of a link. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 02:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is incredibly stupid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 19:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is he from a movie or something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By the time you read this post, I'll be older. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 20:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I'm falling asleep at my desk at work and realize I'm developing some sort of exhaustion erection. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 23:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least that's a plus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> + </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How large was the explosion of the Antares rocket when compared to modern military ordnance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 12:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the guys with 3 or 4 fingers, here's what I have. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anagram is an anagram of anagram. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 17:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ebola, how I lust for thee / your gorgeous infectivity." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 20:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lame Pun Coon is a LGBT ally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 19:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What now? I'm in the third grade and my teacher asked me to write in cursive, but I misheard and accidentally started writing in recursive so What now? I'm in the third grade and my teacher asked me to write in cursive, but I misheard and accidentally started writing in recursive so What now? I'm in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I used the tape measure that came with my new scale and realized my size 33 pants never fit properly because I have a 44" ass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 19:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally broke down and paid extra for a really good quality Thermos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 13:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They'll start soon and will continue until around December. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 19:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard Business Review answers the question everyone's been asking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 13:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Testing keyboard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 18:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please Photoshop an American football into the hand of this Goldman Sachs CEO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 15:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't my pedometer keeping track of all the kid-touchers in my neighborhood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 17:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my girlfriend has been out of town all week and I'm all alone and bored. (Maybe NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 00:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's almost October and you know what that means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 00:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gay is a homonym. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You son of a bitch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Docking. I'm a 33 year old child. (NSFW language.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 20:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since it's Tuesday and we have to wait two whole days for football, how about a thread of the best gifs, pics, and videos of plays from the last ten years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 14:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something to stave off the withdrawal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donovan McNabb just started his AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 17:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
