<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one thing to have the reader excited and think about your story at that moment and time, but for me I want them to keep thinking about my stories. 

I like open ended stories. I can keep thinking up different ways of how it could end, and before I know it I become somewhat obsessed.

I still think about certain stories even now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahhaa i just loved the response i got yesterday!

Excited to close out three stories in one part tonight:p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg I'm going to read it as soon as i get to work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops! Will fix now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Just Came Back Home After Being Missing for 15 Years [Part 4] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole day took its toll on me and I fell asleep quickly. 

In the middle of the night I woke up to something hitting against my legs. I heard the boy start screaming, What if he tastes as good as his dad? I just want a taste! Let me just have a taste! The man finally got the boy calmed down and sat him down on the ground. He sat in front of the boy and said, Drew, you cant be like them. I love you like a son, but you need to calm down.

They got up and left the room. I couldnt sleep after that. I sat in my bed and looked through the browser on my phone. Nothing really sparked my interest. It was just a bunch of shit about the new President, and countless numbers of lists that I must read. I closed out of the browser and clicked on the Life is Beta icon.

The screen went black before white letters floated around the screen. They slowly started grouping together words until they finally placed themselves in their designated spots. Weve saved your life, and all we ask is for you to make a decision. The letters started to fall off of the screen and three words took its place. 

Choose

Kill

Be Killed

I tried to leave the app, but the screen remained the same. I tried hitting the power button, but the phone would not turn off. When I took the back off of the phone the number 5 floated on top of the word choose. The number then changed to four and then three. When it hit 1 I tapped on the icon that said Kill. The app closed down and I turned the phone off. 

I still heard the man talk to Drew in the other room after listening to them mumble a bit more I fell back asleep. 

This morning I woke up to the smell of bacon. I jumped out of bed thinking I was still at my parents house, but when I saw the log walls I could finally calm myself down. I turned on the phone and saw the app logo flashing. When I clicked on it I saw a character that looked exactly like me inside floating in the middle of the screen. He was flashing so I tapped on him and the phone went black for a second and showed the character sitting in an identical bed as me. 

I walked out of the door and walked to the kitchen, and sat down on the sofa in the living room. The animated version of the guy walked up to me and gave me a plate of bacon and scrambled eggs. The sound of knocking came from my phone. We both jumped up and the man put a finger up to his lips. He walked up to the door and saw another man walk in. He was wearing a shirt with a small cookie on the right side of his shirt. 

The screen went black and came back to another scene. I was done with my food and the man was talking to me. I saw the cookie shirt man take out a small pocket knife from his back pocket. Before my character could react a knife was lodged into the middle of his head. The man ran out leaving the knife in my head. The screen went black and came back to a white screen. Kill or Be Killed flashed in black letters before the app closed down.

I threw the phone on the bed and walked out into the living room. There werent any chairs in the kitchen so I took a seat on the sofa. Sweat started to pour down my forehead, but I ignored it. This must be some kind of joke the two decided to pull on me. The man came out and asked me if I was okay. I nodded yes and he went back into the kitchen. He asked from the kitchen, Bacon and scrambled eggs sound good to ya? I called back yes and sank into the couch. 

After a couple of minutes he came back out with two plates of bacon and eggs. My stomach growled in response, but my brain kept me from being happy about a good meal with what seemed like good company. 

He stared at me for what seemed like hours, but he finally said, Hey man my name is Stephen by the way. Im sorry if I have been mysterious so far. Its just I am handing a recent loss myself. Its not only been a little over a week, but it hurts as much as the first day. I had to leave my wife and kid, but I can only imagine how you must be feeling. I understand man. I really do. Kids name is Drew, and he is still a bit unstab

His last sentence was cut off by the sound of knocking. I started to panic and Stephen asked me what was wrong. I whispered back to him about what the app showed. Stephen stared off into space for a while before saying, Good, I thought he was always an asshole. He grabbed a knife from the kitchen and answered the door. The man that was supposed to kill me stood in the entrance with a smile on his face. Stephen said, Morning Andrew, I wasnt expecting you for another 3 days. Andrew looked at him for a second and said, Beta told me you were helping a kid out. Told me to come. 

Andrew started walking towards me, and Stephen crept behind him for a couple of paces before jamming the knife in Andrews back. Andrew fell to his knees while Stephen stabbed him three more times in the back. The whole entire time Andrew laughed and pointed at me. He shouted out, Theyll find you! Theyll find you and kill you like the little bitch you are! He kept laughing before taking his final breath and laid still on the ground. 

I heard the sound of little footsteps behind me and I looked back to see Drew grinning ear to ear. He shouted with joy, Oh you did it! Hes dead. I cant wait to see how he tastes! My momma and daddy told me that he must be sweet from all the cookies he made and ate. Stephen responded back with, No time, we need to get out of here now. Beta told me that we need to leave by 8 and its already 7:45. Drew started to whine, but followed us to Stephens car.

When we were all seated in the car Stephen started speaking. We have 1 hour. Twelve miles away there is a woman. Shes about to kill 8 kids in a school. We get her while she is walking from the parking lot to the school entrance. Ill slow down in front of her and you guys take care of the rest.

He started to drive down the road and I started to relax into my chair. I looked to my right to look out the window but see Drew staring at my chest. He breathed deeply into my ear before whispering, You do smell just like your father. I wish I didnt leave the meat back at the house. He rubbed the side of my neck with his fingers and giggled. Before I could say anything he was back in his seat. 

After a couple of minutes Stephen pulled into an old parking garage. We were the only car there and I started to get out of my chair when he parked. While I grabbed for the handle Stephen grabbed me by my throat. Drew tossed a cloth bag over my head and they dragged me out. 

I landed on hard concrete. 

I grunted and started to scream.

Drew laughed and said, Screaming wont help. There is no one around. You chose to be killed and thats what were here to do! They took the bag off of my face and found Drews face incredibly close to mine. He smiled before slapping me lightly on my face. Stephen looked like he was about to cry, but he managed to contain his emotions. He took out a gun from the back of his pants. 

He said, Im sorry before putting the gun up to my forehead.

I didnt want to sob or plead for my life, but I couldnt think of a different way to react. With snot and tears running down my face I pleaded for my life. I told them I chose to kill not to be killed but Drew kept laughing. Stephen said sorry one last time before pulling the trigger.

Drew fell on my lap. 

I looked at Stephen and he was crying.

He knelt beside Drew and held his head in his hands.

He wailed, You were the only thing that replaced what my son was to me. I loved you even though I knew you for 5 days, but please know I loved you. Please. Im begging you. Please know that I loved you! Please. Please. Please!

I wanted to comfort him, but I didnt know what to say.

We are in a hotel now. 

Im on Stephens phone.

I need more answers, but I know I have a person [I can finally trust] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)

[Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r05w8/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r86pi/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[Part 3] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rfhow/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[Final] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ruipu/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR: Person does not understand that subreddits have different rules. Is butt hurt enough to write a comment as long as all of my stories combined. The butt hurt may continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR: Person can't read for 15-30 minutes. 

Author is supposedly mad when he has over 5000 people that read the first part.

Stay tuned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR: GTFO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I'm sure it's going to be an awesome read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck everyone else's story. Mine only got 5 upvotes but it's the best one."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Where the writers are afraid of the readers." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We have wives and girlfriends, boyfriends and husbands. We are all virgins." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Donald Trump for 2 terms." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Looks like the writing of a dumdum 15 year old boy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha great!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do!!! I've been waiting on a new one by you lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or fan girling idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aw they were just fan boying:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 3 3 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> psh just a bored Korean that has too much time at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omgggg our team was amazing!

haha we did lol and I promise to try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha oh man I will try. I promise lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to write more about love:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ATE YOU WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah the exit is over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much u/osoleve for the gold!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha I still thoroughly loved it!!! 

Thank you very much!

It means a lot coming from you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second part of life is beta is what the man said. He said it's from an earlier story about a month ago. Something about he's 12 and met a nice man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you interested? I have 8 left. I can do this for 15. for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Just Came Back Home After Being Missing for 15 Years [Part 3] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two hours after my last log I handed the phone back to the nurse, and told him about a couple of people staring at me through the window. He looked out the window and turned back around with an annoyed look on his face. With a condescending tone he said, Its really not funny to joke around about things like that. Confused, I looked out the window and saw that there was no one there. 

They were just there when I checked a couple of minutes ago. Where the hell did they go?

I knew it would be pointless to try and convince him so I just told him that I was tired and mistook reflections with people outside. He nodded his head and walked out of the room. 

It was now around 11 pm and I could not fall asleep. I turned on the tv and flipped through the channels, but nothing really interested me. My stomach started to growl so I pressed the button with the nurse on it and waited around. Five minutes later a lady walked in and asked, You need something? I told her I was hungry, and she left without saying a word to me back. Twenty minutes later she came back in with a couple of carrots and ranch. I looked at the plate with obvious disappointment, and asked if they had anything else. 

I stared down at my plate for a couple of seconds after I asked her, and when I looked back up she was gripping onto the side of my bed with both of her hands. Her knuckles started to become white and her breathing started to get heavier. With as much venom as she could muster she whispered, Listen to me you little shit. I dont want you to eat. I want you to fucking starve. You understand me? Eat the fucking carrots or go hungry. I dont give a shit. Just dont fucking press that button again and go to sleep.

She stormed out of the room and I sat there confused and worried. I put the plate of carrots and ranch on the side table. I started to get comfortable on my bed when I noticed a pair of eyes looking at me through the window. 

Slightly pissed off I looked out the window. I didnt care anymore. I was just tired about whatever the fuck my parents were trying to do with me. 

Let my kidnappers get me again.

I just did not give a shit anymore.  

Right as I lifted my hand to bang on the window I saw what was staring at me. My fathers dismembered head was placed on top of the bush. His eyes were wide open and his mouth was sewn shut. Matt was lying on the ground next to the bush with his stomach torn open, and my mother had two bones sticking out of her chest and head. Right as I was about to start screaming I felt someone covering my mouth with tape. I tried to twist around, but the person holding me was far too strong. 

I struggled as a cloth bag was placed over my head and I flailed around as much as I could while my arms and legs were getting tied together. The person picked me up and at a very fast speed. I heard him rushing out the doors, and the cold air instantly hit me. He stopped running and I heard the sound of a car trunk opening. I tried screaming through the tape, but I knew there was no way anyone could hear me. I was thrown down and the person closed the trunk door. I heard two doors open and shut and, a couple of seconds later I felt the car peeling out. 

I knew for a fact that I was going to die. There was nothing I could do. 

I tried to get as comfortable as I could, but the trunk was far too small. Every single minute I felt the trunk get smaller and smaller until I couldnt move my body at all. Having a bag over my head and only able to breathe through my nose made me feel like I was truly trapped and helpless. I just wanted to die. I wanted to give up, but even that option had been taken away from me. That is when I decided to start throwing my body against anything that was in my way. I started to gain more and more space until the car came to a stop. The sound of a childs laugh brought a wave of fear across my body. 

Was I back at the house?

Is there where I spend my last minutes?

I heard the trunk open and they started to grab the items that surrounded my body. After a couple of minutes I felt two small hands grab my ankles and two larger hands grab me by my shoulders. I tried to jerk my body so they could lose their grips, but they held strong and kept carrying me. 

They sat me down on a chair and took the bag off of my head. I found myself in a house, but not any house Ive seen before. We were in what seemed like the living room. It was dark in the living room, but I could still see both of their faces. A man who looked to be struck with infinite depression and a little boy who seemed to be the happiest thing around; the boy stuck out his hand and said, Hey bud. Were kinda the same. You lost your parents and I lost mine. Its okay. They were bad people. By the way your mom didnt taste as good as your dad so I didnt really want to finish off your mom, but your dad is kinda still with us! 

The man put his hand up to the boy and stared at me for a bit before saying, I dont know what kind of trouble youre in, but be calm. We were told to help you. So we did.

I wanted to be calm. I really did, but after what the boy said how did they expect me to be calm? I tried to think of a way to ask a question that wont set the boy off on me. Once I thought of one I took a deep breath and asked, So why the killing? Or the eating? I know they were evil, but why them and not anyone else? Why did you take me instead of just leaving me there?

The man sighed and glared at the boy. He shrunk down in his seat and muttered, I was just tryna help. The man looked back at me and said, We kill because thats what we were told to do. Sometimes we dont kill, but most times we do. The boy has developed tastes through his parents. They did the same thing we do now, but they have started to lose control with hunger and started killing innocent people. I dont know why they chose your parents and the cop. I really dont. They told me to take you so we did. He stared off into the kitchen after his statement. After thinking about his answer I only had one more question. They?

After a couple of seconds he looked back at me and shrugged his shoulders and pointed at a door. Theres your room. You have a phone that you can use. There is internet, but I advise against contacting anyone you know. Im tired Im going off to bed.

They took the ropes off of me and the boy skipped into the room next to mine and the man sat down in the couch behind me. 

I had more questions, but I started to walk to my room. 

When I opened my room I heard the man cough behind me. I looked back at him and he said with a tear falling from his eyes. I lost everything. Just know that. I had a wife and a 2 year old kid, but all of that was ripped away. I dont know what is going through your head right now, but just know that we are here to help you. Look through the phone. Youll find answers.

I told him thanks and walked in my room. It had a bed and a little side table. A phone was lying on top of the side table attached to a charger. I took it off of the charger and looked around the phone till I found the button to power it on. There were only two icons on the screen. One was for a browser which I used to write down this log to you all. The other one was a simple looking app. A blue box with a white circle inside of it; it was called Life is Beta. 

I didnt feel like looking into it tonight, but tomorrow I will look into it. 

I think I finally found someone to [trust now] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).

[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r86pi/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r05w8/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)


[Part 4] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rn3ub/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for it! 

I mean especially since you can provide actual reports and news clips. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 10:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime!

Keep writing!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 10:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. No. No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually remember being really young when I watched it with my uncle.

Something about it that made me really want to cry, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they're dead. sorry

I didn't mean to take it this far...

Can we still be rice friends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. 

So good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anytime! please keep writing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonzobot rips EtTuTortilla's legs off and leaves them to die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  u/Zooophagous

What an amazing start!!!

Keep writing! You definitely have an amazing talent in writing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know if you need any help!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/the_gift_of_g2j My friends and I try "rituals" that used to be popular. Last night I played Three Kings.

Was definitely an interesting read!!

Let me join in next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfectly said!!!

Thank you:)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/TheVykin You impressed me with It's 4AM Again...

I know your next story is going to be killer. (literally) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/poppitypunk

January 6th, 1992 was super creepy o.o

I loved it!

p.s. I know you're innocent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you were on the IRC i would type in ".kill EtTuTortilla" haha

Oh I know! I just remember just wanting some words of encouragement when I first started!

u/demons_dance_alone was too kind to read my series and comment with a compliment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can have 2 then
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/cera_cyanide

It's great that you posted another story today!

I definitely enjoyed Guard Duty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 bucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh my god haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/ATRNL Seduced by black was actually really good!!! 

I don't think I'll go to a club anytime soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Might Seem Childish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I kind of noticed that there was a bit of negativity going around in the OOC. I'm not saying that it is unwarranted, but I just want to see if we can make each other smile.

*Not Creepy Smiles* Well maybe just a little.

So let's just tag a bunch of new authors that have started in the last month and give them a compliment on the comment section!

If someone stuck out to you as becoming someone really good or is already really good bring them in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i definitely do feel good! I don't know about the quality haha 

I loved your "Family Ornaments" story by the way!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahajaja XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really simple to learn actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Noone to trust. 

I hate my life, but i hope i can find support here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone can ever top borrasca lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super moist
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it nice? 

I love happy posts on the ooc!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For you u/feyedharkonnen I don't even need lube bb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No debunking, disproving, or asking for proof.

Yep. Seems like it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rules.

Everything is real here.

Criticisms are done through the messages.

How is that not a hard concept?

I only got frustrated because all day I have been getting comments about how there is information missing.

It's a series. If i made all of the information consistent and out in the open then there is no point in a series. 

The narrator and reader figure things out as the story continues, but how is that possible when everyone keeps pointing out the obvious??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Just Came Back Home After Being Missing for 15 Years [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This morning I woke up to the smell of bacon. I got out of bed, took a quick shower, and went to the kitchen. My mother gave me a smile and asked me if I was hungry. I gave her a nod and went to the dining room and sat down. My father came down a couple of minutes later and stood next to me while breathing down my neck. When I looked up at him he said sharply, So youre just going to sit around and not help your mom with the food? Do you think shes your personal cook? 

I got up from my chair and walked into the kitchen while my father glared at me the whole way there. When I got to the kitchen I heard my father scoff while he pulled a chair out. My mother shoved three plates of bacon, eggs, and grits and told me to put them on the table. I carried them in and placed the dishes down. I went back in, but my mother walked past me while saying Done and put a fork beside each plate. 

No one spoke during the entire meal. I tried to think of something to say, but each time I thought of something I would quickly dismiss it. I just wanted to see if they would somehow slip up and give me some information about my kidnappers and how they planned on getting rid of me.

Once they finished eating they got out of their chairs and walked back upstairs. I didnt get up until I heard the door to their bedroom close. I tiptoed upstairs and put my ear up to their door, but it was completely quiet. 

I kept my ear pressed to the door for a bit more until I felt something grab at my right foot. I yelped in surprise when I saw two fingers holding on to my toes. My father sneered, You know its impolite to spy in on your parents room dont you? I pulled my foot away from his grip and raced downstairs. My father came out with a small handgun and pointed it in my direction. While I ran out of the front door I heard my father scream out to me Sooner or later theyre going to get you again! You running away just makes our job easier! 

I didnt know where I was going, but I knew that I couldnt stay at my parents house any longer. The next two hours was a mixture of running and walking countless steps. With sweat pouring down my shirt despite the cold weather I finally found a welcome sight. 

A cop car. 

 I flagged the car down, and Matts head popped out of the window. He didnt ask me any questions. He just told me to get in and explain when we got back to the station. 

The car ride was filled with silence which made the next 10 minutes a perfect time to fully think about what the fuck was happening. My parents were definitely in on my kidnapping, but why would they send me away for 15 years, send me back home, and kill me off? Why not just kill me off to begin with? As questions started to flood my head I felt the car come to a stop. 

Matt took off his seatbelt and got out of the car. I followed his lead and walked into the station right behind him.

We went to an office in the back of the building and took a seat in front of a desk. He sat down at the opposite end and while crossing his arms said Explain.

I took a deep breath and told him all about my parents conversation the night before. How they talked about my kidnappers will get rid of me. Then I told him about the odd breakfast and almost getting shot down by my father when he found out I was trying to eavesdrop on them. 

He could tell that I was still shaking from the incident so he asked me if my father said anything at all while he had the gun in his hands. After calming myself down I told him that he told me sooner or later they were going to find me. Also, having me run away was just helping them out. 

Matt wrote down a couple of things from his notepad and asked me if I wanted a coffee or some water. I told him a glass of water would be fine. As he got up and started to head out of the room I asked him if he could get and investigator or detective or anyone that can figure this out for me. With eyes filled with pity he told me that since we were a small town it would take some time to get anyone else down here. He gave me a little pat on my shoulder and walked out the door. 

He was gone for what seemed like hours. It started as just an annoyance, but it quickly elevated to panic. I tried opening the door several times, but no matter how much I tugged at the door it remained in the same exact spot. The world around me started to spin and I fell to the ground.

I woke up to the sound of a constant beep in the background. When I opened my eyes I saw a young lady in a white outfit standing in front of me. She smiled widely at me and asked me if I was feeling alright.

No, I really wasnt. The sight of her made me freak out. I started to tear at whatever was around me. I grabbed at the pole with my IV attached to it and launched it at her. She managed to avoid getting hit by the pole, and pain exploded in my right wrist. I tried to grab for her, but she hurried outside of the room. I got out of bed, but after a couple of steps the dizziness came back and I blacked out once more. 

It was dark when I woke up again. I saw gauze and tape around my right wrist and the IV was now attached to my left wrist. I looked around the room and saw that there was a tv in the far right corner. A man was asleep in the next bed over, and there was a little controller attached to the wire on the bed. I found a little icon that looked like a nurse and pressed it. Two minutes later a man walked in the room with the same white outfit. A shudder ran down my spine, but I restrained myself. I asked him to turn on some cartoons for me. He showed me how to control the tv with the remote. 

Before he left I asked him if I could use his phone to log down a daily log. He hesitated for a second, but handed it to me and told me that I have 2 hours with it before his shift is over. 

I was re-positioning my pillow when i saw an envelope under my pillow. The letter "M" was written on the front of the envelope. I opened the envelope and took a photo of when i was 4 out. 

On the back there was a little note for me, "You're only alive because I'm a cop. I wanted to kill you as soon as I talked to your for the first time, but we already have people that will do that for us. Show this letter to anyone if you want. They won't listen. You're the kid that just came back home after being missing for 15 years. The crazy and unstable kid. It's my word against yours bud."

Im logging to you from the nurse's phone, but as I got to the middle of this log I had the feeling of being watched. I looked out the window and saw my parent's and Matt staring through the window of my room. When my eyes met Matt he mouthed the word "Stay".

Without Matt who can I trust [now] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks)?

[Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r05w8/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[Part 3] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rfhow/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[Part 4] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rn3ub/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude.... 

It's called a series.

This is called nosleep where you don't try to disprove stories on here... Do you guys really not know how this works???

In a book. You have countless chapters. Or a series of books have countless pages. 

Take series of unfortunate events. 

Did it all make sense in the first book? Were all holes covered? Or were there holes that filled in those parts as the series went along?

Instead of trying to disprove people who work for fucking hours to entertain your ever so omniscient literature minds. Why don't you just enjoy a story for what it is?

Entertainment.... 

Or just keep trying to write out long drawn out shit worried about NUMBERS when it's going to make all of these comments seem moot as fuck when it ends?

Stick around and comment more shit about numbers. Or just fucking enjoy this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummmm so during the 15 years you don't think people came and went?

Or that i won't know the number to be exact? 

You don't think i was losing my mind a little? 

We can count days though. Plus if the washers work than it works.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry my parents don't have perfect grammar. You can go now thank you:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you are already on the same level if not greater.  I just got lady luck to sprinkle some star dust shit on my stories! 

Keep writing! I really enjoy everything you have written!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft. 

You know we started writing around the same time and you really motivated me to bring my A game whrn i saw the response your stories were getting haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you are a really good writer!

Thank you for sharing your wonderfully written stories with us!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but there are two other parts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well played though. 


Well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes I feel like people that comment on here don't really know how to follow or read subreddit rules.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahhaha thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the only Korean in a private school had some good parts and some bad. 

My mother never really wanted to send me to a private school, but I happened to be the only kid in my previous schools history to be expelled in the first grade. This was completely ironic to me because I was the one that was getting teased the whole entire time.

My mother never really got to angry about the whole incident. She actually understood that I was only standing up to myself. She also knew that I was not as good with the English language as the other kids; which made me an immediate target for teasing. Every time I would stutter the other kids would laugh at me and copy me, and every day during recess I would be completely ignored. I held my tongue and contained my temper until a kid copied what I did in an overly exaggerated manner. After five minutes of him copying me I finally snapped and kicked the boy out of his chair. 

I was taken out of class and sat in the principals office till my mother came. They told her I showed a type of violence they do not wish to see here ever again, and told her to just go ahead and grab my stuff as I will not be welcomed back again. 

After we left, my mother took me to the park and told me to go play. I was on the swings when I noticed my mother on the park bench crying silently into her hands. 

Even at the age of six I understood how terrible my mother must feel. She brought me to America when I was just three months old and had high dreams for us. When we came she had a very good grasp of the English language, but when I was 3 she had a stroke. While she recovered I stayed with my aunt and uncle, but they mostly monitored over my mother. After she recovered around 6 months later she was back to normal, but suffered from memory loss. She learned Korean again, but never relearned English. 

I knew while she was crying to herself because she blamed herself for placing me in such a difficult position, but I have never placed any sort of blame on her. As her body started to shake and she fell into a loud sob I jumped out of the swings and started walking up to my mother. Before I got to her; another lady walked up to her and her two kids ran up to me. 

They asked me if I wanted to play with them, and when I noticed that my mother was now talking to their mother I nodded my head at them. 

They were telling me all about the school they went to. How everyone was really close, and they would really love to have me there. I shook my head at them and mumbled I dont think so and started swinging again. 

They kept trying to talk to me, but I didnt want them to start teasing me if I stuttered so I just silently stared at them when they talked to me and either shook or nodded my head. 

After about an hour their mother got off of the bench and hugged my mom. The lady called for her children and they immediately left after waving to me. My mother wiped the tears off of her face and walked up to me. She hugged me when I met her halfway and told me she found another school I can go to.

We went to the school the next day. Three Cross Christian Academy was displayed proudly on the school and we walked inside. We were greeted by an overly excited lady. She nearly choked me out with the hug she gave me, and grabbed my shoulder as she led us to the principals office. 

The first thing I noticed about the office was how absolutely clean and organized everything was. A couple of minutes later the principal walked in and gave me a very firm handshake. He looked at my mother and told her We will accept your son into our school, but please know that we do not tolerate any kind of violence or harsh language. Meaning no hitting of any kind or cursing. You will not use our Lords name in vain and you will study diligently so that you may be blessed in your coming years.  Understood? He stared at both of us until we both nodded. 

He smiled and sat back down. My mother wrote a check that covered the rest of the school year and I was sent to my first class. When I walked in the whole class stared at me and the teacher asked me to stand beside her. She asked me to introduce myself and before I could object she stepped behind me and gave me a little nudge. For the next two minutes I tried to put together sentences that made sense without stuttering, but it was just not possible for me. I tripped up on words and paused 4 times while I tried to think of the word. After I finished I went back to my seat, and wished the day was over. 

After the bell rang signifying the end of class I gathered my books and followed the teacher to my next class. While on the way a cheeky kid walked up to me and started to babble on and on about how cool it was I spoke another language. Throughout all of our classes he talked about how I should teach him Korean. During lunch he kept talking to me about how much he likes to play Age of Empires and that I should come over some time so we could have a sleep over. 

We became fast friends after that. His name was Mike and he was always there to stand up for me whenever I was bullied or teased by others. 

All the way to our senior year of high school we remained close, and we always made time for each other. We would spend every weekend with each other playing video games, eating snacks, and watching movies when we were younger to going to parties, driving around town, and going to the mall when I turned 16. 

Everything seemed to finally be perfect. I finally got my first girlfriend who I thought I was in love with, my mother was proud of me, I had great grades, and Mike and I were accepted into the same college. I was not only completely fluent in English; I received the best scores in my class in both papers and English exams.  Everything was finally going well for me until my senior year. 

The day started off normal enough, but when I walked into the third period class with Mike I felt a chill run down my spine. I looked to my right and saw that the teacher was staring me down with a look of pure hatred. Panicking a little inside I rushed to my seat and Mike looked at me strangely. He asked me why I was so pale, and I told him to look at the teacher. As soon as he looked up she was smiling and waving to the students coming in. 

When we were all seated she told us that her name was Ms. Jameson. She walked around the class as she taught our lesson, but every time she passed my desk she would either subtly kick me in the leg or pinch me on the arm. The first couple of times I glared at her, but she would completely ignore my stares. When the class ended I stayed in the classroom until everyone left. 

As soon as everyone left I asked her what the hell was wrong with her. She looked at me for a second and then started to pray. I couldnt hear what she was saying, but she kept glancing up at me in between her prayer. 

I told my mother about it, but she just told me it was just from the stress of being in my last year of college. I know my mother had already been through too much so I just nodded my head and just decided to put up with it.

It wasnt easy but I managed to deal with it for the next two months, but when I found a picture in my locker of when I was 6 with you will find forgiveness through death written in red over my body I completely lost it. I walked into Ms. Jamesons class and slammed the picture in front of her. She stared at the picture for a while, but just sat there and remained quiet. After a second she whispered There are no cameras here and proceeded to stare at the picture in silence. 

There was no question that she was the one who put the picture in my locker, but I knew no one would believe me. The principal already didnt like me as he still thought of me as a violent little kid, and I knew if I left this school I would be out of options. I was only months away from graduating and so I just stuck it out. Whenever I found a photo in my locker I just threw it away, and when Ms. Jameson made her jabs or stared me down I started to jab her back and stare her down as well. 

I didnt care anymore. I just wanted to be done with the year and go off to college with Mike. 

It was the same shit until the last month of my senior year. 

Mike started to ignore me and start spending more and more time with Ms. Jameson. I dont know why, but whenever I tried to hang out with him after school he would just tell me he was busy as he walked into her classroom. 

When I would try to listen in all I heard was a weird sort of chant between the two of them. I tried to joke around with Mike and say What up teacher lover but he would just shove me off and ignore me. 

Mike intentionally ignored me till today; two weeks before graduation. 

At the age of 18, Mike was found in his room with a knife in his chest. His mother called me that day and told me the news in between sobs, and asked if I had any idea what happened. I heard a ringing in my ear as I told her I had no idea. She let out a little sigh and just hung up the phone. Even though we had fallen apart in the last few weeks I was filled with more sadness than I have ever felt in my life. I sat on my bed as I felt a wave of tears come down my face. I tried to hold back from crying, but I fell into a deep sob. I wanted to stop, but I kept getting hit with the memories of the time we spent together.

Four hours later I heard someone knock on the door. Two cops were standing outside and asked me if they could come inside and get a couple of answers from me. I nodded and pointed towards the couch in the living room. They walked in and sat down. Once I sat on the recliner the first cop extended out his hand and told me his name was Officer Grant. I shook his hand and the second officer just nodded his head at me. 

After a second of silence Officer Grant asked me how well I knew Mike and if he has been acting strange in the last couple days. I told him we had been close for over ten years now and that the past two weeks he had been acting distant around me. 

Officer Grant stared at me for a couple of seconds and asked if I had ever received any strange photos of myself. I told him that I started receiving old pictures of me with you will find forgiveness through death written on it. The other cop started to jot down on his notebook. Confused, I asked Officer Grant what was going on. 

He took a deep breath, and said I cant really tell you, but I feel like you should know. Your friend Mike was holding on to two things when we found him. A photo of the two of you playing on the computer, and over your body unforgivable was written on it. He left a note for you, and before they took it away for evidence I wrote it on my notepad.

He handed me his notepad and I felt the blood drain from my face once I finished reading it.

All fucking year long dude. 

All you talked about was how we were going out of town for college.

You never asked me if I wanted to go. You didnt care.

I wanted to stay. I told you several times that I wanted to stay.

All you did was ignore what I wanted.

This is your fault. Youre going to be found dead tomorrow because you cant fucking listen.

Ms. Jameson? The one you thought was evil and hated you? 

Dont worry I hated her too. 

An hour before school started I tried leaving a little message in your locker. 

I panicked when I saw that bitch walking down the hall so I tried to put it back in my pocket.

I dropped it. Can you believe it? She saw it and she tried to give you a couple of warnings.

Luckily youre too full of yourself to understand what she was trying to do. 

I know you wont read this letter, but Ill make sure its between the knife and your heart.

Maybe you will get the message then.

Have a final good night.

I handed the notepad back to him, and sat in silence for what felt like an eternity. I heard the officers getting up and leaving. 

I wanted to get up and just resume the day like nothing happened, but I feel as if I am glued to the couch.

Im still sitting on the couch, but I decided to pass along a message to you guys.

Know who your friends are, and know who your enemies are. I feel bad for ignoring Mikes complaints, but I now feel far worse about the way I treated [Ms. Jameson] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).








 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upvotes are Demons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We start to obsess

Over this fake fame

How we stress and stress

For what seems like a game

As the numbers 

Start to rise higher

You start to remember

The upvote is a liar
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just click refresh constantly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Just Came Back Home After Being Missing for 15 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello my name is Phil and I am 19 years old. Yesterday my mother and father saw me for the first time in 15 years. It would have been an amazing moment had I not been lying on the front yard of their house blindfolded with my arms and legs tied together. I woke up this morning to our house filled with all of our close family members and a couple of reporters. A police officer showed up at around 3 pm, but he told us he would just wait around till everyone left. The reporters tried to get information out of me, but I was not in the mood to give them any information. My aunt and uncle asked me if they hurt me, but before I could tell them no another reporter started to bombard me with questions. Annoyed, I left the living room and sat in the kitchen for the next hour. 
 
Everyone left except the police officer around 4 pm. He asked me if he could speak with me in private. We went to the kitchen and took our seats at the dining room table. He took out a notepad and with a forced smile on his face he told me to call him Matt.

*Me- So Matt I honestly dont know who took me or where I was.*

*Matt- Thats fine I just have a couple of questions. How many other people were with you?*

*Me- Well in total around 25. When I left there were around 17.*

*Matt- All males? Or were there any females?*

*Me- All males.* 

*Matt- What was the general age group?*

*Me- No one was under 4 or over 20.*

*Matt- Did the people that took you hit anyone?*

*Me- Not that I know of. They never laid a hand on me. They did shoot anyone that tried to leave the house. 4 tried to escape while I was there. 1 survived the gunshot and returned to the house the next day. He never said another word to any of us after that. A couple of people were found dead the next morning after they didnt follow a rule, but we never saw them get killed. Not even the person staying in the room with them would notice when they came into the room or how the person was killed.*  

*Matt- They? How many people were there?*

*Me- I only saw 2 on guard at a time, but the people seemed to change all of the time.*

*Matt- Can you describe what the place looked like?*

*Me- It was a house. A really big house. Not very fancy, but it had around 12 rooms. We all had our names written on a whiteboard next to our specified room. Our fridge was always stocked with enough food for all of us. We had a tv in the living room, but we never could find any channels that worked on it. Each of our rooms had 2 beds and 2 small dressers which contained only 3 of the same outfits. We had a laundry room with a washer and a dryer, but they would only work on Thursday.*

*Matt- 3 of the same outfits? What was the outfit?*

*Me- It was a plain white t-shirt and blue pants. Everyone wore the same exact thing. One 18 year old kid used blueberries to die his shirt blue, but the next day I found him lying on his bed dead. He had blueberries and bits of his blue t-shirt in his mouth. No one tried to change up their clothes after him.*

*Matt- How many people died while you were there?*

*Me- I know of 9 people that were killed. 14 people left the house along with me, but I dont know if the rest just went back to their house like me.* 

*Matt- Could you ever look outside of a window and see what was around you?*

*Me- I stared outside of the windows countless times. Sometimes I would see a person walking around the house carrying a gun, but other than the people all I could see was countless rows of trees. They stretched so far back and wide I could not see anything else.* 

*Matt- Did anyone ever come inside of the house?*

*Me- They would come inside to pick up the person that was ready to leave the house. Two people would come inside and grab the person that was leaving. They would have two pieces of rope and a black blind fold. They would tie his arms and legs together and put the blindfold over his eyes. After that they would carry the person into the wall of trees.*

*Matt- Did they ever show their face?*

*Me- No, never. They would wear monkey masks whenever they came in. None of us ever had the guts to take the masks off of any of the people.* 

*Matt- Thank you for taking the time to answer my questions. Ill contact you back if we have any other questions or if we make any new developments. Youre a brave man. Please let us know if you find or remember anything new.* 

After Matt left I headed upstairs to my bedroom. I passed by my parents room and heard them quietly talking inside. I put my ear up to the door and heard my father talking to my mother. 

* -argoret, dont worry. This was part of the program. He will come back for 5 days to live with us. After that they get rid of him and make it look like a suicide. This is the only way they can make it as less suspicious as possible.*

I rushed to my room and quietly closed my door. I thought about calling Matt, but I really want to figure this out.

I have [5 days] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).

[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r86pi/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm a fan haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Almost everything I write is short as hell, but maybe this one?] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i87cr/im_12_and_i_met_a_nice_man/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I still love all of the stories and the author's that spend HOURS or even DAYS working on a story to entertain other people. 


That's just me though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw.

I loved boyfriend bonfire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wife's Aunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 10:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three months ago my wife and I were contacted by her aunt saying that she needed people to take care of her. She offered a free room in her 3 bedroom apartment, and said she would fund all of our groceries. At that time we were not completely secure financially so we took the offer without a second thought. It seemed like an amazing opportunity for us to save up some money, and the fact that her apartment was only 5 miles away from my current job made the deal seem too good to be true.

Ive met her aunt a couple of times and she actually seemed like pretty decent person. Her name was Esther, but she insisted I call her Essy. The only major problem I had with her before moving into her apartment was she seemed like she couldnt do anything for herself. 

The first couple of weeks we lived with her we started to get comfortable in our new home. Essy never really asked us to do much. All she really wanted us to do is make her meals and change the channel for her if she got tired of watching constant Andy Griffith re-runs. Essy loved lying in bed while watching tv and chain smoking cigarettes. We never really minded since we could smoke in the apartment as well while enjoying our privacy. Sometimes she would leave her room and join us in the living room to watch a movie with us or talk about the past. 

Five days ago she came out into the living room to watch a movie with us. Around the middle of the movie she asked if we wanted some popcorn. We both said yes and before I got off of the couch Esther started walking to the kitchen. Three minutes later I heard the microwave going off and Esther took the bag of popcorn out of the microwave. She tried grabbing a large bowl out of the cabinets but ended up falling and hitting her head on the corner of the stove. I jumped off of the couch and ran up to her. I asked her if she was okay, but she just fell asleep in my arms. My wife was already calling for an ambulance.

When Esther came back she seemed like her normal self the first 2 days. She would tell us what she wanted to eat for dinner, what she wanted to watch on her tv, and if she was running low on cigarettes. 

Three nights ago Essy asked my wife if we could get her some subway for dinner. She said yes and asked her what kind of sandwich she wanted, but Essy just told her she didnt know yet. Before I headed off to subway I went into Essys room if she made her decision yet, but she just stared at me before saying Just tell that man in the red hat to fuck off. I asked her what man with a red hat, but she just looked at me with a confused look on her face. What do you mean Essy? I asked her with a hint of concern. She kept staring at me for a couple more seconds before saying Roast beef and nothing else. Just roast beef. Thanks. Not wanting anymore of the conversation I rushed out and grabbed the subs. I got back and put the sub on her bed. She thanked me, but still feeling a little uncomfortable about our earlier conversation I left without a single word. 

The next day she was normal up until lunch time. I had the day off so I brought here a tuna sandwich with some French fries, but as I laid the plate down in front of her she asked me if I could tell the Asian man to go away. I thought she was talking about me since I was Korean, but she kept pointing outside of the window. I was trying to think of a way to tell her that no one was there, but I was interrupted by the sound of my wife screaming. I ran into our room and saw that she was in our restroom. When I got into the restroom I saw blood trickling down the side of her head. I grabbed some toilet paper and put it against the small cut on her head, but she swatted my hand away and told me that the brush was moving on its own. 

When I asked her what she meant. She just fell onto my shoulder and cried while slamming the brush against the counter. 

I just never really believed in anything paranormal, and even at that point I just thought the stress was what was causing them to envision these crazy things. I mean, my wife bleeding from the side of her head is scary, but anything could have caused that. 

It was never a hard thing for me to disprove anything paranormal until last night. 

I was watching a movie alone since my wife already went to bed. About ten minutes into the movie I started to hear knocking coming from Essys door. I got up and peeked into her room, but I saw that she was asleep on her bed. I started to close her door when I heard her whisper Just take off the hat baby. I know. I know you dont want to, but the world has to see. They need to see the blood youre trying to hide. Take the hat off baby. Please, just take the hat off.

I felt the blood rush from my face. My hands started to shake, but I managed to shut the door without much sound. After I closed her door I rushed to the couch. On the way there I heard a pop and I dove as quickly as I could on to the couch. 

I dont know why a light bulb that was never turned on would shatter, but I feel like it was more than a coincidence.

Esther is acting weird and so is my wife.

[ I feel like Im starting to act weird too] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks) . 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pizza Bus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 10:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In our college we had three possible places we could get pizza. One was in the middle of our campus. We could buy a slice for 2 dollars or a whole pizza for 15 dollars. It was run by a lady with three teeth missing and dirty greasy hair falling out of her ancient hair net. 

Not very popular.

The next was a major pizza franchise that sells really flat cheese bread and over priced wings. The pizza is somewhat good, but the 20 dollar price tag on even the most basic pizzas made it only the second most popular option. 

The last and greatest choice was a bus that would park at the back end of the campus. He always had a funny joke and a great pizza for every person that walked up to the bus with just 8 dollars in their hands. 

I instantly fell in love with everything about the pizza bus. The unique idea of pizza being cooked and served on a bus, the way the pizza thin crust would crunch with every single bite before it became mush, and the way there always seemed to be the right amount of grease on the pizza and jokes from the owner of the pizza bus. His name was Josh and he quickly became one of my favorite people. 

I was an awkward 19 year old boy that never really made any friends. If anyone tried to talk to me I would always manage to say all of the wrong things or just stare at them until they awkwardly walked away. That is why the first trip to the pizza bus was so important to me.

Right as I started to get close to the bus I could already smell the wonderful aroma of a pizza cooked just right. I saw people gathered around the bus, and every couple of seconds I could hear laughter from the crowd. Right when I got up to the bus I saw the happiest person in the world making a couple of jokes while he tossed two pizzas into the oven. 

When he saw me he gave me a big smile and said Nice to see a new face! What kind of pizza would you like my man? I told him I just wanted a cheese pizza, he started to spread the sauce on the thin crust. He sprinkled two cups of cheese on the pizza while saying I dont mean to be cheesy but your smile just earned you a dollar off this pizza! I wasnt smiling, but at the end of his comment I was beaming like a brand new lighthouse.

After that amazing first visit I kept going back to the bus twice a week. 

3 months of me consistently being a customer Josh finally asked me if I was looking for a job. I immediately told him yes and the next day I walked up to the bus for the first time with a smile before I walked up to the bus.

The next month and a half flew by with a mixture of freshman classes and endless pizzas on my hands. Every night I smelled like pizza even after my shower, but all of it seemed trivial. I was making 11 dollars an hour and I had the best boss in the world. 

Yesterday, which was the last day before winter break, was when Josh started to act strangely. I wanted to say that it was the stress of suddenly having to work by himself because I was too busy with my exams, but it has gone far past that. 

I saw Josh writing on a piece of paper, but when he noticed I was coming he shoved the note in his pants pocket and waved at me. I waved back, but I asked him if he was writing a break up letter to his latest sexual conquest. He stared at me for a couple of seconds and told me to fold up some pizza boxes. 

Thrown off by his command, I asked him if he was okay. He said Fine and pointed at the boxes. I figured he was having a bad day so I just started to fold up the boxes. The first four customers didnt really notice anything different about him and left with a perfectly made pizza in their hands. When a girl walked up to the bus Josh shoved past me and walked up to her. She grabbed him by his collar and pulled his ear up to her mouth. She whispered a couple of things to him and he nodded slowly when she pulled away from him. He then handed her the piece of paper he wrote on. She took a quick glance at it, put the paper in her pocket, and walked away. 

A couple hours go by and I try being funny again with Josh. I asked Josh with a little wink, So that woman someone you know really well? Without even a chuckle he stared me down before saying, Watch for her. If she comes tell me. I am who she looks for.

I tried asking more about her, but stopped when he rushed up in front of my face and heavily breathed on my face. I tried taking a step away from him, but he kept scooting up to me and kept breathing on me. As soon as I said, Ill just keep folding boxes Josh sniffed and went back to counting the money in his drawer. 

At 10 pm we started to close down the bus, but one last customer walked up to the bus. Josh tried telling him to come back tomorrow, but I quickly asked him what he needed before he ended his statement. He mumbled Pepperoni and I got right to work. As I handed him the pizza he looked at me and said Its not right I asked him what he meant, but he just stared down at the box and screamed Its not right asshole! What the fuck did you just give me? I tried to calm the man down, but Josh suddenly ran up to him and started to bite down on his nose. The man screamed and started to run away.

When the man ran about 20 paces away from us he opened the pizza box and started to devour piece after piece. He screamed in agony with each bite, but he kept eating. When he finished his fifth slice the man fell and foam started to come out of his mouth. 

Right after I saw what happened to the man I handed Josh my apron and work shirt. I told him I quit, and Josh just took them from my arms without a word. 

Right as I exited out of the bus I started to run back to my dorm. One the way I saw 7 people lying on the ground with foam coming out of their mouths. 7 people that I saw earlier that day buying pizza from us.

I dont know who that woman is. I dont know what is in our pizza or why our customers are foaming out of their mouths. I want to go back to work tomorrow to try and figure it out, but I dont know if I want to sacrifice both my [winter break and my life] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep writing. 

Don't care about the upvotes.

It only takes one big story to become somewhat known.

Just don't get fed up with the shorter stories that get more attention. 

It actually takes some people hours to come up with a good short story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about Korean subtitles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! I remember talking to you about that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually thinking that movies might do better if they started using longer titles haj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electronics are more expensive here haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry.

I already alerted the cat enthusiasts,

Happy early birthday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that is true too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice! for me it would be I Now Know Why My Best Friend Acted Creepy,

title: The New Friend

I suck at titles haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real horror is all of the lonely cat women showing up at your house one day. 

The leader of the group has the hollowed out head of the director of your film.

You hear a soft noise coming from inside of the head, but it is far to muffled to hear what it is for sure.

They start moving up to your house one step at a time. Right as the leader of the group walks up to your front window you see a cat poking it's head out of the director's hollowed out eye. 

*Meow* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last title of this user's post?

Just got all of my pubes waxed off, from my pussy to my crack... Pics, videos and wax strips for sale. [vid] [pic] [fet] [oth]

Interesting, but kinda strange. Like someone that will wax my pubes and then eat my face with their two remaining teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother clearly said....

I'm worth 3 grains of rice or 5 red peppers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a terrible deal.

No thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to see the OP's history man:/

It's a dirty dirty dirty birdie.

First save is free. After this I'm gonna need those 5 red peppers back... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely watch a Horror movie called "Kittens". haha

or the Serpent of Bourbon Street, but i really like kittens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about the man that tried DRY HUMPING ME IN THE CORNER OF THE CELL? Well he did help me find an escape route for us by having my head repeatedly hit the crumbling wall and making a small hole. 

Thank you for the compliment!!! That really means a lot to me. The r/TheCultOfsubject8631 still makes me feel a bit odd but i love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> being in jail for one night has really softened you up -.-

Seriously, thank you so much for all that you do!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't touch him!!!

The virus "scam" is incredibly contagious.

Please wash your hands with three squirts of sacrificed lamb blood and scalding hot water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will give you 5 red peppers.

Nothing more  nothing less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is not an original idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know what your favorite story you wrote is, but let's put a twist. 

If it was made into a film. What would you name the film?

Okay.

Go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing to get tied up on. My first stories and one in the middle didn't even break 50. It's really just about the quality and luck from the stories. 

You're a good writer. 

Don't let this get you down. 

At certain times certain stories just do better due to having the right title. 

It's impossible to guess. 

Just post as much as you can with as good of a content as you can produce! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DON'T YOU KNOW WHO I AM?

I'M THE KOREAN EL CHAPO.

Left the other two there though. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frantic masturbation from my neighbor?

Yeah you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My original comments were a little too mean. 

I apologize. The story you mentioned was made before they made the no clickbait rule. 

The mods will take down clickbait stories as long as we report.

The commenta aren't automatically taken down because we only have a couple of people trying their very hardest to keep up with the demand. 

I have noticed comments that have nothing to do with the story removed within the next day.

It's good and mandatory we have these rules. It takes time, but we need to have patience and report report report.

Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say that you need to pace out whatever you eat. The average person cant eat a steak in 5 minutes. There are certain circumstances where you are forced to eat quickly, and today I experienced a severe case of such situation.
Twiddling my thumbs trying to keep my mind focused, but still daydreaming about how long today is going to be. Thinking about the cigarette break that I am going to miss out on because of this long and drawn out presentation.  I cannot help wondering if we are going to get out in time for lunch or if I will be forced to sacrifice my lunch for this never ending power point. 
The worst possible feeling is when you are nicotine deprived and hungry. To make matters worse the presenter after the meeting asked if I wanted to eat lunch with him. I know of a place that will keep our conversations short, and we will be able to enjoy this lunch as quickly as possible. 
I take him to one of my favorite lunch spots. Its placed in a nice discrete location. Not a busy restaurant, but the food always manages to be savory and sweet. He said he needed to use the restroom, and I point him to the back of the store. 
So, it has been over 20 minutes and he has yet to return. The food has been brought out and at that very moment so did he. Time to finally eat after slaving over a computer and abused in the ear. Cant lie, I ate most of the lunch by myself, and I do not feel a ping of guilt. Im sure he wont mind. The meal consisted of the sweetest meat could possibly be. The dish itself was surrounded with various types of sausages that would make anyones mouth water.  It also comes with a light side dish of thinly sliced liver, and a salad surrounding it to make it an absolute homerun.
I would post it on yelp, but they have yet to be listed on that site. 
There is always a downside for everything. Even when it comes to one of the best meals I have had in a while I still should have eaten slower. I just cant help myself around good food sometimes, and I know I will have an immense stomach ache coming back to work. There are also plus sides to this lunch.
I am fully content with this meal. 
I think I have found a new spot to splurge on whenever I am having a bad day.
Above all else, I am content with walking back to work alone. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

Why don't you just unsubscribe? Like are you dumb or something?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes u/Polar_Starburst is an amazing writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm.

Maybe it is something that is trying to keep you safe from something you can't hear?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Strange Experiences With an App Called "Life is Beta" [Final] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has only been a day and I miss my wife and child so much. I know I will never be able to see them without having to turn myself in to the cops. I tried sleeping in the sewers last night. Which has resulted in me waking up various times throughout the night to throw up; I kept getting calls and texts from my wife which has not helped me sleep either. 

This morning when I woke up I saw that my wife had left me a voice mail. I click the notification and press my phone up to my ear. 

Choking through her sobs she said, *You know we could have figured this out together. Why did you have to kill yourself honey? You know I would always love you. You know your son and I would always take your side. Why did you have to be so stupid? Why couldnt you just come home so we could figure everything out?* With a loud sob she ended her message.

I saw my Facebook page had around 40 notifications on it, and when I went onto my profile I saw various posts from old and new friends. All saying RIP, Too Soon, Why did you do it, and some from people I didnt know that said Murderer and Good Riddance.

One person without a profile picture, Olive Johnson, posted a video with the subtitle Enjoyed taping that. I clicked on the video and saw a man that looked exactly like me with the barrel of a gun in his mouth. He was standing in front of my company holding the gun with both of his hands, and when the cops tried to walk up to him to intervene he closed his eyes and pulled the trigger. 

I shut off the video and sat in silence while I tried to make sense of what the fuck was going on. In the middle of my thoughts my phone buzzed twice.

I turned the screen on and saw that there were two notifications from *Life is Beta*. I tried tapping on the first one and it just simply said look up. I looked up to see a man standing over the entrance to the sewer. I tapped the second notification and it said catch. I put my arms out and caught the clothes the man tossed down to me. I put on the red shirt, khakis, and gray dress shoes and climbed out of the sewer. By the time I was out the man was gone. 

My phone buzzed again and tapped on the notification. If you want to see your family again one last time go to your house now. 

I grabbed the first cab and gave him the address to my house. When we got there I forgot that I didnt have money. I checked the jacket pocket and found 20 dollars and a portable battery for my phone. I told the driver to keep the change and ran up to the tree outside of my house. I got another notification that said Climb. 

I climbed up the tree and found a branch that could hold my weight. I sat on it and looked into my bathroom window. I know I should have just savored the last seconds watching my wife and son playing on the bathroom floor, but I had to have something to remember them by. My phone was starting to die, but I opened up the camera app and started to take a video of them. My hot breath against the cold window caused it to start to fog. While I watched them I started to feel tears fall from my face and my fingers started to shake. My wife and kid still seemed to be somewhat happy spending time together, but I would just give anything in the world to be right next to them. After a couple of seconds I saw my wife start to look up and I quickly shut my phone off while putting it in my pocket.

I got down from the tree and started to run. 

I didnt have any clue where I was going, but I just wanted to somehow escape out of the nightmare I have created. I wanted to somehow go back in time and hide my phone in the cabinet like I always did so my son could have never downloaded that god forsaken app on my phone. I dont blame my son, but I just wish he had never touched my phone. 

I stopped running as soon as I felt my phone buzz. I opened the notification and found the video I just took with the words Look familiar on the bottom. 

That moment I was tempted to throw my phone as far as I could, but I knew that this app was still the only thing keeping me alive. I started to think that maybe I could just go back home. I know my wife would be okay with keeping it a secret I was still alive, but I just didnt want to put them in any kind of harm. 

Another buzz and another notification by them. 

When I opened up the app I found two buttons on the screen on the left and right side of my character.

Kill or Be Killed. 

Disgusted, I shoved my phone back in my pocket and continued to walk down the street. 

I felt another buzz, but I ignored it. 

After the third buzz I started running again, and tried to ignore the buzzing. I didnt stop running until I tripped and fell to the ground. 

My phone immediately started to buzz continuously then. I took the phone out of my pocket and saw a video of me stabbing Brad in the throat with the letter opener. It jumped to another video of Brad at his house while he was reading the newspaper. The date on the newspaper was from the day before I stabbed him. 

His dog walked up to him, but he shoved the dog back with his foot. A woman came in and started to yell at him and Brad stood up and started to shout back. She got in his face and started to shove him back. He tries to slap her hands away, but she kept pushing him back. He pushed her back once. That was all it took. She fell to the ground and her head smacked into the edge of the table. Her head bent away from her body at an impossible angle and she stayed on the ground completely still.

The video then shot to Brad stuffing her into a deep freezer. She wouldnt fit, but he kept shoving her in until her bones gave up and snapped.

The video ended and I was met with the two options. 

This is the last thing Im writing to everyone. 

I just want you to know that if you ever find an app called Life is Beta you are chosen. You will be met with a final choice. Most people arent able to handle the stress. They dont choose any of the options. They just lose their mind. The app will keep you safe from them. Just please know that your life will never be the same again.

Choose kill. 

You can help the world get rid of the evil in this world [one rotten soul at a time] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).

[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5pv010/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/)

[Part1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5pmu3w/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
