<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6752</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rockstar Support isn't as bad as people make them look like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking up Rockstar Support on this sub, most of the posts here are from bad experience people have so I wanted to share mine, because I believe we have to share both sides.

First of all, about 3 months back, I had an issue with [a player taking over my yacht in Passive Mode](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NrB16CWrJuI) and I opened a ticket. They asked me how much I "lost" and I told them $30k. They ended up giving me $130k. 

Now, one week ago, I traded my Maze Bank (main) for the Maze Bank West. I was supposed to get $1million and some more and I didn't.

I emailed them and within the hour, they gave me $1.9 million. 

I personally believe they are pretty good. I have seen people losing cars and support doesn't help them, so I'm not sure what was the playing factor there but they helped me out twice and without talking back and forth or a bot answering to me. So, thank you Rockstar for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Replay] Thank you Miner for saving my butt! (also thank you Hog for being fast) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tesla Model S hearse is real and actually quite impressive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla increases base price of the Model X by making the Smart Air Suspension standard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI statement raises prospect of second legal battle with Apple over locked iPhone || 9to5mac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discrimination at its finest :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discrimination at its finest :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS users, I'm making a Clash Royale Sticker Pack, but I need YOUR help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings!

After being requested 3 times, and no one stepped in, I decided to do so. So, without further ado, here it is! http://imgur.com/a/9TGo2

However, I have a problem. The images size suck and the king emotes are laggy in terms of frame, so I need you to help me out!

See what I am talking about in a quick demo here: https://youtu.be/zoLcN-FDAus

I need you guys to get me good file pictures and gif, of the emotes and text. For example, a big crying king. The file must be less than 500KB. I also plan to include troops in the pack, or maybe they will be separate. I don't know, I am still brainstorming. 


~~After everything is done, I will drop the IPA (iPhone application file) file after I speak to the legal team over at SC. This won't be in the App Store as I don't have $99 to sign up to be a full developer but you will have the chance to sideload this.~~

Nah this is going straight to the store after is done. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature] You can now Reduce motion and have Message effects! (Pre-Beta 2 on the left, on the right Beta 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a 629 credit score. What should I do to increase the score before I finish college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello PF!

First of all, thanks in advance for the advice and help. 

I have a 629 credit score (which is average). I started doing my credit when I turned 18, back in April, and got a CC from BoA with a $600 limit and a 21.75% APR.  

I always use the card for everything that I need and pay off the full balance every month (never been charged interests) If it helps, I use like 70-85% of the limit. 

What should I do to increase my credit score (it seems to go down over time) before I finish college? My main concern is that if I don't have a good score, I won't have a low interest for a car, and/or I can't get a good apartment if my 'future' landlord decides to run a credit check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the signal bar on your phone on GTA O means your actual connection to the game (x-post /r/grandtheftautov) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw it on /r/grandtheftautoV so I thought about x-posting here if you guys didn't know it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA- I don't know if you guys know this, but if you recently bought a Watch from Apple (14 days), they can do a band swap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The catch however is that it has to be offered on the same configuration of your Watch. Some people let you swap to any band however, so test your luck.

For example, I got a Series 2 42mm Gold AW which is offered with a Cocoa band, and a Coffee Toasted Woven Nylon. I got the Nylon band, so I had the option to have it changed to the Cocoa one.

On my experience, however, the store couldn't do this due to system error, so I contacted Apple and they said to go back to the store and speak to a manager. I did, and she let me swap to any band that I want, so I got a [Midnight Blue band](http://i.imgur.com/iCfqdHV.jpg)

So if the system fails, just don't fret and go back tomorrow when the staff is different. You might even get a different band than what's offered  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm back in the club! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MKBHD is now one of us! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases iOS 10.0.2! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple releases iOS 10.0.2! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple releases iOS 10.0.2! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://ipsw.me/history

I will edit with changelog and articles.

EDIT:

Different sizes for each device. Weird. https://ipsw.me/otas/10.0.2

EDIT 2: Changelog

https://twitter.com/viticci/status/779348293780381696

Thanks /u/pzumk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple has released a 10.1 Beta build for developers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iOSReleases/status/778639635622789120 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.1 available for testing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iOSReleases/status/778639763825909760

 and 

https://twitter.com/iOSReleases/status/778639635622789120 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Automoderator won't post at the time I specified </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I tried making a one time, stickied post for AM, and no matter what I try, he won't post. He has full access and the sub isn't restricted. 

My rule/schedule is here: http://imgur.com/a/ul4WL

What am I doing wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mega Minion is now obtainable! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 08:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google made a new app for iOS, Google Trips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://get.google.com/trips/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google releases a new app for iOS (and Android), Google Trips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/nyc is one of the trending subreddits for 9-19-16! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This phone reminds me of another phone... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 00:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] Sneak Peaks tomorrow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 22:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 7 unboxing: Jet Black vs Matte Black | MKBHD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 23:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/J5HtSy5bATk

E: Also, he shows setting up the iPhone 7+ and how iOS asks which sensitivity he would like for the home button and also he runs a benchmark in the iPhone 7+.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PSA] CloudMagic is moving to a subscription based client [not its entirety though] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This morning, I received an email from CloudMagic. Here it is: [one](http://i.imgur.com/Moz7A1i.png) and [two](http://i.imgur.com/QNBY057.png)

They said that they are rebranding their client. Now they are Newton. This change will also being more features, however, you will need to pay. $50 a year for the [premium features](http://i.imgur.com/5Kq40Oy.png)

If you are a current user of CloudMagic, you will get a year free. Just remember to turn off auto renewal so you aren't short $50 next year. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatsapp has been updated to take advantage of the Phone API in iOS 10. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changelog: http://i.imgur.com/U8k146M.png 

If you don't know what it is, is basically answering a Whatsapp call like any other call that comes to your phone. Screenshot of the example here: http://i.imgur.com/WcEVv59.jpg 

However, after accepting the call, Whatsapp will be launched and the call will keep going there. Only when the phone is unlocked. If it is locked then the native UI will be shown like this http://i.imgur.com/HVwM2kl.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: If you don't have access to iTunes, don't update to iOS 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10 public release is out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as the GM so it won't show under Software Update.

ipsw.me has the ipsw files! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] iOS 10 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple releases iTunes 12.5.1 for Mac and Windows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature] "Only for iMessage" message on App Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing the Gold DS4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 OS 4.00 out tomorrow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm going in a massive win streak. Should I be scared? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the battles in my battle log are Victories with the exception of 2 loses and a draw. Should I be scared of a coming losing streak? I just gained like 700 trophies and all I did was level up to level 10. 

Title Edit: On ** a massive win streak
EDIT: Changed 7000 to 700 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Cook says Apple is "Very Commited" to the Mac and to "Stay Tuned" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature] App Store shows whether an app is available in the ATV or not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing 9.3.4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GM is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Version 2.5 is out for everyone! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Beats products to be unveiled at iPhone event next week || iDB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was I wrong to report this driver? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] -- [UPDATE] [PP] Pangu Jailbreak iOS 9.2-iOS9.3.3 jailbreak tool safari version updated just now to 1.2! 64bit j.25pp.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 15:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Personal Opinion: Every day I hate the game even more, and I don't want to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 17:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warning, this will be a long rant and you might not agree with everything I have said. So, let's keep it civil and if you don't like my post, just hit the button and move on. Simple. I know "one less in this game, bye, yadda yadda". Remember this is a personal opinion and I need to vent out :) 

Okay. Ever since launch day on iOS, CR has been my favorite game. I played it in class, train, hell everywhere you can think about. However, each day I have started to hate the game even more to the point where I'm in the edge of uninstalling it and forgetting about it. Here is why:

1-) **Most players aren't original**

No one is original in this game. Well, let me rephrase that, most of the players in this game aren't original. 90% of the last 50 games I have played, include at least 4 troops that were showed in Youtube or somewhere else. Is the same deck all over, same gameplay, same everything. If I do want to at least win I have to adapt to that deck (to counter and push), however, I refuse to do so because I want to use my own deck that I built on my own (never seen it in YT or somewhere else), and not some copied deck. 

Also skill-less decks. Spawner decks to be specific. That's something that will drain your elixir trying to counter it except if you don't have like a bomber or something like that

And this bored me. I like games where there is always a challenge, something different. I only enjoy the game when I see unique decks. 

2-) **Supercell tries to fix problems using band-aids**

Not a good analogy, but, hey, is something :p

I like when game developers want to listen to their player base and try to do the best to make them happy. I personally don't think Supercell is doing it. 

* On 8/24, they decreased the time it takes the RG to shoot. I don't think that helped. His range is still a problem. He freaking stands literally half a step in front of the bridge covering anyone behind him. So if you ever counter the RG with melee troops (that don't have cannons, bows or spears), good luck. I don't think anyone will stop using the RG after this change.

* No love has been shown to the Wizard even tho this community have asked them to fix it.

* The Giant is **overused (like the RG)**, strong and has a massive amount of health. After many complaints, they haven't said anything.

~~* Poison is still a strong card. It slows you down and attacks you at the same time? The rage just speeds you up. I think they have to change one thing. Either, boost the damage of the raged troops by at least 5% (I mean, that way strong troops aren't more stronger now), or remove damage from the poison. Their call.~~ Nevermind. I was wrong on this one. My bad

* New players are struggling to move up due to players from A7 and above dropping for trolling and for other reasons. We have told them several ways to fix this and they haven't said anything. 

PS: Just FYI, I consider myself to be a good, I have [tournament level cards](http://i.imgur.com/y1EwUPC.jpg) and I'm able to put up a fight. I say this in case someone comes and say that I just suck, or I just don't have tournament level cards
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10 Beta 8 - Bugs and Features Megathread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our friend /u/AppleBetas is missing. He is the one who makes this thread, so unofficially, I made this until he comes, remove this and sticky his. 

/u/AppleBetas please report to my office! 

Edit:
 Release notes by /u/nullpixel here:

 [Meta] Beta 8 release notes
https://www.dropbox.com/s/8zp6021rst1nlnl/iOS_10_beta_Release_Notes.pdf?dl=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS Beta 7 - Bugs and Features Megathread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Beta 8 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Narwhal 2.5 ready for testing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 02:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] First seed of 9.3.5 beta released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple stops signing iOS 9.3.2 and iOS 9.3.3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 01:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See ipsw.me/9.3.2 and ipsw.me/9.3.3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing 9.3.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 23:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Product announcement at noon CA time - Elon Musk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Jailbreak 101 - A guide for new jailbreakers Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up! I'm back again with a second guide of jailbreak, but this one is special. Here is why:

Apple is prone to stop signing 9.3.2 and 9.3.3 really really soon. 9.3.3 came out [one month ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/4tg81s/release_ios_933_has_been_released/) and 9.3.2 has more than 2 months being signed!

So if Apple stops signing these versions, you can't restore to them anymore and your jailbreak can be a goner. So here is a guide to prevent you from losing your jailbreak!

________

#Table of contents

1-) Restoring
2-) Installing Jailbreak again
3-) Tips

_______

#1-) Restore. NOW!

You should restore just to have a clean copy of iOS 9.3.3. It will also help as you might clean your phone before restoring :) 

**However**, iTunes will restore you to 9.3.4 if you don't provide iTunes the ipsw file for 9.3.3. Here is what you'll do:

1-) Download the ipsw file for your device from the link over there ()  - ipsw.me/9.3.3

2-) While the file is downloading, BACK UP EVERYTHING YOU WANT. Use Google Photos, iCloud Photo Library, iCloud, use anything needed for what you want to keep. If you don't want something, [let it go](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L0MK7qz13bU), it will just occupy space. 

3-) Time to restore! Now, to restore, go to iTunes (with your phone/ipad/ipod plugged in) and go to the device's info. 

You see the first box with the storage, serial, and phone number (if applicable)? There should be two clickable boxes there. Update (this might change depending on which iOS are you on) and Restore. Hold the Shift button on Windows and the option button in Mac and press Restore. 

*"Oh shit /u/subject6752, this dude is asking me for a file. Tf did you tell me to do?"* I just told you a few steps so that the NSA can have your location and can get you! (insert diabolical laugh here). No. Chill. Remember the first thing you downloaded in the first step? That's what iTunes is asking for. Go ahead and select that and press "Ok, Verify, Accept, or Allow". Whatever comes up there that means something positive. 

You should have a clean copy of 9.3.3 now! Go ahead and restore that backup you made. 

**NOTE: This also applies if you are on 9.3.4 and 10.0, however, the backup can't be restored due to having a higher OS. So, if you want to go to 9.3.3, you can do so, losing all data. You can also restore the backup you made when you left 9.3.3**

_________

#2-) Installing Jailbreak again

Now that you just installed 9.3.3, is time to get you jailbroken again.

There are various way of doing this. 

You can use Cydia Impactor (desktop app) to sideload the Pangu app, you can use the Chinese version, or you can jailbreak via Safari (there is a method working). Whichever appeals to you. 

There are a plethora of YT videos that show you how to jailbreak using a PC, but I will show you the Safari version.

1-) Head over to www.pgyer.com/TTJB9 (make sure you have the capitals on 'TTJB')

2-) You see the Chinese version of the jailbreak? Good! Now press the green button there. And press "Install" on the pop up

3-) ***This is where it gets kinda tricky***. After you press the Install button, head over to the home screen and find the app that's downloading. Watch it closely. The reason is because you will need to open up the Control Center (have it open after you find the app) and enable Airplane Mode after the status of the app goes from "Loading" to "Installing". 

4-) Did it install? 

No? Repeat Step 3. 

Yes? Good! Don't open it though.

Go to Settings - General - Device Management (under VPN) and select the profile called "Beijing Hong Yuan Online" and press verify. After it is done, go back to the home screen and open the app and jailbreak!

__________

#3-) Tips

Here are some tips to ensure that you will always have a jailbroken device unless you decide to restore to update to iOS 10.

1-) Never. And I mean NEVER. Install a tweak that is not compatible with your version. You see BiteSMS in Cydia? Looks beautiful right? It makes you want to install it right? DON'T! The last iOS support for BiteSMS was iOS 7 so it is prone to cause issues on your iOS 9 phone. 

2-) Don't go all crazy installing tweaks as there are a few that conflicts with one another. What you should do is look here in the sub the name of the tweak and you will see if people have issues with the tweak conflicting with another tweak. Or if they have issues that you want to avoid. 

3-) Install Cydia Eraser as the first tweak you install. Why? Because you might be stuck in certain situations where you are jailbroken (tweaks work) but Cydia crashes. Or any other weird issue. So you can use Cydia Eraser to erase the content of your phone.

However use C-Eraser after: 

* Backing up
* You restored the language/font files of iOS
* You have tried to boot in No-Substrate mode (holding the vol+ button while jailbreaking) and Cydia doesn't work there. 

4-) Install Power Tap. It is a good way to get to Safe Mode if you ever need it. 

5-) Also, if you don't have access to a computer and you need to restore and jailbreak, use Cydia Eraser and jailbreak via Safari method explained in Step 2

_________

#4-) FAQ

**What do you mean by Apple signing an iOS version?**

It means that Apple decides whether you can restore to that version of iOS or not. They do this for security concerns. 

**I want to restore because I'm having an error on Cydia**

You might need to stash. See this [post](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/4ugzui/release_stashing_for_92933_get_more_space_on_your/)

**How long does the certificate last?**

It lasts up to April 2017. And I don't think it matters because there will be an iOS 10 jailbreak before this time. ^^^I ^^^have ^^^hopes. 

**You think you are funny by making corny jokes up there () with that Let it Go shit and the like?**

Bro. You have beef with me? Let's go! ()  (`)  ^^^I ^^^do ^^^it ^^^because ^^^I ^^^want ^^^to ^^^be ^^^cool ^^^:(

________

I hope I helped and if you have any questions, shoot them! I'm ready for them! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Screenshot] PS4 OS 4.00 Tidbit: New firmware shows when was the last time your Friend went online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS Beta 6 released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I sold my Watch.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to get a new one with warranty. I love the Apple Watch way too much.

Now I need to know if I should buy the Sport Gold (I had AWS) or a SS one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look umpire I got the ball but my feet is off the base! He is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] PhotosLive updated with iOS 8   9 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOs 10 Beta 5 released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't mirror supposed to... Well, mirror? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just noticed today after a long loss streak. 

If you have a Level 3 Mirror, and you have it on your deck along with level 1 rares, commons or epics, mirroring them will upgrade them for just 1 elixir more. 

So with a Level 3 mirror, those rares go to level 6, the commons go to level 8 and the epics go to level 3.

Is you look yourself at the mirror, with no accessories on your face and your mirror shows you with glasses, hat, and etc

I always thought they were capped at that level. This makes the Mirror a freaking strong card... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] Cleo by CP Digital Darkroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] If there is one thing Clash Royale has thought me, is to never give up and keep pushing. Also to have strong emotions... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 19:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Aquaboard with iOS 9.0-9.3.3 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases 9.3.4 :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Cydia purchases now enabled. Saurik also added a one-day refund feature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We might buy a car soon. We need some advice beforehand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings! 

Our family is in search of a new car. We are not sure where to start, what to research, or what to expect when going to the dealership. 

Our family is composed of a mother, and 3 brothers (where I'm included) and an elderly person (main reason we want to get the car). 

Here is some info about us that can help:

* Mom makes about $1.2k a month (around 
$14.4k/yr) 

* I make about $6k yearly. 

* We are on public assistance, so we get Food stamps, Medicaid, and assistance for rent (we only pay like $100 of $1k of rent)

* We live in NYC.

* No debts

* $245 of bills (internet, cable, and mobile phones) 



Questions:

1-) Is it safe for us to buy at car of $8k (2007 or newer)? We mainly look for a car so we can transport our grandmother (and take her out to have fun, she suffers from Demencia and I've heard that helps).

2-) If we do decide to get one, which manufacturer should be good for us in terms of cheap gas cost, and cheap maintenance? We look into getting a SUV/crossover.

3-) I'm 18, my mom is 45, how would insurance work? What is something we must be sure to do when insuring the car?

4-) Must likely, we will buy from a dealership. What are some tactics they use to get more money out of us, and how should we counter it? Any tips to get the dealship not to make us overpay?

5-) Any websites or app I can use to check inventory of a dealership? How should we conduct our research?

6-) Anything else we should know? 

Thank you for the help guys! I appreciate it! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feature] Siri suggestion for words that she might have not understood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple is blocking the enterprise certificate used to jailbreak via Safari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For now, Jailbreak via the Windows tool. 

I will update with news as it develops

Edit 1: JB developer @iMokhles (Twitter) is on it
Edit 2: Article written by Anthony Bouchard over at [iDownloadBlog](http://www.idownloadblog.com/2016/07/27/apple-is-reportedly-blocking-some-certificates-used-to-jailbreak-ios-9-3-3-from-safari/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Jailbreak 101 - A guide for new jailbreakers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! 

In the past 4 days, we have increased the numbers of subscribers from [121,207 readers](https://imgur.com/a/MAUdA), to 123,911! This means we have new members who are first jailbreaking and are probably lost on what to do, so I'm looking to solve that issue!

_____

#Table of contents

1. Themes/Setups
2. Tweaks
3. FAQ about the 9.2-9.3.3 jailbreak
4. Things you should be aware of

_____

#1. Themes/Setups

Looking into pimping (informal definition) your device? Jailbreaking can help. 

If you don't know where to start, head over to Cydia, and tap Themes. This will give you a list of hand-picked Themes that are popular within the community. Some are free (at the moment of this writing there is not a free theme in the featured list), some are paid but look around and I bet you can find one that appeases your needs :)

Do you have a theme? Good! First step done. Now, do you want to customize even further? Head over to /r/iosthemes and on the search bar, type the name of your theme. You will find setups made by somebody else, and you can get inspired by them! You will always find the tweak list in the comments or the Imgur description so watch out for those. Common tweaks used to customize the device are HideMeX (iOS 9 -- Not updated *yet*), and Springtomize 3

For example, my theme is Veexillum, so I type that in the search bar and I will get setups for this theme and get inspired!

Also, if you want to change your font, checkout Bytafont 3!

Have fun!

____

#2. Tweaks

Is hard to recommend tweaks as tweaks are basically per needs (for example Snap + for Snapchat if you use Snapchat, if you don't you don't need it)

I do recommend you to go to /r/findatweak and ask if there is a tweak that can do what YOU want. 

However, the Essential tweaks I see people installing over and over are:

**Activator** - This tweak will help you accomplish something, by completing an action. Do you want to play music when your triple click the volume + or - buttons? Set it up with Activator. Do you want to send a message when you put your pinky finger on the Touch ID sensor? Activator can help. 

**BioProtect or Biolockdown** - These tweaks share a common purpose, to protect your apps/settings with your finger (Touch ID), however they both share different options. The option are available in a [Google Docs](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pLKgDYxJRUgtp81nsHK-x9qVUkbZ52NxP1HAMZNGKt8/edit?usp=sharing) file to save space in this post. 

**CCSettings** - Looking to turn off cellular data from your Control Center? Turn on Hostpot? Turn off GPS? CCSettings is for you. 


Looking for more tweaks? See this [Master Cydia Repo list](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/2qmk6m/repos_master_cydia_repo_list/) by /u/codeoriginal

____

#3. FAQ

**What is this Jailbreak?**

Is a semi-**untethered** jailbreak. I like to call it an "On-Demand" jailbreak. What does it mean? First let's get familiarized with some terms:

**Untethered** jailbreak: This means that you can reboot on the go. Once you jailbreak the first time, you won't need to use a computer again to mess with the jailbreak unless you want to restore or use a file manager

**Tethered** jailbreak: The total opposite. You can't reboot on the go as you will need a computer to jailbreak again. The thing is that you device will be a brick without booting tethered again using a tool

**Semi Tethered** jailbreak: This is a jailbreak that allows you to reboot your device, but not without some consequences. After rebooting, you may not be able to run any Cydia jailbreak apps, and even some stock apps like Safari may be inaccessible. A SemiTethered jailbreak is normally a tethered jailbreak with a package installed that allows you to reboot with limited use. You must perform a tethered boot to regain full functionality to your jailbroken device. 

Now, this one is a **Semi-Untethered** jailbreak. Can you guess what it is? Yep. It is a jailbreak that will let you boot disabling the jailbreak (stock apps will work as opposed to semi-tethered), however with the press of a button in an app and locking your device, you can have jailbreak again. Why is it called Untethered? Because you don't need a computer to enable the jailbreak. 

**How do I jailbreak again?**

Open the PP app, press the big circle, and lock your device right away. The device will respring to a jailbroken state

**Can a tool be made to make this untethered?**

Maybe. 

**What happens after the seven days?** 

No one is sure. But if the PP app stops opening after Sunday, delete it (from the Device Management settings under Settings  General)and go to https://totoateam.com/pangujb/ and press the "Install (arabic letters)" link and Accept/Install everything it asks you. 

**How do I unjailbreak?** 

Restore on iTunes

**I have an error on Cydia**

You might need to Stash. See this [post on Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/4ugzui/release_stashing_for_92933_get_more_space_on_your/). 

**You are awesome /u/subject6752**

I'm not. I'm just doing my helping duties ^^^I ^^^Know ^^^I'm ^^^Awesome ^^^;)

____

#4. Things to avoid

* Piracy repos and cracked tweaks - The reason is that you don't know what has been added to that tweak and what can it do to your device. Stick to the default repos
* Craked apps - Same reason as above
* Installing tweaks that hasn't been updated for iOS 9. Just ask here if it works or not, the most that can happen is that you will be downv-ted (put an O in place of the "-", AutoModerato doesn't like people saying it), but at least you didn't mess up your device.
* Installing apps that can conflict with each other - Again, ask here, we will help :)

___

I hope I helped and if you have any questions, shoot them! I'm ready for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] BioProtect v1.9-1 now live on BigBoss with support for 9.2-9.3.3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] Chronicles of Clash Royale -- Royal Giant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 21:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Royal Giant is a **common** troop, which was added to the game on February 29th.  ~~It was really balanced at this point, no concerns.~~ The few concerns were that he was useless and a waste of a card (Thanks /u/mykingislonely) However, on March 23rd, less than a month, the Royal Giants damage was increased by **20%**, because Supercell thought the [usage rates and win rates were low](https://clashroyale.com/blog/release-notes/balance-changes-coming-3-23). At this point the RG is very powerful, and on top of that, his range was increased by one on May 3rd. On May 18th, however, the RG was nerfed by 4%, and according to Supercell, he is not OP. 
This leaves the Royal Giant being heavily buffed from what he originally was before and this becomes a problem eventually, here is why:

**He is a common**
Because the RG is a common, it is easy to get. Whether it is from a Silver Chest (where every card should be a common, with no guarantees of Rares or Epics), or a Free Chest, if you are on A7, you are bound to get a card for the RG real quick. 

On a personal test I conducted, I wanted to see how quick I can get the Royal Giant to level 9. 

I got to A7 about 1 month and a half ago, and I got him on the **first** chest I got from A7. 5 RGs. I got him to level 2 (I needed one card for level 3)

I requested him to my clan, so I expected 30 RGs, and I got it. So I had 33 RGs, level 2, this bump him to level 4 (one more card needed for level 5).

I won another match, which gave me a gold chest, and I got about 10 of him. After requesting, and getting it from chest, I got him in level 9 in just 3 weeks. Im not exaggerating when I say that out of the 100 chests I opened (generic value to illustrate my results), I got at least one RG in 85 chests. Right now, Im halfway to getting him to level 10. Keep in mind that I have not unlocked the guardians, nor the Dark Prince ever since I got to A7 and I already have the RG in level 9. The three musks are in level 5.

Also, because he is a common, is really cheap to upgrade him. I have wasted 7,625 coins upgrading the Royal Giant to level 9 and if you really think about it, it is an easy amount of gold to get. In addition, a common card is really cheap in the shop. Every time you buy a card, the cost gets multiplied by 2. ~~With 510 gold, you can get 8 RG (2+4+8+16+32+64+128+256).~~ (I got the wrong equation at first. Thanks /u/TehFluffer!) The equation used on CR is y = x + 2 so with 503 gold you can get 23 RGs. Not really expensive right?
______

This is what probably gets everybody infuriated about RG. 

**He is a tank**
Because he is a tank, expect somebody who will always back him up and wont die right away if all your attention is on the RG. Popular backups are Witch, Wizard, or a musketeer. If you struggle taking down a Giant, you will struggle to take the RG down (but less struggle due to having less health).

**He is strong and he has good range**

**It is cheap in terms of Elixir**
Do you want a giant with a cannon? Pay an elixir more!

___

**Suggested solutions I have seen from the community**

* Remove the RG from every player and then add him as an epic. This will require his numbers to be reworked
* Nerf him, in all three aspects, Range, HP and damage - *Im not sure this is the right step to a solution but it can work. As long as the nerf is more than 4%.*
___

This concludes this chapter of CoCR. I hope you like this and please leave me feedback on how to improve! Im doing this specially for this sub!
Tomorrows edition of CoCR will be about **Strong Emotions** and I will be choosing a theme for next week from what you guys have submitted [here] https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdrd7IT3D6weB3CqtSVbdwFl16hJNTz8bEV4DWZnB0U1j7lrQ/viewform)
Please submit more themes and I will work on it!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] I'm starting up a new series for this sub and I want YOU to decide the next chapter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be posts that I will submit 2 times a week (Sunday and Monday) about Clash Royale's problems, strength, weakness. Everything about CR. 

The series will be called "Chronicles of Clash Royale" and I just want to do this to spice up the sub and just because I want to practice writing (I'm not English native).

The first "chapter" will be released tomorrow and it will be about the Royal Giant and you can decide the next chapter (for next week) by going to this [form](http://goo.gl/forms/QEslDV6yQbT2iYzm1) and filling it out.

Monday's chapter will be called: **Strong Emotions**.

Are you guys interested in my project?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] I have some battery problems with my 6S. What should I try? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! 

I'm having a problem with my iPhone and I'm looking for some help before I give up and I restore.

I have an iPhone 6S, with iOS 9.0.2, and something is murdering my battery.

With 50% of charge, I left my house and one hour later the phone was at 10%. Just music (streaming), no intensive game, no camera, just music.

My phone gets very warm while out of the charger and charging which contributes to the phone discharging faster.

My top 3 apps according to Settings is Narwhal with 16%, Clash Royale 12% and Safari 10%

[BatteryLife shows me this](https://imgur.com/a/SeVB4) and my Tweak List is [here](http://pastebin.com/XHBX2x5g)

Low Power Mode doesn't help. Anything else I should try?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BUG] On iOS 10, if a child account downloads an app that's sponsored from the App Store, it won't require authorization of parent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PSA] Part Deux of Elon's Master Plan is happening elsewhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla launched the Roadster 10 years ago and came out of stealth mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BUG] My iPad Mini 2 is disabled for 25 years (round it to 26) due to a bug in the disable time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed B3 earlier today and I haven't got the chance to play with it. 

Due to things, my brother takes my iPad and disables it on purpose. He got around the 1 minute wait, the 5 mins wait and just stopped there. 

After I tried to put in my password, I missed by a digit and the iPad locked for 15 mins. 

No big deal. Now, after the 15 mins timer ends, my iPad goes to 26 years of wait time. A reboot will bring the 15 mins timer back and the cycle repeats again. 

 I know I can erase it through iCloud, but is there something I should try first to gain access to my iPad (aside from waiting those 26 years)?

EDIT: I can't invoke a backup through iTunes because, well, I need to put the password to sync it with iTunes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] iOS 9.3.3 has been released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WOS 2.2.2 released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] My game just updated. No changelog whatsoever. Any server fixes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played at 7:00AM EST and now at 9:41AM EST I opened the game and I saw the "Updating" screen, restarting the game.

Anyone knows what they fixed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India's transport Minister visits Tesla, offers up land for factory in the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 22:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] We have a "Thanks!" button, where is the "You are welcome" button? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 20:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually want to say to my opponents "You are welcome" when they beat me and they spam the "Thanks!" emote at the end. I suggest changing the "Good game!" button as no one uses it and just say "Thanks!" at the end.


^^^Yes ^^^I'm ^^^tilted ^^^because ^^^of ^^^players ^^^saying ^^^thanks ^^^when ^^^they ^^^win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Those with AP, can you try something please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Disclaimer: Please please don't try to fulfill my request on a highway, or a neighborhood with moderate to heavy traffic, and don't record it by yourself. Take someone with you to record. I don't want your insurance deductible to increase, get your Tesla damaged, or get yourself hurt.**

Can someone record a video of AP working, then deactivating because you don't have your hands on the wheel and slowing down until complete stop?

I can't find a video of AP doing this, but it will be interesting to see what AP do in these types of cases, and how long it takes to completely stop the car. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumer Reports calls for Tesla to disable AP, Tesla says no </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 14:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For today only, I will be testing out your deck and give you feedback in it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar to another Redditor who did this, I will be testing your deck, and give you feedback about it. 

However, I need you to tell me the following:

**What level are you?**
**What Arena?**
**Deck? (make sure you put the troop level as you mention them)**
**How do you play this deck? (If you have a video from your gameplay it will be better)**
**What's you weakness?**

For example, your entry should look like this:

Level: 9
Arena: 7
Deck: Prince (3), Witch (3), Wizard (6), Hog (6), Spear gobs (9), E-Collector (5) , Zap (8), Rage (2)
Gameplay: I drop Witch behind tower, followed by the prince. Then I rage them . I also drop wiz and hog together and zap hovering over the hog if an enemy troop is dropped to block it. In 2x elixir, I release my 4 main troops together and rage them while zap is hovering. Spear gobs are burner cards. 
Weakness: Legendary decks. 

#I can't try out legendary decks as... I don't have one yet :(  

EDIT: I also don't have the A7 epics, and the A8 troops (except Ice Spirits).

EDIT2: Holy shit! This blew up! I like it because that means I can help more! Keep those comments coming. I will do every single one that was posted before 7/13/16 12AM EST, just hang tight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] TIL that you needed to follow 74 steps to jailbreak an iPod Touch on iOS 1. As opposed to today where you just need to click a button and that's it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I revived /r/johnjay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the JJay sub here about 3 months ago (in the sidebar), however, it was dead, and no mods.

So [I requested it 2 months ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/redditrequest/comments/4h5yuq/requesting_rjohnjay/), and I just finished designing it (it had no CSS code)

Now /r/johnjay is live and ready to be used again :)

I hope you like the design I chose!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 is not outputting video to TV, but it does output sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 02:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I've researched this issue for hours already and no solution was able to help and I just finished my second call with Sony support but they weren't helpful. 

I was playing my PS4 yesterday night and when I finished playing, I accidentally disconnected it from the plug as I was going to charge my phone. I thought it wasn't a big deal, so I just let it off and when I turn it on today it will check for errors in the database/memory. 

Today when I turned it on, I could hear the sound coming out of the TV, however image doesn't. So I tried plugging in 2 other HDMIs and no luck. I tried changing TVs and tried the same 3 HDMIs again and the same issue persist. 

I still can access the PS4 via Remote Play on my laptop, but I can't change the display settings as it won't let me due to Remote Play being active. I have tried going to Safe Mode, and no image comes out however I tried to blindly select [the second option](https://psmedia.playstation.com/is/image/psmedia/safe-mode-ui-01-ps4-en-22jul15?$MediaCarousel_Original$) and it didn't help. 

I want to take the service route as a last option, so I'm still open to try anything. 

Can you guys recommend anything else I should try?

Thanks in advance :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] Game Mode ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still want to see more game modes than the normal battles. Tournaments don't really do it as they are normal battles. Here is my ideas:

#**Trainer Survival Mode**

If SC fixes the trainers, this could be effective (or SC could implement a system that Basically is that you will be fighting with various trainers until your king is destroyed. Once you kill the trainer's king, your troops will die and another king re-spawn, getting stronger by the time (increased king level and card levels).

#**Mirror mode**

This basically puts players based on your king level together in a random arena, with 8 cards picked by the game. However, both of you will have the same cards. The game should end when the king is destroyed only (no time). This is also should have its own specific count of trophies (not to be mixed with the normal trophies). Cards will be capped at tournament levels.

^I ^have ^suggested ^this ^as ^well ^as ^other ^redditors, ^so ^I ^can't ^take ^the ^credit ^for ^this ^idea, ^as ^I ^don't ^know ^who ^suggested ^it ^first.

#**Hardcore mode**

I suggested this before, but I will say it again. If you freeze your opponent when your hog is in the tower, your hog doesn't get affected by the Freeze spell. In this gamemode, every spell you throw, or death damage shall affect you as well. Expect your troops to be zapped, arrowed, frozen, or killed if you play your cards in the wrong way. This should also have its own trophy count. 

#**2x Elixir time + the last two modes suggested above**

So basically 2x Elixir Mirror Mode and 2x Elixir Hardcore. 

#**Clan vs Clan**

This one sounds stupid, but I decided to include it because why not? Kind of like Clan Wars in CoC, this mode consist on having 3 players on your clan searching for a match with another 3 player clan. However, one will be in full control of each tower. Once your tower gets destroyed, you are out of the game. This could work like this:

* You will be handed two cards (at random, and not exactly the same as your opponent)
* Elixir will be shared among each team (so if you drop a Giant Skeleton, it will be 6 elixir that counts for the total of the team)
* You can deselect cards so you can chose which troops your tower should attack (by tapping the enemy troops)
* Your king level will be set to 10. It won't decrease nor increase. 
* Cards will be the cap for the tournament.
* No legendary
* You can actually choose your team so if you know someone trolls, then you won't pick them.


Any other thoughts?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] Another one! iOS 9.3.3 beta 5 released. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone interested in Telegram chat for this sub? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 16:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] This screen is new from B1 or B2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Apple Watch saved my mom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 02:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: At the bottom
______

My mom suffers from allergies of some chemicals found in some detergents. My mom works as a housekeeper in a hotel in Downtown Manhattan and while cleaning a room, she came into contact with one of these chemicals. As you imagine, she gets the reaction cause by the allergies and if she isn't treated quickly, she might go to the hospital

She hurries to ask her manager permission to go outside an anti allergic to the pharmacy that's right besides the hotel she works at. Unfortunately, she leaves her phone in the hotel along with cash/cards to pay for this medicine. 

My mom doesn't know a thing about medicines, so she calls me whenever she is buying one so I can look up what it does and tell her which one is better and as you know, she has left her phone in the hotel so she isn't able to call me. 

During this moment, I text her to check in on her, and the watch vibrates. She was connected to the Wi-Fi of either the Hotel Staff network or the pharmacy's Wi-Fi. She dictates to the Watch that she needed to talk to me, so how can she talk to me if she doesn't have the phone with her. So I call her. She is talking from her Watch and I am talking on my phone. She describes me various medicines for the allergies so I tell her which one is the best one. 

Now is time to pay. She tells she forgot her card and cash upstairs in the Hotel. While she was talking to me, I hopped into her iCloud just in case I needed to Lost Mode her phone. I checked her settings and I noticed that she doesn't have any of her cards on Apple Pay, but mine. So I guide her to pay with my card before we hang up (The call must be ended to pay with A-Pay). 5 minute later she calls me from the pharmacy and tells me that she is getting better and that the reaction of the allergies are slowly going away. 

If she didn't have the Watch, I'm not sure what could have happened. She forgot everything in the Hotel and going back to get it and going downstairs again could have been critical as I said, if her allergies aren't treated fast, she could be sent to the hospital. 

I'm glad I picked up an AW for her!

__________

Okay, this blew up. Let me clarify a few things:

1-) Why does my mom work at a hotel, cleaning, when she knows she is allergic to cleaning utensils? 

She isn't allergic to all of them. But she still works at the hotel, because she wants to provide to her family, one way or the other. She is going to school in the meantime as well, so this is the only job she took in the meantime.

2-) Why doesn't she carry pills?

She just buys the medicine that has the fewest pills. That's on her, I don't know why. Well, either way, she wasn't carrying any that day, unfortunately.

3-) The AW didn't save her. YOU did and the medicine too. 

Okay, I know the title is bad af (I noticed after I posted it). We all put something to save her. Me, her manager, the Watch, the medicine, the guy working at the register, the water she drank with the pills, even the fresh air saved her. Okay? Sorry for the click bait title, it wasn't my intention.

4-) She is stupid/moron/idiot. Why doesn't she know which shit to buy?

First of all, refrain yourself of insulting my mom. I haven't insulted yours, not yourself, nor your family. Okay? I respect everyone's opinion, I respect everyone's family member, but once you insult my mom, you have crossed the line. If you really need to insult someone, insult me (I wouldn't care either way) but do not bring my mom to this. Sounds clear? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this even allowed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 20:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Strategy]/[Guide] Tournaments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, first of all, opinion here, lets get it out of the way: 
#**THIS UPDATE ROCKS! Is the best thing CR has done. Props to you guys /u/clashroyale**

Now, let's talk about tournaments. Tournaments will make you even more addicted to the game, if you are addicted already. You were warned. 

First of all, your location is required to join a tournament or to host one. That's to find tournaments near you. I believe you can also search if no tournament is hosted near you. So this is a good way to get your school to play together, a neighborhood and etc. 

This is my experience playing a tournament of 50 people (Disclaimer, I finished on 32nd place due to reasons... ^^^^I ^^^suck)

- You have to constantly play. There is no doubt about that. Unless you want a chest, you need to play to secure your place. I stopped playing for like 5 mins (I was on 15th place) to get something to eat, and I got dropped to 42nd place. 

- On a tournament of 80 people, the top 40 get trophies. So if you suck at the game (^^^Like ^^^me) then you still have a chance to get a chest. For instance, I got a chest with 8 cards, at 32nd place. 

- It is a great way to get cards if you lose constantly on the regular battles. True, is slower, but hey you still get opportunities to get cards either way.

- You will get notification, in-game if the tournament is about to start. Thanks SC for thinking about this!

- You don't know who you are being matched against. Is random. Unless you remember every deck of those 79 people, then you can't know what they got to play against you. 

- You will be playing in different Arenas, not a specific one. I don't know if it is the one from the host, or based on your tournament trophies, but I played in every arena from 1 to 8 (the new 8, Frozen Peak). 

- It is FUN! 


I'd say to give this a chance. SC really killed it here, so go ahead and try to find an open tournament, I'm sure you will get into one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] Spotify within GTA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 21:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many of you guys (or parents) have cars? A good chunk of you do. Now, if you have  a car that's at least 12 years old, your car could be equipped with a radio that has Bluetooth. That way you can listen to music from your phone, and not from the radio. 

In GTA, most of us have cars that should be equipped with the latest technology. For example, you would think that a T20, a Zentorno, or a X80 should have Bluetooth in the Radio.

You know how Michael has an iPhone, Franklin has an Android, Trevor a Windows Phone, and every character in GTAO has an iPhone as well? All those phones have Bluetooth and can have Spotify installed in them.

Now this is where my idea comes in:

For this idea to work, you will need to be a Spotify Premium as you need [Spotify Connect](https://www.spotify.com/us/connect/) and R* would need to implement the [API](https://developer.spotify.com/spotify-connect-hardware-partners/) (they don't actually need hardware). 

* Whenever you get into a compatible car (think like T20) Spotify Connect kicks in. That way you can control the music from your device or computer. 
* Whenever you get into your own house (only high end), office, or large warehouse, yacht (outside radio and inside radio, if there is one) you should be able to Spotify Connect.
* Modern Aircrafts like the Hydra, Buzzard should have it as well. 

Any other car you don't own, you can't Spoitfy Connect. Stolen car? No, unless you put insurance on it.

Also you could upgrade old cars to have Bluetooth Radio, for a pricy price (you know R*). 


For those who don't have Spotify Premium, Spotify Connect won't be available for you, however you could have a playlist in Spotify where the music could be shuffled, and filled with ads. I believe this will hurt both R* and Spotify economically so if they want, they could exclude this idea (being a free user). 

What do you you guys think?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] Spotify within GTA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 21:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many of you guys (or parents) have cars? A good chunk of you do. Now, if you have  a car that's at least 12 years old, your car could be equipped with a radio that has Bluetooth. That way you can listen to music from your phone, and not from the radio. 

In GTA, most of us have cars that should be equipped with the latest technology. For example, you would think that a T20, a Zentorno, or a X80 should have Bluetooth in the Radio.

You know how Michael has an iPhone, Franklin has an Android, Trevor a Windows Phone, and every character in GTAO has an iPhone as well? All those phones have Bluetooth and can have Spotify installed in them.

Now this is where my idea comes in:

For this idea to work, you will need to be a Spotify Premium as you need [Spotify Connect](https://www.spotify.com/us/connect/) and R* would need to implement the [API](https://developer.spotify.com/spotify-connect-hardware-partners/) (they don't actually need hardware). 

* Whenever you get into a compatible car (think like T20) Spotify Connect kicks in. That way you can control the music from your device or computer. 
* Whenever you get into your own house (only high end), office, or large warehouse, yacht (outside radio and inside radio, if there is one) you should be able to Spotify Connect.
* Modern Aircrafts like the Hydra, Buzzard should have it as well. 

Any other car you don't own, you can't Spoitfy Connect. Stolen car? No, unless you put insurance on it.

Also you could upgrade old cars to have Bluetooth Radio, for a pricy price (you know R*). 


For those who don't have Spotify Premium, Spotify Connect won't be available for you, however you could have a playlist in Spotify where the music could be shuffled, and filled with ads. I believe this will hurt both R* and Spotify economically so if they want, they could exclude this idea (being a free user). 

What do you you guys think?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for opinions before is too late and I regret it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 20:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings /r/cscareerquestions !

I'm a sophomore in college (I haven't started the semester) and I'm worried if I don't take action soon, I will regret it my whole life. So I'm trying to gather as much info as I can so I can know what to do.

Quick background:

3.0 GPA
Study at [John Jay College of Criminal Justice](http://www.jjay.cuny.edu/computer-science-and-information-security-bs)
NYC
I actually like to create things, I love brainstorming. However, I think if I am the one who search for security issues in a program I might mess up and my carreer will be ruined

__________
As suggested by this subreddit, I might to transfer to [City College](https://www.ccny.cuny.edu/sites/default/files/compsci/upload/Requirements-for-B-S-Computer-Science-Spring-2012.pdf) as John Jay focuses on forensics and cybersecurity.

Upon researching further, the salaries for being a Cyber Security Analyst as opposed to being a Software Engineer is lower (about $20k in average). 

I still want to research things further to take a final decision so I have a few questions:

1-) Any website I can see what current graduates of my school are doing?
2-) Any website to see the jobs available for each field as well as salary?
3-) Graduates of NYC, how hard was it to get a job in the field?
4-) Anything else I should be aware and should be doing to achieve success being in the field?

Thanks in advance :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: PlayStation VR preorders opening one last time tomorrow at 7:00 AM Pacific: play.st/2948rUL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 21:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Another beta, iOS 9.3.3 beta 4 released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] This game is good, but I still like to hear from CR about these issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, please put down your downvotes pitchforks and any other pitchfork you may have. Hear me out. 

Disclaimer: I'm not ranting/whining. This is just a game. It won't affect me at all. Just giving my thoughts. 

We all complained about emotes right? Reddit, Twitter, SC forums, and Facebook users were "suffocating" Clash Royale into removing them. They got the signal and they finally spoke up. Not in our favor, but hey, we at least wanted to hear from them. I know I did. 

Now, they have not spoken on any other general issues aside from cards. I believe the reason is because we haven't spoken up, and this is what I am trying to do with this shitpost (yeah, I know, it is one. But hey, no one knows what might come out of this)

#**Matchmaking**

This is an important piece of the game. It prevents you as a level 1 in A1 to battle a Level 13 on A8.

As Supercell have stated here in the sub and [on their website](https://supercell.helpshift.com/a/clash-royale/?s=battle f=how-does-the-matchmaking-work p=web), matchmaking is based on trophies **ALONE**. 

That right there, for me is a big issue. This makes it possible so that a level 13 can drop to A1 and troll new players. This also makes people drop so they can have a chance to be in Royale TV. I can't believe a $2.3 billion company didn't think about this and on the 5 months the game has been out to the public they haven't addressed this. 

Constant complaining won't help you know, so how about suggesting something?

##I suggest that matchmaking's algorithm isn't changed. Is good the way it is. However, I suggest "downgrading" cards and the level of the king. 

 "Specifically how, subject6752?" 

Well, let's think about something. In A1, you expect level 1, 2 players right? How about you will be still be Level 13 (for example, but your health and power will be downgraded to that of a level 2 king. Just my thought. Same concept with cards. 

In addition, if you as a Level 13 have a Dark Prince, the card will be taken out of your deck for this fight and replaced with a card in the same category (epics, for example) as the dark prince is obtainable in A7, not on A1. If you do have a balloon, you could use that as is just something from one arena higher A1, not 6. 

**2nd solution:**When a level 13 reaches A6 per say, whatever loses he gets, he loses 0 trophies, but the opponent gains their trophies they were supposed to earn. That way that level 13 can't drop to lower Arenas. 

#**"Wi-Fi card"**

Now this one seriosuly affects me. How come I'm disconnected from the game to drop my troops, yet I can see my opponent wrecking the sh** out of my towers?

I have researched this high and low but I can't find the root of this issue. What I mainly looked for is whether the games are actually hosted server side (SC side) or from one of the players.

The issue has been present since January (soft launch) and no word from SC in this issue. The most funny thing is that whenever a player contacts support about it, it is always blamed on our connection. They refuse to acknowledge the issue. Heck even the [website blames it on our connection](https://supercell.helpshift.com/a/clash-royale/?s=connection-performance f=why-do-i-keep-losing-connection p=web)

I can't even suggest a solution if I don't know where the problem comes from. I just hope SC takes care of this issue. 


Anyone else have ideas to solve the issues within the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Model S owner builds homemade autonomous "metal snake-like" charger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Watch OS 3, is there finally a way to see the Apple Pay transactions made with the watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 01:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate having to go to my bank app to check the transaction when I could do it right from the Wallet app. I can see my phone's transaction there, so why I can't see the Watch's transaction somewhere? 

If it is not on OS 3, can we all send a feedback to Apple? http://www.apple.com/feedback/watch.html 

Maybe include that every transaction is on the Wallet app and there is an iPhone besides the transaction, if it was made through the iPhone, or the AW when it is made from the AW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] How do I stop the Bigboss repo from directing me to sketchy/scammy websites and from directing me to the App Store? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 01:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

Just ran Semi Restore and I'm sure I didn't have this problem before (maybe a tweak stopped it?). 

What can I go to stop this from happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] I want to semi-restore, but I have a few questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

1-) When I restore, will I be met with the setup.app (To set up the phone as new)?

2-) I was thinking to restore and start from scratch, except that I want all my messages to be there. Is there a way to edit the iTunes backup to achieve this?

3-) Anything else I should be aware of when doing this process?

Thanks in advance :)

EDIT: Downvotes fro asking a genuine question. Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The barcode with the serial number on the back of my DS4 is messed up. If I ever need warranty service, how will it work out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings /r/PS4!

I have bought a PS4 in November. [It is the BO3 Limited Edition](http://www.theblackopsiii.com/images/news/22-playstation-4-limited-edition-large.jpg). The barcode of the remote is all [messed up and the sticky is peeling off](https://imgur.com/a/fGMMO) and there is no way to get the serial number out of it. 

If I ever need service in this remote, how will it work out? When replaced, will I get those standard remotes or will I get one similar to this? 

Thanks in advance :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Strategy] / [Deck] This deck got me to A7 + Few Strategies + clan to train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I will break up the post into three parts. The first one will be about a training clan I made for you guys only, the second one will be about my deck that bumped me from A4 to A7, and the third one will be a few strategies I use. 

### Unofficial /r/CR clan!

**Disclaimer:** This clan **is not** affiliated with SC, CR, or the mods/owners of /r/ClashRoyale. Do not send messages to the mods or SC complaining that the clan is full or you were kicked out. If any problems always ask me in a comment or private message. 

The purpose of me creating this clan is because the trainers weren't good enough to give the feeling of training (did that make sense? :/ ) I mean for fucks sake these trainers use lightning on skeletons (R.I.P Larry) which is something a normal player wouldn't do. 

So the way I want this to work is that I will take in 48 people everyday to the clan (I have two accounts), after 24 hours has passed, everyone will get kicked so that new people can come and train. I will contact the mods here to see if we can work something out like putting it on the sidebar or something along those lines. I hope to see you there! I will be on all day to help you guys out (I'm level 9 on one account and level 6 on another).

In this clan share replays and have friendly battles. You will get feedback from all this and you will be better at the game :)

#**The name of the clan is "/r/CR training" . Clan tag is LLUP9GG**

I just created another account and I will get to level 3 to create /r/CR training 2 so watch out for an edit when that's done


#To join use the word "doot" or put my username in the invitation. This is so that I can know you guys come from here
___________

#Deck

I built this deck when I struggle to get past A4. I would watch YT videos and etc, but these decks wouldn't work so I made up my own. There are some cards I use that are obtainable from higher arenas, but I will suggest a replacement when I mention them. 

* Hog Rider: This one is vital to my push. He has never failed me. When I mention the other cards I will tell you who should he go with. Always place him in front of a supportive troop.

* Mini Pekka: To be honest, I started to use her recently. I don't remember who was in her place, but now she has taken over (3). She is also vital to my push as she deals great damage and the HR and her will take down a tower if you aren't fast enough. I also use her for defensive purposes, like to kill a Giant Skeleton. As with the HR, always place in front of supportive troops.

* Minion Horde: Easily countered by arrows, but when they can clean the troops in your area real quick. I mainly use them for defense or when I know my opponent doesn't have arrows and he have use a fireball or other spell before. I also use them when I have more elixir than my opponent (more on this on strategy). When I know my opponent has no elixir, I use them with the hog or MP so they waste their effort trying to kill them, but at the same time leaving the hog or MP alive. I can expand this more if you guys want.

* Elixir Collector: The name told you everything. You can get this in A6, however, I used an spell when I didn't have this. I used either Rage or Freeze. You might as well use another troop here also like a Giant but my top choice will be a spell. Also when placing it, try to put it as close as your king as possible. Why? Because some people tend to fireball it at the same time hitting my king and that increases my defense. Also, place it down when the 2x elixir time comes. You will thank me later.

* Wizard: Obtainable at A5. I use him for defense and as a support troop for the MP and HR. As a defensive troop, I use him to kill barbs,or Minion Hordes. He is weak against Prince and Valks so use another defensive troop for that matter.

* Musketeer: Like the Wizard, I use her for defense and as a support troop for the MP and HR. As a defensive troop, I use her to kill barbs, valks, and more however she is weak against Prince and Valks so be wise and expect everything.

* Spear Goblins: I use these three for distraction only. That way I have more time to kill troops coming my way with the wiz, MP, or musketeer.

* Arrows: I always recommend carrying a spell with you. AT ALL TIMES. My top choice will be this one as you can take out Minion Hordes, or Skeletons and a bonus is that is cheap when the wiz isn't available. You can also replace it with a fireball, but my go is with the arrows. 

___________

#Strategy

* You are given 4 minutes to battle. Why rush? Keep calm and do your push whenever you have the opportunity. Take it one step at a time. Your opponent most likely will rush to take you down and will place them in a elixir disadvantage.

* Use the 2x elixir time wisely. Don't be like this: http://imgur.com/3uGcK4Z . Just try to get as much defensive troops as you can on one side only. Then when the time comes, release a hog or a MP to make the push. Also try to make your opponent go at an elixir disadvantage if possible.

* If you have to hold on to having 10 elixir, [DO IT!](http://imgur.com/gallery/5P3yozA). It can help sometimes.

* Don't freak out when your opponent has cards higher than yours. I don't know why this is part of my strategy, but hey, it helps. 

* Always drag the troops out of the dock (that's how I call it :p). Do not tap it and then tap the field because things can go wrong and you can be in a disadvantage real quick. 

* Sometimes try to let the enemy troops have a hit on your tower so they don't kill your defensive troops and you don't get messed up. This is what I do when I am against prince decks.

* Always release troops behind your tower. This can help you gain elixir while your troops gets to the bridge

* Last one, **think**. Think. Think. Don't go all crazy releasing everything at once or defending your side with some non-helpful troops. Think!!!! A MP can easily take down a wizard, so rather than putting down a wiz to counter your opponent's wiz, use your MP. THINKKKKKKKKKKKK!!!!!!

___________________

I hope I helped you guys and see you in the clan :)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have written an email to R* in regards to the new update. I encourage to do the same so we can see some changes at least. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys,

I have written an email to R*, however I haven't send it yet as I will include a link to this post and they look at your feedback too. My email is about the new update, Felony and Finance.

My concern is about the griefers and how quick you can lose money if you aren't careful or you are a solo player.

This morning, I had my first package destroyed (from my own company. I have seen packages being destroyed when working as a Associate). I had to pick up the package on a police van, which is armored like the Kuruma. Everything went fine until I was 0.2 miles away from my warehouse. A level 20 approaches me and crashes me from behind. In a sudden turn of events, I had a sticky bomb planted in the back of the van. **Boom** there I go, I'm dead and my cargo is gone. Just one sticky bomb to end my life and destroy my cargo. 

Now, if one sticky bomb could destroy my cargo, imagine how effortless will be to destroy the cargo on a Buzzard (which is quickly accessible as a CEO/VIP), or a Hydra. A quick lock-on on the van I'm driving, shoot, and that's it. 

As a associate, I had the chance to drive a van, like the [Burrito](http://gta.wikia.com/wiki/Burrito), again, one explosive shot could destroy it. And on top of that, the van is slow as fuck.

Based on what I have experienced and what other have said here, /r/GTAV and /r/gtaonline, I believe R* made this update but without thinking about balancing it so that everybody can be happy. 

I have a few proposed solution listed on my email and they are:

* **Make use of our own cars.**

- I believe all cars are "balanced" in this game. Either you have a car that's armored yet you can blow it up with one explosive, or you have a explosive-resistant vehicles that doesn't protect you from bullets. Never both. This is good because you might want to use the Insurgent, or the Kuruma to do cargo missions. Also, they are wayy faster than the vehicles provided by R* in these missions. 

* **Let us carry more than one crate if we are using our own car. We can open our trunks and frunks (in some cars), why not give use to them?**

- Seriously? Who thought it was smart to do 3 trips to pick up crates on our own car? Can we have the option to put all crate in the passenger seat or the trunk/frunk? 

* **Have a 10-minute cooldown for jets**

- A griefer can pick up a Hydra, kill and destroy, crash himself/herself and/or die in hands of another player, and pick up another one right away. This is BS. I believe there should be a countdown when picking up Hydras (or other helicopters) after you destroy it, like SecuroServ does it. Oh and make the player disable passive mode when entering a jet. I don't understand why passive mode is disabled when I enter the heli on my yacht yet passive mode is still enabled when someone enters a jet. 

* **Passive mode users shouldn't be allowed to disable passive mode when near a cargo**

- A player has been chasing me when I have a cargo, while in passive mode. After chasing me for a while and keeping close to me, he disables passive mode and throws a sticky bomb. There I go, dead. 

* **The whole lobby shouldn't be aware I have a Special Cargo. They should play a hacking game before they can figure out my location.**

- This one is self-explanatory. 



--------

Anything else R* should fix in this update? I sent them an email with a link to this post. If they open it (which I'm hopeful they will) they can see more feedback and work on it. Also, I encourage you to send them an email, with a link to this post to this email: GTAOnline@rockstargames.com

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Legere's #tweetstorm (6-15-16) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 00:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1-) #tweetstorm update time! Already over 2M+ downloads of #TMobileTuesdays!! So far, MASSIVE success!! The #uncarrier s thanking you!

2-) Time to change it up! Next week, were switching out @Dominos   giving you another free ride on @lyft (avail through Thurs) - $15 value!

3-) OMG @TMobile customers slammed @dominos stores!! They saw 3x   4x in a typical day and cant handle the volume. (Pic attached, pic here: https://imgur.com/1hWwggh) 

4-) Basically, @tmobile customers love @dominos pizza so much, you broke them! 

5-) So much demand from our amazing customers for @dominos pizzas, they cant keep up   we cant thank you w/pizza next week.

6-) Next week you #getthanked w/ a free Vudu rental, Frosty   $20 of free stuff on http://MLB.com !  Were adding the Lyft ride too!

7-) But #wewontstop thanking you! We have other partners lined up and will share soon! Stay tuned and be ready to #getthanked!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resources found in macOS Sierra hint at upcoming OLED touch bar, Touch ID support, more | 9to5Mac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 04:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm attending John Jay College and I am pursuing a CS degree. Can someone tell me if their curriculum for CS is good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 01:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings! 

I'm currently enrolled at John Jay College of Criminal Justice, and by name, you will notice they specialize in Law and the like. 

They do have a Computer Science program, I believe it isn't the strongest one (on every aspect, tutoring, professors and etc), but what I don't know is if the CS courses offered at the college will prepare me for the jobs in this field. 

Link to the college page about CS: http://www.jjay.cuny.edu/computer-science-and-information-security-bs

Link to info about the courses offered at the school (The computer science course are called "CSCI"): http://johnjay.jjay.cuny.edu/bulletins/undergraduatebulletin20142015.pdf#page=211

Am I good at this school or should I look at other schools to transfer to?

Thanks in advance :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How bad is working as a walker in NYC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I applied to Postmates to see how it goes, but knowing that this is NYC I don't know if I can work more than a few days as I don't have a bike, no car, no skateboard, or the like. Just my two feet.

Any insight in this matter? I appreciate the help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How quick have you 3-star your opponent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me? 50 seconds. 

How about you guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Google app turns Live Photos into animated GIFs and movies with cinematic backgrounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [x-post /r/gtaonline] For those who aren't too sure about the office, I did a quick demo/walkthrough of the Maze Bank office : gtaonline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [x-post /r/gtaonline] For those who aren't too sure about the office, I did a quick demo/walkthrough of the Maze Bank office : gtaonline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those who aren't too sure about the office, I did a quick demo/walkthrough of the Maze Bank office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the video: https://youtu.be/gDtPu00aH-w

Let me know if you want any demo for anything. I'm trying to get a decent lobby so I can do jobs to show you guys. Either way, let me know what you want to see :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which office is the best one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 13:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who have the money and bought offices? Which one is a good one? I'm itching to get the Maze Bank Tower one but I'm not sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Less than 24 hours for the DLC coming out. Are you ready? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 16:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I am. I got 11mil and getting more via Heists and jobs.

Are you guys ready? 

EDIT: If ya'll got any Heists on PS4 let me know and let's knock them out. I don't have a mic, but I know what to do and I know all the tips/cheats/glitches to each Heist. Just please enable Player Saved Outfit and put it Hard when you invite me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ASUS has my computer for 2 months already. How should I proceed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 23:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. Long time lurker, first time poster.

On Oct 2015 I had to send my computer for service for a series of issues including the display. I got it back, however the Touch Panel of my Notebook wasn't working as expected. I tapped on my display and it invoked a series of ghost touches. I contacted Asus about it and they advised me to disable the touch driver as I didn't want to send the computer for service due to college constraints.

5 months later, the display of the computer stopped working for no reason whatsoever. The computer wasn't dropped, nor liquid was spilled. It just stopped working. I contacted ASUS in regards to this issue and they asked me to send the computer in. That was in March. 

Fast forward to April, I've heard nothing at all from them. I contacted them and I spoke to a manager (whose info I unfortunately don't have) who said my fees in regards to the RMA will be waived as I had this issue "coming" (as per his words) and that I needed to wait more as the parts needed to  fix my notebook aren't on their facilities. 

Fast forwarding to May, I received an email asking me to pay $129 so I can get a replacement for my computer. As instructed by the manager I spoke about, I disputed the repair cost. ASUS says that there are no notes for what the manages said to me, so I have to pay either way. 

I contacted them again today and they still want me to pay and that the computer will be held for longer until I finish disputing this transaction. 

What's the best course of action I can take in this case? If anyone is wondering my computer is a ASUS X550CA

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have never heard this here, but anyone else think that the Giant Skeleton is way too OP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 01:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This troop is a tanky unit, like the Giant. His attack is over a 100, like the Giant, yet he drops a fucking bomb that does 7x his damage?

True he is easily distracted, but he does 100+ damage. He can kill any troop real quick if the other troop isn't a tank like him and if your opponent has Arrows and Fireballs then consider yourself rekt as the G-Skeleton can get to your tower quicker.

I think the Giant Skeleton offers too much for 6 elixir. But wayyy too much
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I currently bank with BoA. I'm pretty tired of them so I'm looking at other banks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys. Quick facts about my financial situation:

- 18 years 
- Unemployed
-College Student
- Receive about $4k a year
- Monthly expenses are ~$130
- No savings account whatsoever

I currently have a BoA checking's account. Specifically this one: https://www.bankofamerica.com/deposits/checking/personal-checking-account.go

And I also have a Credit Card from them (Limit $600 - 21.24% APR. Lowest they have in BoA at the moment according to them): 
https://www.bankofamerica.com/credit-cards/products/bankamericard-credit-card/

I am not proud of them per say. Way too many issues like not having the ability to add my card to Apple Pay on my phone or Apple Watch or blocking my card when I am making a large purchase right when I am in the line of the store. I've been contemplating switching over to Chase, or CitiBank. I'm leaning towards Chase for both services, Debit and CC.

For the Debit one, I'm leaning towards this account: https://www.chase.com/checking/student-checking
For the Credit one, I'm not too sure, but I think this will do: https://creditcards.chase.com/credit-cards/chase-freedom-unlimited.aspx?CELL=6TKV

**I only use my CC to pay for things that I would otherwise buy with Debit so that I can start building credit.**

If I decide to make the change, how should I proceed? I owe ~$150 on my CC which is due on at the start of July and I am able to pay for. By closing my CC, will that affect my score? How about opening one?

Anything I should watch out for?

Thanks in advance! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] New Update for Sharefactory: Track 2, Green Screen and More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First AW Custom Bootlogo by @maximehip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] Should I upgrade my TH to 9 in these conditions? Will it affect my clan's war weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Model S is priced at $25k but is messed up. How much do you think one mist pay extra to fix everything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 02:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] Clash of Clans on Twitter: "New optional update available! Be sure to get the latest version from the AppStore and GooglePlay! More info: https://t.co/L9VRVQuUsa" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got my permit. I'm confused on when I am allowed to upgrade to a Senior License. Can you guys help me out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello /r/AskNYC !

Today I passed the written exam for the learner's permit and I'm all set, I can now drive if I have someone over 21 and that has the senior license with them.

However, I've been looking into upgrading my license to the senior's one and I have been told that I need to wait 6 months in order to do so which is where my doubts come in.

On the DMV's office it says: 

" 
**How long do I have to wait after I get my learner permit to take my road test?**

If you are under age 18, you must wait at least 6 months from the date you received your learner permit to schedule your road test. "

I have 18 years old so I don't fit in that category so that means I don't have to wait those 6 months? Or I do have to wait? 

Also, what's a good and cheap school that could teach me how to drive and provide a car for the road test? Preferably one that is in Bronx, NY or in Manhattan

PS: I know I have to drive for at least 50 hours and that has to be signed by my parents or a school I can attend. I have that covered either way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello PF, I barely have 9 hours to make a decision. Can you help me out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought two items, one for $13, and another for $32 via Paypal. The tracking number for both items show that they have been delivered, however I didn't get them. I used Pay After Delivery (PAD), so that I have time to check out my items and pay with my credit card (My debit is linked to Paypal) as I don't have enough funds in my debit to pay for both items and if I get charged, my Debit will go to negative.

First seller was a dick about the situation, so he told me to rely in other terms of getting help, he is not helping me. The second seller didn't even replied to my message.

I called USPS for this matter and they didn't help at all. I called the Central and they referred me to my local USPS Office, where I didn't get any help. They are shit and known for not helping out. 

So I contacted Paypal for this issue and they opened a claim, not a dispute. A few hours later, I get two emails saying that I lost the claim as the sellers provided "valid" proof that I "got" my items.

So I appealed those two claims and I got denied. So I once again called and a Paypal representative told me that my card won't be charged, and that I **won't** be charged and that I should see money in my Paypal balance as a compensation for all my trouble.

Today I woke up to two charges from Paypal, the $32 one and the $13 one, making my debit card go negative. I immediately called Paypal and told them what happened and to see the notes from yesterday (when they told me I won't be charged) and they said that won't happen. They basically said, in cute little words those customer representatives tell you, that I'm screwed and that I lost my money and my item and that I should deal with the bank myself. I also asked them what will happen if I file a chargeback and they said nothing will happen. 

**Question:** Am I safe by doing a chargeback? I have 9 hours to decide whether I should do it or no, but I'm scared of future debt collectors or something along those lines. Paypal said I'm screwed, the sellers too, as well as USPS. What should I do?

**TL;DR:** I used Paypal's pay after delivery to buy some items. Items never got to my hands, so USPS said they can't help, sellers won't help me and Paypal said that I "got" my package so they can't do anything. My only option is to do a charge back and my debit card is negative and i have 9 hours to decide what I want to do if I want to avoid any overdraft fees. Should I do a chargeback and just forget about it? Should I do something else?

**EDIT1:** I just finished speaking with my debit card provider and they canceled out the charges, so I won't be facing overdraft fees. 

I also wanted to clarify that I do have the money to pay for my items, the problem is during the 2 weeks Paypal gives me for PAD, I had a erroneous transaction from Apple for $700, which will come to my card in a few days, thus the reason I wanted to pay with my CC in the meantime before they charged my debit card.

Other have suggested that I speak to a manager from Paypal and I am calling them right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Balance Changes Coming (5/18) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 18:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Misc] UI changes to the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I didn't see a post about it here, so I decided to make one.

Some new UI changes include: 

**Battle results and rewards with chests slot available:** http://imgur.com/3RGEKUi

**Battle results and rewards with no chest slot available**: http://imgur.com/3WT5pVn

**UI change with the player's information (See top left)**: http://imgur.com/yG3f13F

**"Match Over" alert that pops up for a split second after the match is done, adding a +1/2/3 on the crown chest animation and the gold at then end (see video):** https://youtu.be/8vLecu5qy6c

**New Mini Pekka startup sound:** https://youtu.be/xdw8lLpC19o

**New Freeze animation/look:** http://imgur.com/qhg8dCg

Other than the shop, and the TV Royale (you guys have seen these for a few days), what other things have you noticed that are new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases the fourth beta of 9.3.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What side projects I can do with C++ during the summer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from learning Swift, I plan on working on side projects for C++ so I can have more practice to prepare for the future. 

What projects I can work on for C++ that could be a really good addition to my resume? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get some help with iMovie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I'm doing a Final Project for my English and I am in charge of editing a video by myself. I actually never edited something like this before so I might miss out on obvious settings. Sorry :(

I have two questions:

1-) How do I make so that I can make a news report and one of the section is a phone call? I might record my phone if possible but all the design and splitting, how do I do that? I can't get an example now if I come across one I will update my post

2-) How can I make a news intro with my own logo, animation and text? 

Thank you so much in advance :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/JohnJay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 22:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This player followed me around the city with his friend to kill me. I enjoyed that this happened to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 05:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best advice you could give to a sophomore? + a few other questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, little background:

I'm finishing up my first year at college. I took one computer class so far, which is "Intro to CS", where I learned C++. I want to learn Swift in the next couple of months, by myself, so that I can get an internship in the future, knowing more languages. I am a really good learner, but my problem that I'm lazy and I often lose motivation, but if I apply myself to my studies, I can get pretty good grades.. There is nothing else I'm really good at but computers. 

Now my questions:

1-) I stutter. My stutter is from moderate, to severe. Throughout the year my stutter becomes light, but is not that often nor it last for a long period of time. As a Software Engineer, how much talking do you have to do? How is this going to affect my interviews?

2-) I really have no connections to no one. I'm solo on this. Am I going to possibly get far like that? 

3-) How do keep yourself motivated? How do you practice coding at home?

4-) What are the languages I MUST learn in the next 3 years?


Thank you so much in advance :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Anyone's else iMessage acting up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some messages it says "Not Delivered" or messages won't sync across my Mac, iPad, and iPhone + Apple Watch. 

Not sure if it is my tweaks on the iPhone that could prevent this, I recently installed  RemoteMessages so I don't if that is the culprit. I tried uninstalling it, but the issue persists.

I currently have Paragon, Instabetter, SilentMessenger and RemoteMessages installed. Nothing else, aside from the default packages from Cydia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Upcoming] IGExperiments by CP Digital Darkroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Features: 

* https://twitter.com/cpdigdarkroom/status/725455775578095616
* https://twitter.com/cpdigdarkroom/status/725455379916840964
* https://twitter.com/cpdigdarkroom/status/725453960904118272
* https://twitter.com/cpdigdarkroom/status/725444771385335808
* https://twitter.com/cpdigdarkroom/status/725443534376042496

Thank you for your work /u/cpdigitaldarkroom ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion][Release] Apple releases iOS 9.3.2 Beta 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] Various game modes-- Hardcore, and speed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 15:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My idea is the following: 

**Hardcore:** You know when you have placed a bomb tower, or a mortar, if your troops are close to it, they won't get hit? Also, when throwing a fireball to help your troops against minions or whatever, they don't get hit? 

In this mode, I was thinking whatever Splash Damage troops/building do, can affect your own troops. So if a mortar is on your side helping your troops on the other side, they will get affected too. 

In terms of Spell, the same thing can happen. If you throw a Freeze Spell, expect your troops to be Frozen. Or Zapped. Or killed with Fireball/Rocket.

**Speed:** Sometimes I like watching my replays in 4X. They look cool so I thought why don't SC implement a mode where everything is fast paced? Maybe add the 1/2X speed and the 2X speed. Of course, SC could also speed up Elixir, or not. It will be fun regardless.

I'm think this could be like BTD Battles, where you have different Arenas, with different conditions where hardcore could be one of them alongside other ideas/conditions. 

What you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 9.3 for 32-bit devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I plan to learn Swift in 3 months (Summer). What/where I can learn from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: I just noticed the tile is confusing. I meant that I wanted to learn Swift in 3 months, as in having 3 months to learn it. I don't need to wait 3 months.


Hey guys! Little background of me. I am majoring in CS and I am almost done with my first year of college. I already know C++, and I don't think my college has a course to learn Swift so I want to learn it in my own. 

I have looked for good apps/websites that could teach me Swift. I have a few  apps downloaded in my iPad, but I don't feel they are complete and I won't get as much information in my 3 months of vacation (Summer). 

Any recommendations of good websites/apps that won't break the bank and that could teach me how to code in Swift and as well as help me design apps for iOS ? I have heard of Design+Code, but I'm not sure if the book will support/teach me about future iterations of iOS and Xcode. I will need to buy the book ($150) and Sketch which costs ($100) and it will suck if iOS 10 brings something new that the book won't teach me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C++] I need some help before I hit myself for not figuring it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 01:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I'm currently taking a CS class, which is Introduction to Computer Science. In this course we are learning C++. Currently I was given an assignment where I had to: 

 "Write a program that for each of 5 persons has the user  enter name, city, telephone number.    Each of of these should be a string.  In the loop after user enters these, concatenate these with spaces in between to form one string and put the resulting string  into an array of size 5.       Use another loop to output the array ."

I did it with the following code: 

    #include iostream
    #include string

    using namespace std;

    int main ()

    {
    int k = 0, name1=0, name2=0, city=0, tel=0,a=0, b=0;
    int rec[k] = {name1 + name2 + city + tel};
	
	
    while (k++5)
	
    {
    string name1, name2, city, a, b, phone, person;
		
    cout"Enter first name"endl;
    cinname1;

    cout"Enter last name"endl;
    cinname2;
		
    cout"Enter a city"endl;
    cincity;
		
    cout"Enter phone number"endl;
    cinphone;
		
    a="  ";
    b=" ";
    person= rec[k];
    coutpersonendl;
    }
	
    system("pause");
    return 0;
	
    }

However, when I compile this, CMD crashes when running the exe file. I need to test this code so I can do my next assignment which is to: "Modify your "array of strings" assignment to save the data to a file, Use the document at the end of CONTENT  "saving to file".   USE YOUR  NAME FOR FILE NAME, NOT example from class"

Without testing the code above I got this so I can save it to a file, which I believe is wrong too, but here it is: 

 "#include iostream
#include fstream
#include string
using namespace std;

int main () 

{
	int k = 0, name1=0, name2=0, city=0, tel=0,a=0, b=0;
	int rec[k] = {name1 + name2 + city + tel};
	
	
	while (k++5)
	
	{
		string name1, name2, city, a, b, phone, person;
		
		cout"Enter first name"endl;
		cinname1;
		
		cout"Enter last name"endl;
		cinname2;
		
		cout"Enter a city"endl;
		cincity;
		
		cout"Enter phone number"endl;
		cinphone;
		
		a="  ";
		b=" ";
		person= rec[k];
		coutpersonendl;
	}
	



    
    string record = rec[k];
    
    ofstream myfile;
    myfile.open ("EXJRBXNY.txt", ios::app);
    myfilerecordendl;
    myfile.close();
    
    system("pause");
    return 0;
}


Any help is appreciated. Thank you in advance :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] Apple stops signing iOS 9.3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can sign in into the App Store and iCloud on Mac OS X 10.11, but I can't log in to iMessage and Facetime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 17:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone had success in logging in to one of those services when running Mac OS on VMware? If it helps, I'm running the latest version, VMware 12.1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA-- Ask PlayStation on Twitter: "Routine PSN maintenance Monday 4/18, 9:30pm - 11:30pm PDT. More details can be found here: https://t.co/hWat42L736" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Ask] [Humor] I just lost my 20th consecutive match. AMA :p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 19:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all seriousness. 

I was in the 1300 trophy range, with the following deck

* Freeze
* Rocket
* Balloon
* Arrow
* Minion Hodge
* Mini Pekka
* Goblin Hut
* Baby Dragon

I had my a few win streaks (max 6) before losing one or two matches but the game just flat out turned against me and I lost 20 times already. I don't even change the way I play. What's the most reasonable explanation for this?

Now I'm sitting at 967 trophies in A3. Nice :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 325k cars or ~$14B in preorders in first week. Only 5% ordered max of two, suggesting low levels of speculation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 18:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple releases the first seed of WatchOS 2.2.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 18:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] Apple releases the first 9.3.2 beta seed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 18:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 9.2.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [x-post from /r/LosSantosAutoClubPS4] We are having a car meeting tomorrow night to show off our new cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **THIS IS ON PS4, IF YOU HAVE OTHER PLATFORMS CHECK OUT OTHER SUBS**

I hope this is okay to post here :)

Tomorrow, because of the new [DLC](http://www.rockstargames.com/newswire/article/52594/gta-online-tornado-week-lowrider-bonuses-new-sumo-maps)  we are having a car meetup. If you are interested, comment in this [post](https://www.reddit.com/r/LosSantosAutoClubPS4/comments/4ct488/lowrider_love_bennys_april_5th_9pm_est_youre/) so the Host can get your PSN ID and you know what to do :)

We hope to see you there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile introduces Binge On-Up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
