<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1093</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 05) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DATE] It is now June. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is now June. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Ask MTGFinance Anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a weekly thread to ask ask questions. Questions about schedules, rating trades, what to do with your cards you pulled, or anything you might feel we can help you with goes here. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Discussion Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, and welcome to the discussion thread! This thread is for accomplishments, simple questions, and informal discussion about cubing!

No question is stupid here. If you have a question, *ask it!*

Join the /r/cubers Discordapp group [here](https://discord.gg/EdYq6CY)!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Quick Questions Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this thread you can ask all kinds of questions you always wanted to ask without feeling like a total fool.

No matter if it's short Google-able stuff or a setting/skill in-game that you don't understand or a hardware recommendation, feel free to try your luck in here.

Trolling or making fun of people in here will be punished extra harshly! Please report such behavior.

For the purpose of helping people, make sure **the comments are sorted by "new"** in this thread.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What we're Watching Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets take some time and relax with some videos. What are you watching that is not your own video? Big channel, small channel, recommend your favourites to us!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Question/Discussion Thread for May 10 to May 16, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Important links:

[2017 J.League Guide](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccer/comments/5wk3n9/nokels_2017_jleague_guide/)
 
[2017 J.League Resource Guide](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccer/comments/5uh3u6/nokels_jleague_resource_guide_2017_livestreams/)
 
[Internet Streaming Guide](https://www.reddit.com/r/JLeague/wiki/livestreams)

[Japanese Soccer Schedule](http://www.reddit.com/r/Jleague/wiki/schedule#wiki_match_alert.3A) - Updated regularly by /u/DoaraChan

[/r/JLeague On Twitter](https://twitter.com/JLeagueReddit)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Roundup! May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether you are a local, or a visitor - Charleston has plenty of events to offer on the weekend. Several media outlets maintain event calendars that offer up a good starting place to find something to do.  
- [Charleston City Paper](http://www.charlestoncitypaper.com/charleston/EventSearch?narrowByDate=This%20Weekend)  
- [CHSBeer](http://chsbeer.org/events)  
- [chs-tonight](http://chs-tonight.com/)  
- [Metronome](http://metronomecharleston.com/calendar/)  
- [HolyCitySinner](http://www.holycitysinner.com/events/)  
- [Post   Courier](http://www.postandcourier.com/section/search facet.filter=Keywords:Things%20to%20Do)  
- [Charleston CVB](http://www.charlestoncvb.com/visitors/events_news/charleston-events/)  
  
       
Have a question about any of these events? Know of something not on these lists? Want to make plans with your fellow redditors by arranging an impromptu meetup?  Have an event that you want to shamelessly self-promote? This is the thread for you! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Questions - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is for simple style questions that don't warrant their own thread

(although we strongly suggest checking the sidebar and the wiki before posting!)

Fit checks and "Help me find a pair of Jeans that has X, Y, and Z" questions are a great use of this thread.

If you have questions about how your jeans fit, about a particular fabric, when is this jean coming out, where can I find jean X to try on in state Y, what jeans have this fit with these measurements, what jeans fade the fastext, what jeans fade the slowest.

No question is too simple for Simple Questions. Bashing people will not be tolerated. And "Read the Sidebar" is not a valid answer here!

Also we recommend sorting this thread by new comments.

Be Helpful!

Be Civil!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ask Dumb Questions + Newbies Welcoming Wednesday  (2017.05.10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to /r/RocketLeague's Ask Dumb Questions and Newbie Welcoming Wednesday! 

You can use this post to ask any questions you may have about Rocket League, from advice to controls, any question regarding the game is encouraged. Feel free to introduce yourself if you're new and would like to make friends to play with, so welcome all!

Check out the beginner's megalist of information [here!](https://www.reddit.com/r/RocketLeague/comments/3y73om/huge_link_list_for_beginners_and_advanced_players/)

[Want to see our previous threads? Click here!](https://www.reddit.com/r/RocketLeague/search?q=welcoming+wednesday restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PSA] Wonder Trade Wednesday! #WTW -- May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder Trade Wednesday #WTW is the weekly event where you send out your favorite Pokemon and the best of the best for others to enjoy and share. Its the community's attempt to give back to other Wonder Traders and have one day dedicated solely to Wonder Trading!

*This submission is an open format, Reddit Account Age or Friend Codes in your user Flair is not required to comment! Please read and understand our [Rules](https://www.reddit.com/r/WonderTrade/wiki/rules) and know that any violations that would notify a persons inbox will not be tolerated.*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Winning Wednesdays (Week of May 10) - Ask /r/spikes Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking a nod from the successful "Tutor Tuesdays" over at /r/magictcg, we spikes have decided to begin our own series of "Ask us anything" posts. Every Wednesday is your chance to ask that question that's been bugging you without fear of downvotes, ridicule, etc...as long as it involves something relating to a spike (Yes, you can even ask what a Spike is...although I assume you know that at this point!). 

The Moderators came to the conclusion that we needed a weekly thread to 1) benefit the group as a whole, and 2) reduce the number of similar posts we see on a daily basis that can be rectified with a weekly thread. Much like the deckbuilding posts of old, we'll put a sticky on the sidebar for easy access.
Here are a set of general courtesies when posting here, paraphrased from /u/bokchoykn in /r/magictcg):

Ask thought-provoking questions.
Tell us very specifically about what you want.
Be open to any suggestions.

Remember that, in the end, this isn't /r/magictcg. Please gear your questions towards a competitive, play-to-win audience. After all, that's what we're all about!
With that...ask us anything!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 10, 2017 | Show off Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you make a purchase this week you're particularly proud of? Have you had your wedding and want to share some particular pictures? Did your invites come in, or did you just get engaged? Show us things like your dress, your cake, your SO etc. for us to "Oooh and aah" over with you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NZ Post Meridiem Random Discussion Thread - Wed 10 May, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the r/NewZealand evening post. Have a chit chat.

No politics, be nice.

*"What's the deal with those quotes? Where did they come from?"* - /u/Fastllama13 

*"I don't even know what I'm saying anymore."* - /u/honourandsacrifice

[Join the official Discord server, too](https://discord.gg/6hdNNWp).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> !Clear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forum Libre - 2017-05-10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
**Partagez ici tout ce que vous voulez !**

__________________________________________

^(Ce sujet est gnr automatiquement en semaine  7h et le samedi  minuit.  -) ^[Archives.](http://www.reddit.com/r/france/search?q=flair%3A%22Forum%22 sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/Nexus5 Customization Thread - Show us your home screens, cases, ROMs, any anything else you've done to customize your device - [May 10, 2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is for sharing the customizations you have made to your Nexus 5, both externally, and with the operating system. So if you're trying out a new home screen layout, just got a new case, or installed a new ROM, this is the place to show it off!

As usual, be polite to other users, and don't downvote screenshots you don't like.

**If you're posting a home screen layout, please include as much information as possible. This includes icon packs, widgets, launchers, etc.**     
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/EurekaNetwork Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to discuss the Network. Marco will give his weekly updates here. Please put any suggestions you want below and feel free to discuss the new features
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HAPPY APRIL FOOLS DAY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Edit War Post - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  Wednesday! 05/09/17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weekly  Wednesday!  Feel free to ask any questions here, be it language, study habits, or just general experiences in the language!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly 'Read/edit my Personal Statement' thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to find help with your personal statement or secondary essay. You may trade with other users, or try to find a med student or physician to help you. Please avoid making multiple requests in the same week. Please be clear about what you are looking for, and what type of document you need help with. Remember to polite -- anyone helping you is doing so out of kindness. Be respectful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Workout Wednesday - Discuss and Share Exercise Routines, Techniques, etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##Daily Discussion Threads

----

Curated daily at 12:15am ET, the Reddit Ultimate discussion threads aim to cut down on excess content and to provide an opportunity for people to discuss interesting topics in more detail. Today is **Wednesday,** so our discussion will focus on asking about and sharing workout routines and technique questions.

**Please upvote this post** so it can be seen by folks browsing outside of /r/ultimate.

----

In this thread...

- **You could ask about workout routines:** What is your current fitness plan? What routines are best for ultimate? How can I work on my explosiveness? What are your favorite bodyweight exercises?
- **You could ask about specific technique:** What is the best way to perform a deadlift? Where should I keep my feet when squatting? How can I work all of my core muscles at once?
- **You could discuss advanced concepts:** What are some good goals to set for me? What track workouts are great for large groups? How can I use field sprints to better condition myself?
- **And you could share what works for you!** This thread can be a valuable feedback opportunity for proposing exercise sets, critiquing form, etc. What are you proud of? What needs work?

Even if you have nothing to share, check back often and help answer questions!

Note: Content in this thread doesn't just have to be gym-related  it can be field, track, pool, beach etc. Can also be drills in addition to workouts, nutrition discussion, etc as long as it relates to physical development.

----

*This post is part of the weekly reddit ultimate discussion series. [Learn more.](https://www.reddit.com/r/ultimate/comments/596f9a/announcing_the_rultimate_weekly_discussion_topics/)*

Monday|Tuesday|Wednesday|Thursday|Friday|Saturday|Sunday
:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:
Medical Questions|Tips n' Tricks|Workout Advice|Rules Questions|Anything Goes|Trash Talk|Shop Talk
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Team Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread will be used to house your daily team related questions.  
Refrain from making individual posts outside of this Megathread.  

*Don't forget to read the [stickied threads.](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/about/sticky)*

---

Specify, if relevant, which region you are playing: **Global** or **Japan**.

---

#**Resources:**

* [FAQ](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/faq)
* [Global FAQ](https://www.reddit.com/50swfe)
* [Starting Guides](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/starting-guide)
* [Exviuswiki.com](https://exviuswiki.com/Main_Page)
* [Helpful links](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/links)
* [Wiki Index](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/index)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Help Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread will be used to house your **daily questions**.  
Refrain from making individual posts outside of this Megathread.  

*Don't forget to read the [stickied threads.](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/about/sticky)*

---

Specify, if relevant, which region you are playing: **Global** or **Japan**.

---

#**Resources:**

* [FAQ](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/faq)
* [Global FAQ](https://www.reddit.com/50swfe)
* [Starting Guides](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/starting-guide)
* [Exviuswiki.com](https://exviuswiki.com/Main_Page)
* [Helpful links](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/links)
* [Wiki Index](https://www.reddit.com/r/FFBraveExvius/wiki/index)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key Megathread with Information about Giveaways  NDA Ends May 12th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you are aware, anyone that has signed up for the beta will get a key this week. With that in mind there will be a lot 
of keys going around. 

We have set some rules that are to be followed:

- Please dont make posts with keys
- Only post your key(s) here 
- Dont spam for a key
- No begging

I hope you guys can follow these rules, and like always please have fun. 


NDA:

The NDA was lifted on May 12th. Please dont post anything before this date. After this date, we will only take down 
what has been said in the rules. 

Beep. Boop. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persona 5 is out! - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/XtyYe5k.png
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mentoring Thread: Week-200 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

#Please do not reply directly to the thread.  

#Coaches: reply to the regional comments with the application format below.  

#Students: contact coaches (PM/reply) before adding them in-game.

-----------

* This is completely Voluntary and **Free**, please report anyone charging you or paying you to offer these services. **[Summoner School stance on paid coaching.](http://www.reddit.com/r/summonerschool/comments/2w09n7/summoner_school_stance_on_paid_coaching/)**

***

Respect our [Golden Rule](http://www.reddit.com/r/summonerschool/wiki/rules). If you find that certain teachers/students are disrespectful, send us a message **[here](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fsummonerschool)**.

For all the previous weeks: /r/summonerschool/w/mentoring

***

**Format for replies**|Only Teachers should directly reply to the distinguished comments
:--:|:--:

Copy paste this and fill it up in your responses.

    **Teacher**:

    **Summoner Name**:

    **League / Division**:

    **Areas of expertise**:

    **Champions**:

    **Languages Spoken**:

    **Duration of Mentoring**:

    **Preferred Methods**:

    **Other Info**:

***

**Previous Week Threads**: /r/summonerschool/w/mentoring

***

## General Guidelines for Students 

* You will be making the first contact by sending a PM or replying to the mentor of your choice.  

* Come prepared. What do you want to take away from this? Is there anything the mentors can review?  

* Know your issues: In which areas do you struggle?  

* You must understand that getting better is all about yourself. Bring your best attitude.  

* Be motivated. The results are proportional to the amount of effort you put in practice.  

* Mentors are here to assist and help you with the difficulties you encounter. This is not a way to find high elo Duo Queue partners.

----------  

## General Guidelines for Mentors  

* You will accept players of your choice as students upon receiving their messages. The responsibility to make further contact and set up times falls on you.  

* Be clear as to what you want to do for your student(s) in your description: Review replays, lane together in normals, experiment and practice in custom games, simply answer questions/discuss, etc.  

* Try to organize your "sessions" by having specific themes. You do not want to overburden someone with too much information at once.  

* Give yourself discussion prompts to avoid losing your trail of thought. Slow down, clarify your opinions and make sure the student understands.  

* It is important to always promote a positive attitude and mentality towards playing and improving.  

-----  

## Tools  

* http://na.op.gg/ and http://www.lolking.net/ Website for player stats, match history and replays.  

* http://leaguelsi.com/ 3rd party install, similar features as above. Advanced filtering and details.  

* https://obsproject.com/ Local recording.

* http://leagueoflegends.wikia.com/wiki/League_of_Legends_Wiki All information about League of Legends.  

* http://riftkit.net/ Draw board of the Summoner's Rift map.

* [More resources here](http://www.reddit.com/r/summonerschool/wiki/resources).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Crack Watch] Weekly question thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask any question you like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 04) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24-Hour Pledge - Wednesday, 10 May 2017 - The Plan for Today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Wake up with determination; go to bed with satisfaction!

This is our **daily check-in**, to help keep us accountable over the long haul. Feel free to post whatever goals will help keep you on track. 

Here's the regular text on behalf of this thread's originator, kingoftheeyesores, taken with his blessing 

 *I'll be posting a daily, 24 hour pledge to stick to my plan, or whichever small piece of my plan I am currently working on. Whatever your dietary goals may be, I hope you stick to them for the next 24 hours (and then worry about the following 24!). Who's with me?*

Thanks to /u/nofollowthrough who made the 24-Hour Pledge an ongoing /r/loseit institution. 

Due to space limitations, this may be a sticky only occasionally.  **Please find it daily using the sidebar or top message.**  

***
On reddit, your *vote* means, *"I found this interesting"*  (...read more about [**voting on reddit**](https://www.reddit.com/wiki/voting))
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily Support Thread for May 10 - Rants, raves, frustrations, and successes, post them here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use this as a space to discuss whatever and support each other. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Discussion: Wednesday Painting - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
What are you painting right now?

Works in Progress pictures?

Tips and tricks?

Criticism and critiques of each others works?

Whatever you want to talk about regarding painting!

*These posts are an attempt to create more discussion within our community. If you have suggestions or comments about them please send the mods a message [here](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FInfinityTheGame)!*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OFFICIAL] Daily Feedback Thread May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> READ THIS TEXT CLOSELY BEFORE POSTING!!! NO FEEDBACK = BAN

**If you post something for feedback, you must give *QUALITY* feedback at least once before the next thread is up.** Check out the [Quality Feedback Guide](https://www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop/wiki/feedbackquality) for tips on giving good feedback. Sincere feedback requests only please. Posting for plays will not be tolerated.

**One feedback request per thread max** (i.e. one track)   

**Leave feedback *at least once* as a reply to a top-level comment to avoid being flagged as a slacker.** To be super clear, this means you click reply on someone else's original comment. This thread is enforced with the help of the MHHFeedbackMod bot, because our bot cannot distinguish between feedback and gratitude, replies to comments that left you feedback will not be counted.

**NO FEEDBACK = BAN**

This thread is posted every day at Midnight Eastern (GMT -5). [Click here for the full automoderator thread schedule](http://www.reddit.com/r/makinghiphop/wiki/weeklythreadschedule).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily Squad Thread (AM Edition) -- May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is for **all posts** related to squads, including...

* FUT squad building

* FUT Draft squads

* Squad Building Challenge squads

**Do you need a squad built?** 

Fill in the sample below and let others find or create a team that fits your purpose. Other questions for your squad building     needs are also welcome.

* **Formation**

* **Hybrid (Yes/No)**

* **League/Nationality**

* **Players you want in it (Optional)**

* **Budget**

* **Console**

__________

[***FUTHEAD***](http://futhead.com/), [***FUTWIZ***](http://www.futwiz.com/) *or* [***FUTBIN***](http://www.futbin.com/)          *links are strongly encouraged...*

__________

^**Note:** ^All ^Squad ^Threads, ^including ^Build ^Requests, ^Squad ^Reviews, ^and ^Requests ^For ^Critique ^outside ^of         ^this ^thread ^will ^be ^removed ^without ^warning. ^If ^you ^are ^a ^squad ^builder ^interested ^in ^creating ^a ^*feature* ^        *thread* ^for ^a ^certain ^tournament, ^a ^specific ^formation, ^style ^of ^play, ^etc. ^-- [**^message ^the ^moderators**](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FFIFA) ^before ^posting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Official] General Discussion Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Welcome to rMMA's General Discussion Thread!](http://i.imgur.com/cCIH4wj.png)**  

***

Discuss your favorite fighters, the upcoming card or something you forgot to bring up in this week's Moronic Monday thread.      

***    

  
[Click here to message the Mods of rMMA](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FMMA subject= message=) | [Link to previous General Discussion Threads](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/search?q=flair%3Anotice+%5BOfficial%5D+General+Discussion+Thread restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all) | [Link to Moronic Monday Thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/search?q=flair%3Aweekly+moronic+monday restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)  |  [Link to Thursday Betting Thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/search?q=flair%3Aweekly+betting+thursday restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)  |  [Link to Friday Flair Betting Thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/search?q=flair%3Aweekly+Friday+Flair restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all) |

***

[Link to rmma's Thick, Solid and Tight Meme Guide](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/comments/576f0c/official_rmmas_thick_solid_and_tight_guide_to/) |  [Link to rmma's Fight Pass viewing recommendations](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/wiki/fightpass) | [Link to rmma's 2016 MMA Awards](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/comments/5n41m0/official_2016_reddit_mma_awards/) | [Link to rmma's 2016 r/mma User   Post Edition Awards](https://www.reddit.com/r/MMA/comments/5ofky2/official_2016_best_of_rmma_awards_user_and_post/)

   ***  
   
Custom flairs: here are two ways to obtain a custom flair:

- place and lose a flair bet in the Friday thread
- draw a MS Paint-style image for the sub

The rules for the drawing are simply that it must be a ridiculous MMA-related scenario. If you would like a custom flair, send a message to us with a link to your drawing and your flair request. We'll probably grant it.

  
  ***  
 
Interested in modding? [Please fill out the mod application found here.](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1rtGmWM__v1qmLai818nGukAsutU9Xd-fi5GJefMQuhI/viewform?edit_requested=true) Do not leave a comment about this in the thread. [You can send us modmail](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FMMA subject= message=) if you have questions.

  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clear!Clear!Clear! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GPU PRICES FALLIN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi dank memestars. Just letting you losers know that it's been a weeK, so every GPU on the market has droppedat. The question is, how much?

               

Of course, that still means my GPUs are still worth more than yours, as explained in [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ).

Always remember to consult the [ShaQtusTM]( https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OUcSioaXTFU) and review the [golden rule](http://i.imgur.com/54xA2ZZ.png) before making any purchases. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Daily Discussion] Wednesday, May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the /r/LitecoinMarkets daily discussion thread! Thread topics include, but are not limited to: General discussion related to the days events, technical analysis, trading ideas   strategies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hauls   Destashing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been hauling additions to your stash? Looking to cull some items from your stash?  Post away!

If posting de-stashes, you may either link your /r/asianbeautyexchange crosspost (recommended), or your blog sale if you are hosting it there.  However, if you are selling on an external site we do ask that like /r/asianbeautyexchange, you post a picture with the items + a paper with your name on it for authenticity.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ASK HERE! Daily Help, and Questions: May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuck? Lost? Have questions about your routine, or need help setting one up?  Looking for product recommendations? Have a simple question or need something explained in a simple way?  

*Please remember that all skincare is individual and Your Mileage May Vary with recommendations. We are enthusiasts, not doctors, and we cannot provide you with medical advice. Speak to a medical professional if your skin concerns are affecting your well-being.*

**Where applicable, consider sharing with us the following so we can help you better (*click "Source" below this post if you'd like to copy the formatting*)**

**Skin Type**:  | **Country/Climate I'm in**:  | **Top Skin Concern**:

**Current Routine/Products I'm Using**:

**AM**

* [product]

* [product]

* [product]

**PM**

* [product]

* [product]

* [product]

**I specifically [want help with/am looking for a product to/am curious about trying]**...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/WiiU Discussions - Let's talk about anything! [2017/05/10] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to r/WiiU's weekly casual conversation thread!

This thread's purpose is to be a lounge: a place for the Reddit Wii U community to relax, hang out, chat aimlessly, discuss mostly off-topic material (current events, sports, etc.), and maybe get to know each other a little better as people.

As for general rules for this thread:

- we ask to keep the content of your conversations PG-13 at best
- keep meta content (meaning about the subreddit in general) to a minimum
- have fun!

We also have an official /r/WiiU [Discord server](https://discordapp.com/invite/0cNxEzSKWDJEtUXB)! Make sure you check it out if you wish to chat with your fellow WiiUsers.

**Guidelines #1, #2 and #12 are in full effect.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Daily Discussion] Wednesday, May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Thread topics include, but are not limited to:**

* General discussion related to the day's events
* Technical analysis, trading ideas   strategies
* Quick questions that do not warrant a separate post

**Thread guidelines:**

* **Be excellent to each other.**
* Do not make posts outside of the daily thread for the topics mentioned above.

**Other ways to interact:**

* [Get an invite](https://self-inviter-slack2.herokuapp.com/) to live chat on [our Slack group](https://reddit-bitcoinmarkets.slack.com/)
* Set your flair to trade pretend money in [the Flair Game](https://coinsight.org/flairgame)
* Weekly threads: [Newbie Mondays](http://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/search?q=newbie+monday sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all) and [Fundamentals Fridays](http://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/search?q=fundamentals+friday sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/BirthdayBuds' Daily Birthday Post for [May 10] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find others whose birthdays are today. If today's your birthday, happy birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> !clear Clearing Daily Sticky Post with automod! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fiat Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post dank memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Question Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are looking for the FAQ and Super Sticky, it can be found [here](https://redd.it/4m9mff).

Use this thread to ask basic questions: "What do you think of this obelisk?", "What hero should I get?", "What ISO set for this character?", etc.

You are also permitted to use this thread for general game discussion and off-topic discussion. 

Please remember to thank users for informative and useful posts, so people have a reason to answer questions!

Thread will reset at daily reset (3:00 PM UTC). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Method] Early Morning Risers - please check in - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NOTE: Please make sure you're posting to the correct date!**
*This thread is for anyone who wants to make a habit of waking up early in the morning (before 8 am). Check in by posting your wake up time, and feel free to mention any positive things you prioritized when rising early (exercise, meditation, day planning, healthy breakfast, etc).You may also find it helpful to post your intentions the night before and reply to that comment in the morning when you check in. This may help increase the feeling of accountability!*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Method] Early Morning Risers - please check in - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **NOTE: Please make sure you're posting to the correct date!**
*This thread is for anyone who wants to make a habit of waking up early in the morning (before 8 am). Check in by posting your wake up time, and feel free to mention any positive things you prioritized when rising early (exercise, meditation, day planning, healthy breakfast, etc).You may also find it helpful to post your intentions the night before and reply to that comment in the morning when you check in. This may help increase the feeling of accountability!*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Role Model Wednesday Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Morning Soldiers. This is your chance to post about your role models. Who are they? How do they live their life? Let us know and maybe we can find another person to get us moving. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babylonian Chaos - Where all languages are allowed - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Babylonian Chaos. Each week on Thursday 18:00 UTC we host a thread for learners to get a chance to write any language they're learning and find people who are doing the same. Native speakers are welcome to join in.

You can pick whatever topic you want. Introduce yourself, look for native speakers, ask a question or anything.

Please consider sorting by new.

We have a bot /u/LLBot that would remind you about this thread every Thursday as soon as it is created. 

**There's two ways to interact with the bot, via comment in /r/languagelearning and via private message.**
____
To subscribe or unsubscribe via comment call the bot and give it the appropriate command:

    /u/LLBot subscribe
    /u/LLBot unsubcribe        
____
To subscribe, unsubscribe, or check your subscription status via private message send the bot a message (topic doesn't matter) with the appropriate command:

    subscribe
    unsubscribe
    status
___
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly YML thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there!
Please use this thread to share whatever you've been listening to lately.
Avoid leaving a link only comment when possible, and try to elaborate a few words about the track.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/Bored Discussion Thread - May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to discuss whatever you've been up to lately (new games, fun sites, new friends, anything interesting, etc...). Be sure to try to reply to everyone and be friendly! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> !Clear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 03) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official ECR Late Night Chat Thread [05-09-2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about whatever tickles your fancy.

Now being posted at 11pm eastern!

https://discord.gg/CBJ7KGH

https://gifsound.com/?gifv=uRvs9C1 v=hHAP7NvBOU0 s=74 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily All in One Thread (May 10, 2017) - For all your Team Help, Brag Posts, Scout Queries and General Questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything you need, all in one place. Use this thread for any Team Help you may require, any Stupid Questions (or not so stupid questions) that you've never known where to ask, "should I scouts", as well as any and all Brag posts you may want an audience for.

Any and all posts that should be in this thread that are posted to the front page will be deleted.

Please specify any goals/direction you have for your team to aid others in giving you more precise help!

[Read this article if you need help with identifying your direction.](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccerspirits/comments/55ga64/before_asking_for_team_help_in_this_subreddit/)

The basic guide to team building/progression can be found [here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccerspirits/comments/3g9snl/a_basic_guide_in_identifying_your_units_and/)

Other guides and information can be found in the [subreddit wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccerspirits/wiki/index)!

Use the following template if you can't upload a picture of your team (with thanks to /u/AmoebaCel):

\|     |     |     |  
\|:---:|:---:|:---:|  
\|Striker|Totem|Assist|  
\|Attacker|Totem/Assist|Attacker|  
\|Defender|Healer|Defender/Totem|  
\|     |Goalkeeper|     |



Doing so will display your team like so:

|     |     |     |  
|:---:|:---:|:---:|  
|Striker|Totem|Assist|  
|Attacker|Totem/Assist|Attacker|  
|Defender|Healer|Defender/Totem|  
|     |Goalkeeper|     |
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Highlight Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please share your gameplay highlights in this thread. For feedback on this trial experiment, please visit /r/OverwatchMeta.

---

 ## [Upcoming Trial: Daily Highlight Threads](https://redd.it/69q0v7)
 
 Hi all,
 
 This week (starting Sunday night) we'll be trialing a potential rule change: Highlight threads are not permitted, and must instead be posted in a Daily Highlight Thread.  If this change is made, this thread will be prominently displayed either in the Important section, via a banner, or some other way.
 
 For the next week we'll be doing a sticky thread each day, and subject1093 will direct users who submit highlights to this thread, and removing them.
 
 We know this change will have a drastic effect on the landscape of the front page, and we also know changes like this make the mobile app experience less intuitive, and a bit more difficult even for desktop users. We're eager to hear feedback at the end of the week. 
 
 Whether or not this change goes through depends on many factors, but we'd like to see how this trial goes regardless of our intent to pursue the change.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ENG][JPN] May 09, 2017 - May 16, 2017 Weekly Questions   Advice Megathread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This megathread is to house your questions regarding teambuilding or just questions in general about the game. 

Don't hesitate to ask!

#Helpful Resources

 * [FAQ](/r/OnePieceTC/wiki/guides/faq)
 * [Wiki](/r/OnePieceTC/wiki/index)
 * [Common Abbreviations and Nicknames](/r/OnePieceTC/wiki/guides/abbrevandnick)
 * [Comprehensive Teambuilding Guide](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1MJAs8G9BgAp3qhcvz45DxzsWTjJ-78JDpUqPAzhUM4k/edit?pli=1)
 * [Beginner's Road Map](/r/OnePieceTC/wiki/guides/roadmap)
 * [Turtle Time Calculator](https://optctimer.com/)
 * [OPTC-DB](http://optc-db.github.io/)
  * The **OPTC Database** has links to a variety of helpful resources (such as a complete character database, damage calculator and more!). 

***

#Current   Repeat Events

*Please refer to the sidebar.*

#Guides

*Please refer to the sidebar, menu, wiki, megathreads OR use the search bar.*

***

###Question not answered? You may re-post within a reasonable time frame (~2H)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shitpost thread - May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 May 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **A sorta kinda daily open thread to use as an alternative to posting on the main board.You should post here for:**

*  PRs 

*  Formchecks

*  Rudimentary discussion or questions

*  General conversation with other users

*  Memes, funnies, and general bollocks not appropriate to the main board

*  **Help support the /r/powerlifting community, try switching your sort to new and help out the late comers to the thread!**

Need more r/powerlifting in your lift?  [Join our chatroom](https://discord.gg/xnpG5Hv)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caff Italia * 10/05/2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buongiorno cavaliere, il solito? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thread: Simple Questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask any questions you may have here! Remember to sort comments by 'new' so the latest questions are seen and answered! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday Weekly Discussion Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has your week been? What have you watched lately? What has David done to inspire you this week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Episode Discussion: S04E21 - "The Return" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
This thread is for **SERIOUS** discussion of the Sepisode that just aired. What is and isn't serious is at the discretion of the moderators.    

---    
---      

|EPISODE|DIRECTED BY|WRITTEN BY|ORIGINAL AIRDATE|
|:-----------|:------------:|:------------:|:------------:|
|S04E21- "The Return"|Kevin Tancharoen|Maurissa Tancharoen   Jed Whedon|Tuesday, May 9, 2016 10:00/9:00c on ABC

---

**Episode Synopsis:** In the exciting penultimate episode leading into next week's season finale, Coulson and the team's victory in the Framework is short-lived, as an even deadlier enemy looms against them all.

**Kevin Tancharoen** is the brother of showrunner Maurissa Tancharoen, and is known for his work on the webseries Mortal Kombat: Legacy. He has directed various other movies and TV episodes before, and has most recently worked on The Flash.

He has directed eight episodes for Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. before:

- Face my Enemy
- One of Us
- The Dirty Half Dozen
- Purpose in the Machine
- Spacetime
- Ascension
- The Laws of Inferno Dynamics
- The Patriot

**Maurissa Tancharoen   Jed Whedon** are the showrunners of Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D., along with Jeffrey Bell. Jed is the Brother of Joss Whedon, and worked with Maurissa on Dollhouse, Spartacus: Blood and Sand, Drop Dead Diva, and The Avengers.

They have written eleven episodes for Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. before:

- Pilot
- The Asset
- Repairs
- Turn, Turn, Turn
- Beginning of the End
- Shadows
- Aftershocks
- S.O.S. Part Two
- Laws of Nature
- Ascension
- The Ghost

---
***
***

**Please do not discuss the promo following tonight's episode.** There will be a separate thread made to discuss the promo and comments about it will be removed from this thread.

***

"LIVE" discussion for previous episodes can be found [HERE](https://www.reddit.com/r/shield/search?sort=new restrict_sr=on q=flair%3ALive%2BDiscussion). 

***

The discussion / comments below assume you have watched the episode in it's entirety. Therefore, spoiler text for anything through this episode is not necessary. If, however, you are talking about events that have yet to air on the show such as future guest appearances / future characters / storylines, please use spoiler tags. The same goes for things connected to the Marvel like comics, etc.

***

**Please keep subreddit rules in mind when submitting content:**

On top of this anything not directly related to Agents of SHIELD might be subject to being removed. This includes but is not limited to screenshots (FB, YouTube, Twitter, texts, etc), generic memes and reaction gifs, and generic Marvel content.

Feel free to message us moderators if you have suggestions or concerns about these.

**Reminder: [DO NOT POST GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY 2 SPOILERS!](https://redd.it/69b231)**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Questions Thread - (May 10, 2017 UTC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use this thread to ask questions as part of a trial to introduce a Weekly Questions Thread in /r/Facebook. Remember that discussions about being banned, needing to provide ID and account suspension issues should be directed to the Facebook Help Center as nothing can be done here and these types of posts drown the subreddit. Feedback about this new trial feature is welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Hourly, Today's date is - 05/09/17 20:46:23 -0600 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testing auto-mod schedule. though this stuff isn't updating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 170510 Weekly Thread - ONCE Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Once!


Today is all about you, tell us how your week went or anything that's going on with you. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly SUBJECT 1 Discussion - SUBJECT 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBJECT 1'S POST

YAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaas
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows into Requiem - May 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Welcome to the weekly Windows into requiem Thread!  
        
Post your screenshots, stories you feel to small for it's own post and general updates for your character. ^^^Don't ^^^have ^^^to ^^^be ^^^using ^^^requiem ^^^currently, ^^^we ^^^won't ^^^judge...Hopefully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 02) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classic Matches Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a weekly thread for discussing historical 'classic matches' in all cricket formats. Nominate a classic/historical match as a parent comment and discuss the match in the replies. Try to include scoreboard and highlights links if you can.

As a prompt, what are some famous previous meetings between teams playing current series?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wed May 10, 2017 Pick Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a thread for posting your BTS picks for the day.  Include any reasoning or analysis that you want.  Also, if you see the lineups and notice that someone's pick is not starting or if a game is likely to be postponed, be a cool cat and comment to let them know.

A few links that should be helpful:

[FantasyAlarm's daily lineups](http://www.fantasyalarm.com/?game=lineup)

[DailyBaseballData's weather forecasts for each game](http://dailybaseballdata.com/cgi-bin/weather.pl)

[BaseballMusing's table of current hitting streaks](http://www.baseballmusings.com/cgi-bin/CurStreak.py)

If there's anything else that you think should be in an autopost, just leave a comment and I'll try to include it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outfit Feedback and Fit Check - May 09 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post a picture of what you're wearing to get suggestions, feedback and constructive criticism from the community. When posting, please:

* Include what the attire is for (work, school, going out, etc.)

* Include a front-on, full-body picture with your hands at your sides. Multiple pictures from different angles can be helpful, but aren't necessary. There's more info on taking good self-shots [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/16rwft/how_to_take_better_self_pics_for_mfa/).

 Critiquing others is welcome and encouraged, but keep it constructive/factual.  It takes balls to post pictures of yourself on the Internet, the least you can do is accord the same courtesy as you would to someone in real life.

 **Important: Downvotes are strongly discouraged in this thread. Sorting by new is strongly encouraged.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple Questions - May 09 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is for simple style questions that don't warrant their own thread (although we strongly suggest checking the sidebar and the wiki before posting!). Fit checks and "How'd I do" questions are a great use of this thread (although they can also go in the daily Outfit Feedback  amp; Fit Check thread). Other example questions:

* Could someone take the chest measurement for a small J.Crew oxford?
* Is there a place with full measurements for Naked  amp; Famous jeans?
* What slim-fitting green cords do you recommend?
* Where do I find a military surplus peacoat online?

**Important: Downvotes are strongly discouraged in this thread. Sorting by new is strongly encouraged.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Daily Discussion Thread] Wed May. 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to discuss anything related to SFTC, including the [day's matchups](http://streak.espn.go.com/en/entry?date=20170510). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/MalaysianPF Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's talk finance. Ask questions, give advice, share tips and tricks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official Bollywood Weekly Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the Official Bollywood Weekly Discussion Thread. The thread guidelines are as follows:

  Discussion topics include, but are not limited to, details related to events, gossips, rants and raves about movies, questions about movies, tip of the tongue movie names, sharing of wallpapers, trailers, music videos, and movie posters. Please follow Reddiquette. 

Thank you in advance for your participation. Enjoy the discussion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whimsical Wednesday - Mahou Shoujo Discussion - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's take this time to talk about your favorite Mahou Shoujo anime, manga or other media. Feel free to gush shamelessly here with nooo judgement! A new post will be made every Wensday!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Miguel Castro is only 20 years old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, he's so young. I wish I was still 20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 10 - Round 9 - Day 017 - WORKOUT WEDNESDAY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Workout Wednesday is about getting active!

What's your workout look like this week? Have any apps or plans you want to share with us?

Get out and get active and moving.

Check out [darebee.com](Darebee) for lots of daily body weight exercises, too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 01) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Stray Sheep - Off-Topic Discussion - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about anything and everything.

Please mark all spoilers, for all series, as per the sidebar.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official Episode Discussion - S05E10 "Darkroom" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paige's snooping leads Philip and Elizabeth to make a choice that could shift the balance of their lives forever. Also: Stan and Aderholt's recruitment of Sofia suddenly bears fruit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Random Discussion Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

This is the thread for, you guessed it, anything goes discussion. Please follow the /r/Dubai rules and for any feedback/complaints regarding this post, please PM /u/DaedalusMinion

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily challenge discussion: May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi.  Please discuss the daily challenge here!

I am a robot!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let us know what you're working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us know what you're working on and maybe the community will show up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
