<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4988</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 08:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know TWC is a mess and that they've gotten even worse in recent years--but somehow, they actually sparked my initial interest in meteorology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seen this before, and tried to do this--but I just can't get the hang of it.  He seems to fold it so smoothly and easily but I'm sure that'll come with practice.

As a side note... what is going on with his tie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 19:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So can ~~your~~ you're grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 03:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of us are ~~not hipsters/homeless/lumberjacks~~ Asian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 13:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't sound like a real job at all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 08:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I'm pursuing particle physics but am currently in the field of astrophysics.  As you mentioned, the egregious generalizations made while doing cosmological theories are painful, especially to me, but it simply cannot be done another way.  I wish I could bust out thousands of data points--but if you've ever tried you know how hard it is to get telescope time.  So we simply work with what we have.

To address your last point: I do think that we need to carefully poke around and question everything.  But that doesn't mean that a less rigorous science isn't a science!  It may simply be that it's a more chaotic science, or a science with limited data, or anything else that we still call science.  But yes, we should be hesitant to jump onto any theory/model until it has fairly definitive results going for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 16:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with you on (2).  

I feel like (4) is a little iffy, considering how many physicists [ignore](http://www.smbc-comics.com/?id=2675) the formalities of math.  But I don't think any other science goes nearly as in depth in mathematics as physics does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 17:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say, this is the most counter-intuitive tip I've ever heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 17:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had as much trouble finding it as I did: http://i.imgur.com/GIjcC.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 07:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're by yourself or don't mind looking like an idiot, just stand with your head tilted to one side, and jump up and down a few times.  That's always worked for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 04:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I didn't mean that to say that I have it set at a particular time, but rather, that it is set to send me emails at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 00:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting to know, but I don't need to know this.  Seems to be the general trend of this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A massive, cooling-flow-induced starburst in the
core of a luminous cluster of galaxies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 17:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 22:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using Asana for months--it's very useful and well designed.  I really think it would really shine for those working on group projects, since it lets you apportion tasks to other group members, etc.  

I have it set to send me email reminders of upcoming tasks every day at 2:45am, so I basically have a to-do list every morning when I check my mail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Need to mix a protein shake, but don't have a shaker cup? Use a Nalgene bottle, and simply add a few ice cubes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ice will help mix and dissolve clumps of protein powder.  For a 16 oz shake, 2 or 3 ice cubes is enough to thoroughly mix most regular protein powders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
