<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 16:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I too loved this movie but the 'then' teenager in me was most interested in watching Carrie Fisher....man she was hot.

http://alturl.com/xewio

  That is the last time I remember seeing her in a movie where she didn't sound like a truck driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 20:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be sure to wash your balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 18:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush:  sends over a hundred thousands troops off to fight in a war for weapons of mass destruction that didn't exist, where 3,542 U.S. troops have sacrificed their lives and at a cost of 787.5 Billion dollars so far=Best President Ever.

Obama:  has marine holds an umbrella for a diplomat and himself=shit bricks, impeach him.

I just don't get the logic...but that's because I use reason I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 21:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some suggestions from a previous thread.

[Volunteering Opportunities](http://www.reddit.com/r/lincoln/comments/11j9gq/volunteer_opportunities_around_lincoln/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 16:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could have wrote a compelling article pointing out the benefits of certain improvements and what it has done for other teams.  Instead just took school yard digs at a rival team...sad really...like a terrible "yo momma's so fat" joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 16:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 15:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you must have been sitting right next to me for the Minnesota game.  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 23:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it as 1999, I was just about to graduate college with a BA in Theatre production.  I also worked in TV and Film production but always relied on equipment provided by my school or employer for editing.  I was now going to need my own rig to do all that and anything on the market from the PC manufacturers cost a bundle.

I did a lot of research and then I took money I was gifted at graduation and built my very first computer.  I found the passion for something I had no idea I would love.  Never owned a computer, never really used them much except to write papers.  There I stood in front of a heap of wires and I loved it.  (Celeron 466, 128 Mb of RAM, 3dFX 3500 with tv in/out, 20 Gb HD).

Flash forward 14 years and I find myself in my 12th year of I.T. work and in an advanced specialization supporting fortune 500 companies.  I love *most* days, but it is I.T. after all. :)

It all started with that first computer I built, it changed my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 17:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> came here to find out more about the game.  I saw it listed on Steam and became quite interested.

I did find some videos on You Tube and they sealed the deal for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 16:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Nebraska now but grew up in IL and lived in Chicago after college.  My father-in-law doesn't understand how I couldn't love both teams from Chicago...I just shake my head.

Interestingly enough, there is a Chicago pizza place in Omaha now, and the owner is a big White Sox fan, his commercial on the radio starts off..."Hey Cubs fans, your team stinks..."  and that's where I shut it off.  The locals may think it's charming but it drives me nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 14:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same for the one by our place.  She stands on a stepstool and runs the front like a Boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 14:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> came here to say this.  interesting stuff I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 17:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I work from home and it's the best work experience I've ever had.  

  I'm employed by a very large company, specifically in the IT services division.  When I started with the company I went to the office 99% of the time but was given the flexibility to work from home if I wasn't feeling well or if we had bad weather/a delivery/a plumber coming, etc and needed to be home.
  I was recently promoted to a more specialized position in our overall team and the others I work with directly are all 100% remote, even though they are U.S. based and physically near the office.  It's just how they've always functioned and after 15 years and a good track record they just leave them alone.  It was then a perk that I took advantage of when I joined that team, with the blessing of my manager.

I used to get up 6:00 am, do my thing, pack up my gear and get out the door by 7:15 am to fight traffic and get to my office/desk by 7:45 am.  At the office I was interrupted a lot by normal office banter, people coming and going, bathroom/lunch, etc.  I'd then leave at 5:00 pm and get home by 5:30 pm...then setup my laptop just in case I was needed for an emergency or if I was on-call.  Then start all over again the next day.

I now roll out of bed at 6:45 am, turn on the coffee, take a shower, sit down at my desk by 7:15 am and start working.  The bathroom is 8 steps away instead of 200.  The "lunch room" is 20 steps away instead of 250.  I can listen to my music as loud as I want and no one is going to interrupt me while I'm trying to focus on an important task.  I'm much more productive and the time I used to waste commuting, chit-chatting, going to and from lunch/coffee/bathroom is now time used for work.  I save a ton of money on gas and vehicle maintenance and I get to see my kids before they head off to school and as they get home.  If something comes up and I have to "work late", I can run up the kitchen, grab some food, and my mind isn't distracted by hunger or my wife calling asking how late I'm going to be.

I still go into the office from time to time to see my friends and we go out for lunch but I can tell you it has been wonderful.  It's not for everyone and you must be self disciplined but for the right folks, it can be an incredible opportunity.  If you run an organization and you hire the right folks, give them this as an option.  With a multitude of instant messaging options, voip, vpns, I'm really puzzled that a company would waste money on real estate and heating/cooling an office when this could work for a portion of their staff. 

 I've been doing this nearly a year and it has made me a better employee (productivity wise), it has made me a happier employee and it has given me more of a home life than I've ever had during my 12 years in I.T.  This is even when my responsibilities and workload are at the highest in my career.

edit;  TLDR - I work from home and it rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if I was griefed or it was a server issue.  I'll assume its the later.  No worries, I already started fixing, thank you for your efforts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drafting Right Kind of Guys: Running Backs (Rex Burkhead). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 15:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 05:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lucky, congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 06:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your trailer caused an anxiety induced flashback.  I already spent a chunk of my childhood causing patients great suffering while playing "Life   Death"...and apparently I had repressed those memories...now they have come flooding back.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sczxk0IkcVY

:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 16:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxi - Episode that Jim get's his driver's license.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pvn-tBeLpCk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 17:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...well my comment was more in reference to, now deleted, comments expressing rage.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 17:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Cub fan's don't understand visual sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 21:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think everything survived surprisingly but perhaps I'll come visit none the less :) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 18:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In any event, if I've lost my home to a virtual hurricane, perhaps someone can invite me to their town to setup my new place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 18:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, my home is just off the top edge of this image.

I work in I.T. and understand it happens.  I appreciate your groups dedication and resources and don't sweat it too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 14:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> quick, grab 4 turtles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 18:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to try it, thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 23:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my case, I only asked because it's 900 lbs and I felt it best to hear some feedback from experts instead of hearing my wife gripe for 3 or 4 years while I hope a new board pops up for sale. 

If it was a standard cab I'd have it already... :)  Thanks again for the feedback BTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very helpful, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 02:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep that's the one...  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 01:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said the monitor turns on but without the board I guess you never know if it "works".  Thank you for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 00:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> appears the biggest challenge would be to find the dang board for this unit.  a basic search has yielded no results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Dedicated] Need advice, is this worth diving into. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 23:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been looking to build a mame and/or refurbish an arcade machine for some time.  I have a 9 year old and as we are about to move into a much larger space, I have the room finally to begin this long promised project.  Something fun for the two of us to work on together.

I've been watching Craig's list for some old shells and I also designed one to build from scratch.

Suddenly an After Burner Deluxe Cockpit style pops up on Craig's List for $75.  He even offered to deliver all 900lbs to my place. Here are the pics.

[Image 1](http://i.imgur.com/4iXtDqf.jpg)

[Image 2](http://i.imgur.com/zwTm8pH.jpg)

He said it's been rewired and everything works, "just needs a motherboard".

I think this could be fun but it could also be that thing using up a third stall in my garage.  Does anyone have any experience with these, is it worth the hassle or should I pass?

I appreciate your time and thank you in advanced for your comments.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 01:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My neighbors must think I have turrets.  I was cursing up a storm until he got that last out.  

I would have to think that was his last change but I've been saying that for so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for your loss.  This is the second Cubs season without my grandfather and I felt that tinge of pain today.  He was born in 1915 and also never saw the Cubs win a World Series but he loved that team and always watched it on WGN but listened to the game on the radio with his headphones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 20:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OU818, that is it...thank you!  It's been since spring of 96 and hell if I could remember.  Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 19:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, love Mr. Bungle!  I can finally tell my sorta neat Mr. Bungle story.

When I was a sophomore in college (95/96) my friends and I met a really cool guy who was older than us but was in the same bachelors program.  It came up at some party that we really loved Mr. Bungle and he said, "oh yeah, I used to live with Mike Patton in San Francisco".  He went on to say that they used to drop acid and finger paint on the walls...the rest of the details are fuzzy and I could have the city wrong but that's how I remember it, but he went on to say, that he had an original Mr. Bungle demo tape and he'd let us have it, or borrow it or whatever.

We sort of thought he was full of it but sure enough, he showed up to class with this Maxwell cassette tape for an old 8 track mixer or whatever they are called and it had a crazy photocopied cover.  We about creamed our pants.  We used to listen to it all the time but the tape disappeared at some point that year and the only thing I can remember from it was that Mike Patton started out the recording with something like...this is "MR. BUNGLE, DEMO number (whatever) bringing you 8 tracks of mother fucking" ...something...hell I can't remember, it was about 20 years ago.

in any event, being a college kid, 19/20 years old in the Midwest, that was really cool, to get sort of a peak into the past of Mr. Bungle.  Ah the good ole days before youtube lol.

/not very exciting to anyone but me I suppose.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 04:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> worked for me, thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 13:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, they are about to enter Beta and it will then be available on Steam.  I purchased this game a year ago and I play nearly everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 04:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King Arthurs Gold...love that game.

http://kag2d.com/en/

They even have zombie survivor game mode.  You can play for free so why not give it a shot.

/edited...i accidentally a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 16:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking forward to this, thanks for sharing.  I hope it turns out as good as I believe it could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 16:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks cool, thanks for sharing, I'll give it a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 16:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime I see a thread like this I:

1)  Find yet another game I've overlooked and start to play.

2)  Encourage everyone to check out [King Arthur's Gold](http://kag2d.com/en/).  It's truly some of the best gaming fun I've had in a long time and have been an avid player for nearly a year.  They are about to release their beta and it will then also be available on Steam.  You can play for free but I was sold on it after a few hours.

  Also, here is a great article on the game creator that was just published:  http://indiestatik.com/2013/03/20/king-arthurs-gold/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 15:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was watching Dredd a few weeks back (finally) I said, holy crap, Karl Urban would make a great Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought some off of Amazon, 100' for $98. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 20:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM'd as well, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I better start stretching...yes, things might get to that point.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh its not that bad and obviously if the place was going to fall down and the city wouldn't let them do anything, then ok, I can understand.  Most articles of late are how they should tear down Wrigley to increase revenue and I think they've lost sight of what baseball is to a lot of us.  I've been to many modern ball parks and I hate them.  Loud blaring music, giant jumbo-tron with guess which hat the baseball is under, etc.  I love Wrigley and the atmosphere and I think it's incredibly important to who the Cubs are.  It's my opinion and stated from the start I'm probably in the minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 17:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  If they tear down Wrigley or move the Cubs, I'm done.  My grandparents took me to games there, I took my kids to games there.  My family going back to my great grandfather have a lot of memories in the place and is why I'm still a fan despite the decades of pain.  Yes I want them to win, a new stadium, at least in my eyes, is the least of their concerns.  However I do support the upgrading of the facilities and so forth and I hope they can find the right solution that does't impact the beauty of the park.

I realize some people don't care and perhaps I'm in the minority but there are some things in baseball that need to stay and I hope Wrigley is still there for my grand kids to enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 21:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was very helpful, game is still downloading, hoping to hop in tonight, thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 16:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for getting that info.  I've heard similar good things but this put it in a context which tells me I will really enjoy it.  Kudos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 15:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is what my wife would do if she played college football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I got to that damn bridge it cost me $2 to make that jump, the pressure was too much for a 9 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this goddamn jump [Fixed] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 06:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh, that's the very first person I found, there's an older couple walking just to the right of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 17:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a post from a few months back, I listed several I recommend plus many others shared theirs.  Thanks!

[LINK](http://www.reddit.com/r/lincoln/comments/11j9gq/volunteer_opportunities_around_lincoln/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 17:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what to compare it to.  Requires tremendous amount of teamwork and communication.  Its a mixture of RTS and FPS.

Here is a [PC Gamer Review](http://www.pcgamer.com/review/natural-selection-2-review/).

Here is their [YouTube channel](http://www.youtube.com/user/naturalselection2hd).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 15:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this game is incredible, for 50% off, it's a steal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 18:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was an available lot we liked for building our new home.  We saw it a few times and decided to have the builder come look at it.  He liked it as well so we began discussing some potential ideas just when the neighbors adjacent to the property let their giant barking dog out to go to the bathroom.  We all smiled and climbed in our cars and left.

Basically, as some probably have said, visit the home/site several times during different time periods morning/noon/evening/later at night.  Sit in your car with the windows down for a while.  Look at traffic, listen for dogs, maybe there is a loud church/school bell or distant train horn that will disturb your sleep or be bothersome.  Maybe the neighbor gets off work and likes to jam with his death metal band or his daughter is learning the saxophone and never stops playing.  Anything you can think of that may be bothersome over time or will affect your ability to sell the house later on.

When we bought our first home it was about 15 miles from a fairly small airport.  We were not on the flight path and never heard a single commercial flight coming in or out of the airport and trust me, we tried.  We later found out after purchasing our home that one weekend a month, the local Airforce reserve practiced their take offs/landings and fly circles over the airport.  This brought them directly over our home, for 48 hours in a row, once a month...loud refueling planes.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boeing_KC-135_Stratotanker

We got used to it but it wasn't something we anticipated.  Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ran into this as a seller 3 months ago.  Our neighbors fence encroached by 1 1/4" but only starting at the last 1/3 of the fence.  So only 1/3 encroached and at its most extreme was 1 1/4".

http://imgur.com/y5kVFPO

That is the survey marker and the fence post.  The potential buyer wouldn't purchase without a clean survey and this was our first offer after nearly a year on the market.  Even the survey guy was in shock that they cared such a slight encroachment.  

I discussed it with my neighbor and offered to pay for any supplies and I'd even do the work myself.  In the end it cost me a case of beer and a $50 gift card to a nice restaurant as a thank you.  He did all the work and it took him about 6 hours to move 4 fence posts.  He only moved it just enough and it was so close I think the survey guy let it slide.

I tried to be a good neighbor and hopefully I was.  If I was in his same shoes I'd hope to respond in a similar fashion.

Ultimately these are going to be people you have to live with so either choose to handle this in a way to keep peace or I'd look elsewhere.  If you are going to look out your window every day and think about that fence, it's not worth it or if you think it will affect the potential sale of your home, then move on.  Best of luck, it's a challenging situation and I don't understand why people wouldn't get a survey (cheap I guess) and second wouldn't build with at least 2 feet buffer to avoid crazy issues like this.

...just realized after typing this all out that your post is a month old...anyway, I hope everything worked out for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read emaciated and I wanted to buy Canada a sandwich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 15:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 18:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father-in-law has it and loves it.  I was invited to the beta but opted to wait until better phones come out later in the year.  My wife and I pay $95 for two phone lines with very basic phones, very limited texting, no web, etc.   I am a telecommuter and she runs a daycare out of our home so these would be an ideal solution for us.  I'll revisit it again in 6 months.

To answer the question I keep seeing repeated, it is 100% unlimited and they rely on their customers to use WIFI as much as they can to help keep those costs down.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 01:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy mother of god, why am I just learning about this.  Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 01:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been meaning to try this after it relaunched but sort of forgot about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 01:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King Arthur's Gold.  They have a free and a paid version.  I tried this nearly a year ago and after about 4 hours I bought it.  I play it nearly every day and love it.  Give it a try, its awesome!

http://kag2d.com/en/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sad, frustrated, disappointed... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday was my 37th Birthday.  July 19th will be my TEN year wedding anniversary.  I am originally from near Chicago, even lived there for a while after college.  Grew up a huge Cubs fan and when I go to Wrigley it's almost a religious experience for me.  It's my connection to family who have passed on and all the fans who came long before me.  I felt the stars may have been aligned and I would get the rare opportunity to see my favorite band play at my favorite venue for a once in a life time experience.   I'm grateful that some of you were lucky to get tickets and sort of kicking myself for not being in the TEN Club.  With three kids and mortgage, it's hard to justify the expense when it comes down to it. Every penny counts you know.

Pearl Jam has been "my band" since I was 15/16 years old.  Living in the Midwest, I've only been able to see them one time and even then I had to travel 10 hours.  I got to see Brad once at the Ranch Bowl (RIP) in Omaha.  There were 7 of us at that show, total, and it was an amazing experience that will live with me forever.  I got to hang out with Stone at Perkins while the band waited for their food.  I sat there for a while and asked awkward questions because I was too star struck to hardly speak.

I have every cassette, cd, vinyl.  I have posters and bootlegs and t-shirts.  The band saved me during difficult times and opened me up to a world of music, friends, ideas that helped shaped who I am today.  I am a die hard fan in every sense of the word and to the extent I could afford over the years.

What frustrates me is that there are thousands of fans just like me who would do about anything to be at this show.  I've busted my ass the last 10 years to be a good husband and father and we are finally at a point where opportunities like this are an option for us.  To celebrate our anniversary, watching the band that changed my life, with the woman who changed my life, would have meant so much to me.

Yesterday, I try all i can to get tickets as do my friends spread across the country.  Swapping texts of encouragement, holding our breath after each agonizing, 30 second countdown completes.  I know one person whose a friend of someone who got 4 tickets, all spoken for.  I had tears in my eyes when "this event is sold out" appeared on my screen.

I go online today, hundreds and hundreds of tickets for up to $2300 on several ticket broker sites.  Literally breaks my heart.

There is no one at fault, no one to blame, its just the way of the world today.  It's just sad that so many people who truly deserve to be there, probably even more than me, won't get to.  Its disappointing that despite their best effort, "my band" couldn't protect us from the scourge of ticket brokers (lets call them scalpers, that's what they really are).

It's not the end of the world, life will go on.  I've been very fortunate and have an incredible family.  Just had to vent a little this morning after spending weeeeeeks dreaming of the opportunity to go.  As I explained to my wife when the concert was first announced, this was my dream concert, One of those far fetched, what-if scenerios discussed on a long road trip in college, I'd never had imagine would actually take place.

If you were able to get tickets, congrats and I hope you have an incredible time.  I'm probably still heading to Chicago and you'll probably see me standing outside enjoying the tunes anyway.

tl;dr, I'm a big whiny baby who didn't get tickets but hope that many of you did.  :)  Thank you for letting me vent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 20:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natural Selection 2 may be something to look into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was so long ago, I was just saying I enjoyed the multiplayer and I remember, as the OP said, them patching it and it then wasn't fun.  Outside that, its pretty foggy, since then I've gotten married, had 3 kids, etc, I just remember it being fun.  I wasn't hardcore or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if you played it, it doesn't sound like it is the case. The point of capture the flag was to obviously capture the flag and at the start of each round, you could choose 2 force skills from a whole list of them and if used properly, no matter which combination, you could gain an advantage.  That was the point.  Running across a bridge, seeing another coming towards you, blocking their saber toss, then choke and toss them off the edge.  Or power jump over them and saber toss into their back, etc.  It was a lot of fun to play at the time and I think somehow you have misunderstood how the game was played.  I guess I don't get the point you are making about playing a game and not using all tools at your disposal.  I had fond, fun memories playing and I can assure you that's how everyone played the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 06:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this!  With enough practice you could dominate with force choke then force push.  It was incredibly fun if you put the effort in...then they patched it to oblivion and I haven't played it since.  Completely forgot about how much fun that was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 20:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just craziness of recruiting is all I was referencing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 20:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had any choice I'd do Oklahoma and Notre Dame.  I'd swap Oklahoma with Kansas if they were not an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 18:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a very close friend who is the complete opposite of myself and we rarely discuss politics/religion/etc because its not worth it.  We had a similar conversation when the new health care bill was being debated.  

  One of our co-workers brought it up out of curiosity, she is from India and was commenting on how she couldn't believe how much it costs to go to the doctor here in the US.  In India, even someone who is poor and living on the street can see a doctor for free.  My friend remarked that in America, we shouldn't be responsible for others NOT being responsible.  

  I asked if it was someone who had always been responsible, always paid their taxes, good citizen, etc. lost their job and had to choose between paying for Cobra and paying rent/mortgage and chose to let their insurance lapse to survive...then had a life threatening situation like cancer, should they be denied coverage and have to pay the full amount of their care?  Shouldn't we find a way to help them?

His response was, "well, he should of had insurance and it's not our fault he did not."

I asked, "so, not under any circumstance, would you allow him to get healthcare coverage?"

He said, "he should have been better prepared."

I asked, "so is that how you will explain it to Jesus when you get to heaven?"

He said, "Jesus taught people to be responsible for themselves."

ah ok, thanks for clearing that up.

I'm always trying to understand how many "religious" people don't see the huge conflict between their political and religious "beliefs".  

Anyway, sorry to ramble thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 15:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats coach Solich! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, he just said in the press conf it was a pole, just happened about an hour ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 21:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was a rough two weeks.  I would have been pounding my head against the wall too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dixon is now N!

https://twitter.com/sean_callahan/status/299206133481103361 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 18:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also from Sean Callahan.

https://twitter.com/sean_callahan/status/299206133481103361 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tre'vell Dixon signs with Huskers.  I thought he was off the board and on to ASU. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 18:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 15:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My remark was more in reference to OP but agreeing with your statement at the same time.  If we did try and get this guy but lost out, its too bad, looks like a stud.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 15:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article doesn't mention Nebraska and I've not heard of him.

"Alviti chose Northwestern over Michigan State and Notre Dame"

Appears Northwestern got a great get, good luck to him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 22:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> scout.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 15:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just announced on 1620, Sharp   Benning.  Dwayne Johnson's HS coach stated that he verbally commited to Nebraska this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dwayne Johnson commits to Nebraska this morning.  Surprise last minute commitment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 15:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 23:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the whole fiasco started I've:

-met, dated and married my wife, will celebrate our 10 year anniversary this summer.

-had three kids.

-moved four times

I sort of forgot about PJ and Groklaw...was a fascinating yet infuriating case which I enjoyed following for many years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 15:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...i laugh b/c its true.  Now I'm going to go cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 15:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just talking about this the other day with a buddy.

I remember them flagging the home team for the crowd being too loud, and I even remember an NFL game where the QB got on the mic and asked the crowd to quiet down b/c it was hurting the team (penalties).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 15:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got a new suit in Avengers which allowed Whedon to switch back to the classic circle...from what I read he didn't like the triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out my friends vinyl business.  He is going to do my arcade cabinet when I finally get around to building it.

https://www.facebook.com/getivg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 20:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he wasn't quoted by a reporter, a kid told a reporter that is what the coach said, do you know if that is what he said or do you know what the kid said to him...that's all I'm saying.  we don't know if he actually said those word and if he did, what was the context.  Maybe he was being a dick, or maybe the kid isn't being honest, or maybe he told the coach to F off and then this was his response.  context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that this is a quote from a kid whose gone back on his word twice.  Even on Monday he said he was 100% committed to Nebraska.  Then you all are calling out Bo from a second hand quote without context is really silly.

I do wish the kid luck, its a hard choice and I wouldn't of handled it much better at this age.  However, he milked this on Twitter for weeks and maybe he knows what he's doing more than we realize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 02:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to add to this, now that I know the details

-Tickets go on sale on my Birthday
-Concert is on my 10th wedding anniversary
-favorite band
-favorite "venue"

Hope I can get tickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 14:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the hints for this yesterday and just about had tears in my eyes.  I'm originally from near Chicago, huge Cubs fan, love Wrigley and Pearl Jam is my favorite band.  

I told my wife...it's all my favorite things in one place.  I'm going to take my son and it will be his first concert.  Assuming I can get me some tickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 15:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to travel a lot for a job I used to have and spent 1-5 days in a new city each week for about 6 mo out of the year.  I'd often find myself in some pretty cool places like Seattle,San Francisco or San Diego (as well as a ton out of the way places) but of course I was there alone and didn't know a soul.  I often would go to a bar alone and have a few drinks and catch a game.  I'd also go to movies/concerts/museums/etc and yeah, I'd get weird looks but hell, I'm not sitting in my hotel room every night.  I used to be a bartender so I guess I never thought it was that weird...just keep an open mind...might just be a lonely traveler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 20:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I have ADHD.  sounds silly but I feel better...that there isn't something truly jacked up with me or how I learn or manage my life.  Sending this to my wife.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
