<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3414</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 06:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you cant judge people by there character. And maybe thats where you are going wrong. And we all do it, I know.
But just because someone looks a bit rough or something like that doesnt mean they cant be what you want. 
If you were to see my and what I dress around my mates you would look at me like aww yeah typical country chick, really casual, laid back, and its somewhat of a tom boy. 
But when I got out, I dress up and look like a girl.
My hobbies are nothing to what you'd expect by looking at me what so ever.
I'm rambling here, but you have to get to know someone. 
Someone is out there for you, just dont give up hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever thought that maybe your standards are too high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 05:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant look for things like love, you have to let love come to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 05:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 05:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I HAVE THE SAME PROBLEM!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!**
When im around my friends I am just like the funny nerd who says random crap, and with people I dont know, I am all up in their face like i'll fight you raddy rah. I hate it. I just want to be able to be me, but I dont know who I am.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 02:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?
They dont speak Egyptian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 02:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that she is just upset and finding it hard to cope with by the sounds of everything. 
She is worried that you are gong to get really hurt. And you know what mothers are like, very protective over their children. 
She still loves you and your fiance dearly, she just doesnt want to see anyone get seriously hurt over it.
And she will come around, you just have to give her time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she is just finding it hard to cope with?
I mean she loved him at first, and now she knows this, she is struggling with the fact that your partner is doing these things to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia man, not Labor Day here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh I see. 
So she has changed her views once being told about you liking BDSM?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents.
~~The bastards~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your 18 and engaged already? 
That seems quite young to be engaged, how do your parents feel about you having a fiance at this age? 
Maybe if they disagree to some extent, that could be another reason why your home life has become harder?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your parents may not approve of this choice, but if you were to have children with your fiance, i'm sure they would be very happy for you, and be there for your children. 
How long as it been since they found this out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not a wanker, at all. 
You said straight up what you were, and that is basically fuck buddies. 
The thing is, there are some chicks out there who get attached, obviously she is one of them. 
Unfortunately for her, she is going to be in pain at the fact you are moving away and dont want the realtionship, when she does.
I did a long distance relationship. They are shit. And I dont know one person who has been in one that has worked out.
The odds are near impossible to keep the relationship from failing. 
You just need to keep telling yourself she will be okay, and so will you. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work, my boss came in and started to talk to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are one lucky person, I live with my parents, I have to be clothed 24/7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pics or it didnt happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in a simlar situation.
I dated someone for two years who was absuive, nasty and a very horrible person, with an even more horrible of a family. 
His mother physically absued me many times, along with her son (who I dated). At first it was all omg he is amazing perfect guy raddy rah, it took two weeks to make me realise he was scum. Why two weeks? Because thats when he rapped me. I tried telling my friends asking them for help, and they were all like he is amazing you are lying. So I lost my friends. All of them. I had no confidence what so ever, it took me a very long time until I finally got the courage to stand up and say you are a horrible person, and I dont want to be with you. 
It hurts knowing your friends love the person you hate.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 01:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reeow! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I'm in the mood for a soul baring, meaningful, and deep conversation with anyone. Have you got something you need to get off your chest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 00:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 07:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lord.
Someone get this guy out of here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 07:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did.
I have gone twice so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 07:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
My mum is disabled and has been for around 11 years now.
The disease she has, 9/10 people kill themselves with as it is that painful and debilitating. 
A lot of talk around my house is to do with the pain she goes through, the money we spent of her medical bills and what not.
I am 19 years old, so most of my life I have been around a lot of medical talk, financial struggle, doctors visits, hospital visits etc. 

The best thing I find helps me get through the whole ordeal is writing things on paper, and then just burning them or throwing it away. It relives so much emotion, and I also listen to classical music when I write it. Strangely, it gives it so much more emotional relief.

With you wife, you need to get out the house as much as she is able to. Even if its going out for coffee in the morning and then stroll around the town till you have had enough. 
Keep her and your mind busy, do little things, plant a tree in the garden, board games, watch movies etc..

The main thing though, reinsure her every day, no matter what the outcome, you love her always and you will stay and support her through thick and thin, because without support she wont survive.

I hope this helps you, I wish you and your wife the best of luck with the outcome. 
I'm here for you if you need a chat or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 06:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you play that song backwards, the chorus says "eat the body, hide the body" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 06:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately some people in Australia still think they are in fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 06:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all ugly in our own ways.
It takes a real person to see those imperfections as perfections.
Believe it or not, you are a beautiful person 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 05:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a myth, but when I was little I literally thought that when a guy came in a chicks mouth, if she swallowed, she would become pregnant.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 05:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me, but a friend of mine.

Went on a date with a girl to the movies, and she asked him to finger her, turns out she'd forgotten she was on her period along with having a tampon up there. 

I'd never laughed so hard in my life. 
I am a terrible, I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 08:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your help, means a lot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 06:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are thinks I want to hear, I have such a passion for driving and for me to be scared in a car is so hard to cope with. 

I hope you are okay, and that there weren't bad injuries to yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 06:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have a strong passion for people who dont pay attention driving. 
The guy who hit me was using his phone whilst he had two kids in the back, both under the age of 5. 
It is disgusting to think that someone is that careless about their own child's safety along with others on the road. 

It now gives me more passion to become a police officer and help stop people like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 05:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww wow, you are okay now though yeah?

I really like the idea of keep telling myself that others and I are good drivers, if i put my faith in them and myself that should help.
Also the singing loud as well.

Thank you so much for your comment, I for sure will be taking these steps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 05:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This, is the best idea yet. 
You sir, are a genius.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 04:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be taking your advice on board, thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 04:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 04:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your username matches your comment, very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I was involved in my first car accident yesterday. How did you over come the fear of getting back in the drivers seat?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 04:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday, driving home from work, I was stopped at an intersection, when someone ran into my car, hitting me at 55kms/per hour, making my car a right off, and having not one dint on the guy who it me cars.
I'd only had the car for 3 weeks, it was my first car, paid a fair enough for it, and now its completely destroyed.

I ended up going to hospital for a few hours, and have been told I have sever whiplash.
I'm so scared to drive again, I was in the car with my brother today who was helping me with organise things with the insurance company, and at each intersection I screamed because I thought the person behind wasnt going to stop. 

EDIT: Spelling 

Is there anything I should know or do, to help me get over this fear?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 07:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guessing your cats name is ninja? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 06:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When im home alone and cooking, I pretend as if i am hosting my own cooking show. And say what I am doing out loud.
"Now you are just going to put the bacon in the fry pan, and let it sit about one minute each side to make it cripsy" raddy rah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 06:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only person here who actually thinks this is funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 06:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rihanna - Hate that i love you ft. Ne-Yo
I'm still in love with my ex :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 06:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither have I.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 08:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a strong women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 05:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah-MAZINGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGG!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 08:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like im having a bowl of ceral with a side of warm toast in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 08:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and peanut butter, with honey on top of toast!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 08:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot chips and sugar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 08:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference between confidence and cockyness. Mate note of that. 
But confidence is something that attracts women. I myself, love when a guy has confidence, but if its they are over confident you look like an asshole. 
When we see a man who is confident, it shows us that are they are going to make the first move, so say if something was to happen between you and a women, if you have low confidence, she (unless ballsy as fuck) may come up to you and be like "hey whats up" or whatever, whereas we want that to be the guy who comes up and says "hey im ___ and i just wanted to say you look really nice today" or something simple like that to start of the conversation. 
Any girl will continue a conversation, if you have the confidence to go up and start talking to her genuinely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 05:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my reaction as well!
It is quite freaking at the facts he has presented, but then he weird post its just so unusual but its so enticing!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clever number plate needed! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 08:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 08:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2007 Gun Metal Gray Subaru Impreza 
Am needing a cool number plate!
Any ideas Reddit?
The max is 6 letters
KGO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 08:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First day of primary school, a fly went up my nose. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 05:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont do it, just dont.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 05:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had the problem of what to buy my boyfriend a few times. 
You could get him something for his car? New car mats, sound system?
Pair of sunglasses? or a wallet? Watch?

I have plenty of idea, if you want to hit me up a message for some more ideas :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 00:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a god in my eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting it in that retrospect, it is very much true. 
But i still cant work out why is last post is just so out of the ordinary?
If he had the time to log on and comment or even doing it by phone, you'd think he would of had that little bit more time to give us more details. I mean he didnt edit the post, he commented of a post that was very randomly selected... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 08:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW DID YOU DO THAT?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just so unsure of this whole thing.
Like there is a thread on this saying its fake, but I believe it to be true, I mean who would go through all this effort just to get some interest. But if he was well I tip my hat of to him.
But there are a few suss things that make me think it is.
I mean first of all his username is the address of his work.
And then his last post "not okay something wrongg", is not like any of his other posts. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 05:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aussie and not even I know what the hell you are on about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 02:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOL!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell us that you are okay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 10:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah not what you mean there, I got to that stage as well, my motivation lasted for about 2 weeks, and went straight back to bludging in class lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are things that have woken you up and realized you aren't living your life to the fullest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 10:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 19, and today I went of my first plane flight, I know its small thing to some, but for me it was massive. 
And as I was staring out the window, It hit me like a ton of bricks that this is the most thrill seeking thing i've done in my life, and i'm living my life they way it should  be.

What is something that has woken you up and made you realized you do shit all with you life?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 11:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BACON-COVERED TITTIES FTW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 07:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bacon. 
Nothing is better than bacon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 07:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not a dating site mate.
GTFO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 03:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just brought a car and will be needing an air freshener, what brand is it?! I want my days to be made my by this awesomeness of an air fresherner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 03:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That must be an epic smelling car freshener. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 01:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sir, have just made my day. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 01:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is now my motivation for gym.
THANK YOU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm lacking motivation. Reddit what are some of your favourite motivational quotes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 01:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 07:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleeping in an empty bed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 06:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have had a couple rebounds, and they were good, but nothing compared to my ex.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming on reddit.
No matter how hard I try, I seriously can not go a day without checking it at least 7 times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 05:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you, are the best sister, I just pictured my brother doing that for me and came to the assumption you were a boy.
None the less.
BEST SISTER EVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 12:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... This is awkward... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 08:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the best brother ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
