<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2724</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet activists are sending thousands of FAXES to Congress to oppose CISA cybersecurity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true for many offices. They still get flagged as having come in as faxes though, which sets them apart and helps cut through the noise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just the fax: internet activists go analog to fight Congress on cybersecurity bill. Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act would give tech firms broad latitude to collect personal data  even as Congress uses old tech to avoid prying eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 18:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty awesome. It's technically a robot :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISPA is back with a new name. Since Congress seems to be stuck in 1984, people are sending them FAXES opposing the bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 17:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeez, Google, is that how you really think of us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 18:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama rushes to Capitol to save trade deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hours left before Congress votes to rubber stamp Obama's secret trade deals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 22:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate rubber stamps plan to block piracy websites in Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealed: The Secret Immigration Chapter in Obama's Trade Agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 20:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans receive mysterious packages "from" President Obama with a letter asking them to "rubber stamp" his "secret trade agenda" and an actual rubber stamp included for the purpose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So last week, to protest the TPP, we went around to every Republican's office in the House of Representatives and delivered a package with a letter from "President Obama" asking them to please "rubber stamp" his secret trade deal. The packages contained an actual rubber stamp for the purpose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FFTF had a letter hand delivered to each Republican member of House that purported to be from the President asking the legislator to "rubber stamp" his "secret trade agenda," and even including an actual rubber stamp saying "I approve President Obamas secret trade deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So last week we went around to every Republican's office in the House of Representatives and delivered a package with a letter from "President Obama" asking them to please "rubber stamp" his secret trade deal. The packages contained an actual rubber stamp for the purpose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 17:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA surveillance debate gives rise to bipartisan civil liberties coalition. Behind the scenes, the battle to curb National Security Agency call records surveillance catalyzed an unlikely coalition that bridged far-left and far-right political divides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always best to refer to people by the gender pronouns they prefer.  That's just basic decency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes - i did not see that you misgendered her. Please don't do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is a fair point. I (OP) am a transgender musician, so I guess I was just stoked to hear about another trans woman's musical accomplishments from decades ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a nonprofit and get paid respectably. No one deserves to make $500,000 a year while people starve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Wendy Carlos, a transgender woman, helped popularize electronic music in 1968 with a series of reordings of compositions by JS Bach played on a Moog synthesizer. She won three Grammys and recorded music for the soundtrack of Clockwork Orange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 07:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fun fact: Red Cross CEO makes $500,000 per year. http://www.redcross.org/news/press-release/Red-Cross-Statement-on-Inaccurate-Viral-Email-on-Charity-CEO-Pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Cross Built Exactly 6 Homes For Haiti With Nearly Half A Billion Dollars In Donations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Red Cross says it has provided homes to more than 130,000 people. But the actual number of permanent homes the group has built in all of Haiti: six. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 18:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish that were true, but TISA will impact Intellectual Property policies that impact the Internet, as well as things like global net neutrality. Similar to the TPP it is not really a "trade" deal but a backroom agreement that contains all kinds of policies that very much impact technology. Check out EFF's blog post about it here for more about the tech concerns: https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2015/05/tisa-yet-another-leaked-treaty-youve-never-heard-makes-secret-rules-internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks exposes secret trade deal. Critics argue new deal would further consolidate corporate power in the hands of a few companies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks releases documents related to controversial US trade pact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couriers purporting to have a message from President Obama showed up at the offices of several House Republicans with a note reading: Please rubberstamp [sic] my secret trade agenda. I have included a stamp for your convenience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 20:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 100 organizations explain why they oppose Fast Tracking the Trans-Pacific Partnership in their own words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today more than 100 organizations are participating in a day of action to stop Fast Track for the Trans-Pacific Partnership. On this page they tell you why, in their own words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 15:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks announced an effort Tuesday to crowd-source a $100,000 reward for the remaining chapters of the Trans-Pacific Partnership trade deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks offers $100K bounty for release of secret Trans-Pacific Partnership text </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks announces $100K bounty for trade deal text </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As of today, for the first time in 14 years, you can make phone calls without the NSA hoovering up the records of who you called and for how long. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of Sites Block Congress in Protest Ahead of Patriot Act Expiration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of Sites Block Congress in Protest Ahead of Patriot Act Expiration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 19:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14,000 websites protest Patriot Act with 'blackout' and semi-nude photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 03:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 23:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really interesting info. Is there a link or source for this? Would love to check it out. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 10,000 websites 'blackout' Congress in protest of NSA surveillance laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 23:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 20:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Call and email your reps right now: https://sunsetthepatriotact.com

2) Drop by your member of Congress' office with a letter and a copy of the constitution. It's easy: https://www.sunsetthepatriotact.com/?ref=fftf dropoff=1#dropoff

3) Make sure everyone around you knows that the USA Freedom Act is NOT a meaningful reform bill and won't end mass NSA spying. Share this op-ed to spread the word: http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/homeland-security/242736-no-congress-did-not-just-vote-to-end-nsa-spying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the USA Freedom Act. This op-ed explains very clearly how it fails to end bulk surveillance: http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/homeland-security/242736-no-congress-did-not-just-vote-to-end-nsa-spying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These naked activists are trying to black out Congress' Internet to protest the PATRIOT Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To protest the PATRIOT Act, 10,000 websites are blocking access to Congress' IP addresses, redirecting to photos of naked NSA protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Internet Defense League](https://www.internetdefenseleague.org) is leading on this and there are thousands of sites involved in that. Mainstream press are already reporting on this: http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/243416-activists-black-out-websites-for-congress-in-patriot-act-protest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blackout site has a lot more information about this issue than the FFTF homepage. Generally our homepage is not very high traffic, people tend to head directly to our campaigns from social media or news articles etc. 

Our press releases and analysis etc are on our tumblr, which is not blocked.

I forwarded your question about EOP IPs, perhaps they can be added :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link is broken because of silly github thing. This should work: https://www.blackoutcongress.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are few things easier than sitting on reddit making cynical comments about how nothing will change. This protest has already generated several media articles, including the one linked here in The Hill, which nearly all members of Congress read daily. 

Change takes time, but these grassroots efforts make a difference. Imagine how much worse things would be if no one ever spoke up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This campaign just launched and is led by Fight for the Future and the [Internet Defense League](http://internetdefenseleague.org) (IDL.) The IDL alone already has thousands of websites signed up to participate in all their widget-based campaigns, and thousands more sites joined quickly after launch, probably in part due to this reddit thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10K websites block Congress in Patriot Act protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To protest the PATRIOT Act, more than 10,000 sites have added code that redirects any visitors from Internet protocol (IP) addresses stemming from Congress away from their site and towards a protest page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To sunset the PATRIOT Act, over 10,000 web sites are now blacking out access to Congress, redirecting to the naked photos of indignant NSA protestors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul Gets Pressured to Block Any Last-Minute Patriot Act Renewal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To sunset the PATRIOT Act, over 10,000 web sites are now blacking out access to Congress, redirecting to the naked photos of indignant NSA protestors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 23:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC seeks to implement $1.7bn plan to benefit low-income internet users. [B]roadband access is essential for access to education and information, for managing and receiving health care, and for daily tasks, the agency says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC seeks to implement $1.7bn plan to benefit low-income internet users. [B]roadband access is essential for access to education and information, for managing and receiving health care, and for daily tasks, the agency says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 20:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the next few days, the first of many surveillance reform battles will end. Section 215, the alleged authority under which the NSA has been indiscriminately gathering phone data on Americans, will expire, or sunset on June 1st. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 19:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fact is, sunset is the only thing that will definitely stop massive spying under section 215. It wont stop mass surveillance more generally, but killing the law that NSA and FBI have abused for years is the first step. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interactive map shows how your member of Congress voted on NSA surveillance. Congress is having a do-over vote on Sunday night, hours before the PATRIOT Act expires. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever been to a protest? What made you want to go and what was it like for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 21:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet Health Test checks to see if your ISP is secretly slowing your connection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy advocates held nationwide vigils last night calling for Congress to let the PATRIOT Act expire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy activists staged 'sunset vigils' as a death watch for Patriot Act spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So far no mainstream news outlets have covered this, but here are some beautiful photos from the nationwide protest vigils against the PATRIOT Act last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 19:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-NSA artists/activists planted tape recorders around NYC to see whether people really have "nothing to hide" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 06:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's basically what groups like [Fight for the Future](https://fightforthefuture.org) and [Demand Progress](https://demandprogress.org) are... 

Full disclosure: I work for FFTF (and love it) :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment thread for suggested better names for bills that Congress just wants to sneak past us:

"Free Beer and Privacy for All Act of 2015"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 05:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reauthorizes 215 while limiting some of the ways the government can use it (supposedly). But many privacy groups (full disclosure: like mine) feel it creates as many new problems as it addresses. More info here: https://usafreedom.fail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 04:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You betcha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media is trying really hard to frame the TPP issue specifically as a fight between "labor" / "liberals" and "Obama." 

It's really helpful to write short op-eds, only like 600 words, for your local paper encouraging your lawmakers to oppose Fast Track and referencing a variety of reasons that show there is resistance from across the political spectrum. 

Some op-eds to sample from:
[The Hill](http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/foreign-policy/241354-if-pelosi-supports-an-open-internet-she-should-oppose-fast)
[The Guardian](http://www.theguardian.com/media-network/2015/may/08/trans-pacific-partnership-obama-irony)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The op-ed linked breaks down a ton of the issues with the USA Freedom Act specifically. This page has it in bullet point form if that's easier: https://usafreedom.fail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a "snafu" where the Senate failed to get what's called "cloture" last week, but they played some inside baseball, struck a deal and eventually passed "Fast Track" for the TPP just today.

HOWEVER, the real fight over this has always been on the House side, and those close to DC are saying we did well in the Senate vote and we should keep the pressure on. You can contact lawmakers with a few clicks here: https://battleforthenet.com/internetvote

For those unfamiliar with TPP and Fast Track, info here: https://eff.org/issues/tpp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The USA Freedom Act is being hyped as a prohibition of the N.S.A.s controversial mass surveillance practices, but it actually extends the PATRIOT Act for years and opens up new avenues for more invasive forms of government spying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This quick test shows if your ISP is secretly throttling your internet speeds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case we can thank Bush, Obama, and a slew of other politicians from both mainstream political parties who have enabled this surveillance state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how 70% of responses on the Internet are like this:

Person A: This thing is bad. Here's some well thought out reasons why it's bad, to help more people understand that it's bad.

Person B (troll): You thought the bad thing might be good? FOOL!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to one of those PATRIOT Act protests today. I think I picked out the right shirt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 22:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually for the most part agree with you -- it seems very likely that governments will continue various forms of spying no matter what laws are passed, and one of the most concrete things we can all do is protect ourselves. The third link, [Reset the Net](https://resetthenet.org), is an entire campaign focused around promoting encryption, both on the user side and among web apps and services.

That said, the fight against mass surveillance is a culture war. And one of the most public aspects of the government's disregard for our privacy are the BLATANT laws like the PATRIOT Act that straight up say it's okay for them to violate our basic rights. 

We have a real opportunity right now to put the government on the defensive, explaining to the public why these runaway programs should exist, and build a movement of people who agree that bulk collection of our private data is just not okay.

That will lead to more people speaking out and taking action, but also more people encrypting their shit, which makes mass surveillance more difficult and expensive to conduct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 22:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tools   info for those who DO NOT WANT:

https://endsurveillance.com

https://usafreedom.fail

https://resetthenet.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or perhaps [the opposite...](http://www.theguardian.com/media-network/2015/may/08/trans-pacific-partnership-obama-irony) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, Congress did not just vote to end NSA spying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The USA Freedom Act is being hyped as a prohibition of the N.S.A.s controversial mass surveillance practices, but it actually extends the PATRIOT Act for years and opens up new avenues for more invasive forms of government spying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be holding it down in Boston with my 4 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The companies that signed this letter are mostly small startups. The largest companies like Facebook, [are supporting](https://cms.fightforthefuture.org/facebook) the TPP and TPA / Fast Track legislation, because they can afford a seat at the table and it gives them broader power to set policy that protects their profits but stifles competition and innovation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but how much can the individual citizen do when even members of congress don't fully known whats in it?

There are a lot of things that individuals can do! The Japanese press just reported that a TPP ministerial was CANCELLED because Fast Track in the U.S. is still uncertain. We have been really successful in delaying it so far!

Here are things that redditors can do to help:

1) Contact your lawmakers in both the Senate and House. [This site](https://battleforthenet.com/internetvote) makes it really easy with just a few clicks.

2) Write an op-ed for your local paper about tech-related concerns with Fast Track and the TPP. The media wants to frame this as if it's just a fight between "liberals" and "Obama." We need more voices out there about why this is bad from a variety of perspectives. Use this op-ed in [The Hill](http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/foreign-policy/241354-if-pelosi-supports-an-open-internet-she-should-oppose-fast) or this one in [The Guardian](http://www.theguardian.com/media-network/2015/may/08/trans-pacific-partnership-obama-irony) (disclosure: i wrote it) as fodder to write your own.

3) If you run a startup, website, or small company, call your representative's LOCAL DISTRICT OFFICE and request a meeting to discuss your concerns with Fast Track and the TPP. Even if they can't actually attend a meeting, getting lots of requests like this is a really powerful way to pressure them.





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a letter from 250+ technology companies about a technology policy issue... who's stretching? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 21:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just one quote from a letter with many signers, including from organizations (full disclosure: like mine) that ARE in fact experts on international trade agreements and their impact on digital rights. The reason his quote was highlighted was because this is r/technology, and presumably the thoughts of a prominent technologist on this issue might be of interest to readers in this subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those companies support the Trans-Pacific Partnership because they can afford a seat at the table, allowing them to set policies that benefit themselves while endangering the health of the entire Internet economy. 

The startups and small companies that signed this letter are the ones that EVERY politician loves to brag about supporting every time they use the words "small business" and "tech economy."

I feel your pain, but lawmakers SHOULD listen to these voices. If they don't, it's up to us Internet users to fight back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul starts filibuster of PATRIOT Act renewal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul starts filibuster of PATRIOT Act renewal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for paying attention :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 19:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the full text of the letter and list of signers, by the way: https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2015/05/hundreds-tech-companies-congress-tpp-and-fast-track-harms-digital-innovation-and </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of tech companies line up to oppose Trans-Pacific Partnership due to Internet freedom concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creator of Ruby on Rails: "The TPP makes a mockery of democratic legislative ideals ... It's shrouded in secrecy exactly because it would wither in sunlight. It's a terrible piece of overreach to endow a few special interests with enormous and unsavory power." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creator of Ruby on Rails: "The TPP makes a mockery of democratic legislative ideals ... It's shrouded in secrecy exactly because it would wither in sunlight. It's a terrible piece of overreach to endow a few special interests with enormous and unsavory power." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cory Doctorow in The Guardian: If TPPs backers truly believed that they were doing the peoples work, theyd have invited the people into the room ... they went to extreme, unprecedented measures to stop anyone from finding out what was going on" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 17:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of tech companies line up to oppose TPP trade agreement. Letter signed by more than 250 companies demands greater transparency and says dangerously vague language would criminalise whistleblowers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of tech companies line up to oppose TPP trade agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 16:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Follow the Money: USA Freedom Act Backers in Congress Have Taken More Than Twice as Much Money From Intelligence Contractors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use this link to send an email with a few clicks or copy and paste the form letter there if you want: https://www.ifeelnaked.org/?email=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do your Senators stand on surveillance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 19:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress is voting on the future of the PATRIOT Act this week. See where your lawmakers stand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critics blast NSA phone records bill as "fake reform" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 23:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USA Freedom Act passes House, codifies bulk collection for first time, critics say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy groups baulk at government's "fake" surveillance reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Judge: "Don't be fooled by the USA Freedom Act. It won't stop government spying." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plans for Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement "in tatters" after Senate vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victory for Grassroots as Fast Track Goes Down in Crucial Senate Vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 00:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealed: FBI violated its own rules while spying on Keystone XL opponents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 21:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AIPAC got an amendment added to today's vote on "Fast Track" for the Trans-Pacific Partnership that would make it official US trade policy to punish countries and companies that participate in boycotting Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> reddit, the Senate votes TOMORROW to advance "Fast Track" for the Trans-Pacific Partnership. Here's that site where you can email and call your lawmakers with a few clicks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> reddit, the Senate votes TOMORROW to advance "Fast Track" for the Trans-Pacific Partnership. Here's that site where you can email and call your lawmakers with a few clicks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> reddit, the Senate votes TOMORROW to advance "Fast Track" for the Trans-Pacific Partnership. Here's that site where you can email and call your lawmakers with a few clicks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 23:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunlight Foundation: Nike-backed "non-profit" group is pushing the Trans-Pacific Partnership in Oregon with TV ads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nike-backed group pushes Trans-Pacific Partnership in Oregon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trans-Pacific Partnership suggests Obama has no sense of irony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. But she sure likes to say she does, so it's a worthwhile angle to take up with the media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama's visit to Nike headquarters to promote the Trans-Pacific Partnership shows he has no sense of irony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 17:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast may have ghost-written Rahm Emmanuel's letter to the FCC in support of their merger, but we don't know because he's refusing a FOIA request </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 19:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a screenshot of the page, just in case this link gets taken down for some reason: http://i.imgur.com/AcyJpqc.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep Jared Polis (D-CO) does not yet have a public position on Fast Track or the Trans-Pacific Partnership, but this unintentionally public link on his website seems to imply he is planning on supporting it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep Jared Polis (D-CO) does not yet have a public position on Fast Track or the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP), but this accidentally-public link on his website implies he is planning to support it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Koch-funded group that sent thousands of anti-net neutrality comments to Congress accused of "identity theft" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 15:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That exists! https://battleforthenet.com/scoreboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digital rights activists parked a "jumbotron" on Capitol Hill today playing videos asking Ron Wyden to oppose Fast Track legislation for the Trans-Pacific Partnership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 00:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks releases text of secret Trans-Pacific Partnership "Investment Chapter" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 19:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Trade Rep to Congress: if you leak the contents of the Trans-Pacific Partnership trade deal, you'll go to jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USTR to Congress: If you leak the contents of the Trans-Pacific Partnership trade deal, you'll go to jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 21:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This made me so happy and hopeful I had to share it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 20:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 19:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hill is not always known for their subtle headlines, but I think it's fair to say this was an attack on his (terrible, Comcast-funded) position anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruz attacked from the air over net neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 18:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 17:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The folks that stopped SOPA, have delayed CISPA three times, and just won net neutrality? People working to keep the Internet as a free and open platform for exchange of ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 17:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully libertarians agree that decisions that affect the future of the Internet shouldn't be made by government bureaucrats and lobbyists behind closed doors in complete secrecy, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Wyden's internet freedom allies fret that he'll abandon them on trade pact, fly 30-foot blimp outside town hall meetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 17:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is mostly unrelated to net neutrality. Activists are the ones flying the blimp, not the Senator. They're pressuring him to oppose so-called "Fast Track" legislation that would push the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement (a massive trade deal like NAFTA) through Congress with a simple up or down vote and without meaningful debate.

From the latest leaks, we know the TPP contains extremist copyright provisions (think SOPA) that could lead to a more censored, policed, and expensive Internet. 

Some good resources here: https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2014/10/latest-tpp-leak-shows-us-still-pushing-terrible-drm-and-copyright-term-proposals

Action here: https://cms.fightforthefuture.org/ronwyden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet freedom activists are following Senator Ron Wyden all over Oregon with this blimp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet freedom activists are following a Senator all over Oregon with this blimp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet activists are following a Senator all over Oregon with ... a blimp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet freedom activists are following Senator Ron Wyden all over Oregon with this blimp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 22:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
