<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8985</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's not *just* the media's fault? I know... I know... an unpopular view, but maybe they're less involved in moving opinion, and more involved in cravenly following it and echoing it back?

Maybe... the hateful pricks who voted Trump, the DNC pricks who made sure Clinton would get her "chance", the conspiracy waterheads, and of course... the majority of people who couldn't be fucked *to actually vote*... maybe there is a LOT of fault to go around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends in Ireland are torn between an almost psychotic despair, and equally crazy laughter. That said, after Dubya, no one is truly *shocked*, just incredibly disappointed; this may be a new crisis for Americans, but we've been a joke to everyone else for a long time.

Just... a heavily armed joke that sometimes sinks the world economy and invades a country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case, what you're exhaling would still be the biggest factor, but your metabolism would be coming down from a pretty high point... you'd be exhaling a *lot* of CO2 and water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect that one way or another, Trump will not be in that position in four years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much alcohol would an average 6ft tall 185Ib male have to consume to die?

That was the question the OP actually asked... the LD50/toxicity stuff was not presented by the person actually asking the question. Maybe "everyone's agreed" is a bit of an exaggeration, in that light?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not "alt" right... that's the original the neckbeards think they're emulating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In real life? I believe it, online...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Then blaming them for not protecting their castles better, and saying that he made a much better castle and he'll teach them how to make it kick-proof. 

For a fee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Because few, if any people without serious medical issues actually die from the direct effects of alcohol toxicity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still not 100% sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll be too busy "winning" and carving swastikas on tombstones... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the *alcohol* to kill you, in the same way that taking enough cyanide would kill you. Realistically far less alcohol would cause you to lose consciousness, and then you run the risk of aspirating your own vomit; that's what will tend to kill you.

Unless it's taken with other drugs, or you have a pre-existing condition, most people would lose consciousness long before they were able to ingest a fatal dose of alcohol, in the "LD50" sense. Ironically, losing consciousness that way would put them at a high risk of dying... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That might be a bit misleading, given that it's describing death from direct toxicity, whereas alcohol-related deaths (excepting driving and violence) are overwhelmingly the result of aspirating vomit while unconscious; that can occur far *far* below a lethal level of intoxication, in that the alcohol itself is not killing you.

tl;dr You've run into a spherical cow problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think that even many of the more liberal-leaning Americans seem to be unaware of just how *much* of an international pariah Trump is. There is no alt-right/white nationalist community abroad to spin him; he's just "the ridiculous, orange, racist." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that what you're saying is that you're 20 years old, and you feel like you're struggling with your thoughts and behavior? If that's the case, I would strongly urge you to talk to a medical doctor about that, ideally a psychiatrist. This is not an uncommon age for some issues to manifest, and you the sooner you address these issues the better; prevention being worth more than cure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   If they are causing you distress then you might want to see a professional about them.

Just to add, if you feel compelled in some way to follow them, if they're very common, if they take the form of voices of images, etc... seek help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it really is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon's annual data breach report is depressing reading, again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google and Facebook have confirmed that they fell victim to an alleged $100m (77m) scam. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Psyched to Kill NAFTA, Then Advisers Said It Would Hurt States He Won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Best" is not an objective concept, and best of what? Compared to what? In what situation? 

The government has enough trouble checking basic factual claims, such as, "This will help you lose weight" or "This will improve your eyesight;" concrete claims which can be tested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually a problem if their sugar gets too high *or* too low; the situation you're thinking of is one in one someone needs to *very* rapidly raise their blood sugar. Most diabetics have candy, juice, or glucose syrup in case of this particular emergency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ceramic knives do exist, in fact I have a small ceramic paring knife; it's sharper than death itself. That said, I've gone through two of them, because they tend to chip and break without much provocation. 

As for a plastic knife, I'd imagine it wouldn't hold a point or edge for very long, and if you made it very hard, it would also run the risk of shattering. 

Honestly, lots of *metal* knives that aren't explicitly (and well) made to kill people, aren't very good at it. A very sharp blade with no weight, no balance, and whatever you've jerry-rigged for a handle is unlikely to win you an aircraft for example. Even on 9/11, the power of something like a box-cutter died off once people realized what their options really were: fight and maybe die, or die. 

When people get out of line on planes now, people swarm them, and if we're not talking about a plane then the odds are you're not that far from someone with a *real* knife, or a gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people have a larger lung-volume than others, it could have to do with temperature, but mostly it's going to be a matter of the rate at which you're breathing. Humans exhale quite a bit of water, but at rest, in a car, most of us tend to breathe pretty slowly through our noses, which minimizes the rate at which we're releasing water vapor. 

So... mouth-breathers, people who for whatever reason are breathing more deeply/rapidly, that kind of thing will contribute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the CEO of Big Bank, and you're my idiot son with no qualifications whatsoever. I hire you to be a VP however, because you are my son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not magically hard glass, it's usually an arrangement of laminated glass, plastics, etc... designed to shatter in layers and distribute the impact. There *are* glasses which would be better candidates, such as borosilicate glasses, but it would be hard to improvise a blade from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say a lot of shit though... why believe it? 

http://www.snopes.com/bill-nye-gender-chromosomes/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...No. Fuck that shill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... in the timeline of, *The Man In The High Castle*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty much everyone who isn't a North Korean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got you

 https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/66/c2/35/66c2355d05b44f308d8a854a7d33bc0f.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have chosen this, in hindsight, "Researchers have developed a new method to retrieve hominin DNA from cave sediments  even in the absence of skeletal remains."

Sadly, the lure of "Suggest Title" is strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that it's mostly the shitty production values, music, and being aimed at an audience that is the opposite of worldly and jaded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Someone didn't hide Sean's phone after he started *glug glug glug*! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By Being Bad at His Job, Sean Spicer Nearly Causes Market Panic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an adorable albino rug! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh those are young! So cute!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are notoriously picky about letting you stick sharp things in their necks... it's just a pet peeve most of us have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The problem is that a large amount of people read the headlines

The fact is the average person will not read the whole article,

You keep saying this in some form, making a stronger claim each time; do you have any evidence that *the average person* is going to just read the headline?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, hopefully he took that fear and regret the home he faded away and died in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hetjagd auf Nazis" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm truly sorry to hear that, but I am glad that you made the right choice; there is no doubt in my mind that you made the right choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem you're describing isn't with headlines, it's with people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but do you think you could have reached the guy and done real damage with a glass knife? I'm sure he was under guard the whole time, and bailiffs tend not to be small; plus they *do* have guns, truncheons, and tasers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glass is very good at cutting, but it's very subject to chipping and breaking, so glass knives have a *lot* of limitations. In short, you'd need to be extremely skilled to reliably kill someone with such a blade, and evidence suggests you could slip a bomb or a gun past TSA... so why would you try a blade?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Link Discovered between Immune System, Brain Structure and Memory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4036/4254681996_27b1ed7ff0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem isn't the technology, it's people; you can't fix people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Elected by many *many* millions of people, and none of *us* are doing anything to stop them. 

We bitch when some random Muslim goes nuts, and people half a world away don't personally apologize because they're in the same religion. We talk about a "silent majority" and complain that if they don't want to be lumped in with the worst of them, they should *do* something. 

Well... now you know how *they* feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Runs away, while shouting over her shoulder* "You fucking cowards!!!!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the title the BBC chose, although I agree it could be better. Fortunately the article makes it clear that once she'd finished wringing as much publicity and outrage as she could from it all, she bailed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the converse is more likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I'm pretty sure that you're being sarcastic, but I've heard sincere fanatics say *much* crazier shit; Poe's Law is a bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, sorry; I searched, but I must have missed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people with power aren't shooting themselves, they're cashing out; the rest are either powerless, disenfranchised, apathetic, or too stupid/ideological to be helped. 

It's a sinking ship; even if it survives this iceberg, the essential weakness of the state has been exposed, and the reality of its power as purely grounded in military, police, and surveillance is too obvious to go away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't take it with you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much everything is a distraction right now, except what's happening to the EPA, education, and *anything* to do with money (i.e. 15% corp tax rate), etc. 

This is the terminal stage of the pump and dump scheme that is the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh... the satisfied "nyups" at the end... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They never stopped falling for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New computers could delete thoughts without your knowledge, experts warn | No new actual technology, just a discussion of human rights laws pertaining to any future tech [Article itself] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fuck all of this.

That's probably the intended reaction. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wcy8uLjRHPM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew that 'Snow Crash' was going to be *this* prophetic?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Just aside from ruining every American's access to the internet - this will DESTROY the American tech sector. Watch companies literally flee this country, and take all the tech talent with them.

Not just companies... the longer this slide continues, the more people with money or connections, or the education to get out... are going to get out. The US will be left with a bunch of fat, uneducated morons ranting about how exceptional they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. They'll probably also get together with Google and screw with VPN users... bad times ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/xo2KVfR.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me old fashioned, but maybe it's... just a headline... and you're meant to read the article? It would certainly be more productive to do that, than it is to complain about a headline that only exists in your mind, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa-senate-idUSKBN17S0B9?il=0

*lol*

Trump I guess?

http://i.imgur.com/h5dFTcq.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh... thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes... Nature is so famous for being a mouthpiece for the uhhh... San Diego Mormons?

\\\_()\_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does it saying anything about military action in the title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the uneven socks. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not seeing any *claims* of "definitive proof" though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ESPN Axes Around 100 Employees, On-air Talent Included </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any hope of finding better evidence?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not well-versed in this particular area of the sciences, but I have to ask, "No evidence" or "Basically no evidence?" They can be different after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US ready to 'bring Kim Jong-un to his senses' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What people say and claim often has very little to do with anything other than how they want to be perceived.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to add, the fourth most unlikely way is that the target is directly compromised with some kind of rootkit, but that's being totally owned and then having your account compromised, not the other way around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chipotle Is Investigating Unauthorized Activity on Its Payment System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than the lead poisoning they'd get if they questioned orders I'd guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're seriously asking, then I'd contact an attorney; don't trust Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce: http://www.cell.com/cell-reports/fulltext/S2211-1247(17)30456-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genomic Analyses Reveal the Influence of Geographic Origin, Migration, and Hybridization on Modern Dog Breed Development </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sunk my battleship! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, if Donald should actually go down for that, I suspect that Gorshuch will be "encouraged" to resign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KlPQkd_AA6c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Didn't read to the end I see. Maybe on your next account... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the people who believe in government weather manipulation? Unless that changed again, I don't know... keeping track of this shit is tough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out "Cloudbusters"  and "Orgone" too... they're like a special sub-set of these chemtrailers, but they tend to have a psychotic mental illness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know... the way things are going over at Fox News, I wouldn't be shocked if he went down in flames first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Thumbs Up*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/n988gduPMFC8w/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah were buds.

*We're </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/ownrl95.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comma is your friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Repeating yourself... -1

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/DiYooih.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good boy! GOOD boy!!! 

Now... you know the candy that mommy and daddy keep in the locked cupboard?... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Throws a banana* Go on boy, fetch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... it's not like his party controls the house and senate or anything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss the good old days when people like you would want "to have a reasonable discussion about immigration," before launching into a tirade. Now you're just all spittle and fury from the get-go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look... this can't be helpful. These kinds of inaccurate portrayals will never bring this broken land together in the spirit of bipartisanship. A crude bit of animated comedy that makes equally crude people laugh... Besides that's *wwaaaaayyyyy* too many teeth for a Trump supporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love those five rogue black whiskers... what a photogenic cutie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're firing into a crowd, you don't have an intent to kill someone in particular, as you say, but you're trying to kill. Murder requires intent, but it doesn't require that you formulate a particular target except in the moment of the crime (for 2nd degree that is). No reasonable person could expect that firing into a crowd is an attempt to murder people. 

By contrast, firing blindly into a room *could* be a lot of things, including being so careless and depraved that you'd be set up for 2nd degree murder. The crowd though... that's mass-shooter territory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://lovelace-media.imgix.net/uploads/273/b7a1cc40-0250-0133-5014-0ec273752cbd.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You poor, broken toy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mostly used in "depleted" form because it's very *very* dense, and its has a property called pyrophoricity, which means that it reacts very strongly with air (burning essentially). Depleted uranium slugs can be fired at very high speeds, and since Force = Mass x Acceleration, a dense, hard slug is packing a big punch. The pyrophoric effect also means that the tip "sharpens" itself en route, rather than deforming. 

Very... very nasty stuff. 

Beyond that, Uranium could be used in nuclear reactors for power vessels for conventional combat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is called naruto, but more broadly it's a kind of surimi: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Surimi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is going a bit "Ministry of Truth" isn't it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are called "Submarines" in many cases, or it's a matter of a uni keeping interest in a technology with promise, but lots of work yet to do. In this case, I'd say this is a *very* early, very promising technology; no one is talking about "Superbatteries" or anything... much more modest.

What's exciting is that the underlying chemistry doesn't require anything overly expensive, scarce, or difficult to handle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just quoted the article, I'm not trying to editorialize; besides, his name is all over the article and I like to think that the /r/Science crowd tends to go beyond the headlines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A chemistry professor in Florida has just found a way to trigger the process of photosynthesis in a synthetic material, turning greenhouse gases into clean air and producing energy all at the same time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this is an incredibly elaborate experiment to try and get an entire species to facepalm at the same moment? Maybe that opens some gateway to Donald's home dimension of Yuck-Upon-Ptooey... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother spent seven years losing her mind with Alzheimer's, and that was hard enough... your mother... I'm so sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...And the way we've stood up to Chy-^NAH! Yuge!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, and anyone who can't remember them shouldn't be in charge of the lives of other humans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely agree with that, and it's a pretty malignant sort of echo chamber those guys produce. By no means are they alone in that behavior, but they are *loud*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
