<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4399</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 09:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gt banna here. Wham bai.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 08:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All over!! Every corner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 08:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run into sentries n guardians every match on dom and kc. I always use cold blooded. Always get this camo superfast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can still see ur CC number </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf is a snog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 15:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carmen sanDiego  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 06:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You assholes. Pics or gtfo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 07:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG!! IVE BEEN LOOKING FOR A "BENQ" BRAND TV FOR A LONG TIME. HOW MUCH?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 07:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't add this. Its depriving people who paid for the game not being able play it. Imagine if they get kicked from every lobby. They stop buying cod points. Treyarch/Activision  loose money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 05:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply. Now I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 05:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was opening a rare today and the same thing happened to me. Then i reopened it and got 2 commons and a lousy nomad gesture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Question about Leveling up after hitting prestige master </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 05:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently at prestige 9. After I complete my 10th prestige, do i go thru 1-55 again to get #11? or is it just 1 rank each number? Cause, let's say I hit 11 ...is it 1 rank to 12? or 1-55 ranks to 12? Please advise, because to get 1000 would take a long ass time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 04:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you're telling me, they're people stupid enough to BUY hundreds of dollars worth of cod points just to GET GEAR for a 5XP boost? How is leveling up paying to win? I shit on prestige masters....it seem's like i'm under estimating the stupidity of the cod community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got about 7 long shot medals with the Marshall. FFA HC. No attachments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 prestiges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got mauled by an angry mob for suggesting something. Check my last post out. This community is terrible. They have no respect or manners. Or just stating their opinion in a mature manner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how i got massive lashback for  5% xp boost for blackmarket gear. Lol this community is turmoil. I hope u are all happy with the current state of this game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mind me  im a potato.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smh. Does ANYTHING in this game work flawlessly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5% xp on complete blackmarket gear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would like to see the return of this from advanced warfare. 5% xp boost on users with a completed gear set from the blackmarket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highlight reel error. Always crash. Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me I'm wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade in? I said throw it away. Bury it. Have ur dog chew on it or cat poop on it. Sometimes in life we have to take a loss. 60 bucks isnt a big loss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw away bo3. Its cancer. The whole game is broken. Streaks are glitched. Guns are glitched. Maps are glitched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao. I was just on combine and i was the only sob capping B solo 3 times , while others were running around aimlessly. We got got the W thanks to me defending B. Sometimes, its called the bystander effect. Like, i was playing safeguard earlier and my idiot teammates runs past the robot to go killwhore assuming someone would stay back and escort it. I did. And got the W. sometimes people run pass home flag to try n beat the enemy to B Assuming someone would stay back n cap A or C. but theres no mics and everyone is random really. U just hace have to keep ur eyes on teammates and assume the position depending on game mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mw3 - assassin. Need i say more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headshots also was easy for me because i play hardcore primarily on dom or KC ...i got about 5 or 6 headshots per match. I did it when combine use to be voted back to back on that right alley with the x3 scope. I got my longshots and headshots there as well. Headglitched my ass right behind that rock racking up the headshots. Now it doesnt get voted as much, my only 2 maps were stronghold and infected....or is it infection?  I dont even remember. The one in my clip. Lol. Hardcore if ur bestfriend for headshots. If u play skyjacked. Camp right on the side in the back of the map aiming to that small cabin thingy. U get longshots as well as headshots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 06:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg. Finally someone i can relate with. Dude, i hate burst weapons too. After 2 months of playing bo3, ive finally decided to go for dark matter. I started with assult rifles first because i spent most of 2 months using them. I was down to the m8a7,shieva and xr2. Holy hell, the grind for headshots and blood thirstys was crazy. I didnt have a hard time for long shots because i had on the x3 scope and camped in the back on the maps on hardcore mode. After 1 month, i finally got my last bloodthirsty for the shieva today and unlocked diamond today. Then i thought to myself and said screw it. Im not going for anything else. I'll keep diamond on assults only. If u need tips inbox me.

Check out my diamond clip 
https://youtu.be/26Gow1cOpjc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got it a few hours ago. I do pretty ok with it. I get hit markers here and there, but the reload takes foreverrrrrrrr even with fastmags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 11:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use swindler along side a custom paintshop job. I'm at work, i'll upload a pic when I get home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 10:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for me? 8/10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol same here. I gotta check out r/fitness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This morning I went for a run and came back home after 2 mins because I forgot something... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot that I was fat and could only run for 2 mins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game disconnects after match </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime I finish a game and it puts me back into a lobby, after a few seconds,  the game disconnects me. Is this a known bug? Has anyone had similar issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was there a change on hunted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe its me, but recently when i land a match on hunted, I feel like the lighting is totally different. It seems odd and i cant place what happened but i know I'm not crazy but i definitely think the lighting effects were tampered with on hunted. For some reason, it seems as though the sun has shifted. Before, it seemed like we were playing in the middle of the day , but now it looks like we are playing in the morning. I cant be the only one that noticed this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 15:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bo2 dlc snow map. Ski resort map where " lifts " run u over just like trains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 13:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Msg the enemy team. Tell them youre a noob and need to complete camo challenges. Tell them to stand still and not move. Offer them rice Krispy treats . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 13:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont like it because it reminds me of UPHILL and EXPRESS from BO2. you can tell treyarch didn't try with this map. Its the bastard child from uphill and express.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 17:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh lala. Can't wait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 12:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg. Those boobs. Love them. Can we see your pussy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 10:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They play alot of candy crush and just repost every video on their newsfeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope treyarch does something similar for april fools. I enjoyed these from IW. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 09:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 08:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's had many opportunities to, but didnt. 

Bart wasn't,  but lisa and maggie were. 

3 dozen. 

I put him around 320. 

How often does he wear the mr plow jacket? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 08:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao. You beat me to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 07:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mind if i do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 06:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hive was inspiried by TmarT. Hello, I'm Very Excited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 06:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiv everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 06:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hive swarm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 23:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camp in FFA Hc. thats how i got the shieva, m8a7 and xr2 gold. I got about 7-8 headshots per match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 15:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those birthing hips tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 09:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 08:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive gotten 30 back to back as well. Mutiple times. No biggie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 08:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens to me all the time. Shit happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 07:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive gotten many http://imgur.com/YMHllPr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 07:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In paintshop http://imgur.com/YMHllPr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave her. Women are expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 22:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a gf and i cheated on her, but she didnt know and i left my phone at her house one day with evidence on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 14:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 3 year development cycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 07:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I was watching someones Vid the other day and they were talking about black ops 3 was the first true current gen cod with a 3 year development cycle. Then a thought occured to me, while its good in general for a studio to have 36 months to perfect a CoD game, its amazes me that since cod Ghost, cod has literally been shit. Black ops is decent but lets be honest, the beta version was 100% better than the released version. I'll explain why in a moment. People are arguing that black ops 3 is the best cod to date. Its ridiculous that they fail to see that the game is so broken, treyarch has given bo3 so many patches within 3 months that i lost count. With a studio having 3 years to make a Cod, its seem to me that they are forgetting their roots and start putting in shit we don't need or want, they're doing so many unnecessary implementations its taking out the core of what Cod is. If you ask me, the 1 yr cycle cods were the best. In so little time, they've managed to give us alot of shit and cod was at its best (in my opinion). Agreed that they were not in anyway perfect but they were tons of fun. They had their Op guns, tons of maps and hella awesome killstreaks. Which is why it blew up on youtube. Now, I could've delt with bo3 in its beta phase where the hell storm, black hat, m8 was OP AS BLOODCLAAT. It would've been 100% better than its current state. Everyone is praising treyarch, lol. They gave me a game that shipped with basically 4 maps and i only end up playing on 2 ....95% of the time for 13 weeks. What a joke. Bo3 has nothing on mw3 or dare i say even ghost. Now i hear everyone is begging for waw2 or mw4. You know what the real problem is, people don't know what they want, but they like to open their mouths. When these studios first started making these cods as well as olderrrrr video games. You got what you got. You play it, if it was glitched, it was glitched...its what made some games fun. It started becomming a problem when studios started listening to these young twats over twitter, fb and other social media about " how to make cod better " instead of just doing their jobs. That is what started the downfall of cod. Anyways, i hope no one got butthurt about what i just said. IW, treyarch and sledgehammer...are you listening?...boots on the ground, 15-16 maps, tons of guns atleast 1 or 2 OP in each category and some badass streaks that if the enemy calls them out, it would make me wanna turn off my system and go curl up on my mother's lap and cry. Thank you and have a nice day all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 09:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it was me v3 today. I they won obviously. But combined i had more kills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 08:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm weird,  but i wanna see firing range come back. As a freebie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 05:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The latency annoys me to the max in core. I'm tired of dying behind a wall with curving bullets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 04:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks sir. Maybe we can party up one day if you're on the ps4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why i play with a full party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why i said your best friend is the black cell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 07:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you can be the LOVER.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 07:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a sense, yes.  But its cod. Its all about your streaks and the W </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 07:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is irrelevant but before vonderhaar patched key farming in FFA. i was getting 80k xp per match. Check my prior posts. Too bad its over though. Legitly,  i sugguest playing moshpit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From core to hardcore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 07:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since i started playing COD back when mw2 was the bomb, ive only played core. I use to think HC was only for sweats and try hards. Once in a while i would try it out , but i hated it because i always died, i had no uav 80% of the time , no clue how much bullets i had left or if i even had streaks unless i saw it appear on my screen ( text ). I stayed away from HC until recently (bo3) when my friends wanted to party up and play HC, i would away rage quit dying for no reason, 1 shot kill with no time to react,  teammates accidentally killing me, random nades. It was a shit show. About 3 weeks ago, i just hopped into a HC KC lobby to finally get the hang of it so that i can play with my friends. After 2 weeks of playing nothing but HC, i fell in love with it because it teaches you alot. I.e....it teaches you to read spawns. Now, i dont need a uav to know where the enemy is. I dont need to get a shit ton of hit markers to drop 1 guy, 1 shot and move on to the next victim. Its fast paced and tons of fun. HC keeps you on your toes and teaches you to be a better COD player in general. Going back to core would be a noob move for me. guys, play HC for a week or 2, you wont ever wanna go back to core. I had no clue what i was missing out on. Your your bestfriend in HC is the black cell. You dont need a silencer, ghost, fmj, high caliber. Save your slots. I use the HVK with quickdraw, grip and rapidfire. Anteup, engineer and fast hands with seraph combat focus. Hcxd, uav and care package. All i play is HC KC. 3 kills and collect tags, you got your streaks. Using combat focus while picking up tags, omg, i overlap my streaks everytime. What i like about this loadout is that when u get your care package, you can reroll something shitty and always get high streaks. I always get a wraith, raps, lightening strike, cerburus, g.i unit or sentry gun which is why i would always go 30-40 each match. Try HC. Trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 06:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use nothing but the HVK. grip. Quickdraw and rapidfire. I average about 25-35 kills a match. HC KC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 06:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 04:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to build a wall... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 04:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something amazes me though, with his KD, ive never seen him get in a lobby with sweats. Because come on now, no matter how good you are, theres always someone better than you. Never once have i seen him get wrecked with his high KD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 11:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been rerolling since day 1 and have yet to get a mothership. Maybe its just me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 10:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I opened 5 today and got 3 legendaries and 2 epic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 07:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 16:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mw3 is awesome bro!!!! Get a working copy and go get yourself a moab!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 06:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repack? Is that a hidden perk? How do i unlock repack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex rape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fruit ninja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 20:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really. Thats cool. Was this in shadowfall? Because i bought shadowfall and no one was using mutiplayer, so i resold it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries brother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double click the share button to record and repeat to stop. Its automatically saved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. As i said, It didnt necessarily had to be in the order i described. I just want the IDEA of most of the game modes to be implemented in one match however treyarch or respective studio sees fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted about this before the beta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Combo mode idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This idea is in conjunction with chaos moshpit , But chaos moshpit is one mode per match. What if combo m
ode added all the modes in one match at 2 mins each? For example, it starts out TDM, then changes to kill confirmed , then changes to hardpoint, then changes to safeguard followed by demolition, followed by uplink , then CTF and lastly , B flag. These game modes gives both teams a chance to win. They will rank up faster ( for playing majority of modes ). They dont have to be in my specific order. I didnt include S D for obvious reasons. Its something different and i hope one day in the new cods to come that they will add this mode in. Do you guys like the idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U have to get all armor for every character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 13:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Hardcore is so much fun and you rank up faster + more keys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 12:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are u moving? And are u using a silencer? R u using dead silence? R u using hardwired? Having ghost on dont mean shit in cod bo3 unless youre using a silenced gun, dead silence, convering your footprints with hardwired and also moving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wtf does this mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 21:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 20:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, heres some solid advice. Don't waste your money on bo3 for old gen. Save your money and eventually get a current gen console. Trust me. Bo3 isnt bo3 for old gen. Especially with no internet it defeats the purpose. Just save your cash and get current gen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 02:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someome said its like 8 bucks on g2a.com.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 00:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me a few times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 14:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a channel lock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell another player that you banged their mom. Welcome to cod.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 16:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR needs to be at the bottom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 00:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you let your bf of 2 years near your vagina unprotected, you deserve to be pregnant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 18:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 746 crypto keys. I dont even use them. I play HC alot, so i get about 3 keys a match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 13:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats pretty dope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 15:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pattacake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats my PSN name. Punannymagnet. Hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 02:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys add me. Punannymagnet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 01:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything is legal once the government can tax it, whether it kills you or not. Smoking and drinking kills, but the government can profit off it. Marijuana doesn't kill,  but because it can be grown by anyone, its illegal. Prostitution is illegal because government doesnt know about it, henceforth cant profit. Filming it requires license and other fee's,  that's why its legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are u gonna be in NYC?  I would love to take a picture with u.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny pizza joke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 05:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 01:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an idiot. Its BREE-CEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 21:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bro. I did it mostly for the XP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 21:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly kid. Its not exploiting. Its given to us. Provided freely by treyarch. Its not cheating. Do lawyers get jailed for exploiting the justice system? Nope. Its a broken system, just like any other cod.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The secret to my success. (Gun game) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 21:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhh, gun game. At first, i was like wtf? Why is everyone afk? Then i guessed, farming keys. Then i realized, this can work in my favor. I can get nuclear and massive xp in one match. Thus, completeling some dark ops challenges. Trick is, mele them, dont shoot. If another guy is shooting, message him the tip n trick. Proof is below. 

Medals: http://imgur.com/GPEAkpb

Xp earned: http://imgur.com/BVSd5ej </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 18:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to play s d back when it took skill and witts. I stopped playing s d since bo2 because ALL everyone wants to do is get trickshot clips. Faze ruined s d for the casual gamers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 16:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then dont play s d.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 16:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was recently a patch that made it faster to get specialist in s d.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cunt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 00:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYTHING IS..........OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 16:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a joke buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIVE action R.A.P.S gameplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 06:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 15:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me. You don't. I dont even play it. Its just like bo2 n worse. If i could give you mines, i would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 05:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game officially blows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
