<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2928</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erdoan Strikes Turkeys Last Opposition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An expert explains why it would be so hard to sue President Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There were ten mass shootings in America this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 09:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Russia's biggest oil company, Rosneft, has reported a 77% fall in third-quarter profits as a result of lower oil prices." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 08:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Organizations blind trust poses quagmire of conflict of interest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 08:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg is facing calls to remove promoters of dangerous autism treatments from his site" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 08:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Network - We're In A Lot Of Trouble! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I tell my daughter that her online truth is a conspiracy theory? | Life and style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post-its on New York subway provide post-election therapy in pictures | US news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venice #Venexodus protesters oppose tourist numbers - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charity workers of Reddit, what was the most rewarding moment of your career? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump appears to soften stance on Obamacare and Clinton emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge orders door-to-door water delivery for Flint residents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 13:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At A peaceful protest? Don't forget to take and share pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 12:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Media will want excitement on the news and as always violence gets the most views.
Social media now means you can present majority of peaceful protests. Look out for moments which will be inspiring, maybe get a quote from those there to add to the hopeful inspiring message of progress in the photo. Share it online and post them onto Facebook pages of news outlets
Of course lot of people are angry and risks going from chanting into violence. If you're willing, block them as a group and try to calm them down. Or else you risk not being taken seriously. It's not easy but it's what Civil Right movement trained into its best members. Not to be provoked into violence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a peaceful protest? Don't forget to take and share pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 12:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Media will want excitement on the news and as always violence gets the most views.

Social media now means you can present majority of peaceful protests. Look out for moments which will be inspiring, maybe get a quote from those there to add to the hopeful inspiring message of progress in the photo. Share it online and post them onto Facebook pages of news outlets.

Of course lot of people are angry and risks going from chanting into violence. If you're willing, block them as a group and try to calm them down. Or else you risk not being taken seriously. It's not easy but it's what Civil Right movement trained into its best members. Not to be provoked into violence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a peaceful protest? Don't forget to take and share pictures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 12:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Media will want excitement on the news and as always violence gets the most views.

Social media now means you can present majority of peaceful protests. Look out for moments which will be inspiring, maybe get a quote from those there to add to the hopeful inspiring message of progress in the photo. Share it online and post them onto Facebook pages of news outlets 

Of course lot of people are angry and risks going from chanting into violence. If you're willing, block them as a group and try to calm them down. Or else you risk not being taken seriously. It's not easy but it's what Civil Right movement trained into its best members. Not to be provoked into violence 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Llite a perdu son pari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge orders door-to-door water delivery for Flint residents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the hate towards immigrants I'm reminded of the powerful monologue Strangers read by Ian McKellen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Cleese and Eric Idle's New Song, "Fuck Selfies" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What social norms of another culture do you admire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA immigrant community rallies against President-elect Trump's deportation threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps kids to run businesses via blind trust, Trump attorney says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putting Trump's businesses in a 'blind trust' raises questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 15:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be careful of getting stuck in a long term leadership battle during Trumps term </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urge your DNC representatives to get the DNC sorted by the time Trump is sworn in. 

As a Labour supporter in the UK it has been frustrating seeing the constant Leadership challenges and battles in the party as the Conservatives are making their cuts and changes. 

All media coverage has been about the infighting and none of the challenges to the government policy or the alternatives to fix the issues. It's left the party not fully being in opposition, which has been a win for the Conservatives who sorted their leadership battles swiftly.

If you want a new DNC get it ready before Trump and the Republicans start there new day in power. Otherwise you wont be in a strong enough opposition for democracy and debate to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Call to American Friends and Comrades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon drivers 'work illegal hours' - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is a wake up call. I am glad DiEM25 is awake  Brian Eno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is a wake up call. I am glad DiEM25 is awake  Brian Eno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Victory: How to tackle the new 'Nationalist International' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is the European Union viewed or promoted in your country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it positive or is it negatives? 

What drives at promoting or demonizing the union? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asked about Trump, Pope says his concern is for politicians' impact on the poor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 11:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How two Russian defectors helped the FBI nab european mobsters then wound up stranded in Oregon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 10:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Trump-style revolt engulf Europe? - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 10:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are we monarch henchmen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps look to Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heads up to European friends Trumps subs and mods are rallying towards influencing European elections 

https://np.reddit.com/r/The_Donald/comments/5c8gsw/make_europe_great_again_check_out_our_sister/

Le Pen sub Reddit already appearing in all rising tab with Joan of arc shitposts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Brain wi-fi' reverses leg paralysis in primate first - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The President-elect faces court date in fraud case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change has wrecked the planet and the only hope is a self sustaining space station, but there's limited space. Why should you be saved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 13:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any 'Environmentally Friendly' Recipes/meal plans out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 13:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking about climate change and what to do for a while. There's lot of talk about how meat industry and transport of veg/fruit has a huge impact and changing your personal tastes can help.

So I've been thinking about changing my diet. Eating less meat, more chicken, vegetarian/vegan recipes, maybe rotating seasonal fruit/veg to rely less on food that had high air miles etc.
It might do nothing, but might be quite good (lot of large food companies have change business to react to healthy diets people want.)

Anyone else doing this? Any meal ideas worth trying or sources to pull ideas from?

So far found following sites which talk about seasonal foods to start building meal ideas from. 

http://www.eattheseasons.co.uk/ and http://www.eattheseasons.com/

http://www.sustainabletable.org/seasonalfoodguide/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Election Puts Families USA on Total War Footing in Fight to Save the Affordable Care Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Anti-Establishment group is the oppressive Establishment from the point of view of another group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump Implements His Proposed Policies, Well See Him in Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 10:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't let anyone now or in next two-four years shame you for protesting or becoming an activist. Remember your rights and the rights of others you are protecting with the constitution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 09:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be criticism and that is fair enough to listen to. But don't fall for the trap of thinking that any form of activism or protest is wrong or worthless. 

In Bushes government there were anti-war and occupy movements after the sub prime mortgage crash. Yet even with this I suspect Trump might bring about an era of activism we haven't seen since the Hippies or the Reagan era Punks. 

We saw lot of progress with Obama kicking off more LGBT protections, early healthcare reform, climate change talks and general celebration of sciences and much more. I can see why people are protesting since the Republican Party (not just Trump) past behaviour shows they will seek to reverse lot of the things people feel was needed and is still needed on our society together.

It's early days. We shall see what happens if activism is needed or not to protect rights, justice, liberty and freedoms (and all buzzwords America should stand for) for yourself and other people over the next four years.

If it's worst case there will be struggle. You cannot dismiss alt right/trump/republicans etc for being only angry old guys or sad virgins alone in basements. They are mixed and they are more active. Dismissing them has gotten you here and if you sit at home doing nothing you are the dumb angry old guys or basement dwellers who don't do anything. Even the hippies who are mocked as weak went out to face Nixons national guard and to get beaten by batons. That's not weak it takes balls. 

They will try to shame you as troublemakers, traitors, dumb kids, globalists, SJW, liberal (like it's a swear word) a threat. Yet keep on fighting to protect rights of others.

You know who the biggest suckheads in the world are? The people who think they're clever by saying, 'Well, I happen to be politically IN-correct.' And now you get to act like you're a cutting edge rebel, because you're reinforcing the oppressive status quo! You sack of fucking rancid horse assholes! - Barry Crimmins 

Join a political party today, the democrats and Bernie will sure need it. Yet go for whichever group you believe in.

Fundraise and work for activist groups who will have a busy four years protecting those they care for.

Here are some places to start:

http://www.startguide.org/orgs/orgs00.html

https://www.keele.ac.uk/depts/por/usbase.groups.htm

/r/Liberal/

/r/activism/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump Implements His Proposed Policies, Well See Him in Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Adventures of the Most Patient Man on Television - Last Week Tonight With John Oliver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which activist group is going to have a busy 2017? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Krugman: Trump will bring global recession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The_Donald looks to Europe. What do you think about upcoming elections in Europe mentioned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is what President Trump means for LGBT rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warning after a fake model scout targets UK girls online - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 13:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Populists first to congratulate Trump on historic upset | US news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request/Discussion] Are there any 'Environmentally Friendly' Recipes/meal plans out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking about climate change and what to do for a while. There's lot of talk about how meat industry and transport of veg/fruit has a huge impact and changing your personal tastes can help.

So I've been thinking about changing my diet. Eating less meat, more chicken, vegetarian/vegan recipes, maybe rotating seasonal fruit/veg to rely less on food that had high air miles etc.

It might do nothing, but might be quite good (lot of large food companies have change business to react to healthy diets people want.)

Anyone else doing this? Any meal ideas worth trying or sources to pull ideas from?

So far found following sites which talk about seasonal foods to start building meal ideas from. Given lot of US people online at the moment I've added US ones too. 

http://www.eattheseasons.co.uk/

http://www.sustainabletable.org/seasonalfoodguide/

http://www.eattheseasons.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 'environmentally friendly' recipes or meals plans a thing yet? If so what are yours. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What recipes/meal plans are the most environmentally friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The far right are gaining world wide. How can it be combated esp with reaching out to non-anarchists? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Online, in the media and socially alt right far right are getting thier narrative part of normal conversation.

In 1900s fascism had strong socialist competition. Is it possible at this point to slow the rise of the ugly right?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We ignore the warnings and climate change drought/flood/wildfire etc happens, how will you survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still undecided or know people who are? Maybe check out how your representatives vote with GovTrack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Stewart and Stephen Colbert sing about voting on election day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats news story do you wish there was a follow up for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'One-fifth of cancer patients face work discrimination' - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authors join national protest against library closures | Books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What cooking and buying habits are the best to combat climate change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leading authors join protest march against cuts to cultural services | Books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 10:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private Eye News: Jail looms for former police officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 10:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "From Macedonia to the San Francisco Bay, clickbait political sites are cashing in on Trumpmania  and theyre getting a big boost from Facebook" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 09:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Teens In The Balkans Are Duping Trump Supporters With Fake News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 09:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How teens in the Balkans are duping Trump Supporters with fake news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Pope banned eating of cattle meat it would be a huge environmental move against climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is if every Catholic followed through with the ban. Works for other religions too but thought of him first due to him being a big public head of the church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missing South Carolina woman found 'chained like a dog' - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the weirdest fan fiction you've found online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How has your job changed your view on the world and the people in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VICE News on Trumps friendship with Epstein. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leave voters, are you confident or nervous by the High Courts ruling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does sound like this is part of the process. Plus the weight of the vote is still there to apply lot of pressure in the debates. 

I'm curious why those who are nervous think Parliament will vote against it?  

As Remain voter its a bit of hope, but we haven't got the vote results on our side which is a big issue. Only thing we have to hold onto is the negativity since the results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US actor Steven Seagal given Russian citizenship by Putin - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you want to talk to your MP about the Brexit vote/debate in Parliament. This site will find your MP and help you format the email. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 12:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best info-graphics to highlight the mess that is Trumps policies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone's so focused on scandals it really deflected on how poor Trumps policies are or in some cases is pretty scary. 

Are there any shitpost memes or graphics in circulation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police forces 'overwhelmed' by digital evidence, watchdog finds - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you believe as a teenager that you cringe about now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two children and man found dead at house in Hinckley - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump v Clinton: Comparing their economic plans - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 16:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paid Trolls of reddit. What's the craziest trolling you've gotten paid for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Online Troll Tells Samantha Bee Why She Prefers Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump, Pence take aim at ACA health care benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US election: Where Clinton and Trump stand on key issues - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change deniers, what would cause you to change your mind and call for action? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps campaign manager linked to Panama Papers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your 'It could've been me!" story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The shadowy Russian migr touting Trump | US election raises ghosts of cold war-era spy games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.co.uk/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0ahUKEwiUh4rEuIfQAhXLDZoKHdB_BAYQqQIIHzAA url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ft.com%2Fcontent%2Fea52a678-9cfb-11e6-8324-be63473ce146 usg=AFQjCNEZ9_Ha_EbnrdnwEYP-9jtHzcY6SQ sig2=v0EmefWRFn0XxQDJUyK2ig pay wall:

When Sergei Millian was appointed head of the Russian American Chamber of Commerce in the US in 2006, the young former Soviet migr came to typify Russias new projection of soft power.

He gave dozens of interviews to Russian state media as an expert on the US and appeared on US television opposing sanctions on Russia. He gadded about town with New York luxury real-estate brokers, even appearing on a reality TV programme called Million Dollar Listing, prompting one newspaper to nickname him The Moscow Mule.

Friends approved when he posted a photograph on Facebook in 2014 of himself with Donald Trump and Jorge Perez, the billionaire owner of the Related Group, a Miami real-estate developer, at the races. Then this year, Mr Millian, now 36, began speaking of how Russia-US relations would improve under the presidency of Mr Trump, with whose organisation he said he had worked as a real-estate broker and maintained ties. I can assure you he is very positive and friendly, he told the Russian state news agency, Ria Novosti, in January.

In the past, such activities might have seemed harmless. But now the US administration has formally accused Russia of attempting to interfere in the US electoral process through the hacking of the Democratic National Committees email servers, Mr Millians activities  and his ties to the Republican presidential nominee  are coming under increasing scrutiny.

Hillary Clinton, the Democratic presidential candidate, has called Mr Trump a Kremlin puppet, pointing to his pro-Moscow advisers and his consistently pro-Putin line. Mr Trump has played down his links to Russia.

But questions are mounting over whether Mr Millian was one of a number of people who could have acted as intermediaries to build ties between Moscow and Mr Trump. This comes after Paul Manafort resigned earlier this year as Mr Trumps campaign chief after controversy over his years of consulting work for Viktor Yanukovich, the pro-Moscow former president of Ukraine.

At the same time, the US intelligence community is grappling with the fact that Russian intelligence operations on US soil may be more extensive than previously thought. As Russia has sought to restore its standing on the world stage, it has poured funding into soft power outfits such as Russia Today, a state-run global television channel, and Rossotrudnichestvo, a state entity that organises cultural exchanges. Similar organisations were used in Soviet times as a front for espionage.

A debate is deepening in Washington over how to deal with such Russian institutions and whether they should register under the Foreign Agent Registration act, according to a former senior US administration official. The debate is being closely tracked by the FBI, the official said.

Mr Millian insists his Russian American Chamber of Commerce (RACC) has nothing to do with the Russian government. He says it is funded by payments from its commercial members alone.

Most of the board members are obscure entities and nearly half of their telephone numbers went unanswered when called by the Financial Times.An FT reporter found no trace of the Chamber of Commerce at the Wall Street address listed on its website. At the same time, the chamber appears to have close official ties, arranging trips for visiting Russian regional governors to the US. In January 2015, the Russian government awarded Mr Millian a prize for his work developing ties between Russian and American businesspeople.

Mr Millian warned of false accusations and negligent reporting. He said the chamber of commerce keeps an official office address registered at Wall Street and pays for the service provided. He added that it had cut most of its services and activities in the US and Russia due to the adverse political situation.

For Konstantin Borovoi, a former Russian MP and businessman who was president of Russias first commodities exchange, the chambers type of operations hark back to cold war practices. In Soviet times, the American Trade Chamber was the official representative office of the secret services, said Mr Borovoi, who is also an expert on the KGB. These institutions have been revived and developed, he said. The chamber of commerce institutions are the visible part of the agent network  Russia has spent huge amounts of money on this.

Mr Millian came on to the FBIs radar after he participated in a 2011 trip to Moscow for 50 US businessmen and offered to organise further trips. The FBI pulled in the US participants to ask them whether Russian intelligence tried to recruit them during the all-expenses paid trip, three attendees told the Financial Times. One of them said the FBI told him they suspected that some of the people who organised the trips were spies.

The questioning formed part of a wider FBI probe into whether Yury Zaytsev, the head of the Washington DC arm of Rossotrudnichestvo, was recruiting for Russian intelligence. Mr Zaytsev had been the lead organiser for the trip. The Russian foreign ministry said reports of the probe were fabrications that had nothing to do with reality. Mr Zaytsev, however, quietly returned to Russia shortly after the FBI probe, dismissing the accusation as no more than an echo of the cold war.

Mr Millian remained in the US, writing to thank then-Russian President Dmitry Medvedev following the trip and offering to help organise more such visits, according to a copy of his letter seen by the FT.

The FBI probe was part of a wake-up call for US intelligence over suspicions that Russia was activating networks long thought defunct after the end of the cold war. The number of Russian intelligence operatives in the US is much higher than anyone thought, one former senior US intelligence official said.

By the time of the trip, Mr Millian had built extensive ties with Mr Trump and his organisation, according to boasts he made in an in-depth interview with Russian state agency Ria Novosti in April this year. He praised Mr Trump for developing business projects with Russian speakers in the US, citing Trump SoHo in New York, a project led by Tamir Sapir, a Georgian billionaire who started out in the US selling electronic goods to visiting Soviet officials.

Mr Millian told Ria he first met Mr Trump after mutual acquaintances helped organise a visit by the real-estate mogul to the 2007 Millionaires Fair in Moscow. Mr Trump invited him to horse races in Miami shortly afterwards, he said  a statement that chimes with the Facebook photograph he posted.

Mr Millian claimed Mr Trump then introduced him to Michael Cohen, the Trump Organisations chief legal counsel, who granted him rights to market Trump Organisation properties in Russia and the former Soviet Union. You could say I was their exclusive broker, he told Ria. Then, in 2007-2008, dozens of Russians bought apartments in Trump properties in the US. He later told ABC television that the Trump Organisation had received hundreds of millions of dollars through deals with Russian businessmen.

Now that scrutiny has increased, Mr Millian has played down his connections with Mr Trump. He declined repeated requests for an interview and left the US for Asia on a business trip in early October. In emailed responses to questions from the Financial Times, Mr Millian described himself as one of several brokers who worked on Mr Trumps real estate projects. I never represented Mr Trump personally and I am not working with Mr Trump, he said. I have never been paid by Mr Trump for any work. He added that he had never consulted Mr Trump on any political topic.

The chamber of commerce removed from its website earlier this year an April 2009 newsletter, where Mr Millian said the chamber had signed formal agreements with the Trump Organisation, Mr Perezs Related Group and one other company to jointly service the Russian clients commercial, residential and industrial real-estate needs.

Mr Cohen dismissed Mr Millians earlier comments about his work with Mr Trump as nothing more than a weak attempt to align himself with Mr Trumps overwhelmingly successful brand. Mr Cohen did not respond to questions about whether he interacted with Mr Millian or why Mr Millian is one of only 100 people he follows on Twitter. The Related Group, in a carefully worded statement, said it had no record of any dealings with Mr Millian.

Hope Hicks, Mr Trumps campaign spokeswoman, said Mr Trump had met and spoke with Mr Millian only on one occasion almost a decade ago at a hotel opening.

One of the chambers main backers is Mikhail Morgulis, a prominent Soviet migr who also serves as Belarus honorary consul to the US. He told the FT Mr Millian had explained to him he was helping Mr Trump and the Republican party. We have soft power and we are trying to change relations now, Mr Morgulis said.

Russia is officially denying any suggestion it is interfering in the US electoral process or supporting Mr Trump. For Konstantin Zatullin, head of the Russian parliaments CIS affairs committee and a vocal proponent of restoring Russian power, the accusations are redolent of McCarthyism.

But behind the denials, a tinge of pride is visible. While the west was playing with James Bond  we turned our attention to gaining respect, said Mr Zatullin. When the west thought the cold war competition was over, they lost respect for their opponent. Now they are waking up to this again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paris climate deal vulnerable to a Trump presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Far-Right getting funding/support from Russia? If so, how do we combat this new rise of the far right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time this story pops up in the news it feels like I'm putting on a Cold War tin foil hat on. 

Yet if there's any truth in it (investigations is concerning enough), we should be very concerned with how the far right is getting a boost. It does feel like more and more online far right are getting more support or at least handed resources to push their agenda. Feels like we're too many steps behind shady funding or not. 

Issue is there were also stories (think Adam Curtis) who said Putin campaign guy also funds far left to confuse or create this kind of left vs right internal conflict.

http://www.riskandforecast.com/useruploads/files/pc_flash_report_russian_connection.pdf

https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2014/dec/08/russia-europe-right-putin-front-national-eu

http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2016/10/veteran-spy-gave-fbi-info-alleging-russian-operation-cultivate-donald-trump

What do you guys this? Crazed bullshit or something to be worried about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Russian connection: The spread of pro-Russian policies on the European far right | An analysis by Political Capital Institute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should beware Russia's links with Europe's right | Article from 2014 for anyone thinking this is just a US election concern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putting aside the scandals. What do you think are the important policies and issues in this years US election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Compare the candidates: Clinton vs. Trump on the economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Policies Trump, Clinton (somewhat) agree on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private Eye Hp Sauce: Till the PIPs squeak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 12:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's ghostwriter on being the 'Dr Frankenstein' who made a monster | US news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What mistakes from history are we most at risk of repeating in our lifetime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 12:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've Been Trumped Too - TEASER TRAILER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vagina Dispatches episode three: the orgasm gap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 13:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will happen in the season finale of the US Election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Americans Redditors. What is your opinion on the North Dakota Pipeline protest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brisbane bus driver dies after being set on fire by passenger - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before the tin foil hats are on. There is no secret tool. Admins announced 4 months ago the tool to prevent any sub from dominating the front page. EnoughTrumpSpam was hit the hardest by it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 12:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Due to climate change, what major weather or environmental changes would you expect your country will experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] What is the worst orgy you have ever attended? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NI woman charged over abortion pills - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wedding Planners of Reddit, what are the craziest wedding ideas people have presented to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the five reasons why a undecided voter should vote for your candidate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sun journalist has Elveden conviction quashed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spalding shootings: Man's killing of wife and daughter 'calculated' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Geographic 'Afghan Girl' arrested in Pakistan living under false papers | World news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The villages living under Heathrow's death sentence - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "People who think theyre clever by being like, Well, I happen to be politically incorrect! And now you get to act like youre a cutting-edge rebel because youre reinforcing the oppressive status quo! You sack of fucking rancid horse assholes! - Barry Crimmins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time coming across this comic legend when my partner put on 'Call Me Lucky'. Great political comic, great documentary. 

He has another line you guys might dig too.

An angry audience member asked, "If you don't love this country, why don't you get out?"

Barry replied, "Because I don't want to be victimized by its foreign policy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rurik Jutting: Hong Kong murder trial shown 'torture' video - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 13:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your best campfire stories to scare your friends with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I, Daniel Blake reviewed by Mark Kermode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside America's biggest prison strike: 'The 13th amendment didn't end slavery' | US news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside America's biggest prison strike: 'The 13th amendment didn't end slavery' | US news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denise worked all her life. Then she got ill - and the state pulled away the safety net | Frances Ryan | Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I, Daniel Blake review a Ken Loach's quiet rage against injustice | Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 15:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian warships pass through English Channel - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've seen Donald Trump before and his name was Silvio Berlusconi | John Foot | Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anne Hathaway: Male energy is very different from toxic masculinity | Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which actors performances improved the most as their career progressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Micro Bit - the view from the teachers - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 13:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Micro Bit - the view from the teachers - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 13:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mosul battle: Iraqi troops 'ahead of schedule' in bid to retake city - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 09:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which fictional character would make the best new Supreme Court Justice candidate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shelter: More than four in 10 homes fail acceptable standards - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 09:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which insect would be the best pet if it was the size of a small piglet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polling only your friends and family, which candidate is winning the US election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Third party voters, why should a Clinton or Trump supporter switch to your candidate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the US since 2008 which got us into this elections shambles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Without mentioning scandals, why are you voting Trump, Clinton, a Third Party or Abstaining? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decided voters, what policy matters to you the most and how did Clinton/Trumps campaign win you over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [x-post /r/pics] I teamed up with my local college to host another free event for fathers. We went over hair and nails to help encourage dads to better connect with their girls . 23 dads, stepdads and even a grandfather showed up and we all learned something new. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 11:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A History of Horror: Hammer Films and the British Horror by Mark Gatiss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 00:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last art history A-level axed after Michael Gove cull of 'soft' subjects | Education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 12:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What hardships did you overcome in life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the six US immigrant Nobel winners is 'totally speechless' over the push to limit immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 14:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump vows to take on Chinese steel, but then buys it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 14:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "local resident, Susan Munro, explained to me on camera how she had been forced to spreadeagle over the bonnet of her car by Trump security guards, while attempting to reach her home." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 11:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oxford schoolgirl rape e-fits issued by police - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fate of former Schindler's list factory is met with Czech ambivalence | World news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great sequence/edit from Hunt for the Wilderpeople </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Top 5 qualities should every world leader have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are more glitches down to more advanced systems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time a Game is released we see ton of glitches get posted. 
Then people get nostalgic for less glitch games years ago and lack of testing. 

However, is gaming and technical side of creating one getting more complicated it's getting harder to catch the glitches in testing? 

Any insiders know if its lack of testing or a ton of testing not being able to catch everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet trolls targeted with new legal guidelines - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 09:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, where are those Trump voters who said they'd not vote for him if he apologised for offending people with his comments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 10:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was Ask Reddit post about it a while back and most people said this would be a reason why they'd abandon the Trump train.

It does look like lot of his voters focusing more on Clinton comments than the fact he 'apologised' even a weak one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hammond urges calm over pound flash crash - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Reddit, why are you happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 11:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amber Rudd considers tighter controls on foreign workers and students - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 16:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Art dealer killed 'over rare Wind in the Willows book' - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 16:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which charity deserves more attention and support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Mars Elon Musk orders you to design a giant sandcastle which observers from Earth can see. What do you design? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to listen and talk to a friend you're worried about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 12:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.samaritans.org/difficultconversations

There's been lot of discussion about Men sharing thier feelings more when going through a crisis. Yet some people have made interesting points 'it's not just about talking it's also about learning how to listen or helping someone start that conversation.'

Samaritans to me has really good outline on how to talk to someone you're worried about. Going to post full article below v, but there is more on their website:

**HOW TO START A DIFFICULT CONVERSATION**

If you're worried about someone try to get them to talk to you.

* Often people want to talk, but wait until someone asks how they are. Try asking open questions, like 'What happened about...', 'Tell me about...', 'How do you feel about...'

* Repeat back what they say to show you understand, and ask more questions.

* Focus on your friend's feelings instead of trying to solve the problem - it can be of more help and shows you care.

* Respect what they tell you. Sometimes it's easy to want to try and fix a person's problems, or give them advice. Let them make their own decisions.
 
**How do I start a conversation with someone Im concerned about?**

You might feel that you don't know how to help someone, because you don't know what to tell them or how to solve their problems.

You dont need to be an expert. In fact, sometimes people who think they have the answers to a problem are less helpful.

Dont forget that every person is different, so that what worked for one will not always work for another.

**Find a good time and place**

Think about where and when to have the conversation before you start.

Choose somewhere where the other person feels comfortable and has time to talk.

**Ask gentle questions, and listen with care**

You might feel that you don't know how to help someone, because you don't know what to tell them. But you shouldn't tell them anything. Telling doesn't help.

The best way to help is to ask questions. That way you leave the other person in control. By asking questions, the person you are talking with finds his or her own answers. 

**The more open the question the better**

Questions that help someone talk through their problems instead of  saying yes or no are the most useful. Questions like:

* When  'When did you realise?'

* Where  'Where did that happen?'

* What  'What else happened?'

* How  'How did that feel?'

* Why  be careful with this one as it can make someone defensive. What made you choose that or What were you thinking about at the time are more effective.
At Samaritans, we call this style of conversation active listening.

**Find out how they feel**

Dont forget to ask how this person is feeling. Sometimes people will talk you through all the facts of what happened, why it happened and what actions they are thinking of taking, but never say how they actually feel.

Revealing your innermost emotions - anger, sadness, fear, hope, jealously, despair and so on  can be a huge relief. It sometimes also gives clues about what the person is really most worried about.

**Check they know where to get help**

If someone has been feeling low for some time it is probably a good idea that they get some support, whether it is through talking to someone like a counsellor or getting some practical help.

Useful questions you might ask them include:

* Have you talked to anyone else about this?

* Would you like to get some help?

* Would you like me to come with you?

Or, for someone who is reluctant to get help:

* Do you have someone you trust you can go to?

* If it helps, you can talk to me any time.

You can also suggest to your friend that the following sources of help may be useful:

[Note these are from the UK, Menslib resource bar has more international links]

Samaritans (by phone on 116 123 or email jo[@]samaritans.org.
Befrienders Worldwide includes a directory of emotional support helplines around the world.
NHS 111 offers health advice in the UK and is free from landlines and mobiles.
A more comprehensive list of charities providing emotional support and help for mental illness can be found here.

**Respect what they tell you, dont pressure them**

If they dont want help, dont push them. Sometimes its easy to want to try and fix a persons problems, or give them advice.

Its usually better for people to make their own decisions. Help them think of all the options, but leave the choice to them.

Being there for them in other ways, like through socialising or helping with practical things, can also be a great source of support.

**If you say the wrong thing, dont panic**

There is no perfect way to handle a difficult conversation, so dont be too hard on yourself if it didnt go as well as you had hoped. 

If you feel able to, put things right: Last week I said  and I realise now that was insensitive so Im sorry. What I meant to say was 

**Show you understand**

Ask follow-up questions and repeat back the key things your friend has told you, using phrases like So youre saying, So you think.

**Look after yourself, and talk to someone too**

Hearing someone elses worries or problems can affect you too. Take time for yourself to do the things you enjoy, and if you need to talk, find somebody you trust to confide in.

If you promised not to tell anyone else, you can call us, and well keep it private.

Dont take on so much of other peoples problems that you yourself start feeling depressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movember is coming up and the charity behind it made this advert to start conversation about male suicide rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 23:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Movember advert has a powerful message to tackle male suicide rate this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women of Reddit, what is something traditionally considered manly that you enjoy using or doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 12:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deutsche Bank fears rattle stock markets; UK growth revised up  business live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've been Trumped - Full Documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Note on reaching the annual low point [in the Mauna Loa CO2 curve by Scripps Institution of Oceanography] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 13:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People share the times Trump bullied residents near his golf courses and tenants in New York with building walls, cutting off water, introducing rats to buildings, filing fake non-payment charges etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 10:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Junior doctors lose High Court case - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American voters what policy promise would secure your vote and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cat Man of Aleppo [Cats break Rule 1 on the other sub] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London man 'training to cure autism' filmed abusing client - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Riace: The Italian village abandoned by locals, adopted by migrants - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Michael Burry. The first investor to notice the subprime mortgage crisis was going to happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The EpiPen boss tried to defend price hikes to Congress. No one bought it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 23:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buzzfeed LGBT community show off their best Born This Way kids pictures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 13:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of reddit. Going only by who your closest friends or relatives are supporting. Who would win the election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] Jewish woman chased by men and youth armed with clubs during the Lviv pogroms, July 1941 [X-post from /r/historyporn] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which insect would be the most terrifying if it became the size of a bus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best films in your countries Netflix selection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure to say your region. So we can see if its on ours or just be jealous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the creepiest folktale from your country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria war: Aleppo's children and families suffer conflict's horror - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 17:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Film studio Fox seeks female blockbuster directors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Curtis - Oh Dear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 14:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do the drugs and medication we take affect blood/flesh eating insects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 13:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Russian migr Dies Mysteriously, but Its a Different Britain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 11:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four questioned in Italy after woman's suicide over sex video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 11:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a thalidomider, I feel Im being treated like a scrounger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favorite book is now an episode of Always Sunny. How does the episode open? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who, What, Why: What made electricity prices soar during a heatwave? - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 16:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Americans don't take sick days - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Care for elderly 'increasingly rationed' in England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 08:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A deadly Plague breaks out in your country. What would you do to survive the next 10 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What creepy cults that brainwash people should we be more aware of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 12:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How family tragedy turned Roald Dahl into a medical pioneer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tunnel (2016) Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent a day trying to get to know a Real-Life Narcissist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are you from and what did you eat for breakfast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 11:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demonstration for libraries, museums, galleries (5th November) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Khan's statement on the loss of Fabric </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> via his facebook page

Londons iconic clubs are an essential part of our cultural landscape.
Clubbing needs to be safe but Im disappointed that Fabric, Islington Council and the Metropolitan Police were unable to reach agreement on how to address concerns about public safety.
As a result of this decision, thousands of people who enjoyed going to Fabric as an essential part of London's nightlife will lose out.

The issues faced by Fabric point to a wider problem of how we protect Londons night-time economy, while ensuring it is safe and enjoyable for everyone.

Over the past eight years, London has lost 50 percent of its nightclubs and 40 percent of its live music venues. This decline must stop if London is to retain its status as a 24-hour city with a world-class nightlife.
I am in the process of appointing a Night Czar who will bring together key stakeholders including club and venue owners, local authorities, the Metropolitan Police and members of the public.

No single organisation or public body can solve these problems alone  we all need to work together to ensure London thrives as a 24-hour city, in a way that is safe and enjoyable for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best Original movies to come out this year so far? Also any upcoming ones we should know about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 12:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What slipped from the radar but were surprisingly good enough to recommend. 

Also which upcoming original movies look like they deserve a movie ticket for. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NHS: Jeremy Hunt to announce new online 111 services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
