<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2930</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that song has been around longer then Reddit?  That whole thing about "what song it this?.....Darude - Sandstorm" also was started before Reddit was even around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain to me why it's the cab drivers fault when it was the passenger that opened the door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bikers out in California make driving a car dangerous.  They just passed a law saying that you have to give a biker 3 feet http://blog.sfgate.com/stienstra/2014/09/08/bikes-vs-cars-3-foot-rule-to-take-effect-with-a-twist/....when did road ways become bikeways?  Not to mention the amount of traffic laws bikers break and then blame car drivers when they get hit.  I'm all for people riding bikes but maybe you shouldn't do it where cars drive.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 00:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> original pic from NetGeo http://photography.nationalgeographic.com/photography/photo-of-the-day/chicago-rooftop-stanfield/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 20:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the Marina City building which was completed in 1964.  Great picture! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When things just come together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 18:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 22:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually called Cloud Gate http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cloud_Gate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ad placement fail on CNN... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 19:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the full story why this started. http://espn.go.com/chicago/nhl/story/_/id/11350487/chicago-blackhawks-nix-stripper-online-petition-launched
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ban Marissa Miller from the United Center - Chicago Blackhawks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 19:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 20:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was expecting this to happen to me yesterday when I called to cancel....but I was very surprised as to what happened.

I was able to get a live person within about 1 minute into the call.  The service rep was very nice and asked how she could help me.  I said that I would like to cancel my service.  She then asked me if what the reason was....here is where I learned a little trick comes into play.  I said that I'm moving out of the country.  Service rep then said thats great hope things work out for you.  She did then ask if someone else is moving in that would like to keep the service.  I said that it's an apartment and I'm not sure who is moving in.  After that it was all smooth sailing for me.  She even offered to send me boxes to ship back my equipment , which are arriving tomorrow.  The phone call lasted less then 5 minutes and my service is disconnected.

I know this not typical but I think the big take away here if you canceling just tell them your moving out of the country.  Not much they can do to keep you as a customer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
