<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not saying he is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I control-f'd "neo" because I knew someone would post this.  Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. The threat could not have been any more brazen unless they said "you better stop this or we'll beat up more black kids" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaepernick has criticized both the left and right.  
"I mean, you have Hillary who's called black teens or black kids super predators. You have Donald Trump who's openly racist. I mean, we have a presidential candidate [Hillary Clinton] who's deleted emails and done things illegally and is a presidential candidate. That doesn't make sense to me, because if that was any other person, you'd be in prison." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's clearly a horrible human being, but this sort of mass outrage based on sketchy information is only going to strengthen her indignation. You don't break someone like that.  My biggest regret is that the guy who hacked her twitter didn't do anything interesting with it, immediately using it to post pro-trump tweets and to taunt Nielsen.  He could have impersonated her and at least tried to make it believable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 08:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm just face palming so hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 02:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering tanks fire so slowly, requiring two less shots is a pretty big deal imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, i don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when a term is thrown around as liberally as "dank meme," it quickly loses whatever charm it originally carried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like you're doing now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oui oui zi zi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hate you : ( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, good to know someone here has standards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with posting humorous things, but calling everything a "dank meme" is seriously so dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop saying this please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to nerf siege tanks, don't reduce the damage per shot. Just reduce the firing rate slightly.  We want the shots to instill fear and awe, that's the identity of the siege tank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 07:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow that's really fascinating, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question: how did hermit crabs evolve to become so dependent on discarded shells for protection?  Assuming it evolved from an ancestor that was fully armored like other crabs or lobsters.  Like, is there any benefit of being partially unarmored like that?  Seems like a huge inconvenience... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just people on reddit talking about people on reddit they know fuck all about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just can't fight that muscle memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she looks great.  One of my favorite fan arts of kerrigan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crazy thing is that you can put your finger in the laser and it won't harm you. 

 https://youtu.be/6TN9WNgxsmo?t=25s

no idea how that works... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Memes are a lot less funny when people call them memes. Like when your dad goes "Oh let me tell you a pun!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 02:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Say what you want about the character models, but KOF XIV has the best looking flames in fighting games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 21:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orochi Nagi never looked better!  Everyone bashes the graphics in this game, but there's one aspect of the graphics I think KOF XIV does better than any other fighting game: the FLAMES! I've never thought that fire looked particularly realistic in any fighting game until now.  I mean just look at these supers:

https://youtu.be/3z8q7pYU_xw?t=14m45s

https://youtu.be/3z8q7pYU_xw?t=12m36s

https://youtu.be/3z8q7pYU_xw?t=4m50s

https://youtu.be/3z8q7pYU_xw?t=19m20s

Just beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 03:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is theoretical possible is one thing, misrepresentation of the current technology is another.  People are saying this is the answer to the meat problem, when in fact, in its current state, lab-grown meat kills more animals than it saves.  This is total disinformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 03:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a laboratory that does cell culture every day.  It's common knowledge among biologists, which is why most of us scoff at this idea.  This is a company that sells animal serum for cell culture: https://www.atlantabio.com/catalog/animal- -human-sera

Here's the wiki on fetal bovine serum, a very common serum used in cell culture:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fetal_bovine_serum#Serum_use

I mean, if you want more detail I could refer you to a textbook?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 02:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may already know this, but in case you don't: hydras are currently being buffed in the official balance test map.  They start with 6 range, upgradable to 7, and they have increased speed on creep after speed upgrade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 01:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll ask again, because I'm not sure you understood my point.  Do you know what is used to feed the cells being cultured?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 01:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the quote is totally wrong, but still pretty entertaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 01:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who don't work in the laboratory don't usually know, but cells grown on a petri dish have to be fed too.  This is typically plasma serum derived from cow, goat, or horse blood.  To get lab-grown meat in the quantities needed to feed people, you need liters upon liters of serum.  You're actually killing more cows than you are saving.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we already do therapeutic fecal transplantation to treat some microbiome pathologies.  such a pleasant thought : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're not taking into account the people that vowed to eat extra meat for every vegetarian they see ; ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lab grown meat doesn't bypass the use of agricultural livestock. Do you know what they use to feed those cell cultures?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agent Smith: I'd like to share a revelation that I've had during my time here. It came to me when I tried to classify your species and I realized that you're not actually mammals. Every mammal on this planet instinctively develops a natural equilibrium with the surrounding environment but you humans do not. You move to an area and you multiply and multiply until every natural resource is consumed and the only way you can survive is to spread to another area. There is another organism on this planet that follows the same pattern. Do you know what it is? A virus. Human beings are a disease, a cancer of this planet. You're a plague and we are the cure. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/avilosc2 You fucking moron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was a real Harley Quinn this would be her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harley is that you?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harley is that you?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 22:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine the fucking gravity of a rocky half-neptune.  It would be like Krypton or Planet Vegeta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it illegal to dump a ton of your own company's stock when you know it's going to tank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think they'd post warning signs by on-ramps saying "Speed up now!"  This shit annoys the hell out of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who drive slowly don't want to break the speed limit. The bigger problem here is that speed limit signs are so ambiguous. Everyone drives around ~5 mph faster than the limit. Either they raise the speed limit signs and make them a true, hard limit, or they have to make separate speed limits for left and right lanes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 08:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1980, the IHR promised a $50,000 reward to anyone who could prove that Jews were gassed at Auschwitz. Mel Mermelstein wrote a letter to the editors of the LA Times and others including The Jerusalem Post. The IHR wrote back, offering him $50,000 for proof that Jews were, in fact, gassed in the gas chambers at Auschwitz. Mermelstein, in turn, submitted a notarized account of his internment at Auschwitz and how he witnessed Nazi guards ushering his mother and two sisters and others towards (as he learned later) gas chamber number five. Despite this, the IHR refused to pay the reward. Represented by public interest attorney William John Cox, Mermelstein subsequently sued the IHR in the Superior Court of Los Angeles County for breach of contract, anticipatory repudiation, libel, injurious denial of established fact, intentional infliction of emotional distress, and declaratory relief (see case no. C 356 542). On October 9, 1981, both parties in the Mermelstein case filed motions for summary judgment in consideration of which Judge Thomas T. Johnson of the Superior Court of Los Angeles County took "judicial notice of the fact that Jews were gassed to death at the Auschwitz Concentration Camp in Poland during the summer of 1944,"[49][50] judicial notice meaning that the court treated the gas chambers as common knowledge, and therefore did not require evidence that the gas chambers existed. On August 5, 1985, Judge Robert A. Wenke entered a judgment based upon the Stipulation for Entry of Judgment agreed upon by the parties on July 22, 1985. The judgment required IHR and other defendants to pay $90,000 to Mermelstein and to issue a letter of apology to "Mr. Mel Mermelstein, a survivor of Auschwitz-Birkenau and Buchenwald, and all other survivors of Auschwitz" for "pain, anguish and suffering" caused to them.[50] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A Holocaust-denial organization offered $50,000 to prove that Jews were gassed at Auschwitz. When they refused to pay a Auschwitz survivor who submitted his familys execution as evidence, he sued the organization, forcing them to pay $90,000 and issue a letter of apology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone likes catching someone in the act of perpetrating a hoax.  It gives one a rush of self gratification.  I would be VERY wary of accepting this narrative as fact without more verification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you the actual person in the tumblr?  You are not obligated to prove it to me or anyone else, but it would help to establish the truth.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 01:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pointing out, this doesn't prove that the person actually taped the sign himself.  The person accusing him of doing so could also be making a false accusation.  If someone accused you of perpetrating a hoax, wouldn't blocking that person be a normal reaction?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Told everyone that this game wouldn't live up to the hype, people summarily told me to stfu.  I'm not one to gloat but....okay yeah I'm gloating.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I find so despicable.  The developers said it was "virtually impossible" to meet each other.  They implied that the universe was so vast that it would be very hard to meet other players. They actively concealed the fact that there is simply no multiplayer. Talk about deceptive advertising. They should have said "literally impossible."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "some of you need a sense of humor"

Oh the irony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 09:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do infestors spawn infested terran... it doesn't make any sense.  Do they store terrans inside of them?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm convinced now that SC3 should be a Homeworld style space sim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the fgc is able to foster a strong amateur scene because the vast majority of tournements, including major events sponsored by capcom, do not require any sort of qualifying credentials.  anyone can join a tourney and go head to head with the best japanese players in the world.  in the fgc, no matter how much of a skill gap there may be, the players are treated as equal human beings.  in sc2, you wouldnt even be allowed to participate in a professional league if you haven't qualified.  people consider non-koreans as not even worth paying attention too.  its elitist and frankly really holding it back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cuts them faster than the guy behind can skin them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally would have just made teleport cost 100 energy instead of putting it on a timer.  Would be a lot more flexible (teleporting in and then out, double yamato cannon, or yamato then teleport out) while also allowing counterplay from feedback.  In its current state, it's just a guaranteed harass every 71 seconds, which is boring.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered, how do the other criminals know what you are in prison for?  Can't you just lie to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balance map suggestion: remove MSC, make all protoss buildings (including photon cannons and pylons) chronoboostable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 08:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it sounds drastic, but please bear with me.  Since David Kim is entertaining the idea of radical changes, I thought I'd throw out an idea I've been toying with for a while.  A lot of players dislike the MSC and pylon overcharge.  But if MSC is removed, there needs to be a compensatory buff, or else Protoss cannot survive the early game.  

What if instead of MSC, chronoboost had a lot more utility than just an economic boost?  What if it could be applied to photon cannons to increase its rate of fire, or applied to pylons to increase the speed of warp-ins?  Yes, there is potential for cannon rush abuse, but expending the chronoboost on cannons necessarily comes at the expense of one's economy, such that I think it could be balanced.  Also, the cooldown of switching the chronoboosted building could be adjusted to further tweak the balance.  For example, if you devote your chronoboost for cannon cheese, but your cannon gets taken out, then the chronoboost becomes unavailable to switch to another building for a time. 

I think this change could potentially add a lot of strategic depth to Protoss play. Any thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 08:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny cuz this push might have been fine if the hellbats held back until the cyclones ran the queens out of energy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 05:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unplayable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy crap how long did that vulcan battery take to build?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably less performance enhancing drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was sufficiently accomplished by increasing the supply cost of tempests, thus making the overall protoss army weaker.  This would mean that terrans can actually take some of the engagements that the tempests are designed to force.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ground attack is only 5 damage stronger than the air attack, and given its slow rate of fire, this buff is basically meaningless.  Also, Queens' and Thors' attacks look visually distinct, and neither have a range discrepancy of 9! That's just ridiculous to me
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this sentiment, its almost better to have no ground attack than a weak and confusing one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I find the new tempest really confusing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love most of the changes, and I understand the intent behind the new tempest, but the huge discrepancy in range between the air and ground attack is really aesthetically uncomfortable.  Air attack is 15 range, but ground attack is 6?  That's an entire thermal lance difference in range!  For two attacks that are visually identical, this just feels really awkward and unintuitive.  

I'd rather remove the ground attack entirely than have a 6 range attack that does nearly no damage. The ground attack is basically like the sentinel at this point--while it technically can attack, it is totally irrelevant.  

Shouldn't the two attacks be the same range, and the new ability have the short range?  If we're worried about tempests being OP, you can make both air and ground attacks have slightly shorter range, like 11-13, and still have it accomplish the role of long-range siege. That would make a lot more sense to me... am I the only one who feels this way?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has noothing nothing, nooothing nothing~ 
Motherfather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But but invincible nydus but but 8 armor ultras WAAAH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would way rather watch this than the Olympics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember in the expansion they had the vulcan which was big bertha on steroids.  Took forever to build, plus required like 4 fusion reactors just to power.  But once it was complete, it rained absolute hell on your enemies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know who remembers this game, but I personally think it should sound like the big bertha shells in Total Annihilation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the hydralisk sound was the most realistic audio change from BW.  In BW, it looked and sounded like it was firing some kind of liquid, when we all knew from the lore that it should be spines.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you recommend someone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im tired of being alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nvm i take that back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then we are mutually entertained. perhaps we can be friends? my life is otherwise too miserable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doesn't affect me at all. tbh i want an apology from the entire world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> overall the visual impact of the purification nova is not impressive enough.  it should like implode and create distortion ripples around it. more lightning arcs surrounding the ball would be nice too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're right, and reddit is where i go to vent all my pent up frustrations with the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your continued response proves that i succeed to some extent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol TRUE COLORS?  thats so funny, like i would attempt to hide my colors.  unlike you, i am fully aware of my flaws. i merely embrace them. you think you are civilized?  no, you are just like me on the inside.  you know its true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'll suck yours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> miserable sadists just like me.  everyone is the same on the inside. we are all rotten to the core. i'm just honest about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its okay, getting you to write that long ass response was entertaining enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 08:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT UNTIL YOU APOLOGIZE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 08:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey snowmanVIII how does it feel to play RIGHT into my hands?  Look how salty and butthurt you are!  What a fool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apology accepted.  thanks for being the bigger man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History is written by the victor.  And you're on the wrong side of history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact of the matter is, people who are wrong need to be punished.  That is the definition of justice.  They need to be taught a lesson.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're anger isn't legit.  Stop having a meltdown.  Your feelings are childish and nothing more
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, don't even try to backpedal.  You said what you said.  You were wrong.  Apologize and move on.  Wonder why everyone is downvoting you?  Cuz you remain completely unapologetic in your self righteousness.  That attitude is unbearable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so you aren't an asshole.  You are just terrible at spotting photoshops.  Let that be a lesson to you in the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not photoshopped. Idiot. By the way, congratulations, you are featured on kotaku!
http://kotaku.com/final-fantasy-xv-delay-rumors-trigger-fan-meltdowns-1785297405 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it feel to be so wrong?  Idiot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those who denied the delay should apologize to us all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 07:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 08:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sweet maize </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 05:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know it's supposed to be a missile? Personally I think it looks like a small shrapnel cannon, hence blaster is fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But is it as fun as worker harassment? ; ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really like most of the changes but I agree the tempest ability needs tweaking.  I propose that they keep the ground attack range the same as the air range, and instead make the disruption sphere 6 range.  This way, the tempest still has a consistent role as long-range siege, but it can also be used to deal AOE to small units in a pinch if it needs to.  The reduced range would keep it from being an abusable harassment ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE NEW CYCLONE IS AMAZING!  It looks like it fires a barrage of shrapnel, that's so cool!  Now it actually performs like its namesake!!  THANK YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does look really nice. I think your balance idea is a great idea.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe they are making siege tanks powerful again.  Ecstatic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i immediately downvoted him for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What idiot tried to put Israel on the same land as Palestine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I'm not the only one who thought the new protoss was a headless templar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because we know they just LOVE enforcing drug laws.  I'm sure they wouldn't rather be go after more pressing crimes.../s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to burst your bubble, but growing cells in a petri dish takes in these quantities will require gallons of plasma serum..... Usually bovine serum or goat serum.  Where do you think that serum comes from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I know it's a joke but I actually refuse to kill spiders out of principle.  They are great little critters.  When my girlfriend sees one I always just take it outside for her.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 04:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make the zergs pay for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would have been perfect if those forcefields he placed behind the marines were placed before the disruptor exploded.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he had a lot to prove.  it probably made him work that much harder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've convinced me that Steve Buscemi is the only suitable Batman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly the point.  Even though killing Zod could be construed as justified, and could be used to further develop Superman's character, the creative minds behind these films never exploited these potential gems.  And if they couldn't even utilize killing Zod to develop Superman, there's no way in hell they could use the killing of random thugs to further develop Batman. .. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Runs him over with the batmobile, shoots him with a shotgun, then murders his entire gang.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 09:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty clear that redditors cannot control their urge to joke and spam memes.  If it were permitted, all the scientific discourse would be drowned in a sea of puns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
