<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to read it in my freshman year of high school for my English class. The whole book is an emotional roller coaster. Books do not normally make me sad but when the main character hears about what happened to Hassan, it wrecked me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Side of Paradise by F. Scott Fitzgerald and Steppenwolf by Hermann Hesse both changed my life. They were not my first books with both authors but they are both my favorites from each. TSOP is not a typical Fitzgerald novel but it shows his genius at such a young age. Steppenwolf blew my mind and I think about it at least once a week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend The Stranger by Albert Camus (also all of his novels are pretty easy), Demian and Siddhartha by Hermann Hesse, Nausea by Jean-Paul Sartre, The Alchemist by Paulo Coelho, and Candide by Voltaire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darkness at Noon by Arthur Koestler and Brave New World by Aldous Huxley were two dystopian novels I loved. I hear The Iron Heel by Jack London is pretty good aswell.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 04:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lending books is my favorite thing to do. I feel like I am sharing an experience with someone else. However, recently I had to adopt a new policy for my booklending. I used to lend any book I had to my friends. But after giving three copies of The Beautiful and Damned to three different girls and never having a copy for myself to read for the first time, I had to change my style. Now I only lend books that I have already read to my friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 04:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the book while going to school in DC. I agree with the mindblowing history of what DC used to be. For example, the area where his "rundown" apartment was is now an incredibly expensive area. I have read almost everything HST wrote and if you enjoy '72 then you will love The Gonzo Papers series. I just finished Better Than Sex (Gonzo Papers 4) and loved it. He talks a lot about the Clintons and gives his "interesting" opinion on Hillary. Stick with '72. It gets a little boring towards the end but the ending made me smile. It was also fitting that when I looked up from the last page, I saw the Washington Monument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choke by Chuck Palahniuk has by far the most aggressive beginning I have ever read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Little Life by Hanya Yanagihara. The whole book is depressing (and incredibly long, I still haven't finished it) but the chapter about Willem's disabled brother had me almost sobbing in the middle of an airport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
