<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm a carrot!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of those weird Californians who never craves In n Out. Maybe because I know my friends will always want to get it on road trips, but I've never gone out of my way to eat there. I still like it, but it is definitely over-hyped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like it's supposed to get here Monday at the latest. An in-person appointment won't really do anything, though, since it still has to be sent out of Sacramento. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CA - Renewing my license </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I renewed my license on 1/11, a few weeks before it expired. DL was sent out on 1/30 and subsequently sent back by the PO because apparently I neglected to check my mail. Finally got on the phone with someone just now who explained the situation to me. She gets snippy "can I explain this or are you going to talk for me?" after I point out how bizarre this whole situation is. Lady hangs up on me before I finish clarifying. Screw the DMV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree, but winning has to count for something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mahorn was always a starter during the Pistons' 88-89 seasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time, the west was pretty much a bloodbath between SA, Utah, Seattle, and Houston. I'd send them to the east to try to knock the Bulls out before the NBA Finals. Most likely would be the Magic, because Penny + LeBron + Shaq is filthy enough without needing to add another star. Probably would take Kawhi to have that second elite wing defender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crybaby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a UCLA homer so I'm not going to even bother. Alford will never play in the NBA, and there are hundreds of more deserving candidates who could have been just as good in his position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not my point. You put Lillard in that position and I'm sure they're contenders still. Why does Alford deserve that top D1 spot over everyone else that isn't a coach's son? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm being ignorant because it bothers me that this coach's son got his spot over someone who might have deserved it more? Damian Lillard went to Weber State for god's sake, you don't think he deserved to play at a top program more than Alford?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article or my earlier post? This guy's father was reserving a spot for him before he was even being recruited. That's a D1 position that someone more deserving could have had. Moreover, the guy takes some really bad shots every time I watch UCLA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fan of neither. SDSU all the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm referring to his shot selection, not the percentage. He puts up some really questionable 3's when they're least needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if youre not going to decide to commit to New Mexico now, Im going to have to start recruiting to fill your spot.

That statement hit me in the mouth. Hed give up my spot? His sons spot?

...

Are you fucking kidding me? Daddy had already reserved his spot when he was 15??? Fuck this kid, nepotism all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope and I can't fucking stand watching him play. The guy must think he's Jimmer or something with all the garbage 3's he puts up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBS just ran a terrible re-ranking of the top 50 of all-time and had CP3 above Stockton, Kidd, Nash, and Isiah. That's four guys who combined for 3 rings, 9 Finals appearances, and 17 Conference Finals appearances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that OP didn't even know it was the 13th FG made in a row tells me he probably just saw that one play on a highlight reel somewhere and didn't bother looking up anything else from that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll still only need about 18/game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Math checks out. 280/20=14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad we cleared that up. So what exactly is bullshit about my comment? Am I not adequately praising Kerr or Paxson for their phenomenal defensive contributions while playing for the Bulls? Am I underrating Nash's superior athleticism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! So in regards to the apparent Russian meddling, what specifically should I ask for when I call? Encourage my local Congressman to investigate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Re: paragraphs 5/6) Is the sort of thing that calling my local Congressman might help influence? What exactly should I ask them to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to check it out from the library before I realized how long it is. Definitely a summer vacation kind of read, I definitely can't finish 1000+ pages before it's due back when I'm working every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should make OP count to 23456 and then ask if he regrets this post. If he doesn't, then he has to continue to 30000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll take the Canucks in this one, population difference is nearly 3:1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He pushed him over so easily! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think I got where I am today because I dressed like Peter Pan over here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Ricky Bobby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe I forgot that one. In all fairness, Scottie's was more of a "stand over you" dunk, whereas AI stepped across Lue. Both fucking amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I love ad hominem in the morning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy but it might have something to do with 17 seasons vs 13 -- and sadly CB probably won't play a 14th. My original point, if you recall, is that Kukoc, Kerr, and Paxson were not "all-time" role players, which is why I'm listing guys who were unquestionably better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just comical that you had the audacity to tell the other guy that his post is just wrong, but you think Grant being on CB's "WS comparables" means he was anything better than a third option. CB literally carried the Raptors to the playoffs, Grant never had the kind of talent or reputation. All-time role players? Shane Battier's ability to play defense made him way more valuable than spot-up shooters, Tristan Thompson is a better rebounder than anyone MJ had outside of Rodman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily, but you literally said these were "all-time role players." I would expect someone of that caliber to be capable of playing defense every once in awhile. Think Fisher, Harper, Horry, Otis Thorpe, Gerald Henderson, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then casual fans shouldn't be allowed to weigh in on who is the GOAT and other related debates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao you are actually trying to tell us that Kerr and Paxson were good at anything other than knocking down shots? Clutch as hell, maybe, but let's not pretend they were any better than Nash on defense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I was four years old, doesn't mean I haven't made a point to watch all the MJ footage I possibly can to make my comparison objective and fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it feels good to crossover the GOAT, but the stepover on Lue is the biggest "fuck you" I've ever seen in the league. It has nothing to do with making the shot or making him fall down, this dude literally stepped over someone on the ground and further made him his bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude used to give me fits in NBA Live 05. Literally the only guy on the Nuggets who could hit a 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Blake...just kidding, fuck that guy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a hero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a +0 tonight. Knicks should cut Rose and sign me obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The B-score is skewed because the MVP almost always went to a center (averaged more rebounds) in the '60s and '70s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While watching it kinda sounded like he was just trying not to say the same names bc Butler went first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KG wasn't even born until after he retired, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caron Butler and KG just listed their top 5 SG's of All-Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butler: 1) MJ 2) Kobe 3) Wade 4) AI 5) West
KG: 1) MJ 2) Kobe 3) Carter 4) Drexler 5) T-Mac

Generational bias? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about historical footage? Most of his best games are on YouTube  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong band. Good taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit. What year is it? I just crawled out from under my rock yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This fact is less fun than I was hoping for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trying to poke fun at age, in all seriousness, are you old enough to have watched MJ? I'm genuinely curious about the demographic of people who already say he is the GOAT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zhuri in 20 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeDon'tStopMeNow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you think a tied game is "clinched"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he tries, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JOB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in 2006 I was playing MapleStory, and my buddy needed a partner in crime to scam people out of valuable equips by doing the "Drop Game" in the Henesys Hair Salon. One of us would hide behind the beam by the door and jump out when the victim starting dropping stuff. I remember one time the guy kept going for like a minute after I jumped out and I got everything. I regret nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh...2006? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandably, the premise and characters are pretty morally ambiguous, but they brought back the director from No.2 and No.5 as well as the composer from No.1, No. 4 and No. 7. Overall No.3 is still my favorite, you can't beat a finish like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 of 42 people were Commies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backdoor Sluts 9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No this was obviously Pokemon Blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah he gotta point first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to your metric, Grant Hill in 1997 was better than ANY of Kobe's seasons...yeah I'm not buying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why my subconscious can surprise me during dreams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I think Brown's more like 16.5ppg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like Machamp with Mewtwo's psychic ability </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac and cheese is my fucking kryptonite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> only Rose, Melo, Porzingod... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting fact if Bogut and Deron join Cavs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If both guys join the Cavs, Cleveland will have the top pick from 2003 (Bron), two of the top 3 from 2005 (Bogut, D-Will.1), number five from 2008 (Love), and three of the top four from 2011 (Kyrie, D-Will.2, Thompson) for a total of 7 former top-5 picks (9 former lottery picks if you throw in Frye and Jefferson)

Is there another team in history with this many former top-5/lottery picks? Is there an easy way to check? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see, because LeBron and the Heatles used to be the bad guys, now it's their turn to be the good guys? Like dress up, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. But I hope people don't forget (10-20 years from now) that Deron Williams is the reason Jerry Sloan no longer coaches. Regardless of what he does for the Cavs, dude is a (legendary) coach killer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awful full of yourselves ain't ya?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg please. Wiggins was plenty enough for Love, Bennett was a throw-in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nephew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm relatively amazed at how far this has come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 08:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me crazy but I'm really into multidimensional stuff. I'd like to think of it as OP's consciousness crossed over into the 4th dimension and saw what would happen later on in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack sounds like a twat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely watch it, one of the best movies I've ever seen. The idea is that if something isn't unanimous, people can be swayed in either direction -- just like a courtroom verdict. Obviously we can't measure 100% of all basketball fans around the world for their opinion, so the GOAT needs to be agreed upon by an overwhelming majority. 

As time progresses, these opinions may shift depending on what people value more. If we ever get to an era where 3-pt ability is the end-all-be-all, then MJ will lose his luster, but based on what the current iteration of basketball calls for, he is the greatest.

Addressing your point of multiple players winning every single year and so on, the GOAT eventually comes down to head-to-head records (which is why players voted Russell as MVP year after year because his Celtics always beat Wilt's Warriors/76ers). As you can see, the criteria goes in cycles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok two actual points I want to make. 

1) If you've seen the movie, you know about how the one guy holds onto his prejudice until the very end when he is the overwhelming minority. At that point the paradigm has already shifted and he knows he's wrong. With MJ/LBJ I'd say it's probably like 9-10 jurors in favor of MJ and 2-3 in favor of LBJ. 

2) You have to look at it in the context of time periods. Wilt was by far the GOAT that had ever come along (sorry Celtics fans, Wilt was more talented than Russell and the league only had 8 teams). By the time MJ arrived, everyone who'd watched Wilt was 20-30 years older and probably set in their ways or not a part of the discussion. Did Michael break Wilt's records? No, but he dominated in a more modern era with better competition and improved skills. The game changes, and over time certain skills become more impressive/valuable -- same reason people were including Steph in the convo last year prematurely. In LeBron's career, efficiency has been a major factor in determining greatness since we were coming off an era where hero ball was widespread (T-Mac, Iverson, etc.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive me for being jaded and used to being downvoted so much that it hardly matters. I respect the hell out of LeBron for the player he is, but the fact of the matter is he and his fans are trying to dethrone a guy who obliterated everything in his path en route to becoming GOAT. For LeBron to surpass him it has to be unanimous and indisputable -- enough to change the minds of people old enough to remember Kareem and Magic and Bird also -- otherwise it's just personal preference. Think of it as 12 Angry Men; if there's any room for doubt, the verdict can be overturned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok you want a rebuttal? 

There is literally no way to make this a fair argument because MJ never had a chance to play a team as good as the Warriors because his Bulls were too busy kicking the crap out of the rest of the league. And he still managed to defeat two 64-win teams in the Finals (Seattle and Utah '97) and two 62-win teams (Phoenix and Utah '98). 

If beating the Warriors is the feather in LBJ's cap, then it stands to reason that it must be something MJ could not do -- otherwise the argument is a wash. We will never know if MJ could have done it (personally I think he could), so I submit that if you want to dethrone the GOAT you need to have a multitude of indisputable arguments in addition to LBJ beating the Warriors. 

Currently, MJ has rings, MVPs, Finals MVPs, scoring average, the ability to average a triple-double at will, the greatest one-minute stretch to finish an NBA Finals, DPOY, cultural influence, seven straight scoring titles, "shoot it you fucking midget," playoff record points in a game, total points in a game between he and LBJ, an NCAA championship-winning basket, the ability to hit .200 after not having played baseball since HS, and I'm done. 

If you're willing to ignore all that, then I'm really wasting my own time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh is this a discussion? I thought it was just LeBron stans downvoting me because I'm disagreeing that he is the GOAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am dismissing it as a joke because it isn't true. Le =/= GOAT. I'm not saying it's because he isn't close, I'm saying it's because he currently is not the GOAT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If beating the Warriors is the end-all-be-all accomplishment in NBA history for you guys then nothing I say is gonna change your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A farce = joke, which is what LeGOAT people are doing (unless they actually believe it, which destroys their credibility already).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If beating the Warriors is the end-all-be-all accomplishment in NBA history for you guys then nothing I say is gonna change your mind. The actual NBA circle of legends and coaches seems to respect MJ far more than this sub does so it's not like any of this matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what gets to me the most. It's a generation of people who just want to be able to say they watched the GOAT play or are swayed because of a lack of reference. And the part that sickens me is they know he isn't there yet, but they persist with this LeGOAT meme bullshit because even if it's in jest it makes people start thinking about it and lends validity to a farce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your assertion is that beating a team of the Warriors' caliber would make LBJ the GOAT. So in essence, you're insinuating that MJ would not be able to beat this team if he were in the same situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're punishing MJ for being said stacked team?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought as well. Not even during that 27 game winning streak?

EDIT: Just checked. Longest in 2013 was 6. A bunch of games in the high 90s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with more skilled big men (Porzingis, Cousins, Turner, Davis, Towns, etc.) there are fewer guys clogging the lane nowadays. Modern PF/C stretch the floor more than guys in the '90s used to, meaning their defenders have to follow them out to the perimeter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you could also attribute that to more balanced offenses like SA and GSW that spread the ball around, but my ultimate point is just that big guys can't camp out in the lane like Olajuwon, Robinson, and Mutombo used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my edit in my latest response to Prophet. Annointing LBJ based on beating the Warriors punishes MJ for never having the chance to play a team that good -- his team WAS that good.

I'm not sure if we're on the same page with the zone D idea...teams aren't allowed to use zone D's anymore (3 second rule), which is why driving is easier today than opposed to 20 years when a shotblocker could camp out in the paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand and appreciate that you're trying. The issue, which the other guy who responded to me mentioned, is that weighing these particular accomplishments is completely subjective. Where you have them at 100oz. and 98oz., someone else might have LBJ at 96 or 95, all extremely impressive and probably qualify him as 2ndGOAT, but inconsistent and far from unanimous. If he hopes to dethrone MJ, it MUST be unanimous, meaning he'll need more than just 1 or 2 more oz., he needs an entire cup, something irrefutable that cannot be mitigated.

EDIT: I also feel like it's worth acknowledging that making a win over the Warriors the deciding factor punishes MJ for never having a chance to play a team that good. His Bulls WERE that team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's not looking at the whole picture, that's allowing one individual feat to trump anything else that has ever been done in NBA history. By that same token Eli Manning is the greatest QB of All-Time for taking down the 18-0 Patriots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As for your last sentence, you could also point to current zone defense rules as making it easier to drive. I agree with you that it is very subjective as to which feats you give more weight to, and this is why a discussion/debate like this will likely never be unanimous. My larger point, as you can see in my second response to Prophet, is that if LeBron is unanimously known as #2 now and MJ is #1, then beating the Warriors should only TIE them, not allow LeBron to leapfrog Michael. And to refute my original point, a feat like beating the Warriors cannot be the sole catalyst for dethroning the GOAT; there need to be multiple, indisputable feats that make it clear that a new GOAT has arrived. Otherwise they might as well just be 1a and 1b. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the way I see it: if LeBron is right below, then why would a win leapfrog MJ? Wouldn't it just tie them, making them 1a and 1b? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MJ scored 69. LeBron never did. Your basis for GOAT can't rest solely on what one has done that the other hasn't. You have to look at the entire picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even sadder, I don't think it'll be that he can't catch up. He'll have an opportunity and decide not to try because he'll know he won't get there in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! Which show are you going to? I'm seeing them in Hollywood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's any consolation the Bulls are my second favorite East squad. Would like to see you in the Finals again someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like that big market status has really been a factor in the past. Shaq is the only star we've acquired through free agency. All others were through trades or the draft. Second biggest FA is probably Artest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately the Lakers don't give two shits about impressing you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
