<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8625</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thinks that is his lunch box....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sort of theme do the calenders have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best tips for networking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are some tips to network with other lawyers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.stuffindianslike.com/2008/04/170-holding-hands.html more information about Indians holding hands...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is common for straight Indian males to hold hands, to express their friendship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading all these crazy stories makes me appreciate my partner even more.  I am going to buy her flowers and chocolate tomorrow to say thanks for being so sane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL cone also means joint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that can kill you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinner is sorted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In farcry 4 these bustards kill villagers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bedtime for baby and Jack Daniels for grandma  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he knew her...  Or that's assualt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dumbest guy is always at the end of the rope,  and the smartest at the beginning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for STEVENNNNNN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you do it in reverse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be in r/funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a positive side:

-your age is not a big issue,  there are people starting their law degrees in there 30's

-your mental issue seem to be resolved and triggers are identified

-your family situation has seem to improved

-you have a passion to study law

On the negative side:

-the law market is not improving and finding a job is becoming harder

-competition for graduate level jobs have increased significantly 

-grades,  work history,  extra curricular activities, and  networking connections fuel most hiring decision 

Overall I say you should do what makes you happy,  only you can shape the future you want,  even if it takes a bit more hard work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do lawyers have a higher chance of becoming depressed then other professions? I think yes and no,  it depends on your work environment,  the type of work you do,  and the company you keep.  I believe that all lawyers are prone to depression just like all other professions,  just that our industry doesn't directly like to deal with it....

As someone who doesn't drink,  I dread most company sponsored events the ratio is 80% alcohol to 20% food.  Not a good environment for someone who is an alcoholic or on the brink of becoming one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds abit fishy to me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What flavour cookies were they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think sandwhichs taste better grilled than cold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be quite interesting learning about successful people and their affairs.  Are most of your clients self made or trust fund babies? and what is the most common industry did they gain wealth from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say for a man a gift of cufflinks is pretty awesome,  because it's not something you would normally buy for yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess he couldn't sea it as a bad gift  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 08:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain the fresh fish gift?  I'm bream-ing to fin out more?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man he jiggles in the movie when he fires that ak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the pub on Monday, Tuesday,  Wednesday,  Thursday,  Friday and Saturday night.  Sunday we stay home to nurse our bruises.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll second this,  mooting competition organisers are pretty generous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 14:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man those guys need a shower  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends what the card said  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder what they would call thus shot  a roof trick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish all clients were like this,  demanding and rewarding LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why do salaries get quoted with super?  It seems kinda pointless since no one negotiate based on what super they recieved haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kinda funny to think people would try to avoid paying a lawyer haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The great part about conciliation is that it is more flexible and a better communication platform for two disputing parties.  The main issue you may face is who has the better leverage to exercise more power throughout the process. 

As suggested above you should try to contact a lawyer who can at least advise you of the main points of concerns,  risks,  and how to minimise these. 

Many people on here can't give you specific advice as no one knows the facts of the case. 

Best thing you can do is understand the situation,  take out all emotional bias,  prove your case based on facts,  and know your employee rights. 

Most of this information can be gathered from your employee contract,  government websites based in your state,  and free legal aid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever recieved a gift from a client? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring a lawyer can be quite a thankless profession,  just wondering if anyone has actually been rewarded by a client.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daddy has a plane,  you get yeezys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we know who's paying for drinks all night now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He surprisingly good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be the number for spec it ralph  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish my life was held together with such a nice blue strap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta work for those Jordans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 09:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is becoming the norm,  recently slater and Gordon wound up their conyancing arm because it was not profitable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 09:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had to pick an area to practice,  which area would you choose and why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 05:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you consider family law to be the same as you described wills abd estates?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is it like to be a wills and estate lawyer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am curious to find out what it is like to work in the wills and estates area. 

What is the work life balance like? Would you except a lot of long hours and after hour client calls or is it better then corporate. 

What stage of your career would you interact with clients? 

Is career progression slow or fast? And I do understand this is dependent on your networking and work ethic,  but I am more interested in a general view. 

Is job market for these type of lawyers stable or erratic? 

How is the salary compared to other areas? 

Any information would be helpful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe people hunt these animals for sport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 12:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uou shouldn't feel bad dude,  who smokes a blunt at work.  Him getting fired was going yo happen,  even with you intervention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
