<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything here is true, even if it's not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, those are pretty much my life goals also. 

(besides being a nurse once I can actually afford college)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why but your comment brought me such joy. 

The best thing about '97 is that I used it when I was 11 to make a song about my birthday, to the tune of the Pizza Pizza jingle (Not sure if they're only in Canada, but if you know what I'm talking about you can imagine how lame this is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Red Bull tastes awful, Monster is the only energy drink I actually enjoy the taste of. But then, I am technically still just a dumbass teenager, so of course I'd like that drink over the others. No tape worms in my eyes! 

Squiggle eye free since '93

Not really though, I'd love to be four years older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh that's a much better idea o.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, I hope you feel better soon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww thank you! That one was actually really easy to write :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could collaborate if there's an idea floating around, having someone else around to keep me on track or give me a deadline for pieces of a story would definitely improve the fact that I have three half written stories that I just forget to write. I believe I'm technically just a starting out writer, I've put out a few things in the past couple months, and a small series on my old account over a year ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see someone else infected by my Population Control "infection"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thank you! I am honored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had quite a few amusing ones on My Children Never Lied, many people telling me I'm a bad father, and things about how I kinda ruined the message I was sending them with my actions. Parenting lectures were quite amusing. 

Two specifically made my day 

"Well damn Dad"

And a little comment chain where someone asked in the end of the comment how to make their children always honest. Have to find the link for it, much better without my crappy summary. 


Edit: 

Here's the comment because I don't know how to link the comment specifically : 

I mean, wow, and all that. But how did you get them to be honest? I guess maybe you aren't the best person to get parenting tips from but... with a 6 and 3 year old at home I'd love to know who actually colored on the walls last night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where would you categorize stories dealing with diseases, or pandemics? Would that be Human, supposing that humans caused the "plague" or whatnot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular alarms, like the horrid beeping my clock makes at 5am, and fire alarms, and the sirens the oil plants I used to live by had, don't scare me though. It's just some specific ones that if they last more than thirty seconds, would send me into a full on gasping-heartpounding-bawling panic attack. I get the planes thing though, I'm afraid of heights, but not roller coasters. Mostly ledges though. A few times when a ride operator hasn't checked my restraints thoroughly enough. I had them hold the Rougarou at Cedar point because they didn't push down the restraint over me, and I was so loose I nearly cried, but they shoved it down hard enough that my pelvis was in great pain after that, so we eventually got to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late on this, but this may be my most fucked up: [Population Control](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/545jly/population_control/)

Though I do love adding in that fucked up twist in every story, those are not nearly as drastic as this one. Can't wait to do something gruesome again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will have any attachments may not be in my life in my name and then the way you have any attachments may not be in my name and then the way you have been sent to see if it would love it would love it would love it would love it would...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that if I try to plan a story, it takes forever. I've had one sitting on the sidelines for over a month because I keep getting ideas to add to it, and put them in a little mental checklist, but then end up over thinking when I feel like writing, and just start a new story. The few I've put out there took about five hours each including editing. I just sat down with a vague idea of beginning middle and end, and wrote whatever came to mind. They didn't turn out too bad, I really liked them. Though when trying to expand one of these into a series and trying to plot out where to take it, I entirely psyched myself out over how well the first part did compared to the second, and scrapped the idea, with a part three sitting as a draft somewhere to wrap things up. I just can't organize my thoughts enough to get back to it. I've never actually plotted out a plan for my stories, they're not super stars, but they haven't been total garbage so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds really great however you end up doing it, if you do!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 02:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the post with the doc was stickied it would be easy to find for those interested, but if not, a separate sub could be useful. A master post that either shows the current stats, daily/hourly/howeveryoupdate and then new posts for when additional statistics are added to the entirety of your project, for example (Update: Now includes most common up vote hours). Or just periodic posts about how the statistics change. Master post for all time statistics, weekly posts to alert that the master post has changed, and/or statistics for that week. Things like that. A sub would give you more freedom to display old drafts of your statistics with new ones, and to use your statistics on both large and small scale data (all time, yearly, weekly), without having to link a bunch of different spread sheets and such. 

So many things you could do with your data! This is a wonderful display of your talents, kudos to you c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good survey (as weird as that is to say)  
Hopefully it is well responded to, because you have a lot of questions in there that can give great feedback for the sub c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding the popularity based on time posted/subject/next to another story would be an incredible statistic for authors to see!  Able to find what the readers most like, when they are most active and would see the post, and help avoid posting content if it negatively affected by being next to another type of story c: Love stats, this is amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The estimated reading time sounds really cool, definitely a feature I'd like because I'm a relatively quick reader, and I read stories between doing things and it would help me see what I have time to complete between tasks. Thanks for this post, makes me definitely interested in checking it out since I'm just using BaconReader right now c: 

Edit: I feel like I sound like a paid promoter for this app but still, estimated reading time for the win  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 08:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up being asked to try and end after you, praise your addition for helping inspire my twisted ending  I was scared as hell making it, and didnt want to burden the captain who had offered to finish if I couldn't come up with something, your part made my creativity blossom in my over extensive ending, bless you wonderous soul  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 08:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote the ending for my team and I was so into while doing it, I'm technically a noob though so I'm hoping everyone likes it and that even though it was three comments long that most of it gets in there. Anxious anxious anxious waiting for the final draft!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read it and some of the comments, great story, and the puns are killing me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohmygosh that first one is gold  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Children Never Lied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 06:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always raised my kids to tell the truth. They needed structure in their lives, and I needed peace of mind in mine. You see, during the birth of the twins the doctors couldn't save Amelia. Complications, blood loss and such, I try not to think of the actual details too much, it always causes me to feel hatred for the doctors who couldn't save her. I blamed them for it all. I never blamed my two beautiful girls though, they were a blessing and the legacy of my wife. I raised them on the beliefs that Amelia had held so dearly, honesty, courage, the willingness to learn and discover new things, and the strength to stand up for their own beliefs. 

I knew I had taught them well. Whenever a problem arose they came to me, they told me the truth of what was going on in their lives. They told me of arguments with other school children, and admitted when they had committed actions that were wrong. They never lied at all. I made sure they knew how valuable it was to be honest and trustworthy, how much they embodied the soul of their mother, and how she would be proud of anything they did so long as they were truthful in doing so. 

They were so young, they could barely grasp the entire concept of all the reasons I praised their honesty, but they felt good about themselves knowing that their words always held true and couldn't be disproven. They came to the point where they honestly couldn't tell a lie, they didn't know how to conceive a story in their minds to cover up the truth of something. I mean of course, at times it caused minor issues, they seemed like the sort who couldn't keep a secret. They could to a point, but they couldn't outright lie or try to deceive when asked. They were the most honest little girls you'd ever meet. 

There also came times when the girls were a bit older and would be with friends who were of a troublesome sort, and they were always honest to the parents about what had happened. This led to untrusting parents who thought their own children wouldn't lie to them, and untrusting children who detested my little girls for their outright honesty. I always stood up for my kids, I did whatever I could to prove how pure and honest they were. It took a while, but I think after all the things the girls have experienced lately, that the people of our town finally believe that my children were entirely honest. 

It all started just after the girl's thirteenth birthday. They had gone to a friend's house one weekend, and come home terrified. Apparently they had been watching a series of horror movies, which was something my daughters rarely were interested in doing, but their friends at the sleepover insisted upon having a little marathon. Sure, the girls had seen scary movies in the past, and spent a few days paranoid about the content and that it could be true, but in the past I had been able to ease their fears by disproving the existence of whatever it was they feared. This time was an exception.

After a few days with no alteration to their terror, Marissa and Claire came to me hoping to further explain. Not only had they been watching the movies, but a specific one in general had piqued their interest. The film had been about a man who appeared to people as a silhouette, almost a black shadow of a person, and once you saw this man you, or someone close to you was fated to die. Apparently the girls had gone into their own attempts at disproving the existence of this man, and had failed. They had only found more evidence, videos, stories of encounters. Everything seemed so true, and they couldnt prove any of it wrong. I reassured them that I would find a way to show them that this wasnt real, but no matter what I searched and looked for, I found myself becoming curious at how all the recounts of this entity seemed so true. Everyone who gave true names for those killed by this man seemed to be telling the truth. There were accurate obituaries matching the details of the stories, some of which were not public until after the encounters were released. I even found that some authors who had seen the man were later found dead.

The girls knew I was coming up with blanks in disproving the reality of this entity, and suddenly their reputation began going downhill. They couldnt stop talking about the stories, and how they were real, and how they were afraid that it could happen to someone they knew. Their classmates laughed at them, school officials thought they were being childish and silly, and they began to get in trouble for their adamant belief in something they had never seen in real life. They were losing their record of being honest, and it was causing people to think that my boasting of the girls amazing morals was false all along. I had to revamp my efforts to fix their reputation, my daughters never lied. 

A few weeks later they began telling disturbing tales. They told me that they had started seeing the man in the middle of the night, standing in the shadows of their room. It got progressively worse from there, every few days they would have another encounter. The man hovering in the shadows, watching them with eyes they couldnt see. Whispers next to their beds in the night, saying that he was coming for them. I put a voice recorder on the bedside table between Claire and Marissa. It recorded low, raspy whispers which threatened the lives of my children, beckoned for them to wake up, and told them not to run. I allowed the girls to have this, to prove to people they were not lying, and I researched the entity they were facing with renewed worry for the girls.

The people of the town still werent believing the story they told, even with the proof right there. I could find no one in town who was willing to help my daughters, they were branded as liars. Everyone thought they faked the recordings, and that they were just trying to scare the friends who had initially introduced the girls to the idea of the shadowy man. I upped my efforts once again, and it was the last I would ever do for them.

I woke up one morning after a long night of researching the stories of what happened to the people who had faced the entity, no good endings. The house was quite, an odd thing because it was a weekday and the girls were normally awake before me to prepare for school. I walked into their room and saw the most horrifying sight Id ever experienced. Blood and gore splattered their beds and walls, my two little angels were cut from ear to ear. Dead. I called the police, I cursed everyone for not believing them, for not helping them. That was just this morning, but it feels a thousand years away. 

My love for them knew no bounds, and I would have done anything to save them from a dishonest life. My children never lied. They saw a man in their room, they heard a voice whispering to them, even on the night they were murdered. Im running out of time to prove once and for all that they were honest until the moment of death.

I tried so hard, I lost so much sleep trying to help them. I stood in the shadows wearing a mask for hours at a time, waiting for them to see the figure they were convinced was real. I hid under beds and whispered terrifying words, I broke lightbulbs so that they couldnt turn them on and ruin the effect of the dark silhouette. I ended them in the height of their belief, just to show everyone that they really were being honest about the danger they faced. I made one error, one that is having me sent down to the police station to answer questions I was not prepared for. Telling you this before I go has helped me figure it out though.

My children never lied, and all the proof to the stories they told lay in a voice recorder I had forgotten was turned on during the last night they were alive. There was a man in their room. There was whispering under the bed. There was the sound of muffled gurgling as they tried to speak through the deep gashes laid into the flesh of their throats, and then there was the sound of their father crying and apologizing, and telling them that he would make sure that everyone knew that they had never lied. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ((final part, just over the character limit on that last bit, my apologies))


Her face was full of surprise, adoration, and relief. She quickly leaned out the door and beckoned to someone, and seconds later my wonderful, amazing Anisa came running into the room. It was a day filled with tears, joy, and laughter. Quite possibly the happiest day of my life.

Its been three months since then, Im back at my old place of work, with a promotion and a pay raise. My family is happy, my daughter and wife have never looked so beautiful. I cherish every moment with them. I could almost write off everything that had happened to me as some type of horrifying comatose dream, but every day I see people in the corner of my eye who have faces like that of the Torturer. Some of them I know, many I see and suddenly their name pops into my mind. Everytime I see one of these mutilated, disgusting, disfigured faces, I write down the name that pops into my head. These are the faces of true sinners. Every so often, I run into Nachstern at a crossroads, where I hand him a list. I still see Francis on the bus often, he has been helpful in becoming accustomed to my new role in the world.

Everything is okay now, for me at least. All I can say, is I hope if I ever see one of you who have read this, is that your true face is the one you see in the mirror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ((part two due to character limit))

I stood less than a foot away from her when I stopped and met her eyes. She was amazing, still fully nude and appearing like the first time we had ever fallen into bed together. I longed to touch her skin, and as the thought appeared in my mind, she smirked. The facade broke for me there. The woman I loved was astoundingly beautiful, but always self conscious. I knew I was seeing an illusion of my Elizabeth. She reached out to me, and I swatted her hand away. She scowled. I willed myself to look past the illusion, but the appearance of my wife did not waver. She tried to seduce me, and I resisted with a will I didnt know I contained. That was when this Demoness decided to begin the real torture. 

She screamed at me in my darlings voice. Blamed me for the death of our daughter, for the fact that she was trapped in eternal servitude to a Demon. She described in detail vile acts in which she had to perform for him, sexual favors, self mutilation, seduction of men and women who became victims she was forced to torture and mutilate to entertain her master. It pulled at my heart slightly, but I couldnt let go of the fact that this creature was not my wife. This was the Torturer, a liar, even if it was the truth this Demoness meant only to hurt me in any way possible. I withstood it all, my will was entirely made of steel at this point. I tried blocking out her voice, and my head was filled with screams. The screams of my daughter as she was murdered. I closed my eyes, and my head was filled with awful visions of her being mutilated in my own home.

I took a deep breath, and smiled to myself. Perhaps if I got through this, I could save them. It felt like years of this torture went on before the creature noticed my grin. The face of my love melted into that of a terrifying mutilated monster. Rotting flesh dripped from jagged, malformed bones, and the stench of death emanated from the Demoness. She shrieked at me, and told me I was Damned for not having any compassion for those I should have cared the most about. I was suddenly chained, the bonds had appeared from nowhere and I was suspended on a wall I had not been up against moments before. The Demoness raked me with claws, my flesh returned and she peeled it off with every tool that existed. Over and over  my skin regenerated, and she mutilated me in every way imaginable for eternities. Cuts, burns, poisons, I lost count of what was being done to me. I laughed hysterically, You think you can make any pain imaginable equate to the pain I lived with before I came here?

She grew bored with me. I watched as the forms of my wife and daughter appeared, and sang softly to myself as I witnessed them brutalized and slaughtered in front of me time and time again. The Demoness finally gave up with these tactics, and returned to the form of the Goddess she had been when I first gazed upon her. I was released from my bindings, and I went to kneel at her feet. I pity you, Demoness. Condemned to punish for eternities, even to those who dont deserve the things you do. A mind filled with such sinful evils, some such evils which you punish others for. You cant even show your true form, are you ashamed of it so much? Or is it simply not satisfying to live an existence where you are only feared for how despicable your true face has become, so you must put on an illusion to recall the feeling of actually being wanted? Its sad to see that you are nothing but a lowly servant of the one who truly passes judgement, a mindless, pathetic little tool to be used to carry out the dirty work, with no true reward to you. I smirked at that, her face seemed taken aback for a moment. 

I am no tool, she sneered at me, I will bring you to Sir Morningstar, and show you what the true face of fear is. A rope appeared around my neck, and she led me deeper into the pit of despair, towards the source of the undying heat. He cares for me, and only me, she spoke softly as I trailed along behind her, down a jagged stone stairwell, If he didnt, I wouldnt have the means to condemn him to a mortal life. I pondered over that as we continued deeper into the depths of Hell. The heat intensified, something I didnt think was possible. 

What happens if he was to become mortal? I questioned, not entirely sure if she planned on sharing more. 

Well, youll never live to see it once he gets his hands on you, but if I was to Damn him to humanity, then the highest ranking of the Greater Demons would consume his place, take on his identity and memories, and the Morningstar we know now would live as a human until his death, then being sent unto purgatory, never to return. She smiled at that, as though it was a peaceful thought for her.

Would you become Morningstar? I asked. She scowled at me with distaste, and yanked the rope forward so I stumbled down the stairs. I choked as she pulled me up by the rope and leaned close to my face. She tilted her head to the side, as though in deep in thought,

No, that would be Nachstern. I am the Torturer. I remain as I am. Though this Morningstar has become corrupt, wasting my time upon people like you who dont deserve to be treated by my talents. He lacks the vision to see true sin these days. I got back onto my feet as she continued with our descent. 

We came upon a grand hall, lit with lanterns of blue flame, the ceiling was not visible, and our steps echoed through the cavernous space as we walked along a path of tall, black, stone pillars. As I had become accustomed to, something appeared out of the darkness as we approached. A great throne, fit for a king, stood ahead of us. A man in a black tailored suit sat in the chair, he was abnormally tall. Even sitting I could tell that he was nearly ten feet, broad shouldered, and astoundingly handsome. He scowled as we approached. Why do you bring this soul upon me? He spoke in a booming voice that shook me to my core.

I was sent by Nachstern, you are to supply me with the means to redemption, and return me to the mortal world. I spoke loudly, and did not waiver. I knew what needed to be done. He laughed, and the entire room shook. I was suddenly brought to my knees by the sound of millions of agonized screams in my head. 

You think I would offer you redemption! He bellowed. You belong here, with the rest of the Damned. You are a sinner who deserves nothing but punishment, this is my judgement, and so it shall be. He glared at the Demoness who still held me on a leash, Why have you not cursed his soul to eternal Damnation? She seemed surprised, and slightly disgusted. 

This soul does not belong here, he is a man of judgement, and there is no punishment to break his soul. 

You useless pawn! Rocks began to fall from the volume of his voice echoing through the cavern. He began to grow larger, the seams of his expensive suit split apart as his body reformed into the disgusting creature I recalled from the vision Id had at the crossroads. The putrid scent of decaying corpses began to weigh down the air, I tried to shallow my breathing. I could taste vile, rotted flesh on my tongue. His soul is Damned. Only I may pass judgement. Sudden footsteps from behind us made me glance back, only to see Nachstern approaching the scene. The Demoness smiled. 

My dear Morningstar, you are not to pass judgement alone. You are unfit for it. I heard whispers all around me, which turned to howls and shrieks.The room shook, more debris began to fall, and Nachstern continued to approach. I looked at the Morningstar, his face was filled with rage. I could no longer hear their discussion, only screams in my head as the shaking intensified. There was a sudden flash of blue light from the direction of the Torturer, and then I was struck with a large piece of falling rock. Everything went black.

I started to become conscious and felt that I was in a bed, I was awash with relief. Before I could open my eyes, I heard a voice in my head. Mr. Cole, the new Morningstar has arisen. The life you knew is not the same as the one you are about to open your eyes to. You will see in your fellow man the faces of true sin, but you will finally receive what you deserve. Good luck in your new life. The voice of Francis faded away, and I opened my eyes to a brightly lit hospital room. In the chair next to my bedside sat Mr. Nachstern.

Good morning Mr. Cole! He exclaimed pleasantly, Now we only have a moment before dear Lizzy returns, but I need to let you in on some things about your newfound life. You have fulfilled the terms of your debt and shall be reward as such. According to everyone here, the night you were fired you suffered a brain aneurysm and have been in a coma ever since. All the memories you have of the events which occurred after our meeting at the crossroads did not occur. I will apologize, you are a man free of sin, and you had to face great hardship to have the strength to play the role that you did, and to become my aid in the passing of judgement upon your fellow humans. He  smiled before continuing, 

In an interesting turn of events, the company you were working for was taken into new ownership. These new owners did not approve of the shady business going on, and luckily ended up with your work in their hands, and have since fixed the corruption in your office. Im sure theyd be glad to have such an adept employee back on their payroll, considering the downsizing in staff they have done to remove the parties at fault. I think that about sums up the need-to-know information. Well be in touch. He walked out of the room, and as soon as he was out the door my beautiful wife entered.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ((Sorry for the delay, took a bit to tweak my ideas to flow with everyone else, and I was a bit late on replying to my turn. This is super long because I thought it made a well wrapped up ending to the story, but feel free to add/remove/replace/change anything to keep the story in tact and such, this is part one because of the character limit for comments))

I fell into a black abyss. I was lost in thoughts and memories for what seemed to be an eternity, memories that brought on questions. I thought of how this all started, how perfect my life had been before I had been fired over doing my job just a little too well. I recalled the wonderful days of playing with my beautiful daughter in the park near our house when she was just learning to walk. Making castles in the sand box, which she loved to destroy as she became an adorably destructive dinosaur. Her first words, first steps, the excitement in her eyes when I came home from a long day at work and could pick her up and spin her around in my arms. I remembered the day I met my lovely Lizzy, how beautiful she was, and how her beauty had been dimmed when I saw her in the office of that Demon. She was still so gorgeous, but it seemed her beauty was laid over an empty shell. I thought back to the day at the crossroads, the day I lost everything. The day I *gave away* everything. What had I gained in that deal?

I was a smart man. I always read the fine print when I signed any contract, I knew when something seemed too good to be true. How could I have not seen it this time? I had made a deal without knowing what the cost was, and what I would receive for making it. What did I gain? I couldnt think of a goddamn thing. Why did I make a deal that I gained nothing for? I screamed into the endless void that I felt myself falling into.

WHAT AM I PAYING FOR!

I felt myself hit the ground hard, my skin felt aflush with a sudden heat. I broke into a sweat, was this hell? My question was answered abruptly. 

No, Mr. Cole, this is not Hell, not quite yet. I turned to the voice and was faced with a tall dark shadow in the distance. Behind him stood tall, black, worn down doors, laden with iron chains. I felt a cold feeling in my chest, and realized the sensation came from my pocket. I pulled out a small piece of paper, which emanated an ice cold sensation that leaked into my heated fingertips. It was the card Francis had given to me. As this realization dawned on me, the card fell to dust, and I returned my gaze to the dark figure before me. Ah yes, the deep voiced boomed, You know me as Francis in the mortal world, but here I am Brother to He who passes judgement upon the sins of man, I am the Keeper of Gates, my name is something your mortal tongue could not speak. I was in awe, how could this be the man I had met on a city bus? 

I felt that the questions I held were of no value now, I was about to discover the truth behind the deal I had made. Yes Mr. Cole, I tried to warn you as I could, but your fate has still brought you to me, and to Him. I must tell you what lies ahead of you. Behind me stand the gates to the realm of the Damned, these gates you shall soon pass, and begin on your final task to reap the rewards you have been longing for.

You will find yourself faced with the one who delves out the punishments, and you must suffer through them, and in return find yourself a way to return your pain unto her. If you can defeat her, and face my brother himself, you may finally receive the reward you have been seeking. If you can stand in the face of judgement, and prove yourself unto him in whichever way he deems fit, you may surpass him, and return to your mortal life. Not the one you once knew, but as one who may pass judgement upon others, see the true face of the wicked mortals of the earth, and seal their fate in the afterlife. Do you understand?

I stood dumbstruck for a moment, but the anxiety and fear that would normally consume me did not arise as I had expected it would. I thought on his words for a moment. Basically, I would be sent through these gates, face possible torture, somehow overcome said torture, face the Devil himself, and possibly find a way to gain his approval and be sent home? It seemed insane, like I was living a nightmare. If I succeeded, what would my life be like? Would I regain my love? Would I be constantly tied to this terrifying place, tasked with deciding which of my fellow humans deserved eternal damnation? Would I gain the wisdom needed to do so? It was quite a lot to handle for my fragile broken mind.

I understand, Mr. Cole, you may feel reservations. As you go through this you shall gain more understanding. You have faced great hardship and loss, this could be your chance at redemption, perhaps even vengeance against the truly sinful souls who have wronged you, you- I cut him off abruptly.

I understand enough, and Im ready. He nodded solemnly, and extended a shadowy hand towards the gates that lay ahead, I started forward. He moved his hand in a sweeping motion, and the large doors began to slowly open, allowing an intense and nearly unbearable heat to seep towards me and sear my skin as I progressed forward. 

Good luck, Mr. Cole. He stood by as I entered the gates, the last thought in my mind was one I had thought often since the day I first met Engel Nachstern, *what else have I got to lose?* Then gates slammed shut behind me. 

I lost all sight. The room before me was sweltering, it felt as though my skin was melting from my bones. My clothes burned into my skin, becoming a disgusting mess of fabric and bubbling flesh. Layers upon layers of skin and muscle were seared away, blood poured from my deteriorating veins, and my nerves were exposed to every sensation possible. Heat, air, and dust particles sent waves of pain vibrating through my body. It was dark as pitch, and I could see nothing in front of me for endless moments as I stumbled forward in agony. Blue flames suddenly lit up the edges of the room, and the light stunned me for a moment. I vaguely wondered how my eyes hadnt melted from their sockets, but I found myself becoming accustomed to the heat. I steeled my resolve, this pain was nothing compared to the night I lost my family. It was merely physical, and would never scar me the way my losses already had. 

I was a mutilated and nearly skeletal figure, trudging forward into the heat of the room. The stench of death and decay surrounded me, and from the center of the darkness, where the dim blue flames could not quite penetrate, appeared a figure I had not been expecting. An ethereal beauty of a woman stood before me, tall with long hair, skin like porcelain, and eyes a deep dark blue of the ocean depths, not to mention completely nude and sporting curves only a goddess could hold. She stared at me inquisitively, head tipped to the side as though inspecting my malformed body, but her gaze was deeper than that, she was peering directly into my mind and soul. In a mere instant I watched the gorgeous creature melt away, and become my dear Elizabeth. I strode towards her, knowing in the back of my mind I was about to face a great test.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (( not the greatest at dialogue so feel free to suggest extra dialogue for my parts, or make up for it within your own))


I grew even more anxious as I approached the door, well, I was practically pushed to it. I felt the urge to turn and run as far and fast as I could, but I knew that not only would these two goons be able to catch me with ease, I truly needed to give my payment, I owed far too much to escape this. I tried to put a resigned look on my face as we got to the door, Lem looked at me like I was a roach he wished to squash. I glanced over at Piotr, he seemed to have a look of pity as he stared at the wooden door in front of us, the navy blue paint peeling with age. 

I stood a second too long trying to collect myself I suppose, because Lem gave me a sharp jab with his elbow to just below my ribcage. It made my resolve falter a bit as I tried to catch my breath after the blow. "You better get your ass in there, you know He doesn't like to be kept waiting." He smiled at that, and gave me a shove forward as Piotr grabbed the handle and swung the door open for me. I tripped over the lip of the doorway and found myself on my hands and knees in a dark foyer. I heard Lem's laughter behind me, "Already prepared to beg, just how he'd like it." Piotr gave me a disgusted look before he grabbed the door and swung it shut, they remained outside. 

The building seemed cavernous, and empty, but I knew He was there somewhere, waiting for me. I stood and brushed off my clothes, the place was full of dust and cobwebs, as though no one had been here in years. I gently patted my pocket that held Francis' number, knowing that calling him could just end with him being another victim of my debt. Knowing the option was there did strengthen my will slightly, but still I knew there was no leaving here without seeing Him. I began my way through the dim room, the only light seeping through dust caked windows near the entry. My options for travel took me towards a long dark hallway, and a set of stairs next to it that led upwards. Something told me that going upstairs was not where I should be, so I continued down the hallway. As I made my decision on which pathway to take, the space below the door at the end of the hall seemed to illuminate with an eerie orange glow, as though a light had been turned on in the room it hid. I knew I was heading in the right direction.

I sighed as I went towards the door, I could only vaguely recall my last meeting with His people, but I can remember unpleasant details about just before. It's been a while, the scene wasn't as similar. It began in an upper-end neighborhood, at an office-type building you could tell only someone very wealthy could own. It didn't feel uncomfortable to be there, but almost calming. I was confident going in, though I was surrounded by thug-like escorts that time as well. Security comes with being wealthy and having power. I had no idea how much power, I just hoped He could grant me what I wanted, and I was willing to pay anything for it. That wasn't what I most recalled about it though, because you never quite forget a man stumbling from a room screaming in pain, and clasping his shattered, bleeding hands to his chest. I can't imagine if that was his payment, or the result of not paying, and I'm still afraid to find out. At the time all I could think was that the man I was about to see obviously lived a mob-like lifestyle, and was not one to be lightly fucked with. I remember being slightly wary about stepping in the trail of blood the previous client had left in his wake, more out of hoping to make a good impression on the man I was about to see than my own disgust at the blood itself. I was such a confident man as I approached that door, I wish I held the same confidence now.

The dark hallway seemed oppressive, like the walls were closing in around me. My breathing hastened, and dust caught in my throat as I gasped for air, sending me into a coughing fit. My vision went hazy again, I was so close to paying off my debt, and here I was choking for air in a dark corridor. I had to lean against a wall to catch my breath, collect my thoughts, and dry my cheeks of tears that I hadn't realized had escaped. I was truly scared. I calmed myself slightly and took the last few steps to the door. As I reached for the handle, the dim orange glow seemed to vanish. I took another deep breath and steeled myself for what lay behind the door. I closed my eyes as I opened it, I was so cowardly. I opened them only to reveal an immaculate black marble staircase, which wound down into the depths of the building. It once again brought back memories of my first meeting, but I felt no calm feelings as I started down the steps towards the true person who held my debt in his hands. 


((just for clarity, when I flashback I was trying to make it so that the person he initially met was not the same person he is about to encounter, just to stay in context with the last sentence of our awesome captains part, feel free to tweak my details if they're hard to flow with)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrote a true one on my old account, somewhere buried in oldness and no interest for it, I believe there's at least a hint of truth in many of them, and some are actual accounts of things that people have experienced, but I also feel that the truest get less attention because it's hard to write something true as a gripping story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me, but my stepmother when she was four. She swears on her mother's grave this is true. 

When she was about four, she was sleeping in a room with her aunt on the third floor of the house when she was awoken by tapping on the window. She saw what she calls 'The Man in Black' and the angel of death. Apparently the man, basically just a black sillouhette of a person, was tapping on the window and calling her name. "Michelle, Michelle, open the window and come play with me."

She hid under the covers and fell back asleep eventually, all while the thing at the window called for her to come and play. The next day when she told her mom about it, she said it must have been the neighbor next door walking home with a stuffed cow on his shoulders. Walking home, at like 3am, with a cow big enough to reach a third story window? Ridiculous. A month or so later her Uncle died, hence the beginning in her belief of it being an angel of death. She felt like if she had opened the window it would have pulled her out so that she'd fall to her death. 

To make matters worse, and what helps keeps this memory constantly fresh in her mind, is that when she was a teenager her friend(Ashley for clarity)  saw the same man walking down the street rolling a baby carriage. A few weeks later Ashley's brother's girlfriend miscarried. This added to the belief that it is an angel of death. 

She warns me and all my siblings constantly to avoid at all costs if we ever see anything like this, because it will bring death somehow. 

Freaky shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why I was expecting bondage, but that was much freakier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had me smiling the entire time, my my, you took fantasy to a wonderfully unexpected place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Quest that was Not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were given one task. Just one, and we couldn't even do that. 

In the Seelie Court we were considered good. We were the best qualified for the job. All we had to do was retrieve one thing. We Fae are odd creatures to some, we bask in decadence and lust and desire, but we were the good guys. Sure, the queen had us do the changling bit for a while, go out at night, snatch up a mortal child and put an identical Faerie in it's place until it had matured enough to come back into our society. We kept the mortal children comfortable in a place we called Dmerea, it was a blissful place where they were ignorant to the fact that they were not where they should be. No one was hurt, the mortal parents were only vaguely suspicious, and we always had envoys watching out for our children in the mortal world. 

The Unseelie Court however was far more cruel, they relished in the pain of mortals and lesser Fae creatures. They were those that raped, tortured, murdered, and bathed in the blood of the innocent. They committed acts more vile than any mortal could imagine. They were the Dark Court. 

Our world exists just beyond the veil of human sight, those mortals who enter may never leave. One taste of Faerie wine or fruit would have them in a madness that gave them illusions of pure happiness, and in our Court we made sure they had as much fun as we did. Oh the revelries, the midsummer festivities, the decadent treats and swaying music that could wisp a mortal away for hours, when it felt to them like only minutes. Time moves beautifully here, immortality is a dish best served with all the finest garnishes. 

I've lost track recalling the wonderousity of my home. It feels wrong to be only a wisp now, floating through the worlds unseen by mortals. I used to allow them to see glimpses of my beauty through my carefully constructed human glamour, oh how the mortals begged at my feet for a taste of me 

No longer though, I failed my quest and shall never again taste the wines and fruits, I shall never be lusted for again. I am shunned for the mistakes we made.

It began with the Seelie Queen requesting our audience to complete a task for her. We gave our word that we would do whatever we could, and our word is binding. We were to go into the mortal realm and retrieve a Sylph by the name of Nimrae. She was by far one of the most beautiful of the Fae, and she was also a Seer. Knights of the Dark Court had taken her in the hopes that her future sight and wisdom of the Seelie land could give them the advantage in the ever present war between the Courts. 

She was to be retrieved before they could torture too much information out of her, or kill her for her resistance. They sent in the three most cunning and strong of us to complete this task. I, Ashe, the bow wielder, one who could have an arrow flying into the throat of an enemy before they could beg for mercy. Rowan, the man of the sword, as quick with his blade as he was with his wit. Finally, Emrhia, a temptress whose magickal abilities were of the strongest wed ever known in the Light Court. Her powers of persuasion could convince a priest to break every commandment. The Queen was sure in her choices.

We set out an hour before dawn, through a vast expanse of tunnels hidden from the mortal world. It was a pure labyrinth to those not bred in Seelie world. On and up we went through the dirt staircase beneath a hollow tree. We rose from the veil between worlds sightless, and glamoured to mask our awe striking beauty. We appeared as three normal humans walking through a deep forest in the pale rays of dawn. By the time the sun had fully risen we were close to the mortal house in which the servants of the Dark Court had Nimrae captive. The house was covered in iron bars, it hurt to be near it. 

Immortality came with a ferocious weakness to iron, the touch of it seared off the skin of the Fae, and it struck me as odd that any of the Unseelie Court would be near a house with such toxicity surrounding it. The nearness of the metal had us slightly weakened, but if we avoided its touch we could get by. After all, we were the best suited for the mission. We were forced to enter the home directly through the front door, all other entries were barricaded in iron. I felt confident in our strength, though we could no longer maintain the glamours under the overpowering stench of the metal pressing around us, it didnt matter now that we were out of the mortal eye.

I felt sympathy for Nimrae, she must be in great pain as one of the Fae who was powerful in mind, but not great in strength. I doubted she could have run on her own. The house seemed surprisingly empty, but it was large and cavernous, she could be hidden anywhere within. We were deep in the house when we finally heard what sounded as though it was the stirring of a great beast. 

Suddenly from all sides creatures of the dark began to swarm, not Fae, but the products of evil. The products of Necromancy. Once mortals, these beings had been brought back by the darkest of magicks, the Unseelie Court had gone to extraordinary measures to keep this house guarded from other Fae. Their numbers were great, and they were unaffected by the iron confines of the building. These poor soulless beings, they had no sense of control over what they were doing. They were maggot ridden puppets, dirt strewn, muscle and tissue exposed, and armed with deadly blades of iron. Some appeared to be freshly dead, never buried at all. Those were the fiercest of them, with bloody dangling limbs, knife and bullet wounds, and gore covered bodies, they were still not deteriorated enough to fall as easily as the dead risen from the earth. We were outnumbered, but not overpowered. Rowan and I were excellent warriors of the Court, we cut down the hordes of undead monstrosities with great speed, though we received many small wounds from the nails and teeth of these beasts our abilities offered us quick healing. The wounds from the iron weapons were slowing us just enough that we couldnt entirely keep them at bay. Our flesh burned, and these wounds would not heal without treatment. The scratches and bites were already gone, fading pink scars on flawless skin, the cuts from the iron were already festering with infection. 

I looked over to see that Emrhia was being overrun by the creatures, her powers of light magick and persuasion did little to nothing against the disgusting monstrosities. Mindless and soulless beings, there was nothing for her to persuade, and the strength of the dark magick used to create them was not something she was equipped to combat. Try as we might, through the hordes of undead we were unable to reach her. Between the strikes of my arrows hitting putrid rotting flesh, I watched as they overtook her. She was viciously ripped apart, I could hear the sound of her skin searing away as they used their iron blades to lay into her. She didnt scream, she fought back with the ferocity that only the Fae hold. With all her might Emrhia tore them apart with her hands and teeth, but the sheer number of combatants was too much for her. They tore her limb from limb, cutting her apart with the toxic blades. I could smell the stench of burning flesh, it was almost sweet as the summer she was born in. 

The sickly sweetness gave away to the vile odor of infection and I caught one last glance of her resigned face as they overtook her, golden blood poured from her lips as she took a final gasp of air. She fell then, and they consumed her body and came at Rowan and I with renewed strength from the immortal flesh. We had decimated nearly two thirds of the undead army at this point, and being surrounded was not fairing well for us. With the speed that only the Fae possess we decided to make a daring dash for the nearest door with no enemies in our path. It was warded with iron chains, but with Rowan was quick to use  the hilt of his sword to break open the padlock holding them all together. Without second thought I pulled the chains from the door, the flesh of my palms smoked as I touched them, and the burning, searing, infection was instantaneous. I was in too much of a hurry to realize my grievous error at the moment, I was a warrior, pain was something I was trained to deal with. It hurt, but there were worse things than the feeling of the skin of my hands melting away. I watched my aquamarine skin turn black momentarily, and then the pus of orange infection began to bubble from beneath the burnt tissue. I hardly registered it. 

Rowan had grabbed me by the arm, cursing me for touching the toxic metal as we ran through the door, slammed it behind us and scurried down a darkened spiral staircase. Ill never forget what we saw, not only had our mission failed, but it seemed we had no chance of ever completing it. We found ourselves in a dark basement, more iron filled than any other part of the house. I could feel my lungs longing for pure air as the metallic scent invaded my senses, I felt my strength leaving me. The walls were entirely made of iron, it was as though we were in the hull of a ship. I could tell Rowan was having a hard time breathing in here as well, but we had a few moments of respite from our attackers, and he had managed to find a light switch. The illumination of the room only brought on sheer disgust and anger. 

Nimrae was dead. Her golden blood was dried to the floor, it would have looked appropriate in a mortal strip club. Her beautiful, waifish, lilac body was laid over large iron spikes, she was pierced through and through. Each metal protrusion was surrounded by blackened skin, and the pus of orange infection, now browning from age. Shed been dead for days, her translucent limbs had begun to disintegrate and turn to dust. She came to us from a far corner of the room, a wisp now. In her moment of near corporeality her soft voice whispered across the expanse, Do not die in here, the wisps may never leave this place. Then she was gone. 

I felt a moment of panic, if the wisps could not leave, then we could not confirm her death to the Seelie Queen. We would have failed, and faced the possibility of being banished to wander without a Court. The Courtless Fae were nearly as bad as the Unseelie. Centuries of purposeless wandering led to mischeviety, and that led to unwanted consequences for mortals. Many become slaves for the Dark Court. Rowan and I shared a look of despair, and then of resolution. We needed to leave this room, we couldnt die here, but perhaps we could win the favor back of the Queen somehow. I would have rather been a low level Seelie servant than be stuck as a wisp in this torture room. 

With determined resignation and the sound of the undead monstrosities thundering down the stairs, we began our ascension back up into the main room of our previous battle. The close quarters made my bow impossible to use, and I was limited to the use of two small enchanted daggers I kept for emergency use. The enchantment helped to cut through the decaying flesh of the creatures rapidly, and the small space made it easier for Rowan and I to cut through the masses in a linear fashion. We made it to the top of the staircase, covered in blistering burns, and deep pus filled gouges from the iron weapons used against us. The undead army was entirely decimated by the time we made it past Emrhias dismembered and disintegrating corpse, and with our waning strength we made a mad dash for the front exit. In the back of my mind I hoped that her wisp would not be trapped here, and that it was only the iron room that could forsake us to eternity locked away. I dropped my daggers, the skin of my hands was peeling apart rapidly, as the infection that I was trying to ignore ate deeper into my tissue and the pain was intense. 

We made it out of the house, but as we ran down the pathway towards the edge of the land the house sat upon, I felt my quiver and bow torn from my back where it rested. I turned with slowed reflexes, the effects of iron poisoning muddling my heightened senses. They had been waiting for us to leave the house. I watched almost in slow motion as a Knight of the Dark Court sent one of my enchanted iron tipped arrows flying into the air. An arrow that could kill any Fae creature if it struck true, and that it did. I turned to see Rowan several feet in front of me, in the midst of raising his sword to fend off our attackers, his other hand raised in shock to touch the arrow that had pierced his heart. I watched him fall, dark green skin covered in lines of the orange bubbling iron infection such as my own skin surely was. The look in his eyes before the life left him told me to run, but before I took two steps I felt a sickening sensation as my own bow was used to spear me. I felt in press sharply into my back before piercing through my skin and severing my spinal cord, the Knight used such force that I watched the bow tear out of my stomach before I fell to my knees, watching golden blood spill down my body onto the grass. I only remember a small pain in my neck before I became a wisp as my friends before me had.

Ill never see them again, the dead Fae are limited in their existence. I saw our bodies, golden blood mixed with orange pus, a bright array of violence on our delicately colored skin. I was sad to see that the Dark Knights had beheaded me with an iron blade, I saw that it seared their hands, but they relished in the pain as they used it to viciously tear Rowan and I apart. At least I died a gloriously colorful death. As a wisp I could only rarely show myself as semi-corporeal for moments at a time. The rest of my existence is spent as what mortals would think of as a ghost, though I can see other wisps on midsummers eve, and become nearly corporeal enough to actually be a part of the revelries. Midsummer is far off though, and I wont know until then if Emrhias wisp made it out of that cursed place, and Ill forever wish we knew how to set Nimrae free from the iron prison. 

We failed our one task, we failed it before we even began. We fought hard, and fiercely, but it was all for nothing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours is the first I plan to read once I've finished typing mine, based on your comment on my comment on the original annoucement thread!
 death and faeries ahoy!

Very very much so, and so excited to read yours 


**Edit: Holy elven apocalypse, I can't even begin to imagine what half of those words meant, but they made it that much more amazing** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently typing up a storm, then I'll be reading everyone else's entries! My excitement is pouring from my puny, girly fingertips! Edit for this comment soon with the link to my epic, gruesome, and failure of an adventure c: 

Edit: Wow life is distracting, this took longer than expected but here it is!

[The Quest that was Not](https://www.reddit.com/r/SLEEPSPELL/comments/54ziap/the_quest_that_was_not/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reposted it correctly now c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love that movie, maybe one day I'll be able to watch it again and wish that my town ended so simply. Suicide with the lack of disgusting crystallizations seems much prettier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved both of those before everything started, kind of close to home now.. If only it was as simple as a story line like those.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely sure of locations, but I explain more in the update </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Series has been updated, thank you little bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is now more, an update has been posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of this I have answered in the update that has just been posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was 8 others, I would be the ninth. I touch upon this in the update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was not initially intending to update so it was not marked as a series, the bot has now been tagged, and an update is available for your viewing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminding you, 4 days later. But update was just posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has indeed been an update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt that can happen now c;  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've now discovered so much more than I think anyone would want me to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of keeping you updated, my new findings have been posted in an update. I'm as safe as I've ever been.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 12:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More terrifying than I knew at the time.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 12:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd, I've seen other people update worded that way before, thank you though! Reposting now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I have posted an update, it may have been removed, I assure you that before I begin my tasks I'll be sure you can all see it. I've tagged the series bot in case I have to reupload the update later tonight. It may be my last, but one day in the future I'd hope to come back and give you all closure. I'll be finding a way or two to stick around** ...

*The update is now accessible* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/NoSleepSeriesBot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry my brackets only contain (Part 2/2) ? What is wrong with the title  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds to me like the intrusive thoughts were actually being caused by the therapist. Giving his patients false advice that worsened their conditions, using suggestive wording to increase the frequency of the thoughts, possibly even using some type of hypnotherapy to give his patients symptoms and intrusive thoughts. The real question is, was he an insane man set on hurting children, or was he a greedy man giving his patients more issues so they'd have to continue coming?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
