<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4692</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 06:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think one figure refers to US (~200m) and the other international (~315)... 515m total.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 12:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still much debate about it, but here's one possibility: "And it's not just sunlight that can trigger sneezing. Lots of sun-sneezers say that breathing in cold air, or tasting a strong flavor like mint gum, also makes them sneeze. This suggests that activating any nerve close to the trigeminal nerve-the one involved in sneezing-can cause the sneeze reflex." http://genetics.thetech.org/ask/ask239 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motion perspectives, eh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just stumbled across this: http://grapevine.is/news/2015/05/28/scots-and-irish-might-have-preceded-vikings-in-iceland/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I hope they rethink their position. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically "I don't give a fuck about chickens, why should I? I don't care if they suffer and live in small cages I need to eat hurr durr durr" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 16:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the most depressing Reddit comments I have ever read. I don't understand how people like you can be so aggressively entitled and seemingly void of empathy... and smug about it. It is very abnormal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 20:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what to say... it is clear that you just don't "get" what everyone is saying here. You should really do some research on the causes of homelessness in your region... maybe then you'll see why everyone is downvoting you. Take care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 11:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that the majority of homeless people also have histories of abuse, sexual and otherwise, addictions to drugs and alcohol (as a means to self-medicate in response to said histories), and disproportionate rates of mental illness that make them unable to work, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this thought, too. I found this:

"In one of the largest studies conducted on the effect of birth order on the Big Five (personality traits), data from a national sample of 9,664 subjects found no association between birth order and scores on the NEO PI-R personality test."

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Only_child  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 18:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi - this was posted a couple days ago: http://www.reddit.com/r/SkincareAddiction/comments/30dbj9/any_ideas_on_how_to_combat_chronic_back_acne/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had pretty severe bacne when I was younger. I was prescribed 75mg/ day of Spironolactone by my dermatologist. I also began using a mild laundry detergent and wearing a new, clean T-shirt to bed every night (no exceptions). I also applied 5% benzoyl peroxide Lotion (from drug store) every night before bed (tip: get white sleeping t-shirts as the peroxide can bleach fabric over time). In the mornings I washed the area with Spectro gel as my last shower step (to wash away any shampoo/ conditioner) and applied some benzoyl peroxide lotion. My back is completely clear now. Honestly, I think the bacne was mostly hormonal and the Spironolactone did most of the work. Also, my derm told me the other week that the newer forms of Accutane are "the closest thing to a cure for acne" that we have... you might want to consider it. You should book an appointment to see a dermatologist regardless. Best of luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar issue last winter... in fact, I itched a spot so much that it became raw. I went to the dermatologist and it turned out to be eczema (I was prescribed hydrocortisone cream and it went away). This website might be helpful; it lists some other causes of itchy legs: http://www.healthhype.com/itchy-legs-causes-and-treatment.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 06:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is defying her gender role, yes, but the whole King-Princess dynamic still places the Princess below the King. It is still reinforcing the idea that being a King is better than being a Princess. Just a thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 14:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/3n7oYhr.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look who I just found on the front page (of the National Post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 14:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
