<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 08:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're so close, to something better left unknowwwn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 07:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought $80 worth of merch... does that count? friggin $20 shipping tho lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 07:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That helps, thanks! I guess I didn't have a map..and such as... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 06:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that being a veteran makes it even worse. I myself am a veteran and I would be livid if this happened to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 05:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I just throw shit in the cart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 05:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao. They were doing a Super Bowl pool at work and someone asked if I paid in and I said no, I'm stingy with my money. He was like "didn't you donate $75 to BernDog?" My response "ITS FOR A GOOD CAUSE!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of the point he's trying to make I think... I don't personally know how well/poorly the Medicare system is run, but I've heard varying things. Someone said she tried to change her address and they said "okay it's done!" Then a year later they claimed she never did it. 

That's the biggest thing I hear. "Do you really want the government in charge of something like this?"
"Look at Canada and how long their wait times are."
"I shouldn't have to pay for something i might not ever use." "He's a socialist." 

Makes me sad :[ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just shared this in Facebook so hopefully people open their eyes lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when I bought my laptop. $1200. I held my breath while typing in my information online lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird, whenever I think about how much each item costs, I spend MORE money. If I just get whatever, it works lol. Doesn't seem to make sense.

I think what makes it worse is that I can actually afford to buy nice things, but I don't because I always have buyers remorse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me really sad. I'm sorry that happened to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime I have to slide my card for a purchase over like... $150, I close my eyes and take a deep breath before I swipe lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only ever seen one group live and that was the backstreet boys lol. They didn't disappoint!

I haven't heard any of their stuff love recorded, so ill have to check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's incredibly frustrating. I'm completely outnumbered as well. Basically 8 against 1 lol. 

One guy said that because Bernie and everyone is saying "political revolution" it's actually communism he wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sobs* DONT TALK ABOUT IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire fucking show tore me apart. I have watched it 3 times and I still cry every time. I think the one that really gets my soul is Denny. As much as everyone hates Katherine Heigl, I think she did a phenomenal job portraying izzy's pain. The episode after he dies, where she's just lying on the bathroom floor... I don't think I stopped crying that while episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn metric is so good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing Kingdoms of Amalur, so I think we'll be okay :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 14:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apologies. *steps away* you may continue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 13:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit gets sticky!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 13:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree 100%

The idea of change and the idea of helping anyone but themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 13:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *pats* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 12:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a heavy sleeper is a gift! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 11:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually surprised to hear this. I've been with them for almost a year now and haven't had any issues. I didn't really have a choice but to go with then since AT T offered 3 Mbps for $50. (lulz). Time warner was like $60 for the 100mbps. 

Theyve been great and haven't given me any reason to not like them. Sorry for your luck op  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 09:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't worry, I talked to my mom today and she said that she was going to vote for trump. Because everyone else was doing it. --LOL

I squashed it real quick and got her to consider :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 09:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you!

When politics get brought up, I mention one little thing about Bernie and I'm a socialist. I try to fight it and it gets turned into him wanting to take over the government.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 09:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap... This is actually a genius idea! Find little hole in the wall bars (where there are bound to be older peeps) and wear your shirt! (EVERYONE DO THIS) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 09:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, these primaries have made me realize I seriously know NOTHING about geography.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 08:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I jokingly said to my husband "OMG he's in bed with N. Korea!"

Then I realized that the media would probably do it lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pretty Reckless - Blame Me [Rock/Alternative/Post-Grunge] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 09:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 08:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 08:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just spent the past 15 minutes laughing my ass off. Coworkers have even more reason to think I'm crazy. And this does indeed sync up with "Without Me" By Eminem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen Puts Bernie Sanders in the Hot Seat! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 07:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 07:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Love you and so does Bernie Sanders! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, the places I go to don't have family restrooms lol :p but toilet paper works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question: Does Bernie want to legalize it in the sense of Colorado? Like, make it federally legal and allow it to be taxed? That would bring in some maaaaaaaaad cash.

When I hear "decriminalization", I don't think of it being in the Colorado sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the link not post? Hold on lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Tax Brackets Work: Examples and Myth Busting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 06:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

A huge trend I have noticed is that people really have NO idea how taxes work. Please share this to educate people.

It would be silly for people to be against Bernie because they think they're going to get taxed out the wazoo :)

Edit: http://blog.taxact.com/how-tax-brackets-work/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://blog.taxact.com/how-tax-brackets-work/

You get taxed in increments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 05:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single ad for Bernie has almost brought my to tears each time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 05:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saturday isn't Sunday? Why is this an issue? He can do it saturday night and then go to flint on sunday?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 04:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bing it out!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 03:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice username :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 03:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you supposed to rinse those out in a public bathroom? The whole process confuses me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 02:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao, just made me think of something. I work for a company that is made up of quite a few Veterans (including myself) and works directly with the military... WE WORKED ON VETERANS DAY! I didn't even notice it until I walked into work that day lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 12:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could lol. Unfortunately, I spend 12 hours a day at work. Even when I have down time, I doubt my coworkers would be respectful of what I'm doing. (They're not exactly #FeelintheBern) 

When I'm not at work, I have a roommate who is asleep when I could be calling :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I have some ideas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 12:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 11:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And men! I'm a contractor (prior Air Force) and my husband is a certain kind of woman I guess XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 11:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fuck that's messed up LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 11:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if she is, that's none of YOUR business :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 09:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, thats half true for me. The veteran side of me says "NO MORE WAR!" The contractor of me just shrugs and moves on lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 09:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get too interested in politics, I did and now I can't sleep because all I can think about it how to save the world lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 09:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is where I think he fell really short and it kind of set the tone for the remainder of the debate for me. He knows his views, but because he almost *NEVER* talks about them. This is actually a huge deal for a lot of people.

While the war on banks and Wallstreet is important, it is not the most pressing issue at this time. ISIS is a massive threat. ISIS isn't just pulling shit in the States, ISIS is pulling shit in the countries of our ALLIES. Something needs to be done, and something needs to be done soon.

I agree with what he wants, 100%. These other countries that we've helped over the years should be the ones to lead this. We should be there for support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 08:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That video was fantastic lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 07:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, high roller over here using Delta! 

I'm just kidding, guys! Thank you for your work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 07:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 07:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ex-military Bernie Supporter... I won't kill you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 06:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, I do too! To myself T_T
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 06:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like his plan for ISIS, which in my opinion is our biggest threat right now. As a veteran, and now a contractor, I think the countries we have defended time and time again need to take the lead on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 06:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think saying "Bernie didn't too well on X" or "That was kind of bad" is perfectly fine! But if you're saying shit like "OMG BERNIE IS GOING TO LOSE OMG OMG OMG OMG". that's not productive, AT ALL!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 05:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has nothing to do with the arguments in this case. It has to do with the fact that no one wants to see an imperfection!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 05:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! I think he's going to get a lot of feedback on that and grow from it. I'm just concerned about the results of NH now :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should all learn from this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 05:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. 

I was basically attacked on a Facebook group that supports BERNIE~ I joined it yesterday and have been very active about posting information on voting, livestreams for dem hall, dem debate...etc. 

During the debate, I pointed out that he was a little weak on his delivery for FP. Holy shit did I get attacked. I was accused of being a troll! I don't understand how pointing out a weakness is trolling. If it were on an open group, maybe that could be seen as bad, but this was a group of supporters.

I countered them with something that  basically shut them up. I actually think this should be a lesson for ALL of us.

I told them that we can't sit here and bash Hillary supporters because they don't see what wrong with her, if we arent even willing to acknowledge an issue with our OWN candidate. I'm not saying be a bunch of negative nancies, but we can't sit here in delusion thinking the sun shines out of his ass.

We need to be able to identify an issue so that we can fight it ourselves! I do not support Bernie any less than I did before. So please guys, don't call people trolls for simply(and respectfully)  pointing out an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 04:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, fake it til ya make it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 04:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's weak on it. Iowa gave us some visibility and now we look kinda shitty lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kanye man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do, for the most part. Hillary just isn't trust worthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay that makes sense lol thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting frustrated with this debate. They're BOTH talking circles -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently they pipe in applause  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay. So I'm assuming you vote for/against certain aspects of bills vs it's entirety?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have so much anxiety lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary bashed him about voting against that. I'm curious why he would vote against the background checks lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean from the little bit I just read, it requires background checks to purchase... Why is that a bad thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have hit her lol. Then again I'm a hunter :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary seems to be getting more applause -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lemme look up the Brady act on break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the effort was there lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's silly. If they failed to do a background check, then yes, hold them accountable. But if they did everything right and some weirdo shoots up a school,  no. Absolutely not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately that seems to be all anyone cares about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to progressively stick my foot through the screen :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extra shiny bald spot lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not often I get excited about turning on the news lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the bras stay on, we're goos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My taxes pay for that. You should contribute more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie needs to do an actual definition of democratic socialism for people. Maybe use examples of how America is already basically socialist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: go weaver! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needs to just come out and say how socialist America already is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 01:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this has been floating around a lot. Do we have an actual assessment of what might happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 01:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, has anyone in the media actually mentioned how "socialist" our country already is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 01:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw somebody mention that because we are significantly bigger, it's less likely that will happen :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 00:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NH Democratic Debate at 9pm EST!

Live stream at www.msnbc.com or

www.nbcnews.com 

No cable credentials required :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 00:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean they can't buy swag either? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 11:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious why someone has a duck inner-tube in their bath tub o.o

My life is boring  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 10:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 10:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's why the loud noise shocked him so much. PTSD from the hood :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 07:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now im watching Sandy Hook conspiracy videos. Thanks, Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 06:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't obama do that? lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pilot I used to work with used to fly C-130s and hilldog was coming. secret service briefed them not to look at her ankles. She hates that. EVERYONE LOOK AT HER ANKLES  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately they're feeling the bern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her hour is really dragging lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means they're for Bernie :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they actually choose a winner? Or is it an assumption?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dem debate drinking games! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I JUST THUNK THAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
