<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I play Abaddon as a support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find any specific guides for this, at least not recently updated. I'm going to assume you save maxing Curse of Avernus until last, but which one do you max first? and what items do you build? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do I do with Treant after the enemy starts five manning and buying dust/sentries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I've made like three posts about Treant in the past 24 hours. OK, so I'm used to healing towers over and over until, finally, the enemy wises up and decides to push as five instead of tickling it with one or two heroes fruitlessly. What am I supposed to do after this, assuming my team isn't really pushing back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Treant supposed to do against a 5 man push? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite the buffs to Nature's Guise and Overgrowth, I feel like Treant is still bad against any team who decides to push as five or who carries dust. Should I just not pick him against most teams or am I doing something wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Valve, telling us in-game which skills are dispellable is really nice. Now, can we get the same pass through for which skills are disjointable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 02:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dispellable and disjointable skills are the two things a newbie really needs to rely on a wiki on the most. I think both of them should be detailed in the tooltips. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I roam around as Treant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love Treant. And I mean, now I like him even more, but I feel like I'm struggling with him. I'm so tempted to stay in the trees for as long as possible, walking through the jungle and being undetected, that when I TP to try to gank a different lane, I'm always left wondering "How do I move it from point A to point B without being seen?" 

This is easy enough to do later in the game with a blink dagger, but when you don't have one, it's honestly difficult. It's either that or I'm so bad I can't see the obvious solution. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got put into low priority with only 4 reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck? Did they change how this works?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What graphics settings do the pros use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like to ask about key bindings for pros, but I'm more interested in graphics. For example, do they turn off shadows? They look pretty but surely can't do anything good for your frame rate. What other settings do they turn off, if any of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valve, please give Treant back his +20% 2s Bash chance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe nerf it down to +10% 2s bash chance or +20% 1s bash chance, just please keep it in the game. 

If Weaver can get +200 Shukuchi Movement Speed, if Venge can get Magic Missile Pierces Spell Immunity, if Spirit Breaker can get +17% Greater Bash Chance (lol), and if Lich can get Attacks Apply 30% MS and AS slow - among other cool level 25 talents that I'm neglecting to mention - then why can't Treant have a bash chance? 

If you feel this is broken in regard to Skull Basher, simply don't let him proc Skull Basher's bash if he takes the level 25 talent that gives a bash chance instead of the additional living armor stacks.

Please, Valve. For us. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Venge suddenly so popular? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to I'd never see her (unless I was spamming her) and now she's in every other game the past few days. Did a streamer do something with her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Invoker's EMP take away so much mana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 625 mana burned in the early game, gg you are dead. How is this a balanced skill? He's already got 9 other amazing skills, why is EMP so broken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valve, here is your daily reminder to fix your Hero Builds cloud server. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been broken for at least two weeks. I know there are other pressing issues to fix, but please also fix your guides as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To a certain point, does it really matter WHO builds a counter item as long as it's there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an example, I was support Treant and rushed an Orchid against a magic heavy team, because at my MMR I assume most carries are going to stick to their standard build instead of picking counter items. Especially since supports don't need items to function, why not buy something that will help the team?

And btw I'm not stealing farm to do this, typically I get like 10k gold at the end of every match and still end up being lowest net worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To a certain point, does it really matter WHO builds a counter item as long as it's there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an example, I was support Treant and rushed an Orchid against a magic heavy team, because at my MMR I assume most carries are going to stick to their standard build instead of picking counter items. Especially since supports don't need items to function, why not buy something that will help the team? 

And btw I'm not stealing farm to do this, typically I get like 10k gold at the end of every match and still end up being lowest net worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skywrath's Aghs will work with his items as well as his spells - is this intended? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had my first game against a Skywrath with Aghs earlier, and he used Atos on my teammate - and then it triggered on me, too. I know the website says "any time you use an ability", which I guess is vague enough to mean items as well as spells. Is this a bug, does anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which heroes should and should not buy a wind lace at pre-game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to buy it on EVERY support, but since eeeverything in this game is so situational... I thought I'd ask /r/learndota 2 about it. For example, I'm not sure Venge NEEDS one, though it's quite nice. I've tried a couple games now without one and it seemed manageable.

But for example, Ogre, especially with the recent movespeed nerf, shouldn't he be getting a wind lace every game?

Is that the general rule, "low base movespeed  buy a wind lace", or is it more nuanced than that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will hero builds ever be fixed? 7.01 claims there is a fix, yet the issue persists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't want to fix hero builds for whatever reason, then fine. Tell us as much. Claiming in the patch notes that you've fixed hero builds when you've clearly done no such thing is a little dishonest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valve, please give us the option to view only a guide or only the main shop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I'm more of a casual player and love that the guide is now the focused window. But I understand that many people dislike this. I feel there needs to be a way to switch between the two, without the modal panel, and actually *remembering the settings between game sessions*. That way, it's still a small and clean UI that you want, but also a UI that can please everyone.

And on the subject of guides, they're still broken despite the claim in the 7.01 patch notes that they're fixed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are the Popular Items in the shop determined for every hero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 05:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this stuff Valve choose or is it statistically what players are currently building? Some of these confuse me a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I take the gold/min talent basically every time if I'm playing a support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the most part it's the best option for heroes who aren't going to be farming, right? Especially on Ogre and Undying who get it at level 10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think anything in this game triggers me more than a Treant who refuses to heal towers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motherfucker, this is coolest, most broken ability in the game, and you can't be bothered to use it to give us an advantage against that team who is refusing to push as five to counter you? And all you're gonna do is heal yourself and MAYBE a teammate who has 10 hp? Makes me so mad tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As support Kunkka, is it a good idea to use your ult a bit like Dazzle's Weave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the damage reduction and movement speed buff on Ghost Ship (and especially now with shrines, you can take a fight and heal up after rum wears off, if you take the fight near one, instead of running back to base), can you cast this on your team pre-emptively before an engagement, or is the 10 second duration too short to really do much? I guess it would also depend how many other stuns there are on your team and if you need to initiate or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That time when you play Single Draft and still get Monkey King on the enemy team... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you get Venomancer as one of your three picks, so you rape him. Awwww yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite part about the new UI is you can now see your HP/MP regen even when you're full health. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the past, I never knew for sure how much regen I had with a Euls/Perseverance/etc when combined with my hero's natural regen, unless I cast a spell and looked at it. But now you can always see it, so that's a nice touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How viable is a roaming Monkey King? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really see anyone do this, but when you think about it, couldn't he function a bit like Riki/Treant in that he's a mobile ward? What would be his item/skill build as a roaming support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I counter Monkey King if I don't want to play a hero with flying vision? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no other hero in the game that requires this amount of counter play in the laning stage. Damage over time so he can't jump in trees barely seems to work because he's still going to get the four hits on you to proc his bullshit. I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Drow be played as a support now with a Rod of Atos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a 1k retard, always wanting to see which heroes can potentially be played as support. Support CK is fun as fuck, he's good at roaming around for unexpected ganks. Naga Siren, tried her... she doesn't really seem to work as a solo support, so I ditched her.

But what about Drow? She's got a silence, a slow, an aura that increases ranged damage of your teammates - and if she builds for a Rod of Atos, she's got a root. She's squishy, but most supports are squishy anyhow. Would this work out at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OK, can someone explain to me what the fuck Drow's ult does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played this game for a year and tbh I'm still confused about the purpose of her ult. To my understanding, it's disabled around enemy heroes. So she's got an ult specifically designed around split pushing and avoiding the enemy? Then how does she do so much damage to heroes, is it the Precision Aura alone? '

edit: And while I'm on the subject of Drow, when is the best time to use the active ability of Precision Aura?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I convince a friend to stop getting so stressed about feeders/losses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  used to LOVE playing Dota with her. Lately, she's got so salty. Basically every time we lose, she sounds on the verge of tears. "(insert hero name) is so broken. I give up Dota, man. This game is bullshit. Cancer heroes." You know, just dumb shit like that. Occasionally there will even be tilting in the pick phase, "fuck.. I'm so squishy and they have both a Clinkz and an Ursa. We lose."

And then after the venting I'll always say, you've played hundreds of matches, you'll win some and you'll lose some. Yet every time, she'll do the same thing. Is there any way to get through to someone like this or should I just stop queueing with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I convince a friend to stop getting so stressed about feeders/losses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to LOVE playing Dota with her. Lately, she's got so salty. Basically every time we lose, she sounds on the verge of tears. "(insert hero name) is so broken. I give up Dota, man. This game is bullshit. Cancer heroes." You know, just dumb shit like that. Occasionally there will even be tilting in the pick phase, "fuck.. I'm so squishy and they have both a Clinkz and an Ursa. We lose."

And then after the venting I'll always say, you've played hundreds of matches, you'll win some and you'll lose some. Yet every time, she'll do the same thing. Is there any way to get through to someone like this or should I just stop queueing with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does vision near the shrines work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been playing a lot of Treant. I've been TPing to my shrine so I can quickly cross the river, hide in their trees, and steal one of their runes. Decided to actually watch a replay and it looks like the shrine can see me AND the vision lingers for a radius far wider than the shrine itself. Is this a replay bug or an intended mechanic?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tanky teamfight items on Treant, good or bad idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 11:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in this patch with the 2+ mana regen at level 10 and the fact that Nature's Guise no longer costs mana, that it's actually not necessary to build arcane boots on him. I've been staying at brown boots and building things like Vlads or Crimson or Pipe - I mean, not all of them, just whichever one seems most crucial to that particular game.

Is this a decent idea on Treant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suddenly realized Treant's high ground defense is now even better than before </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 19:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because sanctuaries/shrines are now a thing, you can keep healing them for sustain if the enemy is trying to siege you. As if it weren't already difficult enough to take on a Treant. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most useful items not listed in the new shop's "common items"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this little tab, and it makes buying starting items really easy.Despite listing most of the crucial ones, though, there are a couple missing that I think I'll customize to add to the Starting Items tab. There's OoV, Blight Stone, Quelling Blade, brown boots, and... I guess that's it? Maybe also magic stick and iron branches to fill it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's something ironic about a Slark/Monkey/insert other "cancer" hero here, whining about the enemy team being too good and stomping them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like.. you were planning on doing exactly the same thing. You are a dirty (hero name) picker. And you're pissed off that someone else did it to you instead? Fucking hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel about the talents in 7.00 potentially changing the way we itemize heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 09:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, and for all I know this is a bad idea, I don't bother with arcane boots on Treant anymore because of his level 10 talent that gives 2+ mana regen. Skipping the energy booster, I can get a blink dagger that much faster. 

Do you feel this is just an experimental phase or will item builds become more varied because of talents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I've been playing more heroes ever since the new pick screen was introduced </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of this is surely owed to wanting to experiment with the new talents, but also I feel like the new screen is much more clean and friendly. You'd never get to read hero info in the old one without going back to card mode, which I never liked at all. Plus I love that it's finally alphabetical instead of the haphazard release order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I itemize/skill a support Zeus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Torte de Lini is possibly going to publish a support Zeus guide for 7.00, but since guides are currently broken, I thought I'd ask this sub.

Basically I'm desperate to find some good counters to Monkey King and I main support. I can't think of a lot of support counters and Zeus seems like the best one because of Lightning Bolt giving true sight over him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the reason to level up Underlord's Dark Rift past the first one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, there is a shorter cooldown... but I'm not sure how that's incredibly useful compared to his other three skills and/or talents. Care to explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> But seriously, why the fuck does Monkey King have 50% lifesteal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Combined with the 200%, this shit is broken as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building Enchantress as a tanky aura support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a decent idea? She's susceptible to magic nukes so she could buid Hood or Pipe, and if the enemy doesn't have many nukes, she could go with Crimson Guard.

Like, how tanky does Untouchable make her really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the value of a bounty rune? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean how much, I know it's 100 gold. 

But what is its importance to the early game, really? Statistically speaking, are you more likely to get a HUGE advantage if you grab that rune or is it just a nice little headstart? 

Is it really worth fighting for it, either in the past or present versions of the game? Especially because experience hasn't been on the first rune for quite some time now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love that you can see stat gain and attack range in-game now without consulting a wiki! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always felt this is basic info that everyone should have ready access to. The wiki is still useful for learning the intricacies of any given hero, so it's not like it's useless, but I never enjoyed trying to figure out who had what attack range.

My only suggestion now is that this info should also be displayed in the heroes tab when you click "about" - this is much more important than the silly lore.

^^also ^^please ^^let ^^us ^^see ^^the ^^three ^^primary ^^attributes ^^without ^^hovering ^^over ^^anything ^^^^sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't towers reveal Monkey King? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 00:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's insane enough already that you need flying vision specifically for one hero, but he can hop around in your tower range and still not be seen. The fuck??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valve, user-created guides are currently still broken. Here's a reminder to fix them asap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, we love you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Monkey King the only hero in the game that REQUIRES a certain hero pool to counter him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really can't think of anyone else in the game where the counter is this specific: you NEED flying vision or you can't see him. At least with invis heroes, any hero can buy sentries or dust. This guy... uh.. yeah. What the fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Other than invis heroes, who are the best heroes to steal bounty runes in this patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like most of the time, the teams are split up to take both runes on their side of the river. But with invis heroes, it's usually possible to take at least one. Are there any other easy tricks to take the rune? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the likelihood we will get a replacement for the custom grid feature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the option to grey out heroes we never play would be a decent substitute for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fact that we can now see our teammates' items at a glance on the scoreboard is my favorite change of this patch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 08:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is something I've wanted for quite some time, especially since the spectator mode had something like this, and I'd always thought it would be incredibly handy to have for playing as well. No more clicking each hero every time you want to see what they're building and no more accidental two Vlads or some other aura item. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 80% of the Monkey Kings on my team don't do anything other than jump from tree to tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 07:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't farm.. they don't fight.. they just bounce around in the trees. This hero is fucking stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the new talent system, what if Enchantress could control ancients? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would this be too broken? Or simply make her a little too similar to Chen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treant made me fall in love with the game last year when I started on 6.86, and now Treant has helped me adapt to all the scary changes of 7.00 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a grade A "who cares" shitpost, but I gotta say Treant was my first love in this game. The fact that you can globally heal your teammates always seemed wickedly cool to me and my attachment to him gave me more map awareness than if I'd tried playing most other heroes.

And now that the map has changed and his invis has turned into a passive, he's been the easiest way for me to learn the jungle camps and juke paths in betwen the trees. Twice now, Treant has taught me how to play this game.

Bless the big tree man. :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honestly, does anyone else other than Torte de Lini make up-to-date guides for all heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like a different perspective. Not that I dislike his guides, I do enjoy them and he's the reason I got into the game. But surely someone else attempts such an endeavor, right? When you look at the most recently updated guides that are not his, they're all consistently two or three years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the distinction between safe lane and offlane becoming smaller? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Looking at this blog post from Tsunami](http://howdoiplay.com/blog/2016/12/14/easy-is-the-new-hard.html), I can see his point that maybe the "hard lane" isn't so hard anymore because of various changes over the years, notably the introduction of iron talon and shrines.

Have the lanes reversed themselves? Or perhaps does it not even matter much in this patch who goes to the side lanes due to the bounty runes and larger jungles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am so fucking sick of being in the trench </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 11:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Them: "Level 12 Underlord LOL"

Me: "I'm a support... I'm not supposed to be higher level than you."

Them: "LOL noob Underlord isn't a support"

???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the fuck does CM get a blink dagger at 11 min? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gold gain is a little out of hand ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are the Tinker wards on this new map? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 07:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to counter Monkey King in the laning phase with vision.. and uh.. where are the ward spots, exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I crazy for trying to play Techies as a solo support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have told me Techies isn't really a good ward bitch, but the way I typically ward, and the way I want to play Techies with this new patch, I don't think it's an issue. He's great at just being in the front lines, off to the side, using Blast Off to kill himself and silence everyone. Since you're no longer encouraged to spam mines since it's not even possible anymore, I typically use the mines for wave clear when my carries are at the mid standoff.

Does this work only because I'm in the trench or can Techies be a good utility support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UI suggestion: move the commonly suggested items to the top of the shop panel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that big of a change, but I do feel like the most important items should grab your attention immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I crazy for trying to play Techies as a solo support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have told me Techies isn't really a good ward bitch, but the way I typically ward, and the way I want to play Techies with this new patch, I don't think it's an issue. He's great at just being in the front lines, off to the side, using Blast Off to kill himself and silence everyone. Since you're no longer encouraged to spam mines since it's not even possible anymore, I typically use the mines for wave clear when my carries are at the mid standoff. 

Does this work only because I'm in the trench or can Techies be a good utility support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do we think Treant will be nerfed before being reintroduced to Captains Mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 09:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the current iteration of Treant and I'm afraid they'll nerf him too hard. Are there any super OP areas of the new permanent invis? Or is that not the reason a hero is taken out of CM, is it just because it's a drastic change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you counter Monkey King if you haven't already picked Timber, Batrider or Jakiro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 08:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like how the fuck do you counter someone who can jump in between trees on a ludicrous 1.4 second cooldown? I can't think of any other hero in the game where the counters are so specialized. Get someone who can cut down trees or be fucked. Is there ANY way to play around him without these specific heroes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain the broken yellow circle thingy on the top part of the screen? Inside the hero portraits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's supposed to be related to hero abilities.. but what does it do, how do I use it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The kill sounds are INCREDIBLY weak. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like most of 7.00, this is a fun patch. But the little "thunk" when you kill someone sounds pretty tacky. Either create a better sound or get rid of it, is my suggestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How viable is a pushing/teamfight Techies in 7.00? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd always liked the idea of Techies as this role, but wasn't entirely sure if it were possible. You were kind of encouraged to plant mines all in one place. Now that you can't really do this nearly as much, what is stopping him from nuking down entire creep waves, or being on the back lines to silence everyone with Blast Off? I feel like the only reason he'd still plant mines all across the map is with Remote Mines and that doesn't happen at level 6.

Or maybe I'm entirely wrong. He's still fairly squishy, though can't he itemize around that to an extent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are supports getting too powerful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play support 95% of the time so I should be happy about these changes, and I am for the most part, but I can't help but feel supports are getting buffed and carries are arguably being nerfed.

Supports have four different bounty runes to take, tomes now scale with each use, some talents give respawn reduction, and as a whole they give much less gold than a carry upon death because of the rework to that formula including net worth.

Then carries seem to be nerfed because jungle camps spawn only every two minutes and in general kills give less, not just for supports. 

Do carries need a buff to offset all the perks supports have been given? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel talents will affect early game item builds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if talents are extreme enough yet that this can happen for a lot of heroes, but as an example let's look at Crystal Maiden and Enigma - at level 10, both of them have the option to get magic resistance, 15% and 12% respectively. Assuming you were going to buy a cloak in that particular game anyhow, and you skill up at level 10 for the resistance - do you skip the cloak now, or do you still buy the cloak for even more tankiness against magic?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some ways the backpack have made the game more convenient for you so far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, when I was ahead and rich as a support, and slot starved, I'd often build Boots of Travel so I could still have both TPs and wards. With this new backpack, I won't be wasting all that gold because I can keep TPs on hand at all times. Granted, I don't think I should have ever been building BoTs as a support anyhow in most cases - but hey, that's why I'm only 1.5k mmr.

Keeping something like an Aether Lens recipe on hand is also incredibly handy so I don't need to fly out the courier, that way carries can use it. But with the backpack, maybe the courier won't be used as much in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel talents will affect early game item builds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if talents are extreme enough yet that this can happen for a lot of heroes, but as an example let's look at Crystal Maiden and Enigma - at level 10, both of them have the option to get magic resistance, 15% and 12% respectively. Assuming you were going to buy a cloak in that particular game anyhow, and you skill up at level 10 for the resistance - do you skip the cloak now, or do you still buy the cloak for even more tankiness against magic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm puzzled by the people who complain that talents make the heroes potentially feel too similar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't we typically pride ourselves on the fact that our meta is much more flexible than other games in the genre? Why would you be annoyed that we can diversify our item/skill builds even more because of talents?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Purge is literally repeating his comments about Crystal Maiden from hours ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whyyyyyyyyyy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Purge is going to eat a snack and make out with his girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU HEARD IT HERE FIRST !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am SO glad the pick screen in 7.00 now lists heroes alphabetically. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, look at this shit. Even Purge, someone who's been playing much longer than me, can't remember where Axe is in that random mess of Earthshaker, Sven, Tiny, Kunkka, etc - I know that's their release order, but damn is it confusing not only for newbies but also veterans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain to me what is the "new unit query panel" in 7.00 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played the test client for a couple hours yesterday and I'm still lost about this. "With the side-aligned unit query, you can gather info on other heroes, units, and buildings without sacrificing any actions on your own hero." 

What is this referencing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7.00 won't let you click the minimap to travel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't be the only one who does this, clicks the minimap somewhere and then checks items in the meantime or whatever. In 7.00 (at least the test client), if you were to click towards the top part of the map when you're playing Radiant, expecting to go top, you'll just go somewhere near your base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does 7.00 have the option to mute the entire enemy team with one click? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muting them all one by one is pretty annoying. If there isn't already a way to do this in 7.00, I hope they'd really consider adding it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Fogged have inside info about the 7.00 patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a Q A where the panel was asked what they'd like to see in the next patch. Fogged said he wanted illusions to give gold. Was that just a really damn good guess or did he know??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite and least favorite things about the patch notes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone please explain to me why Enigma got a remodel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the more annoying chat spam: "Well played" in Dota or "Nice shot" in Rocket League? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm curious what is the larger demographic for DBZA: do you still like the original DBZ or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of a better way to word that question. Basically, I'm curious how many people watch DBZA solely for TFS's great writing instead of as another way to rewatch DBZ. These days I try to rewatch DBZ and I cringe at how bad it is. Of the anime I watched as a kid, it's easily aged the worst. I'd rather watch Sailor Moon or Yu Yu Hakusho if I want a nostalgia fix.

Are a lot of people watching just because they dislike DBZ and want to see how they make fun of it? I know TFS genuinely enjoys DBZ (or I'd assume they would with how long it takes to edit these), but surely I can't be the only one who doesn't like the original anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never seen pro CSGO. What are some videos that will make me say "Damn, that's amazing"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 03:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching a bit of pro Dota the past year. The best part is how the tense games are made even *more* tense by the casters. Sure, there are occasional overreactions that can annoy me - but a good hype caster can make something special.

Can anyone link me to some good games of CSGO that will turn me on to the pro scene? Maybe a list of slang the casters might use just in case I get confused? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most hype moment I've ever seen in pro gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most important question: who's casting the grand finals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cap and Merlini plz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underrated platformers on PSX, PS2, N64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Crash Bandicoot 2 and 3, if that tells you anything. Not really a huge fan of open world stuff like Super Mario 64 unless there are platforming challenges smartly built into the level design (think Tick Tock Clock or Rainbow Ride, those were the best levels in SM64 in terms of staying true to Mario)

I like Klonoa quite a bit too, although it can be kinda easy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get a quick opinion on Afterbirth for someone who's still not played it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played a bit of Rebirth back when it first released and didn't like it much. The appeal of the original flash game, for me, was the hilarious ways you could become OP. This was still possible in Rebirth, occasionally, but I feel like most of the new items in Rebirth were intentionally bad, like the game was daring you to pick them up to make the game harder. 

Does Afterbirth change this item drop balance so the good and bad items are equally likely to appear? And are the items from Afterbirth fun in themselves or also as tedious as those from Rebirth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For someone who didn't play Dota 1, someone paint me a picture about the farming system back then </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the analysts being asked the question "Have supports in the early game ever been more important", that made me wonder.. was there ever a time, even among the vets (and not just the current 1k mmr), where supporting wasn't really a thing? Did they just fuck around and have fun or was Dota always taken seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assuming I'm the only support, how do I harass as a Crystal Maiden? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her right click doesn't do much, she's too squishy to take much of a beating from the two offlaners, and you don't typically want Crystal Nova until level 3 or 4. While I feel like I'm pretty decent with her past the laning phase, during the first 10 minutes I feel like it's all a gamble. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time a caster says "objective based gaming", I want to stab them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if that's a secret strategy and we should be so impressed they're playing the game by hitting.. the.. towers? What the actual fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I hold on to my gold until I have enough for an entire item? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pros do this a bit. And I've come to the conclusion some things they do just cannot translate to pub games where you have no trust or knowledge of your teammates (level 8 support at 26 minutes into the game, for example.. uh no.)

Holding on to gold until you're sure which item you need to buy seems like one of the few things that might be worth copying from the pro players. Would you agree or disagree? Or should you have a game plan right from the beginning, "the enemy has this hero, so I should build this item"? Should you hold on to gold even if you do have a plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why haven't they played Majesty live in three years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Setlist.fm says the last time this was played was November 2013. Excluding Lissie's Heart Murmur (a song where I can understand why they wouldn't play at a concert except as maybe a closer), every other song on The Fool has been played in at least 2015, if not 2016.

Are they embarrassed of this song, maybe? I'm not sure why they would be, always loved this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston Major makes me realize pro supporting is so different from pub supporting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like... this Ogre is level 8 at minute 26. I'd never be such a low level, because usually I'm pushing out a lane since my carries are standing at mid waiting for some imaginary fight to break out. I'm gonna have no idea how to play this game if I ever get into a bracket where my carries push and farm like pros do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find a list of all music used throughout the series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I can tell where something is from, and other times it's a little more difficult. For example, [this scene in episode 42](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dppBF4mSxn4#t=5m29s) where Gohan is explaining how Trunks' time machine could have been damaged, the music sounds a little like Professor Layton. I go to the TFS wiki expecting a list of music used in an episode's entry, but that actually isn't the case.

Is there a master list of music used and references made? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What genre of electronic music has interesting drum patterns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite electronic music at the moment is Anjunadeep and, while I love most of what they release, sometimes the beats are a little boring. At the same time, I don't want anything glitchy or dancey. What I'd like to hear is [something like this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o0PXEfFrP0k) in electronic music. Are these kinds of drums not common outside of rock music? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think is the best (tightest) drummer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I've never liked a drummer who throws in flashy fills in an attempt to overpower the other instruments. I've never really liked guitar solos much either, for that matter, but that's not the point. More than any other instrument, I feel a drummer needs to be restrained yet not boring.

I'd say Stella Mozgawa from Warpaint is one of the better examples of this. Her beats are all a joy to hear and she's never making an attempt to bust out into an annoying solo. She's holding the song together, just as a drummer should do. [Here's one of my favorite examples.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ISwQavXuMhA)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do I buy boots/wind lace immediately and when can I delay buying them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching the EG vs Wings game right now, and I'm seeing something new to me. iceice on Dazzle got raindrops first and didn't get wind lace, got brown boots instead around 10 minutes.  

I'd heard that wind lace is the thing to get first on supports ever since its introduction. When do you skip it and go straight to boots? When can you skip boots entirely for a while? Dazzle is a good example of where I think this might be acceptable because 305 is a respectably high starting movement speed. 

And alternatively, when do you buy boots/wind lace immediately? I see people do this sometimes, whether in my games or pro games, and it seems risky to me when you could have regen instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do the Namekian spaceships look a lot like Freeza's armor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm rewatching DBZA, and I'd never actually noticed this. [They're both white and purple.](https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-tETEZSfQ48M/Tx9FWHjtDPI/AAAAAAAAJ40/Nn-rs0mVhRU/s1600/dbz38-26.jpg) Is there any significance to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Omniknight's win rate still beastly at 5k+ mmr? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the diffusal blade and Eul's not enough? Is it that choosing items simply to counter a support fucks up gold for other items they'd rather have? Or is there something else?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Omniknight's win rate still beastly at 5k+ mmr? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the diffusal blade and Eul's not enough? Is it that choosing items simply to counter a support fucks up gold for other items they'd rather have? Or is there something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IIL] the way each season of Mad Men is set in a different year, [WEWIL?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how you really get a sense of progression of time in this series. Whether historical or fictional, what else is like this? Sorry if it's a super vague request. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain the differences between the different versions of Wallander? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And which of them are worth my time? There are two Swedish ones and an English one. Netflix has two of them, the one starring Kenneth Branagh and the one starring Krister Henriksson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... for someone who hasn't played in like half a year, how is TF2 doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the competitive mode? How's the quick play? I remember reading all of it was a shitshow when things changed. Has it settled down into something better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OT] When will anything be done about the content on this sub? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I avoid getting killed by enemy heroes when I'm ahead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound.. really dumb.. but more often than not, I'll have 0 deaths or 1 death, and we'll be stomping the enemy team. I'll just keep pushing a lane out, TPing to join my team when a fight breaks out - and then suddenly I'll get killed and I'll be like "Shit, I forgot they even had a Nyx/Spirit Breaker/insert hero here."

How do I teach myself to remain aware of my surroundings even when I'm doing well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I avoid getting killed by enemy heroes when I'm ahead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound.. really dumb.. but more often than not, I'll have 0 deaths or 1 death, and we'll be stomping the enemy team. I'll just keep pushing a lane out, TPing to join my team when a fight breaks out - and then suddenly I'll get killed and I'll be like "Shit, I forgot they even had a Nyx/Spirit Breaker/insert hero here."

How do I teach myself to remain aware of my surroundings even when I'm doing well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are there SO many Peruvians in games lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Purge says "a small camp into a pull through is currently out of favor". What does this mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DiZzrBWhG4o](In this Terrorblade coaching video), he makes a point that a side pull is better because it's easier and because it benefits your carry more. I'm actually curious how a pull is supposed to benefit your carry. I thought it was for your support and for your carry to get farm closer to tower. And isn't the enemy offlaner more likely to get exp this way?

edit: whatever, reddit's formatting is bullshit, but there's the link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When and why do I use Treant Protector's invis on my teammates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I guess another question is *how* would I do such a thing, since a lot of people in my bracket don't seem to understand they need to stay near trees to stay invisible. Should I get on mic and tell them to stay there until the enemy gets closer to us or would that be too demanding? Is it best used as an escape or an initiation? If I use it too often, will the enemy start buying detection against me? I know when there's a Treant on the other team that I rarely think to buy sentries since he's "just a support", so maybe other people think the same way and won't counter me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How reliable is it to use a smoke/dust combo against invis heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching some of Slacks' older videos and I was shocked to learn a few things. Namely, you can still use abilities while smoked, which is pretty cool. But more importantly, you can use a smoke and then when it's broken, just use dust and you're supposedly almost guaranteed to hit an invis hero, because their ranges are essentially the exact same.

I have to wonder, though, does this really work in practice? Look at heroes like Clinkz and BH whose movement speed increases while invis. Yes, dust slows them down, but is it by enough? Is this combo really effective against anyone other than a Mirana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How reliable is it to use a smoke/dust combo against invis heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching some of Slacks' older videos and I was shocked to learn a few things. Namely, you can still use abilities while smoked, which is pretty cool. But more importantly, you can use a smoke and then when it's broken, just use dust and you're supposedly almost guaranteed to hit an invis hero, because their ranges are essentially the exact same.

I have to wonder, though, does this really work in practice? Look at heroes like Clinkz and BH whose movement speed increases while invis. Yes, dust slows them down, but is it by enough? Is this combo really effective against anyone other than a Mirana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I hurting myself by sticking to 5 or 6 heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only 1.4k and I feel like I might be shooting myself in the foot. I know I'm not SUPER great at Dota, hence the mmr, so I tend to spam the same small pool of heroes - Venge, Ogre, CM, Dazzle - heroes where they're simple to play, that can allow me to focus on positioning and map awareness instead of mechanical skill, and where I feel I have a firm grasp on which situational items to build on them.

It's not that I'm getting bored of them, because they're also my favorite heroes, but I feel like maybe I should branch out to other supports. But I don't really trust myself with most other supports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do you stay at brown boots to get an item faster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing this quite a bit lately, particularly a CM who went brown boots and then immediately got a glimmer cape. Pretty much lost the game because I didn't expect her to get it that early. Is this a situational thing or can I get away with doing the same thing more often than not? 

The biggest problem I can think of here is most supports need arcane boots and I'm not good enough with managing mana to afford that, probably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got low priority because two games in a row the Steam client froze up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 22:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Valve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are defensive supports a waste of time in a solo queue at low MMR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes like Dazzle and Omni seem great on paper, but I don't know what the fuck my teammates are gonna do. I can heal or grave them, and for all I know, they're just gonna go right back into the fight to die. I have much more success with aggressive supports. Am I hindering myself here or are defensive supports just bad at a certain skill level?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are defensive supports a waste of time in a solo queue at low MMR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes like Dazzle and Omni seem great on paper, but I don't know what the fuck my teammates are gonna do. I can heal or grave them, and for all I know, they're just gonna go right back into the fight to die. I have much more success with aggressive supports. Am I hindering myself here or are defensive supports just bad at a certain skill level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't there an ability that can turn night into day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Night Stalker has his Darkness, shouldn't someone be able to do the opposite and turn night into day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do carries think it's funny to steal the last hit on an obs ward from a support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy even had the audacity to say "I forgot it gave gold" - if that were true, why didn't he hit it from the moment I found it instead of the last hit? Fucking hate the idiots who play this game.

edit: ITT downvoted by those same carries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else feel the game is less responsive lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 07:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to, I could right-click the base and buy items and check other heroes' items while walking to the fountain. Now, I'd say about half the time when I try doing this, my hero stops moving. Why? Is this a new bug? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the differences between Radiant and Dire that the average player might not notice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the fact that Radiant has a bit of an easier time pulling and also that Dire has Rosh advantage. Are there any other little tips about Radiant vs Dire that will help in your ordinary match of Dota? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do when a player bullies the team into a disadvantage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right from the start, I had a Jugg who convinced everyone we needed a trilane safelane and that he needed solo offlane. Since this is like fuckin 2k mmr at best (it was unranked so I don't know the exact mmr, but I'm sure the same thing would happen in ranked), we were all underleveled. 

Should I just say fuck supporting the "trilane" and go roaming? Or should I stay there and try to pull, because the two heroes in lane are always going to be autoattacking and we need it pulled back to our tower? Or is there some other option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone point me towards a very detailed guide on itemization? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is an impossible task, in a way, since every hero whether core or support has different needs. But I'm asking in a more general way, for example what do you prioritize building when you're ahead vs when you're behind? If you know you need a Pipe of Insight/Crimson Guard, do you build it as a first item? And those are just example questions, there's surely smaller things that I'm forgetting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone point me towards a very detailed guide on itemization? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is an impossible task, in a way, since every hero whether core or support has different needs. But I'm asking in a more general way, for example what do you prioritize building when you're ahead vs when you're behind? If you know you need a Pipe of Insight/Crimson Guard, do you build it as a first item? And those are just example questions, there's surely smaller things that I'm forgetting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's hear some advanced tips on how to play the "easy" heroes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 11:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Ogre to CM, from Viper to Wraith King - some heroes in this game are undoubtedly considered easier than the rest. Despite their simplicity, that doesn't mean there isn't a lot to master. I'd like to know what small tips higher MMR players could provide to take even more advantage of these simple heroes' skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Glimmer Cape on Razor becoming a thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear I'm not making this up, I've seen this in two or three of my games this week. I'm a bit confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which comedians do you consider endearing when they laugh at their own material? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is often considered a bad thing, right? And usually I'd agree. But there are certain comedians who can do it (whether it's forced or real, I can't ever tell because I'm not a comedian myself, just a fan) that are all the more charming because of it.

One of them I'd consider Dave Chappelle (please don't kill me, I know the sidebar says he's low-effort but this is a discussion about many comics). Which other comedians do you think can laugh at their own stuff and not make you want to roll your eyes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there such a thing as tactical feeding? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is partly venting, partly curiosity. I had a Slark in my game who died 19 times. He thought his feeding was justified because he said something like "look at those idiots, wasting all their ults on me." He seemed to think he was helping our team by having the enemy use all their ults only on one hero.

Is this actually a thing? I'd always thought feeding was ...bad. The only hero I can think of who might benefit from dying is Venge or a Bloodstone carrier, maaaaaybe Shadow Fiend or Venomancer in some scenarios. And even in those situations, wouldn't you prefer to live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you get the feeling certain hero spammers are complete assholes in real life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine a Techies or Slark spammer to be anything but a total prick, the type of person who would steal your lunch money, your girlfriend, your car, your house, your intestines... just to say he could and then throw it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it always a bad idea to choose a melee support if you've got a melee carry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to play Kunkka, Ogre, and Naga. The problem here is it seems harder to harass with these heroes, especially against the dual offlane that's found in 99% of games. Should I stick to ranged supports or is there a way to make melee supports work with ranged carries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are people in unranked smarter than ranked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear this is a thing. I'm on a new account, just calibrated... and my teammates do the dumbest shit compared to the games in unranked. People like to say unranked is where people go to goof off and ranked is where peple go to tryhard, but I swear it's the other way around. I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people think it's acceptable to leave a support to a solo lane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has happened to me multiple times. I'll say "I'm going to support" and they'll even say "OK thanks a lot" and then there's two in the offlane and one in the jungle .. and I'm trying to stay alive against a dual offlane. It's like these people WANT to lose. Why would anyone do this? Is there an honest-to-god reason someone would do this, or is this an example of an unwinnable (or very difficult game)? Or do I just suck? Some people have told me I should really know how to 1 v 2 as a support, but that seems crazy to me. A support is not an offlaner.

edit: [I made the same thread on /r/dota2](https://www.reddit.com/r/DotA2/comments/5e7lpi/why_do_people_think_its_acceptable_to_leave_a) and someone told me "It's not only acceptable but is also recommended". Am I being trolled? I'm so confused.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people think it's acceptable to leave a support to a solo lane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has happened to me multiple times. I'll say "I'm going to support" and they'll even say "OK thanks a lot" and then there's two in the offlane and one in the jungle .. and I'm trying to stay alive against a dual offlane. It's like these people WANT to lose. Why would anyone do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One small thing that's bugged me about Shut Up and Dance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's entirely inconsequential to the larger plot, yet has been nagging away at me. What did the hacker organization do with the money robbed from the bank? I suppose maybe they use it to fund their equipment (like the flying drone camera, the cake, the gun, etc)? But if that's true, couldn't the serial numbers on the bills be traced back to them, if somehow the police were to catch on to their game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a custom game that is 1 v 1 where each hero controls 5 heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 07:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically a whole lot of micro, seeing who can win like a game of Starcraft or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the hero pool for Single Draft rigged? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 06:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like almost every match there's a PA, Pudge, Troll Warlord, Shadow Shaman, and a couple others. Why is this? Or is this a case of confirmation bias? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I use Witch Doctor's Voodoo Restoration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed while practicing him in unranked that he can heal creeps. As long as I have the mana regen, should I use the health basically every time I push to make a stronger wave?

And a slightly related question, is Witch Doctor or Dazzle better at this kind of thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are people in ranked so immature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a Nature's Prophet who died to first blood because he overextended, so he said "you guys don't wanna help me, I'm gonna feed for the rest of the game." What the actual fuck? Why do people play a competitive mode if they're gonna throw a fit like a child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the fuck does "late ss" mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd always been under the impression that "ss" meant (for whatever reason, never understood this either) that a hero is missing. But I saw someone say "late ss" like 40 minutes into the game during a teamfight. I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I play Enchantress as a disabler despite having poor micro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Enchant giving a 50% slow at max level is amazing as fuck and I want to abuse it. Do I really need to enchant creeps beyond jungling for some gold? I know I wouldn't be using her to her FULL potential, but is it still viable? Maybe building Eul's and other items like that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I play Enchantress as a disabler despite having poor micro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Enchant giving a 50% slow at max level is amazing as fuck and I want to abuse it. Do I really need to enchant creeps beyond jungling for some gold? I know I wouldn't be using her to her FULL potential, but is it still viable? Maybe building Eul's and other items like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I try to stop using camera grip? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 00:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using this for a long time and while it's what I'm used to, something about it feels off to me. But since I've never really used edge panning very often, that also feels awkward. Basically my problem is too often I'll camera grip all the way across the screen instead of clicking on the minimap to see what's happening much quicker. 

I know everything is mostly personal preference, but what do you consider the quickest way to move the camera? How often should I be clicking the minimap instead of panning/gripping? I feel like there are a lot of finer points to camera movement that are never discussed and I'd like a little commentary on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the skill/item build on support Legion Commander? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 08:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm convinced that LC as a hard carry isn't really a good idea. Her duel should be a counter initiation kinda thing and her Press the Attack is a great purge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can you disassemble Aquila when Wraith Band doesn't build into anything else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like disassembly is one of those things, especially as a support who doesn't get as much farm, that would really help out if I remembered to do it. So I'm looking at all the items that can be disassembled and Aquila is one of them, which confuses me because of the Wraith Band. Is it simply for Ring of Basi into Vlads and sell the Wraith Band? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm wanting to play more Naga. Can someone explain auras for illusions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 11:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried reading the wiki page on this, but I think I need an ELI5. Which items do and do not give benefits either to my illusions or to my teammates around the illusions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the fuck do you lock down a mobility hero like Ember Spirit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 10:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I'll use Naga's song to keep him in place and furiously tapping my stun - and I'm sure he's also furiously tapping his remnants. How in the actual fuck do you stun this motherfucker? Same goes for Morphling and a couple other heroes I'm forgetting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I quit trying to play "unconventional" supports? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 06:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every time I try to play Kunkka or Riki as support, I get someone whining on my team about it. I know I can mute them, and usually I do, but that doesn't stop them from getting tilted by my role choice. Should I stick to the heroes that people KNOW are supports so I don't tilt people right from the draft screen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Night Stalker as a counter to Tinker - can this work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 09:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the annoyance of Tinker is his ability to hide in the trees. Night Stalker's Aghs upgrade makes that impossible. Is he a good counter to stop Tinker's shenanigans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people say Rod of Atos is useless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't actually get it often, but now that I think about it, there are quite a few scenarios where it makes sense to buy. For example, I've always liked the idea of using it with a hero that's already got a slow (Ogre, CM, maybe even Kunkka) to slow the enemy even more, effectively stunning them. Also, I have this idea that it could be a situationally good pick-up on Venge after you swap a tanky hero into a group of melee teammates so they can get a lot more right clicks.

But most people say it needs a buff. Is Rod of Atos truly useless in its current state? How can/should it be used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Crest a counter to PA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 09:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to I'd go for heavy magic nukes to counter PA. Lately, however, I've just been getting a Solar Crest for the 25% evasion reduction and... it seems to be working out? I think? Is this actually actually a good idea?

edit: wait, it's 25% miss chance for enemies. Still, this seems helpful. Is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does playing with friends affect your hidden unranked MMR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing with friends on a new account. But then suddenly I thought...solo MMR and party MMR are obviously different things. When I get to profile level 20, does it combine whatever I've done in unranked up to that point or only my solo matches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any coaching videos that take a look at how to win the 2-1-2 meta? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dota D.Bowie's videos are great and everything if you see trilanes or solo offlanes ... but you never do at a low MMR. A lot of the tips from this sub, from coaches, etc, aren't really aimed towards the reality of the game for many players. Are there any coaches that look specifically at the scrub tier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I place the first two wards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the longest time, I'd put one right next to enemy mid tower and then one as close to enemy offlane tower as I could. No one has ever dewarded me and I don't expect them to do so any time soon. But I know if I'm ever going to climb MMR that they'll deward this, simply because you can easily see the hero on the minimap when they place these wards. I didn't even know this until I decided to look at a replay from the enemy perspective, and there I was, clear as day walking up to their mid tower.

So how do I ward mid without being caught? Or should I even ward mid at all? Should I be constantly checking the map myself instead of looking at the minimap to know if the enemy mid is missing or at low health? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An easy way to ward aggressively in dangerous areas: scan the area before you go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one else really uses scan in my games, so I've been using this trick to ward behind enemy towers. Maybe I'm getting lucky, but more often than not it's worked and there's no one in their jungle at the moment. Of course, you should also look at the minimap to see how many heroes are currently visible. If you see like 3 heroes who are all the way on the other end of the map, you're probably safe. I'm convinced this is one of those small things that's been winning me games lately, so I'd say try it out and see what happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there ever a reason to build Battle Fury on a ranged hero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like an obvious "No, you dumbass" but you have to remember Meepo and Terrorblade will often build Dragon Lance which isn't super logical at first glance. So is there ever a reason for a ranged hero to build a BF?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there ever a reason to build Battle Fury on a ranged hero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like an obvious "No, you dumbass" but you have to remember Meepo and Terrorblade will often build Dragon Lance which isn't super logical at first glance. So is there ever a reason for a ranged hero to build a BF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which heroes can be played as support and then transition to semi-carry in late game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I've got Vengeful Spirit, Kunkka, and Silencer. Can't think of any other really good ones who can do this. Can someone enlighten me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When people at low MMR say "haha 3 v 1 to kill me" ... what do they mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens a lot, and it's puzzling. They laugh because you "had to use more than one hero to kill them" but uh... I'd always been under the impression that's how ganking works, unless you're just stupidly overpowered compared to your enemy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rant] Watching how my sister raises her kids makes me never want my own children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister (21) doesn't read, and so she rarely if ever reads to her children, a set of 2 year old twins. She sits them in front of the TV, either her own shows or children's shows. I know they're not that old, yet I feel like they should know more words than "no", "hey guy", and ... I'm struggling to think of other words they know, honestly. I don't think this is normal.

And this is one of the reasons I don't want kids. It's scary that you are the reason your kids are fucked up. If I had kids, I'd try my hardest, sure. But there's still the lingering thought: what if I fail them? (Though I seriously doubt this even crosses my sister's mind... she doesn't read, so why would she be worried that her kids aren't being exposed to it? She doesn't understand the importance and I don't see a scenario where she'd regret it.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Hero colors are still broken during the pick phase in Random Draft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it's a small thing but it's still something I'd like to see fixed. And because it's so small, I don't think much effort is required to fix it. Win-win for everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few general questions about supporting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Should I build items to counter heroes based on what I THINK they'll do? An example, I had an enemy Mirana. I was like, ok, I'll build a Pipe of Insight to mitigate some of the Aghs damage. But she goes for Manta and Maelstrom and I was like... oh, I guess I wasted gold. This happens every now and then with other heroes, too. And I know I should be checking their items, and I did, but I was expecting the Aghs to come eventually.

* Is it generally ok to buy a gem right after boots? I've been told by a friend that this only works at low MMR. I don't quite understand why. I know part of it is at low MMR the invis heroes are incredibly reckless and I assume they'll become less so as I go against better players. But surely a gem is still useful?

* Let's say I'm in safe lane and my carry refuses to farm against the dual offlane, just sits there and soaks up exp like they're an offlaner. Should I continue to try to babysit them or should I start roaming to mid or wherever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: If the enemy has mega creeps and you are trying to take the last set of rax, DO NOT go back to your base to defend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 10:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, it's infuriating how stupid people can be. If this is your one last chance of winning the game, don't go back and waste it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is that list of which items most effectively counter which heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw something like this a few months ago, tried to search for it, couldn't really find anything. Anyone know where something like that can be found? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I sell magic wand as long as I have enough regen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an example. I'm Vengeful Spirit. I have Tranq Boots, Solar Crest, Orchid Malevolence, TP scrolls, Aether Lens, and Magic Wand. The problem here is I no longer have room for wards. Thankfully, in this was the rare game where I had a second support with me and she warded a lot of the time.  

But in a normal game where that's not going to happen, is it okay to sell the wand to make room for another slot as long as you have enough health/mana regen through your items? I do this quite often and don't see a HUGE problem with it, so I'd like to know if it's a good or bad move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nature's Prophet - can he be played as a roaming support? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been a fan of the jungling Furion that I typically see. Can you use his teleportation to be mostly a ganker/disabler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The selection of licensed music on this show was absolutely stellar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much every choice sounds like it could have been written by Ramin Djawadi himself. When I heard The xx's Intro playing I'd almost forgotten it was their song because it fits so well.

And then there's The Glitch Mob's Fortune Days from If-Then-Else, a song I'd actually not heard before. I didn't even suspect it would be a licensed track until I looked it up online because I liked it so much.

There are surely other standouts that I'm forgetting, I think there was a song from the Propellerheads when John was going on a rampage after Joss' death which, again, was a stroke of genius. Whoever chose the licensed tracks deserves some recognition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do the experience levels on your profile work, exactly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 09:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on a new account trying to get to level 20 for ranked. I was sitting at level 4 for a couple days, then all of a sudden after a long 82 minutes game, I jumped straight to level 8. Does it have something to do with how long your matches are, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I stop myself from tilting when my teammates die constantly to invis heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a game where I did excellent as CM in the early game, no deaths at all. Caught Riki every time with sentries, as well as the Sniper who decided to get a Shadow Blade despite seeing I was controlling Riki. But things didn't last. One time I had to go back to base because I was almost dead, and when that happened and I wasn't saving their asses with detection... they immediately started feeding Riki and things got out of control.

This is the sort of thing that makes me rage and sends me to low priority. I'm sincerely confused how people don't understand that they need to be cautious around invis heroes. Not like any of them were six slotted, I could at least understand that. It's as simple as no one at my skill level wants to buy detection other than me - and if I leave for one second, they are all dead. Every time.

Is there any hope to win games like these? If your teammates are feeders to invis heroes, can you somehow play around their stupidity to win the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I stop myself from tilting when my teammates die constantly to invis heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a game where I did excellent as CM in the early game, no deaths at all. Caught Riki every time with sentries, as well as the Sniper who decided to get a Shadow Blade despite seeing I was controlling Riki. But things didn't last. One time I had to go back to base because I was almost dead, and when that happened and I wasn't saving their asses with detection... they immediately started feeding Riki and things got out of control.

This is the sort of thing that makes me rage and sends me to low priority. I'm sincerely confused how people don't understand that they need to be cautious around invis heroes. Not like any of them were six slotted, I could at least understand that. It's as simple as no one at my skill level wants to buy detection other than me - and if I leave for one second, they are all dead. Every time.

Is there any hope to win games like these? If your teammates are feeders to invis heroes, can you somehow play around their stupidity to win the game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I'm going to stop fapping for a while because of Donald Trump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't your typical reason, but damn hear me out. Every time I close my eyes when I'm trying to fap, I see his face. The fact that he somehow won the election and will be in command of my country for the next four years is terrifying. He is haunting me, like a ghost. I feel ill. So I'm just going to stop masturbating until I can stop thinking about how Trump will fuck up the world... which might be a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Crystal Maiden said to be a bad support at low MMR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a couple people say that CM is bad for low MMR. I'm not sure I understand why, actually. Perhaps she can't itemize for damage in the late game like, for example, Kunkka or Vengeful Spirit, but she is excellent at ganking in the early game. And typically (for me anyhow) if I manage to dominate the early game, I'll usually win. Can someone explain why she's considered bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a support, should I TP to a guaranteed death just for the EXP/assist gold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing the answer, as with everything in Dota, is "It depends." But used to if a death looked obviously assured, I'd hold off my TP for another more urgent kill where I'd decide who lived and died. Now, I've been using my TP anyhow for the shared xp/gold. In general, this seems to be working out for me. 

Another thing about TPs is I've read you should walk to base (or just suicide at early levels) instead of TPing to base, and that's what I've been doing for a while now. Is this generally a good idea or is it ever better to TP straight home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does more damage: Rapier and a Deso, or two Rapiers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was playing Weaver, had a Deso and a Rapier. Couldn't seem to break high ground, so I said fuck it, sold the Deso and bought a second Rapier. Won the game. I'm curious which one is actually the better option, though. The two Rapiers SEEMED to be more damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you avoid getting put in low priority? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a new account, because my old account was on low priority and I wanted a better behavior score. I've won 7 games in a row and yet I am now in low priority. It's not for trash talking because you're not allowed to speak for the first 20 games on a new account. It's not for feeding or trolling. I tried my best, as I said I won the games and usually had the highest kills and lowest deaths.

My only theory is maybe the spam pinging when I told people to get back to safety made people annoyed and reported me, because I'm also on a communication ban. But when that is literally my only option because I can't talk for the first 20 games... Idk, this shit is fucked up.
 
So ... does low priority carry over between an IP address or something? I don't fucking understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Valve ever give an explanation why new accounts can't talk for the first 20 games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even understand the idea of not letting me communicate for the first 20 games. It is SO painful seeing something like a Death Prophet slowly trying to take down a tower with autoattacks. Why the fuck can't I tell her "Your ult is really good at taking down towers, you should use it right now"??? That's just one example.

How is this a welcoming environment for newbies, to have them lost and confused? There are people who have been playing for a while who can give them minor tips to help them out. I mean, in my experience as long as a player says "I'm new go easy on me" in unranked, people WILL help them. Or would have, in the past. 

Why are we no longer able to do this? If not for understanding strangers when I started, I'd probably have quit pretty soon because the game can be so overwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a new account. Why did I get low priority? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've won most of my games and it's not like I'm trash talking because you're not even allowed to talk during the first 20 games on a new account. What the fuck is wrong with Valve's report system?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a new account. Why did I get low priority? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've won most of my games and it's not like I'm trash talking because you're not even allowed to talk during the first 20 games on a new account. What the fuck is wrong with Valve's report system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often can I get away with brown boots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 07:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this in my games fairly often and I'm always thinking, what the fuck, they're kinda dumb. But then I go to Dotabuff and see there are a fair amount of high level players who will do the same. How often can you hold off on an upgrade until you get an item or two? Seems like an early morbid mask/urn/aquila would be more beneficial in a lot of cases, now that I think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloveress ASMR (the banana girl) wants to stab you with a knife. This girl is trying too hard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 07:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should a support ever buy a Linkens or Lotus Orb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking I'd buy it to cast it on whichever carry looks like he's in immediate danger. I know these items are typically built on carries/tanks, but can supports also use them for the team utility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anything else not-porn like the recent banana eating video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All at once, this girl was a revelation. Never saw anything sexual from ASMR, but for various reasons (especially when she said "if you're jacking off, that's fine") I was like.. huh, this could be neat. But her channel has quickly turned to shit.

So who are some other ASMRtists who are playful and funny? Even if it's not entirely dirty, just someone who doesn't take it so damn seriously. One of the best for this that I've seen (not dirty at all though) is probably [ASMR Attack with her Nancy roleplay](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZraSqnzXS3k). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 why does anyone queue for Single Draft and then abandon when they don't get a hero they want to play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 01:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is especially ironic because, if they abandon a second time, they'll get Low Priority where they HAVE to play Single Draft. Do they not understand this...? If you want to choose your hero, do not play Single Draft or All Random or Random Draft - or uh, I guess anything that's not All Pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
