<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2851</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's not like this Bush can do much worse.  Vote Jeb!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Okay, so, you guys drive across the border,   when you're well away from the crossing, pull over   let me out of the trunk,   I'll give you the rest of the directions to your hotel" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Johnson!  What is with these numbers?  The approval rating for this game is in the toilet!"
"I.... I don't know boss.  Paperboy was on so many systems back in the 80s, I thought... oh god I thought a sequel would do well.  But these kids... these damn kids, they just don't know what a paper is!"  *sobs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "OH MY GOD I can't believe I got to hug Justin Bieber!!!| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I know it seems like a 10 bedroom mansion is much too big for one person, but where else are all my invisible friends going to stay?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gosh, I wish I wasn't dying" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 08:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of people just learn how to hide it better than others.  Anyone who sees me IRL would have no idea how bad things have actually gotten in my life.  I'm just good at faking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 07:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it came as more of a surprise that he was finally admitting it than that he didn't love me.  I had been expecting it for years,   I could just tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything I've ever attempted has been a failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 06:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I have no real reason to keep living.  Everything I've ever tried to do, I've failed at

I tried to be an artist.  I tried for over a decade,   I just couldn't hack it, I was never good enough to do anything with it
before that I tried to be a functioning adult with a 'real' job.  I was having nervous breakdowns   panic attacks

my panic attacks just got worse as I got older.  I'm on meds for anxiety but they only take the edge off, they don't help me function in the way I need to.

I've been in a number of relationships, that all are basically variants of the same relationship over   over. 
I got married in 2013, for probably the least romantic reason ever - basically to make sure that if anything happened, we'd be each other's proxy for emergencies

I live with my husband,   he supports me, but all we ever do is fight anymore   he doesn't love me (this isn't speculation, he actually told me this, he doesn't feel love)
the only time he ever wants me in his life is when things are going well, which they haven't been for a while as I'm not getting the emotional intimacy that I need,   I feel so very alone

we moved 1500km away from our hometown 2 years ago,   not like it would have mattered, as I didn't have any friends there   I don't have any friends here.  I'm anti-social   an introvert, so it's not like anyone would miss me if I was to kill myself

I'm not close to my parents, I'm an only child,   it'd probably be at least 6 months before anyone realized I was gone (I honestly doubt they'd ever find out, I talk to them MAYBE 3 times a year,   that was when my mom wasn't dying)

I just feel like I have nothing left to live for.  I'm a failure as a person, I can't be independent,   I can't depend on anyone to take care of me.  I don't see the point of going on


Although I'm also a chickenshit, so it's not like I'm in any danger of actually going through with anything.  I'll just cry   mope   do nothing, just like I've been doing for the past year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "ok, a differing opinion. Firstup, I'd like to clarify that I haven't broken up with her."

THIS IS FUCKING NEWS TO ME, BECAUSE THE LAST THING YOU TOLD ME EARLIER WAS THAT IT WAS OVER

Also, you had 3 days off last week.  You still did nothing.

I. AM. DEPRESSED.  Some days are better than others, some days are worse.  Shit like this, or you not resolving anything or communicating with me, makes things worse.  Which means I barely have the motivation to get out of bed   cooking dinner means having to try to find space to work in the kitchen more often than not.


I WOULD be making more money, but seeing that I had to support us for an entire year just off of my art, I am still suffering burn out   had to switch what I was doing just to continue wanting to draw, I am not making nearly as much as I used to.

You only recently started paying off my credit card.  Like within the last few months.  Before that, I managed it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You put the individual rooms up on the wall of post-its, which means that you plan on getting to it eventually. You never told me differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever actually listen to what I actually say, or do you just do the TL;DR of it   make up your own context?

I'm giving you flack for showing me this thread, because you know how deeply I'm affected when people say something mean about me.  I JUST told you about this 2 days ago when I told you about the Yelp people rater.
You knew the kind of comments that were here, you knew how much they'd hurt me   eat at me,   you showed me this anyway.  You keep me in some sort of bullsh*t limbo, then do stuff like this that looks like you're just trying to hurt me more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 00:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also go out of my way to not use it when I know you have to work,   either walking, or doing my errands   groceries on a different day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
