<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1320</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist - Snow and Wall Markings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 03:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Two things was interesting and memorable about Thanksgiving Day 2014. It had snowed the days leading up to Thanksgiving. Snow was still on the ground the day of. Thats  Memory  #1.  Memory #2 was my girlfriends son coming to pick up some Thanksgiving plates for himself and friends.  Nothing unusual there right?  After hugs to me and his mom  he departs.  He's grown - never has lived with us.  Minutes later there's a knock on our door and its him again.  In a chuckled voice he asks me "Dude what's this writing on your lawn?"    And thats where this story will begin.


I walk outside our house its after 9pm Thanksgiving Day and say "what do you mean writing on the lawn?"  He ushers me further outside and on the front lawn there  written in the snow are words that look like "D %ck".  Snow had been on the ground and was beginning to melt but its nightfall and the temp drops so the melted snow is frozen. The letters themselves has begun to melt but it looks like there are two lines. Line 1 carved into the snow says what looks like "D--ck"  the second word on line two underneath is unreadable.  We both look at the word and my GF son chuckles and says it looks like someone wrote on your lawn the word "D* ck"   The second word beings with a K and the rest of the lawn underneath is snowless. The snow has melted on that patch area.

We look at it for about 3 minutes. Its cold outside.  He laughs, young kid, his friends are honking the car for him to come on as we're departing we both agree this must be some weird prank because it looks like what's carved in the snow is the word "D* ck" and something else.  I assume most of you know how writing looks carved in the snow after its been there awhile. By awhile I mean a day or two.  The letter size gets wider and less readable due to the fluctuation of the temperature. Yes we had snow on the ground days prior to Thanksgiving. But by day time the temperature was low 40's. In the shade mid 30's.  The writing looked like it has been there for awhile. A  day or two.  Our thought at that time was there must have been some teenagers in the neighborhood who while walking by decided to write in the snow.  Thats the conclusion I left with.   Keep in mind inside the house from 2012 to at that time Thanksgiving 2014 crazy stuff had been happening inside the house.  Even with the unlimited amount of activity for the past 2 years - I walked away from my GF's son pointing out to us we had writings on our lawn thinking this was some neighborhood prank. Bigger fish to fry inside the house than worry about some group of kids getting kicks out writing "d ^ck" and etc in the snow outside my door.  I would monitor it mentally but thats about it. NOTE  TO SELF.

Thats November. Few days after Thanksgiving the snow melts.  Writings gone.

Two weeks after Thanksgiving comes my bday. I have a Bday party at my house. 12 of my closest friends come over.   Yes we did have activity. Tina's notebook which we didnt even know was missing materializes in the middle of the floor between 3 of my friends while THEY WERE doing Karaoke. Various alcoholic beverages, one being Pacifico beer. The guys and I go through  3 cases. Good Times. The day after the bday is cleanup day - the story of the bottle hitting the wall and noise arriving first and the bottle appearing minutes later was during that time frame.  The Monday after my bday party I wake up and discover the wallet I keep in my safe for fear of it going missing is in fact missing. Safe sits in my office. Combo safe. Only I know the combo. GF leaves for work before me that day. I get up, shower and dress and go to my office to grab my car keys(my remaining set) and grab my wallet. Car keys are in the safe. My wallet is gone.  Once again after about 100+ missing items you dont really go around looking for stuff esp. when you know you purposely put something in the safe to prevent it from going missing in the first place.  My wallet is done. I have a business trip to  in a few days and I now have no ID, no credit cards.  I call my job and tell them I wont be in today - I'm working from home.  After that I call and tell my GF what's going on. After that I grab my birth certificate and head to the Drivers License office to get a new drivers license.  

An hour later I return home with my temporary drivers license. I do a quick look over the house and head back out. Now its time to go to the bank and get more bank cards, cancel the existing, etc.  I even run to the Mall to grab a new wallet. Blah Blah Blah right.  Are you  seeing better yet feeling the inconvenience all of this is doing?  For those who know Poltergeists, Demons and Malevolent entity's.   The entity behind all of this is watching EVERYTHING.  Thats why IT did it. 

I return home about an hour and half later from mall and bank and this video below is what I find in my office.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q3meCW-YznM

I could've been gone for no more than 2 hours. Maybe even less than that.  The writing here or the material used to produce it is different. Its more runny. More oily.  Patches of it are still wet. I attribute that to me just being gone for less than 2 hrs.  As well as it being Winter vs. Summer. We own nothing even close to this inside our house.  Three things you need to know when watching the above video.  The cross hanging on the wall above the TV.  That cross hangs in the living room kitchen area. Was in the living room before I left.  Its nailed unto the wall with the all too familiar Upside Down Man(Native American symbol) which means "a man has died" based on Google searched.  Directly across from cross is a pair of scissors - stuck into the wall.  Thats been done before remember this video? See where the scissors is placed?  Dead center of the "Upside Down Man's" head.  The 3rd thing I want you to notice is the bar stool. That's the kitchen bar stool. Like the cross on the wall above the TV it too has been in the office before. But study the direction of the bar stool.   If you look at all the videos of when a chair was moved be it down stairs or upstairs. Once again check the videos and compare. You will see minus of how many chairs are re-located. One chair is always purposely turned to face towards a TV: office living room TV.  

Now I can't explain that. I'm clueless as to why is that. But it means something. We might not ever know. But the chair facing the TV, or facing one of the "Upside Down Man" markings is not a coincidental.  I pray to God and his Christ Jesus that someday, one day someone seeing this will be able to put two and two together. There are other things in this room out of order or in order "Order in Chaos" I should say.  But lets move the story forward because it goes south from here.

The Upside down man and cross stuff are not new.  What's new here are my initials KL with the word "Die" in front of it. A milestone in my house  is a new event, often a similar event with something new added.  This house, this office has had similar events like this before. What's new are the words "Die KL". That's a mile-stone i.e.  call-out. Does not take a rocket scientist to look at this and realize this alone speaks volumes.   People can debate what constitutes a "Residual Haunting" and what constitutes an "Intelligent Haunting" all day.  This mile-stone as it exist right now has for me based on what I read about both "residual" and "intelligent" constitutes an Intelligent Haunting.  This is another feather in the cap of what ever living in this house being a Poltergeist.  Dont get me wrong Demons have the power if not more to the very same thing.  But in doing the Paranormal community a favor I'm going to lean towards Poltergeist. I'm in agreement with you. This is a Poltergeist. This true account alone should be a Parapsychologists wet-dream.  But I digress. Back to the story like I said it goes down hill from here.  Now every mile-stone in this house always signifies the activity is about to raise things up a notch or two. Thats been the pattern with the missing Bibles, burnt posters, objects being thrown, objects disappearing, and etc.   Other house attacks, aka Poltergeist vandalisms have happened when GF and I were at work. House is secure. No forced entry. ADT is armed.  Locks changed 2-3 times since living here. Police and crime reports show no other related activity within the 2-3 counties next to us.  All attacks have been in day light hours. This happened in less than 2 hours.  The entity knows I'm returning home and  soon. No one's coming in doing this?  No one outside person or group of people can predict Keith lost his wallet today. Keith's not going into the office today. Keith's going to leave and be back at a certain time. He's gone lets break in, paint and all and go to work on the furthest room in the house, a room upstairs mind you. Vandalize it and take nothing else in the process. Leave no paint residue anywhere in the room. No spilt paint on office furniture, carpet, wall etc. everywhere the paint is are the words "Die KL" "Upside Down Man" " Paw prints" 3, "Cross" and etc. No blobs or etc. anywhere that would indicate who ever did this was rushing to get it done or more or less was amateur.  I welcome that debate with anyone. 

This was a few days after my bday.   Two weeks after Thanksgiving.  Please re-read paragraph 1   2.  You have a luxury even I at the time did not have.  Now lets talk about Christmas.

Christmas afternoon. We return home from a celebration with friends.  About two hours later I'm in my office.  Its late in the day.  Nothing usual. I stepped out of my office and this video is what I find.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rX5PKCPhsck

Pic 1
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/KL_Die1.jpg

Pic. 2
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141225_223003275.jpg



I'm not going to go deep into the events of the video above accept to say. This is a Christian prayer card and Native American necklace my co-worker bought me when he went on vacation to Arizona. Like I said before friends, family, paranormal teams and co-workers know of our ordeal and they all believe us. My co-worker bought two necklaces when he ventured into a Indian Reservation shop as a mean of protection. A necklace for me and one for my GF. This necklace now broken was mine.  The card where you see the familiar "Die KL" remember the  "Die Kl" from the video above? Now its "Die KL" on a Christian prayer card. I got this card a few weeks ago. I was in a Christian store buying new wooden crosses you see them upside down in the previous video-(all are now missing BTW).  I went to this store to buy more crosses and Christian symbols.  As I'm standing in the check-out line the lady behind me pokes me and hands me this card. She says something to the effect "Sir you should have this. You need this." She's about 80+ yrs. old. I smile and read the card and knowing 200% that I probably do need this kindly accept. Now this card being a gift was kept in my office on my computer desk under my monitor.  I will admit I forgot what it said because after the "Die KL" was written on it my GF being in tears upon reading it threw it away.  

Now if you look at the video and pic you can see the words "Die KL"   those are my initials. The web substance does resemble the web substance on the 1st video. Its very sticky, but not adhesive. Its wetter than wet if that makes since.   This is Christmas Day. I'm still not connecting the dots.  Until

Few days later a new snow comes in. It snows for a day or two and the first night of the night I leave my house to retrieve something on in my car. My car is parked curb side. I have to pass a majority of my lawn to get to the car. Since its icy outside I avoid walking on the pavement and instead choose to walk on the grass.  Thats where I see the new writing.  There which much better snow. New snow. 1st night of snow are the words "Die KL" Once again its two lines. Just like the office and hallway (card pic) "Die KL"

Now we can return back to Thanksgiving 2014 where all of this really began. It began with my girlfriends(GF) son knocking on our door after 1st leaving with plates of food for himself and his friends.  He knocks on the door to tell us on our lawn is the some writing we both at the time thought was the word "D* k"  It was not the word "D ^ck". It was "Die KL".  It was just un-readable due to the snow melting.  Just like the "Die KL on the card which if you look carefully is almost un-readable to.  

Now I'm sorry, truly sorry I didnt get a picture of that.  In my defense I didnt have my cell phone with me.  But thats a weak excuse I could've easily grabbed it. But me going back inside to retrieve my camera or cell phone would have caught the attention of my girlfriend.  Seeing "Die KL" in both office and hallway is one thing. That plus the other events and I'm leaving a lot out trust me.  Between each "Die KL" are days/nights of flying candles. Flying vases. Lights going off and on and worse.  I see the "Die KL" on my front lawn and thinking some neighbor walking their dog is going to see this because at this stage every other house knows our house is haunted.  That secret got revealed the day the 1st paranormal team came and with them came their logo and paranormal van with the name "No Bull Paranormal" on the side of van.  People know. In the snow are the words "Die KL". I take my foot and remove it.  It never snowed the winter of 2014 after that night. But the "Die KL" would appear one more time.  The last time being inside my car.

Like most boyfriends if your GF asked you to go to the store for a cooking ingredient you opt to go. This weekend would be no different.  My GF asks me to go the store for OJ. I grab my keys, and throw on some sweats. I'm out the door in minutes. Using my key-fob I unlock the car as I'm heading to it.  When I get in my car. My Hyundai silver blue Sonata - 2008. I sit in the drivers seat and the words "Die KL" is written on both floor of the car. Driver and Passenger. Written on the seats are "Upside Down Man" and "Upside Down Cross" On the ceiling is "Die KL".  Same oily, gluey,, non adhesive substance. But its still wet and thats mostly due to the temperature and humidity outside.  Once again same oily substance as what was in the house. And what was in the hallway.  No excuse for not taking a picture. But once again my biggest fear and level of panic attack was neighbors walking by and seeing the words "Die KL" or better yet see me cleaning the words "Die KL" off the inside of my car upholstery.  Instead of pic taking I pop open the garage door and back the car inside and immediately grab what ever cleaning ingredient is inside the garage (not much). Couldnt go into the house seeking cleaning stuff. Once again GF would be like why are u looking for cleaning stuff and its 9am or so in the morning, when you're suppose to be going to the store.  Grabbing cleaning gear from inside would just beg the question.  I find a towel and use the outside water faucet and some Windex I found in the garage and remove the markings.   Its the scene from "Pulp Fiction" all over again where Jackson and Travolta are forced to scrub brain matter off the innards of their car before Quintin Tarintinos character wife returns home.

Conclusion:
This was an emotional story to recount. Number one just reliving it, and recounting it in one's own brain is hard to do. These events happened over a year ago.  Thats not easy to do ladies and gentlemen. Dates, and times therein get blurred and the more distance between then and now stuff gets forgotten. When stuff gets forgotten thats where certain individuals leap in and try to poke holes in hopes of calling out inconsistencies.  Its also emotional because up until  now most of the activity in the home centered around the home. Meaning GF and I shared in a majority of the events that took place.  We saw it together.   After the "Die KL" episodes events begin to happen more with just me in the house.   All vases being thrown are on my side of the bed. GF leaves for work and its just me there. Objects get thrown at me while in the shower. Lights go off with just me in the house. Objects get thrown at me while I'm on sitting on the toilet.  I'm in the bathroom and GF is gone. Something walks by turns off the light manually and slams the door shut.  GF is at work. We live alone. Wallet gets taken again in January.  Candles get thrown outside my office.  Im sleeping and something is poking my rib cage. Poking from inside the pillow while I sleep. I wake up and look at my Gf she's sound asleep. As I mentioned before each NEW event is a mile-stone.   Weeks prior to the 1st "Die K:" which was Thanksgiving Day 2014, there might have been more. We just don't know. There are questionable stuff that happened weeks and months before that were weird that I ignored that we ignored that might be in fact Poltergeist related activity. I've gone into grocery stores and come back out and all my car doors are wide - open.  Your in the middle of Safeway parking lot and you walk outside, patrons and employees are standing next to your car scratching their heads, trying to alert you(me) that all your car doors are open.   My neighbors have rung our door bell 4am, 5am on a weekday to inform me that all my car-doors are open. Thats happened 3 times. Nothings ever taking. Nothings missing. Nothings sabotaged. Or is it? Your going 60 mph on the Hwy. Is the entity with you?  Is it going to jerk the steering wheel while you're driving? What does "Die KL" mean?  Is it Omen. These question rule your mind.  You become isolated mentally from your own partner because now you're witnessing and experiencing events she's not privy to. And when you try to fill her in or when there's spillage to where she does see some of it. She erupts into tears of her own. And guess who's sitting on a wall like spider-man benefiting?  

When the "Die KL" started appearing that's when I started putting 2 and 2 together.  Once we discovered the "Die KL" in the office and room more activity began to happen towards me vs. towards the house vs. towards my GF.  To this day my GF still doesn't know about the "Die KL" inside the car.  I think I finally clued her in on the "Die KL" on the lawn. Only because every now and then her son brings it up.  That cross you saw stabled on the wall?  Its missing. Its gone. Those religious objects you saw underneath the HD TV. There gone. That Big Black cross?  Thats the same cross my cousin gave me. The same cross that went missing for a week and returned in the washing machine while it was running- the weekend Capt. America came out.


Now I want to be clear about something before I close this story out. This true story out.  The entity be it a Poltergeist or Demon. I think we all can agree its malevolent.  And I believe its a Poltergeist. A Poltergeist thats tied to the land or building.  The reason why this malevolent entity does these things is to raise anxiety within the house. More importantly to raise anxiety between the house occupants.  Be it fear or anxiety both when raised provide fuel for the entity.  I'm not sharing the fact that this entity wrote "Die KL", or drew an "Upside Down Man" symbol, or took every cross in our house and put them upside down in key spots to make you think this all too Hollywoodesque to be true.  The entity goes through great lengths to make it too fantastic to create skeptics and doubters.  I smirk when people say something this active should be able to be captured on Video.  Videos can be faked just as easily as a video can be doctored. $99 worth of software can do the trick. A extreme level of intelligence, consciousness, and mischief making is at play here. Calculative on steroids is at play here.  It is true. All of it and more did happen. Its not happening now. Lets be clear. Its not happening now. But for about 8 months it happened everyday.  EVERYDAY. I'm not trying to  paint you an Apocalyptic picture. The picture I'm trying to paint is these things live and prey off fear and ignorance.  If I had less wits than I have now I'd be peeing my paints and loosing it. Doesn't make me special. Doesn't make my girlfriend special. It just makes us grounded.  They live off fear and ignorance.   The ignorance portion I want to talk about 1st because the more ignorance you have about these things the more level of fear you will develop. The entity knows this. Matter of fact its counting on it.

To most people an upside cross, burnt Bible, burnt cross is terrifying. And thats understandable. It to a degree it is. It's terrifying to us.  You try taking a shower and all of a sudden all the house alarms go off. You run to figure out whats going and something BIG, with mass, with density and gravity attached it runs right pass you - as it to suggest how little consequence you are to it.  Its invisible. You see a silhouette and outline or nothing but then again you feel the wind zip past you based on how fast its running by you.   Are you grasping the picture I'm trying to paint for you? But as equal as its terrifying the thing you have to do immediately when this happens is immediately put it in perspective.  Ask yourself why is it terrifying?  Its terrifying because Hollywood, Books, TV and movies therein and to some degree organized religion sells it as  terrifying.   More people are fearful of the water due the movie Jaws, more afraid of Sharks due a blockbuster summer movie that came out in the 70's. The shark that appeared 20 minutes at the end of the movie is ingrained in our psyche some 40+ years later.  The entity knows this. And by IT knowing this, our weakness we developed ever since man left the cave and began walking on two legs vs. all fours.  The fear of the unknown governs us.  The unknown or the fear of is at the root of most decisions being made. Usually the incorrect ones.  I've made mistakes living in this house. My GF has to. To error is human. But lets be honest if this thing wanted to kill us it could've killed us in our sleep.  It can't kill you.  It can make you fearful enough to make you kill yourself or your partner next to you.  It can make you suicidal. But its not creating those things. Those failures already exist for the entity to exploit.  If failings exists it will exploit and it will try to use it to raise the level of fear.  We're not special people (GF and I).  This has been scary, haunting and terrifying at times.  But the ignorance or the decisions, and loss of sleep we make due to ignorance is the realm of where these things thrive.  Seeing "Die Kl" or an Upside Down Man which means "a man has died, or means death" or better yet a burnt Bible or burnt cross while troubling, more so compelling than troubling  does not make me roll up into the fetal position.  If you're not rooted in truth but more so rooted in folk lore then yeah these  events will get the best of you.  Thats my reason for sharing this story. 

Regards

sorry for the length. No way to cut this story down to size that expanded 3-4 weeks.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 03:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people are suspicious in general quick to call out hoax and fraud when the information the see and read doesn't fill in the blanks for them. Evidence is a relative term.  Shown to 5 people you get 10 different interpretations. I posted youtube vids(exploit the channel) i posted the photobucket with 300+ photos: previous house occupiers testimony, pic of the female apparition, reports and notes from the paranormal teams investigating the house. I don't know what else to do. I will share my true account. My GF true account when the motivation and free time hits me.  As we use to say back in the day you can either take it or let it alone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 02:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You carry on and I will carry on. So carry on.....................exercise   your 1st amendment and I will exercise mine. Its obvious your level of knowledge about Poltergeists is minimal near 0. In your free time you might want to research more  and rise above the thrill seeker, arms folded mentally-mentality.  But I digress. Carry on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 21:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your observation to detail. These are questions worth asking because it allows me to expand on things we've seen.  Yes the images I drew are the creatures I call minions. When the activity was at it highest Oct-Feb 2014/15 those shadows would be seen out of the corner of my eye or in dark corners of the house.  They love hanging around the foot of the bed, arms of couches and love seats and under tables. They are very low laying and cling to the outer perimeters of the room.  Its my opinion based on experience that these  1-2 ft beings appear when a house is highly troubled, highly stressed and highly active with Poltergeist activity. They could've been spirits summoned by the former Native American people when this land was in turmoil with the US settlers.  They might be remnants from that era. Current situation is the dangerous activity has subsided. The Episcopal church performed a House Cleansing July 11th of last year - activity was subsiding at that point. Whats left now are the knocking, occasional Rapping sound, thud foot steps and poking and prodding while sleeping. Last week my garage door rose and let itself down by itself.  Paranormal teams off the east coast, CA and the UK are monitoring the house collecting new data. The things that's constant 24/7 are the wall taps, ceiling movement and pops and pings.  Through study we think we might able to get rid of it.  Maybe.  If its tied to the land this 10 year old house might always have some sort of activity. Great questions. Thanks for understanding and for allowing me to share. Need more info let me know. I have more to share but its hard determining whats of value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 20:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then you can kindly exit stage left.  Obviously you ignore everything else I said including the reason why or are stuck only one aspect.  Either way I could careless what u believe or dont. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 11:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Objective, subjective and relative.
https://app.box.com/s/lmero13u8x58h27rphc6i3rl8uimj6vy

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cMflNdqHayo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 11:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please!....see previous posts about what happened to the cameras.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cMflNdqHayo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 11:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it was or maybe it was rebooting doing a reconfig from a power loss. Obviously if I'm standing right about the cam I'm not doing the remote control of it.  But as I said before we bought cameras into the picture to try to catch the very thing you all question and seek i.e. evidence that increased the level of activity which included: cameras going missing, cameras being unplugged, cameras being thrown or destroyed or the electricity to the room or outlet the camera was in being cut. Those are the facts I'm putting forth.  Electricians have been to the house many times. There is nothing wrong with outlet or the wires behind the wall. No other electrical device has had problems when plugged in those same outlets.  That's my true story.  Whether you find that believable or plausible is TBD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 11:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beer bottle was Pacifico . Left over from my birthday party the night before. Bottles were placed in the recycle trash can in the garage the night before by my GF and I.  I was in my office on my PC and my back is turned to the TV and portion of the room the bottle came flying in.  I saw movement out the corner of my eye and heard a sound.  Like I said sometimes you hear the sound and even see something zoom by out the corner of your eye and hear the crash but the object is no nowhere to be found until minutes later.  This has happened more than once. Last time being Dec 2014. So yes in 2012, and 2014 objects flew forcefully in our house, Another indication of a Poltergeist.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cMflNdqHayo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 11:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the link to http://s299.photobucket.com/user/subject1320/slideshow/Stafford%20Way  When u execute the slide view remember you're looking at pics from 2015 to 2012. The slide show moves backwards in time not forwards.  And you're correct the only thing proof or evidence provided here does is start flame wars and activate the trolls.  I mean are the one's really requesting evidence deeply involved in paranormal research or do they just want to be judge and jury as to whats real? I have 0 time for them.  The reason why "WE" think its a Poltergeist is a cumulative facts gathered and patterns. I think we all can agree that its an angry spirit.   The Rappings, other taps, items missing, objects being thrown, wall markings, and electrical stuff.  Interviews with previous tenants who speak of similar stuff make a Poltergeist the likely culprit.  You're correct about both a highly emotional person and a collection of random negative energy that sort of becomes the entity. The later is the theory we believe most to be true. Based on what we know about the land underneath the house. The Native American history.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sammamish_people  and http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141219_112235347_HDR.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 10:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shawner unless you are the CEO of Reddit or own majority of the stock or better yet are God Himself I find it impossible for you to tell me what to do.  I don't owe you anything.  If you don't believe it. ignore it.  That's about the best advise you're going to get this early in 2016. There are plenty of other posts here to keep you busy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You hear the sounds first and the markings come later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 22:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hear the sounds first and the markings sometimes come later.

The bangs known as Rapping began occurring in summer/fall 2012. Pretty much the same time every night once the 1st one began. After a few weeks they'd even begin in the morning esp the weekends. Often waking us up.  This story below is  different: the experience is a little different. There are 3 types of noises we would hear 1. The banging known as Rapping( I later discovered that terminology) 2. Thuds - foot steps pacing back in forth. I'm a big guy. 6"5 1/2 250 lbs.  The thuds were louder than mine. We'd hear the thuds late night, early morning-hallway, bedrooms. Constant pacing. And 3) Loud wall taps. Different than the rapping sounds. Whats interesting about #1 and #3 phenomena is you can't trace the sound. You hear it but its hard to tell where its coming from directly.

One Saturday morning my girlfriend and I were trying to sleep in(sleep past 10am) House was active with sounds and movement.  Around 8am or 9am a series of wall tapping begin. They were loud and they felt like they were one room over.  They came in sets. TAP TAP TAP ( very loud)  Pause  TAP TAP TAP (Pause). One second they seemed far away. Other second they seemed real close. Finally enough was enough we got up and began our day. 

After an hour of being awake and in respective parts of the house. My GF call's me into the master bedroom. Mind you the noises stopped after we got up.

I walked into the bedroom and on my girlfriends side of the bed are the marks below.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140810_125338731.jpg

Now next to her bed and mine are night stands aka lamp stands etc. Its about a foot or less between the stands and our bed. I'm going to out on a limb and say those dents in the wall were not there before we went to bed. There very noticeable.  I believe almost 100% those dents were not there when we woke up.  We were hearing sounds yes. Loud sounds. Some felt close some felt very far. None felt like they were just inches from our bedside. No way we would've slept or stayed in bed that long.  

And the noises did stop when we got up.  I didnt know then but I know now because similar phenomena has happened since then.

That phenomena being we often would hear loud noises. Crashing sounds be it glass, pottery, objects thrown, furniture being drugged around, chains, etc and minutes later an object would appear broken or destroyed. An object sort of matching the sound we heard.

True Exampe.  I've been in my office and something out of the corner zips pass my eye and then there's a crash. I follow the direction of the glimpse and there on the wall is a new hole.  But where is the object that caused the hole?  GF and I look to and fro in the office a confined space mind you. Nothing out of the ordinary. We heard the crash. I saw what appeared to be an object zooming past. It impacted the wall. We search the office tooth and nail. Minutes later after giving up our search and resuming normal activity - the object appears. In a spot, plain sight. No way we could've missed. Its in a logical spot. There on the floor is a broken beer bottle or candle.  The nose of the beer bottle matches the dent in the wall. Matter of fact the residue from the wall is on the nose of the beer bottle.

Pics#1 is the  LOUD Tapping. 
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140810_125338731.jpg

Pic #2 is the dent in the wall. Office wall Dec 2014 where the bottle that caused it appeared many minutes later.  I saw it travel out the corner of my eye. But couldn't account for where it landed. The dent and noise were immediate.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141214_145351279_HDR_1.jpg
Hole caused by flying beer bottle. Bottle appeared minutes later.

The how interests me more than they why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was posting video evidence and got accused of trying to advertise my youtube channel. Here are some EVPS. 
https://app.box.com/s/kkh9v4mxjjob2qdbmr8v4d5xx0f9xryi
https://app.box.com/s/67mqd70e2634l6lmo3schwc11l9btq6o
https://app.box.com/s/67mqd70e2634l6lmo3schwc11l9btq6o

you tell me what they say and I'll reveal what a paranormal team who did these says what the evps are saying.

https://app.box.com/s/lmero13u8x58h27rphc6i3rl8uimj6vy

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-F9K0bvVa2s


real time video is far, few and in between because as I mentioned the entity would unplug the cameras, take them or out right destroy them. But occasionally we got lucky. And it was luck nothing special.  Exploit the channel I will answer all questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 05:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have provided a photobucket slide view of 300+ photos. In it includes the apparition itself, the paranormal teams involved, more Poltergeist fallout, and the statement of several previous tenants that lived in the house before us. If people are two lazy to go through that full album themselves then I dont know what else to say. I'm not out to prove anything. That effort is fruitless and brings little reward as most here are not in the position to help and help is not needed.  The activity has ceased for the most part. I'm just sharing accounts from 2012 up until now.  Trying to stay in the order of how the events un-folded.  "Show me the proof doesn't interests me." Sharing a true story does.  You can please some of the people all of the time, you can please all of the people some of the time, but you cant please all of the people all of the time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 05:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question, I will share that one soon.  it's going to really get dicey now because here on out every step we take to quite the house antagonizes the Poltergeist. Wasn't always that way things go from weird to CRAZY. Our first proactive step to simmer down all activity was Sagging. Did not have the result we were looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 19:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sincerely think you hope that. At least with me. I've noticed with some who read, or hear this story. Truth is sometimes stranger than fiction and this story if true brings up reality some people are not ready to face.  I wake up some days and I'm not ready to face it.  You're scared I get it.  You're thinking if what this guy is saying is true there where does that leave my belief system? Where does that leave God, Satan, religion, Ghosts, UFO's, Quantum Theory, History or the Universe, heck the history of man, etc.  What kind of person does that make me if what he is saying is true. Its a big burden to bear not knowing the unknown.  Where one fits in it all and should a person come wandering through with a story so surreal, so eerie that it must be a hoax. It has to be a hoax.  The world is full of people like you.  That's called denial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not but hurt. I just wish people had a more intelligent back in forth minus the accusatory/innuendo tone.  Advance not stagnate the dialogue. Just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's funny lol. Yeah a 3 year hoax.  that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist Activity Time Line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the activity in the house went from bangs, thuds, and missing objects to throwing objects and other damages. I began to keep a log and time line of events. This highly encourage within the paranormal community.  Its not complete. To be completed soon. December 2014 and all of 2015 is missing.  I'm hoping more astute eyes can see the bell curve here.

https://app.box.com/s/vjtcq6mg1za9ka8x61e87nuxb6sero33

It's an Excel file/format

Thanks

color field and icons indicate the frequency of events that month.

2012, 2013, and 2014 respectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 01:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can honestly say some of the darkest activity has come in the wee afters of 2 and 3am. We've been jolted awake by lamp and iron boards being thrown. Eyes bolt open due to the feeling of being watched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 01:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Built in 2005 which confuses everyone. How does a house so young become so active.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 22:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked at the DropCam you recommended. They are nice cameras. Not cost effective with a Poltergeist stealing and smashing things.  One factor I had to analyze and weigh before buying a camera was cost factor, setup and ramp up time, windows and phone app friendly and again cost factor.  Foscams go for $30 - $50 bucks tops on Amazon. Even less on Craigslist. It was not my 1st choice but due to cameras being stolen, destroyed and messed with the foscam makes it economical.  But I will keep my eye on the DropCam. They look good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question. i can honestly say the cameras moving by themselves are not the only things ever manipulated.  We've had TV's come on by themselves. TV's turn off by themselves. Channels change by themselves and TV's play by themselves with the TV being unplugged. That's not made up. That's 100% truth.  That same camera does the same movement after a reboot. so maybe the outlet it was plugged in lost power?  Thats happened to. Power has been lost to one room. One section of the house and one outlet off and on at times. Electricians, cable and phone companies come in and find nothing.................wrong.   That's all I'm saying.  Add this to objects being thrown, objects missing, writings, knocking, bangs, and tapping its text book Poltergeists.  We didn't come to that conclusion on day 1. ironically it took 2 yrs to reach that belief.  That belief came from more seasoned paranormal teams investigating the house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, markings in the office were drawn by the Poltergeist.  We didn't do this. And the house is well secure from the outside. All locks have been changed twice after moving in. You can see from the time line how soon we bought ADT in to secure the house. That was 2012.  The writing and scratches on the wall came immediately after we started putting up Christian themes and cameras.  Obviously from an IT point of a view the office became the command center for me trying to capture evidence and activity so the office became instantly the most active room in the house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 19:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah its touched me, my girlfriend-she's been scratched and friends who've come over and had their hair brushed, pulled or touched.  http://s299.photobucket.com/user/subject1320/slideshow/Stafford%20Way Slide show goes from 2015 to 2012 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 18:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that idea is being entertained among myself and the paranormal teams right now.  We're looking at the IT requirements and logistics of.  I can give you a user name and password and u can access my house now. I'm at work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, catch up. I googled many months ago. 2 plus years ago. Stop insulting my intelligence. I value my time above your own and I have no time to be sharing made up stories. The only reason I'm here is because researching led me here.  Yeah when the entity first drew the upside cross yeah my GF and I panicked. Who wouldn't?  But knowledge is power. So i went online and learned that a upside cross drawn by an entity could be a form of trickery. It wants us to think its a demon. It wants us to go down the wrong path of figuring it out. The more mistakes we make the stronger it gets.  The fact that it not me drew an upside down cross doesn't make the story less real. In truth it speaks volumes as to how real it really is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a Foscam camera Fi8910W  I believe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trashing of the house makes me mad which is a catch 22 really. because thats what the entity wants. It wants you to be angry and make ill-advised decisions. Like I said it destroyed my cameras and I went out and bought more cameras. It trashed my office setting me back a few days and I began to curse out loud and leave it little notes. All in all this makes the entity stronger and lash out more. Whats scary is when it lashes out when you're trying to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 09:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said it was Satanic? I said Poltergeist. And maybe the Poltergeist drew an upside down cross so you could be skeptical? Wise up. You're dealing with an intelligent entity that quite possibly is ages old.  It's obvious it's trying to use Christian lore, urban legend and cheap tricks to scare. Poltergeist feed on fear. I know what a upside cross means. I'm a Christian lol duh. But the entity might not know the depth of my belief system.  Wise up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 09:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tried all types of cams. Even the paranormal teams. Cams run off energy. Energy gets drained. Cams went missing. It takes the cams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 08:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everybody wants to arm chair quarterback.  Second guess. Second guess I agree till they live with something their suggestions are just theory. Truth be told I wouldn't wish this encounter on a skeptic. Almost but not quite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of course cameras were installed. But .....!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 05:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't fault individuals who ask where are the cameras. Where is the footage of all this activity?  Those are good questions. I suffered the same paradigm many of you suffer thinking cameras are going to work. Cameras are going to catch the ghost red handed. I was thinking the same thing. So when I went online and bought multiple cameras. But what you're going to find out hopefully from seeing the links below. Me buying cameras and digicams made the matter worse. Some even think I was playing into the Poltergeists hands.  View each link and read the foot note underneath.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140701_215834170.jpg
this is my office. After cameras were installed the office became the most active room in the house. This room had 2 cameras in it. You can see one camera still on facing the doorway.  The upside down cross on written on the carpet the entity drew not me. A second camera is missing. The printer that you cant see in this shot has 4 blank pages in it.  Which means the house or the room itself lost power.  each camera emails me when motion, or sound is detected. By the time I log into to view in real-time, the camera is offline. When they come back online the room is trashed. GF and I are at work.  ADT security alarm system is on not-tripped.
(That chair facing the TV BTW belongs in the kitchen FYI.)

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140701_215908768_1.jpg
same incident. I'm home now taking pictures. Office chair is split in half resting on a Bible. That Bible is now missing BTW

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140630_180152650_1.jpg
there use to be a camera siting on that table. Camera is gone. See the wiring? Couch is pushed backwards. One time the couch was upside down. Same story. Not at home. 

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140601_142938787_HDR.jpg
One camera out of eight that were mounted in the home. 24/7, motion and sound detect. That camera got unplugged, thrown around, went missing, returned and finally went missing . Its still missing.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140630_180350910.jpg
Same room the wall mounted camera was in. Master bedroom. See the book on the floor? Mom gave it to me to help deal with our problem. 

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140630_180323532_1.jpg
same masterbedroom. Different angle. Once again when cameras came into the picture. Activity spiked. 

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140729_221659152.jpg
Here's a good picture. The hallway. 2nd most active room in the house. You can see the camera on the floor. Everything you see sitting on the floor wasnt there originally. They were on the hall book shelf. Bible thrown down. Sage ash tray thrown down. Prayer documents thrown down. Clock thrown down. Camera thrown down. Bible is now missing. Camera is missing. Prayer documents missing. Sage tray missing. Clock missing. That step ladder. I'll tell u about the step ladder once I get into the paranormal teams coming to my house. But its been thrown a few times. 

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140729_221719639_1.jpg

Some where underneath all that mess is two destroyed cameras. One you can see sitting on the rubble. 

Now for the video where the entity is manipulating the cameras.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BsGic0oG7qk
We're asleep. This camera sits above the fire place in the living. Same living room above. If you look closely you can see a light not too far. That light is another camera in the kitchen.

We did lucky a few times.
This camera did catch the entity banging the door. We're asleep
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BsGic0oG7qk   Best with head phones as the bang is loud. The door does move inward. But as you can see no one is there.  

these videos are my first attempt of trying to capture whats going on.  I have the camera positioned in the hallway because previous nights that ironing board and can starch go flying. Instead the video cam captures the lights going off and on.  Summer/Fall 2012
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZE-BpTve31E

and

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DcAeKqGDlLc

Once again we tried video cams, we tried cell phones, we tried motion cams, and we tried hidden cams.  1st stage the camera was un-plugged, thats the Poltergeists warning shot. It gives one per camera.  When I plugged the cameras back in-the next day that cam was either gone or destroyed. As a parting gift the room the camera was in was turned upside down.  Like an idiot I bought more cams. Putting cams next to cams. Putting cams in vents, cabinets, in the foliage and etc. Doesn't matter. A Poltergeist can see through all of that. A demon especially.  Thats what I mean by our paradigm i.e. way of thinking. Its not these things sleep or are hidden and dont see when i walk in the house and begin installing cameras. Its proof of power is having the ability to just cut the power to the room the cam was in or to the house period minutes before activity broke out.

But I did get lucky a few times. And get some footage. Not the Holy Grail , but non-the-less footage.  Its not a kid breaking into the house. Its not my GF. Its not either of us sleep walking.  Its real and its its happening in more homes throughout the world everyday. Im just trying to come forth to share and provide what little info and experience I have with the hopes of bumping into others who experienced the same thing for the benefit of note taking.

More to come.

I'm sharing

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RdA1cvJf3S0




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantum Tunneling perhaps?  Good theory.  I'm entertaining similar thoughts based on my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its indeed creepy. I can't even get into the meat and potatoes of it yet because of all these troll detractors. But I will try. I wouldn't wish our 3 1/2 year ordeal on my worse enemy.  The only cool component to it all is watching the laws of physics get broken right before your very eyes.  Outside of that its pure hell in all sense of the word. People in the business of helping you say they want the Holy Grail before they get involved. The church takes its phone off the hook and wont move a muscle.  Friends and family say move, which seems logical accept for the fact what if it follows us.  This is a new house. We are new occupants living here. I can't fault the entity too much for doing what it does. Its a demon, Poltergeist or angry spirit. Its destined to do this stuff. I fault the human beings who ignore us and resemble some of these same skeptics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of being accusatory why don't you ask a question.  I promise you you'll like my answer better.  These boards are so clitche.  People are more interested in being right vs listening, reading and asking good questions.  Ive been dealing with this for 3 years and of course I got video and pictures.  But I'm trying to tell the story, re-live the account in a chronological order. You skeptics want the 2nd and 3rd truthful Act before the 1st Act is finished?  Is this how you act during a movie.  1,2,3,4, now with that out of the way....allow me to answer.  The events I shared and more lasted 4-5 months before cameras were bought in. 1st camera was a video camera.  It went missing. So I bought more cameras. Foscam IR/WIFI motion detect cameras - bought about 8 of them. Once those cameras got installed that's when the fun began. I would soon find these cameras unplugged or sitting upside down.  Naturally if they're unplugged I plugged them back in. GF wasn't unplugging the cameras-it became comical because soon I began buying cameras to watch the cameras. At this stage the Poltergeists has me chasing my tail.  Finally the cameras started coming up missing. If they weren't missing they were destroyed.

And by destroyed I mean just that destroyed. Broken, crushed, thrown up against a wall. Lenses and AC Adapter wiring ripped out. Like an idiot i simply bought more cameras. Amazon and Craigslist became my best friend. After that the entity started cutting the power to the room the camera was in.  I lucked up a few times and did get a little footage. But the footage I got is like 2% to the amount of time, energy, and money put behind each camera.  

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140729_221659152.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140630_182158530.jpg

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BsGic0oG7qk
In the dead of night the camera moves. Freaks out on its own 5:40 thru 7:15( about a 2 min weird session ) I've already gone to bed. May 2014. Late at night. We're asleep. Cameras tripping.

Now should I continue the story in the order of events happening or jump around all over the place making the true story more confusing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow somebody had too much caffeine this morning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is noway I can size this down to one paragraph.  So much was left out even with the current size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I understand its redditt and there are a lot of false stories on here. Mine is not one of them. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rlldSmE5T4  and https://app.box.com/s/nojwcs5mgwhq216t6q2x6977gf5sqlce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fr. Roy an Episcopal priest came on board and assisted as did paranormal teams from Maryland, Connecticut and Massachusetts. house is some what quiet. but thats happened before. Everyone's monitoring and observing. goal now is to loosen attachments on myself and others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cameras were setup spring, summer and fall of 2014.  When we put the cameras up the activity spiked.  Religious objects and cameras were placed out in the open and it didnt have the affect we wanted.  Activity escalated and things got worse. Some cameras went missing. Still our missing. Other cameras got thrown around after being unplugged. After about 7 months of trying. I put the cameras away. Just became too dangerious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Ghostwoods.  Popularity doesn't deter me. Its not like I can carry these conversations with friends and family. I mean where is someone to go but a community like this. Its so ironic that in a paranormal community that prides itself on believing in the unseen can at times resort to childish acts. I'm not deterred. If this entity cant run me out of my own house - then neither can total strangers online.  Most of what I'm sharing is past tense. Happened in 2012, 2014. Good teams are involved now and the house is being monitored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coming home to this became a everyday event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 07:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's one thing I could compare a haunting to, a malevolent haunting at that. A Poltergeist haunting. It would have to be the analogy of a plane coasting to the run way. That's how I would describe the actions of this story. Things happen very slow and then one day, all of sudden its suddenly all around you.  The first ignored signs were ( and I say ignored because ) early we're non-the-wiser about the subtle things happening around us. By subtle I mean on day one upon moving in we began to notice weird things. I mean we'd see something. Hear something and shrug it off. Going about our normal business within the new home we just bought.  What were some of the subtle things?  Subtle things like faint tapping sounds. Faint thuds. Faint movement that sounds like its coming from inside the wall. Leaving a room with the light on only to come back with the light off.  First few times you sort of scratch head asking yourself "why would I turn the light if I was coming back?"  After all I just went down stairs for a water refill.  Other subtle things include coming down stairs and finding a closet door open. Weird right?  Not really maybe my girlfriend left it open.  That happens for a few weeks and once again we keep shrugging it off.  Besides those subtle things I just mentioned you also start noticing items are coming up missing. Nothing earth shattering. my favorite coffee cup is gone. My GF hates coffee and no one else lives with us. Why is my coffee cup missing? A 30 minute search for it becomes pointless. No coffee cup anywhere. Then you begin to notice other things in and around are missing. Moved in the house with 20+ spoons and forks and now we have 5. Once again its only us living here and all of this within 4-6 weeks. Where is all the silverware.  You begin to question each other. Girlfriend accuses me of throwing away expensive silverware. I begin accusing her of loosing my coffee cup. Neither one of us has proof the other one is doing it.  But we deduce these events down to one another. After all no one else lives here.  In going back to the plane metaphor. At this stage the plane is now left the hanger proceeding backwards, about to do a turn around and head for the runway . Steady as she goes right?  We're still in the subtle phase. Finally you're in your bed sleeping. Its been a busy day. A busy week even and you and your girlfriend are pillow talking and while you're talking you think you hear tapping sounds.  You put your hand on your girlfriends shoulder and say "Sssssh, I heard something."  We both pause and wait. Nothing.  Minutes later we resume talking and minutes after that the faint tapping begins.  I hear it but I'm not ready to tell my girlfriend because I'm thinking maybe I'm just imagining things. Then all of a sudden she asks me "do I hear something?"  And I say "yes, you hear it" BUT soon as we both acknowledge it the noise stops.  Some nights it resumes. Other night it doesn't especially after we begin talking about it.  That happens for a few nights in addition to the other stuff mind you till one night before going to bed my girlfriend and I are both in the bedroom prepping for bed.  I'm sitting at the foot of the bed taking my socks off and etc. Girlfriends in the bathroom doing what girls do before jumping into bed. As she's walking out of the bathroom I'm about to lay in the bed when all of a sudden we hear the sound of doors closing.  There are four bedrooms upstairs. We occupy one of them. And out of the blue we hear the sound of three doors closing. Its almost as if someone is in the hallway going from room to room closing each door.  All 3 doors are within a few feet of each other.  I get up to look and see and all the doors are closed. But once again I can't remember if they were already closed to begin with.  We talk about it and go to sleep.  The plane is now made a 180 degree turn is just about lined up to the runway.  The hanger the plane rested in is hundreds of yards away  After a few more nights of weird stuff girlfriend and I go to bed and minutes later fall asleep.  Fast forward 8 hours later I get up and ready myself for work. House is a two story BTW.  30 minutes later I'm dressed.  I'm dressed enough to go venture down stairs and either make some coffee, throw something in the trash, grab my laptop brief case or what ever.  When I get down stairs this is what I see.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140521_171829096_HDR.jpg

every door on the 1st floor. Every cabinet door is wide open.  

We began finding our kitchen like this for several weeks and months in 2012, and coming home after work in 2014.

ADT security and motion and home monitoring in place 24/7.

No pets. No hole in the attic. No super squirrel or super raccoon.

With the flight tower clearing the plane for take off. The plane takes off.  Activity spikes here on out. The plane is airborne and gaining altitude.

The Poltergeists has fun run out of patience with us and upped the ante to where plausible denial can go to hell.  The games afoot and this story is 100% real.

Just thought I'd share one account out of many

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 06:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes cars can be haunted

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have a Ghost - Documentation is Key </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 06:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So theres one thing Ive recently realized is going to benefit the house occupant should he or she ever be faced with a home occupied by Ghosts. I use the word Ghosts loosely as the word Ghosts could apply to variety of things.  For this read well just say entity or entities plural.  The thing Ive learned that are important to an investigator entering your home is the need for good documentation. Documentation of events.

 The compliment I get the most from teams entering my home is the level of detail of which things have occurred. Be it a paranormal team, minister, clergy, Priest, Bishop or reverend the need for good documentation is important.  Most paranormal web sites if their worth their weight in gold should have a downloadable PDF or word doc questionnaire. The questions be they generic at times are important and should be filled out in earnest by anyone trying to get to the root cause as to what events if any are happening in their home.  The things Ive learned over time helps complete those questionnaires more quickly and efficiently is ones ability to keep good notes.

 There is a such thing of mediocre documentation and good documentation.  I humbly say do it good or dont do it all.  In dealing with the paranormal I cant over stress the need for good documentation.  So how do we define it?

 The process is both simple and complex.  Youve already asked the question.  Is my house haunted?  The answer immediately should be why do you think your house is haunted?  Whats happening to make you come to that conclusion? Or better yet maybe you havent reached that conclusion but need and want to. Guess what good documentation will help you sort it out.

 Obviously if youre having thoughts of your house being haunted  - there might be a governing piece worthy of setting up to reach yes or no conclusion.   Perhaps a Tier 1 level of deduction you want to sort out before escalating to Tier 2.  Tier 2 being any individual living outside the home that may be able to help you. In the realm of good documentation there is no such thing as too much information. After all the answer to your question might be days, weeks, or months away. How many of us can remember the subtle things happening in our home say last night?  Well try remembering the subtle things 3 months ago. Here is where documenting helps the most.

 Good documentation is simply keeping a record of weird things happening in your home you think may or may not be ghost related   (theres that word again).

 Here are my tips for documenting the paranormal or normal I should say.

What should I document?
 The rule for documenting has both a liberal and conservative approach to it.  Obviously there are many things in the home not worthy of documenting. The refrigerator re-filling the ice tray is one of them.  But if theres something in your home that makes you pause and by pause raise an eye-brow and have a mental thought as to what was that? if that what was that moment has happened more than a few times  it time to start documenting.  Keep in mind if you can rule it out with logic then strike through it labeling it a false-positive. In all practical purposes false positives will occur.  Theyre supposed to.

Why am I documenting? 
 Shouldnt the paranormal investigators document when they get here? To document means to trust your gut instincts. No one knows your home better than you. The human body can detect  an foreign object and go to work immediately ascertaining whats its purpose, friend or foe? If foe steps are auto-kicked to begin the removal process. Homes are the same way. Trust your 6th sense while at the same time dont give into paranoia
 Paranormal teams will always document when investigating a home. Those that dont  kindly show them the door. What helps them is your good record keeping. The ability to compare notes. Ascertain and troubleshoot are more paramount than ever before.  As human beings we tend to forget things rather quickly. Things with little consequence early on get over written memory wise by other current events. We keep documents i.e. journal, diary, log keeping to assist us later on.  In a field where one size never fits all, good documentation is probably the most not sought after constant within the realm of paranormal investigations. If a team is not going to sit down and go over the events youve documented before, during and after they start their investigation once again kindly show them the door.

What does documenting consist of?  We dont know what we dont know
Since were talking about the paranormal pretty much anything and everything. Remember think conservative and liberal.  Ex. if you hear a loud BANG of unknown origin not only should you document the bang itself but equally important is the time of the bang, the day of the week the bang occurred, where were you when you heard it. Where were others in your home when the bang occurred.  How loud was it ?(use a scale of 1-5) and assign a number value.  What were the events prior to the bang?  What were the events after?  Are you starting to get the idea?
 In June  July of 2012 in my house loud bangs would begin at 8:04. Not 8:00pm But 8:04pm. It took me weeks before I realized that.  Interestingly enough by the time I realized that and updated my record keeping the bangs started an hour later and got louder. Those particulars are extremely important. Most never make sense right then and there but trust me, someone investigating your case later on will regard your documentation as the notes of Mozart.  It takes time, effort and dedication.

Who should be documenting events in my home? 
 Good question. Easy answer. The adults of the home. If something is happening in your home that causing you to raise questions, wake up in mid sleep, retrace your steps, constantly ask your spouse if he or she turned off the lights to a room you was just in then the one documenting might as well be yourself. The need and will to document is not for everyone.  Me personally I love documenting. Im a IT project manager and documenting and the importance gets drilled into us from day one. Just ask the PMI organization.  That being said no one should go it alone. If others in your house are witnessing and seeing stuff then its important you document their accounts.  I have one word thats important to you if you are to take up the task of documenting. Verbiage.  How its being talked about is exactly how it should be recorded.  Remember that cop show called Dragnet?  I love it when that lead detective would take down notes from the witness and his tag line which became famous was just the facts maam , just the facts. If your son saw a little green man walk across the room while going to the bathroom how he reports it should be how you record it.  Remember the noise being heard is whats being documented there is no such thing as noise (too much info) in good record keeping.

Different Types of documenting
 Now when one says documenting one immediately might think that applies to just writing stuff down and youre right it does. Nearly 90% if not more of good documentation requires pen and pad. Or does it?  Ladies and gentlemen behold the 21st century and the era of the smart phone. Pen and pad is great but lets face it those items can go missing just as quickly as a your missing set of car keys which if it did go missing better be logged in your documentation.  Where was it taken?  When was it taken?  When was it last seen?  What was it last used for?  Who touched it last? Etc.  So to prevent the documentation of evidence from becoming evidence theres something you can do.  Electronic documentation. Technology will become your best friend if you but knew how easily accessible it was. Its all around us now.   The best form of documenting electrically is emailing yourself.  Email accounts are free to setup. Within minutes you create a Gmail, Yahoo, or Outlook account and youre in business. All 3 can be accessed from a smart phone and guess what when you email yourself or anyone for that matter there are multiple time stamps taking place. Make sure to document within the email the actual time the event occurred and send email to self. Reason for this some networks have lag and the time stamp shown in your inbox might not be exact time the event occurred. Remember you want to be concise as possible. If a light went off at 10:15pm dont round up or down. Log it as Example light went off and on at 10:15pm Tuesday, was baking cookies, weather is clear, 54 degrees outside, 68 degrees inside. Why is everything I just listed important?  What if the lights going off and on is a weekly thing?  Every Tuesday at 10:15pm the lights go off. Well I doubt you bake cookies every week let alone at 10:15pm but if youre like me youre going to forget the time you actually was baking cookies once 7 days have passed.  But an investigator combing your logs or maybe even you combing over your own logs notice a pattern of the lights going off at the same time once every week. On Tuesday. Last week you was baking cookies.  This week you was..balancing your check book at the kitchen table. The week after that at 10:15pm you was folding laundry. But guess what at 10:15pm the lights didnt go off.  And by lights I mean a particular light down stairs.  Is it starting to make sense now?  The reason for good record keeping is for you and I to rule out events in the home being paranormal. 99.9% of all events are not paranormal. But keep in mind while youre attempting to rule out something you might be ruling in something. One of you reading this will be that 1%. And if you are, good documentation will be important.
 Now here is where some of you reading this will part company with me.  But to the home occupant stay put and dont go nowhere.

 There are some in the paranormal field that say documentation is not evidence.  Guess what?  There wrong. Not only are they wrong these investigators you never want near your house. The need for documentation has several components attached to it. The first component is the obvious one which most paranormal investigators will agree with. Ruling out the obvious. There a trillion different things happening within a home that when revealed to some people might cause them to suspect ghost activity.  If you just came back from seeing the latest and greatest scary movie at the local Regal cinema you might want to delay documenting your home for 6 months. J/K LOL

 Just saying. The purpose of documenting is to determine whats home grown i.e. house noise, people noise, tree noise, dish washer trying to tell you its about to die, etc. Those things be they man made, human made are not going to escalate. They plateau immediately.   The second component to documentation is capturing the things that are not man-made. Those things be it paranormal (but we dont have enough to go on yet) tend to escalate and repeat themselves.  There are two words worth remembering here. Trend Analysis.  Study those words for a second and incorporate it with two other words: Common Sense.  The best evidence of all is common sense. If a chair slides across the floor. By all means document the occurrence but guess what youre no longer living in the do I have a ghost in my house phase  The ghost just answered your question. Congratulations youve entered a new phase. Might not be the phase you was hoping but congrats non-the-less youve reached it.

 Be your culprit a Ghost or human. Good documentation is going to reveal  one or the other over time.  Documentation is evidence - it is the precursor, the preamble and the index to what is or what isn't happening in your home.  Let no one tell you otherwise.  Is it the Holy Grail evidence?  No such thing. But once again depends what you documented. All evidence is relative. Some will find value in what you documented. Some will say its hog wash. Experience has taught me those that find value in documentation i.e. your documentation are in fact the ones worthy of being in your home.  90% of Paranormal Investigative work is labor intensive. There are no short cuts.  Combing through pages and pages of written material is equally as important as walking down a hallway with a voice recorder.

 Remember the decision to document is for you if you already have begun the thought process of suspecting weirdness in the home. It could be a raccoon in the attic. Maybe it is . Maybe it isnt. Time will tell. If its a raccoon what have you lost? Ill conclude with one final example. If you have guests over and a guests walks up and tells you they keep getting the feeling of something pushing or brushing their hair. Is that evidence? Should it be documented?  Tic toc tic toc.  The answer is yes.  Once again liberal   conservative actualities must be weighed in conjunction with common sense. If youre child has been telling you the same thing for weeks  definitely document it. And if youre like me  email your friend days later and kindly ask them to re-live that moment. Get their verbiage in email form.  The thing I noticed about activities escalating in the home is #1 their unpredictable. You, me, us, aka the house occupant are usually the last to know when activity is escalating. But I challenge anybody to go back and review their good documentation and not see the trend of where the activity is spiking.

 Wont make sense now but if you are the 1% that has paranormal events in your home.  Good proactive documenting will go a long way. Good teams find it useful

Thanks

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/House_Home_Chair/April%202014%20Paranormal%20Team/IMG_20141222_112800614.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miss Cross (Gone for a Week) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 08:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 07:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update is several Bibles are still missing. The Virgin Mary statue and the holy water a Priest gave us is missing.  All of this was last summer and last fall. The theory believed now based on the history  of the land and some of the wall marking which are Native American in origin is Christian themes , and symbols upset this demonic or Poltergeist whose roots are Native American.

Bothell WA has a rich but troubled history with the local natives. Especially back in mid 1800's.

Each time we erect a Christian symbol for protection we're in a since challenging or double daring the Poltergeists, or evil spirit.

Last House cleansing ( exorcism ) by an episcopal priest was July of this year.

So many items are missing I doubt we'll see them again. Perhaps the future tenants will. 

http://s299.photobucket.com/user/subject1320/media/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140729_221659152.jpg.html?sort=3 o=299

religious objects and sage tray all thrown and trashed on the floor. Both tray and Bible are now missing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
