<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1055</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beau Bokan - something a little different! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 07:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 06:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Biffy Clyro - Woo Woo](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zaVw8MH9b_c)  --  This one is just so upbeat and the lyrics are really positive in a sort of "I want to be better, and change" sort of way, I love it.

[A Plastic Rose - Move Islands](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=camt5xswP-s)  --  This is so good, it's positive in a more "I CAN DO ANYTHING BECAUSE I AM FUCKING FANTASTIC." way!

I love them both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 03:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I used to love it, but I just finished secondary school, and I studied that album for three years as part of my music class. Honestly studying it just made me resent parts of it. Whenever I hear 'When I'm 64' I get serious Vietnam style flashbacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 01:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Bonham's groove, but yeah, the rest of it kinda sounds like a mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](https://i.imgur.com/cypiiZO.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 23:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god I'm the exact same. It just brings the whole thing down after some really creative verses, ugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 23:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would appear so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 21:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always felt guilty about The Beatles always being a "Greatest Hits" sort of band for me - just whenever I listen to an entire album I usually finish it having really liked about two thirds of the songs tops. Musical blasphemy probably, but hey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an album that is outstanding, but one or two weak tracks hold it back from being perfect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is an interesting sort of discussion. For me, it's Anathema's 'Weather Systems'. It opens incredibly strong and every song is filled with emotion and power and amazing composing, and the final track is, for me, basically the official theme song of frisson. It's just incredible. But there is one of the tracks that just doesn't sit well with me, it doesn't flow nearly as well as the others for some reason; The Storm Before The Calm. I honestly think it's only an alright song, which is disappointing because I consider every single other song on the album to be incredibly strong, both musically and lyrically. 

Does anyone else have albums like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so happy this whole idea worked out. I can't imagine the feeling that the guy who organised the whole thing must have gotten when everyone started playing in sync, let alone the feeling when Dave responds. In Italian. Because Dave Grohl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 06:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's definitely not a bad actor. He was great in Foxcatcher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 06:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think bringing Taylor Kitsch back would be great, if it was done really well, and more true to the character; like what's being done with Ryan Reynolds and Deadpool. He suited the character really well, just had an awful script. 

If not, I think Josh Holloway would be absolutely perfect, though he's nearing 50 so that might be a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 00:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Enjoy!](https://vimeo.com/39447511) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anna Kendrick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 00:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anna Kendrick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 23:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 18:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, if anything, I'd say we're sick of the past. Bands like Of Mice and Men, We Came As Romans and now BMTH are trying to revive this early 2000s, nu metal/ hard radio rock sound, which died over a decade ago - I don't see it as a 'bad evolution' of these bands sounds, really; I see it as a devolution (pretentious word of the day yay). The thing the annoys me most about people who pride themselves on being "accepting" of the new styles of these bands is that they attack people who aren't happy with it in comment sections by saying things like "these people can't accept change!"/"let the band grow!"/ "nothing new will ever come about in music if bands don't change!". I hate this, because I welcome change, I really love it a lot of the time. I thought Bring Me The Horizon's change from the Suicide Season sound to the There Is A Hell sound was fantastic, I thought Architects changes, first to a more melodic sound, followed by a heavier, groove sound were both great. I love blessthefall's change to a more serious, darker sound on the last couple of albums. 

So I think it's bullshit when people say we can't accept change. Like, no. What is happening, in my opinion, with things like the new BMTH songs isn't change, it's borrowing a dead sound that most people were happy to see dead. It's especially disappointing with Bring Me because they've proven how innovative they can be with their melding of Post Rock and metalcore on There Is A Hell. I never liked that early 2000s sound, and don't like it now; I don't think that means I'm stuck in the past, really. If anything, I would say Bring Me and OM M and the others are a bit stuck in the past if they're so eager to bring back the sounds of their adolescence, rather than forging a new sound!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 05:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the book I'm most looking forward to reading, as I remember finding the movie pretty bland and lifeless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 22:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the exact same with Lupin. He didn't seem, I don't know... cool enough I guess? In the movies, I mean. He just looked like an ordinary teacher and just rigid in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When reading the books, which character did you imagine most differently (in the way they came across; looks, voice etc.) to the interpretation of the character in the movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 20:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, as I'm actually properly reading the books for the first time since seeing all the movies years ago and finding that I'm picturing some characters a lot differently to how I first saw them in the movies. Like, I remember what Victor Krum looked like in the GoF movie, but as I'm reading him, I'm imagining him much differently - just the way he comes across, I'm picturing a sort of lanky, but strong, awkwardish guy (as described), who comes to life on the pitch. He also has longish hair and a badass beard. (I think beards and long hair are cool on characters that are supposed to be really cool idk)

Also, the obvious thing of Harry's hair, how it'd described as persistently messy in the books, but it's perfect in the movies. I definitely imagine it differently in my head as I'm reading.

Who did you find yourself picturing differently to how they are in the movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're in a movie together that's shooting at the moment, I think. But who knows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She probably felt uncomfortable or embarrassed. Her band Candy Hearts isn't that big and she knew she was playing in front of hundreds of thousands when you include the live stream, and honestly she sounded pretty bad, so I'd imagine she wanted to just get out of there as fast as she could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 04:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear lord, that silence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 23:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hozier seems to be doing quite well so far! Let's hope he goes down in history as more of a Rory Gallagher or Phil Lynott, and less of a Bono or O'Connor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 23:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube commenters will be YouTube commenters, I guess! (that is, they'll be ignorant hate filled children about most things)

But I'm sorry for bringing back memories of this show if I did when I posted it here, if those memories made you feel shitty - but thank you for being so gracious about it in retrospect! Your mindset of positive learning and perseverance is always appreciated so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A younger Jonah Ray booing a younger Chris Hardwick on Web Soup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 08:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 08:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awh they sound great, sucks they're not there anymore. What was his Singled Out accent like? I don't remember it being vastly different, other than him seeming to have trouble pronouncing his "s" sounds, always making them sound like "sh" sounds... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 08:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did Mandroid a few years back, there's a few clips on YouTube I think! Other than that, I'm not sure. I know he's been touring new material the last couple of years, but it's definitely strange how little footage there is of his stuff online, considering how much he performs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Johnny Cash's album "American IV: The Man Comes Around", which contained his famed cover of Nine Inch Nails' "Hurt", was his 87th album overall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 08:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 06:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you could hear the cheers when he came on pretty well, and Chris' reactions to the first jokes not going too well makes it clear that the audience wasn't really too into it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 04:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (it's a little hard to watch in parts at the beginning but I don't think it's representative of his stand up overall obviously yup) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Hardwick stand up from 2010 - not many videos of Chris doing his stand up out there, so I thought I'd share post this one here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 04:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 01:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two Afterman albums by Coheed and Cambria together. There's not a song on there that I don't adore, and there is such a wide range of influences, it's incredible. By the time you finish it, you already miss the first few songs so you just go back. It's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 01:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ilan Rubin. He has such an incredibly unique style, both sonically and visually, and has played with bands like Paramore and Nine Inch Nails all while doing his own solo project, which is something I aspire to be able to do in life.

Also Josh Eppard from Coheed and Cambria, and Bonham, of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 01:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Justin Foley is hugely underrated, such a solid player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 00:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I said "not that that is definitely not what happened, it's just a sad thing to think". I don't think that is what happened, but it might have been, and the thought that it might have been is honestly a bit upsetting to me.

And yeah, that's plausible too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trivium release mysterious interactive teaser for upcoming Seventh album </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 21:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just out of curiosity, what was the general reaction when the first songs off Sempiternal were released? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 20:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Shadow Moses was the first, followed by Sleepwalking. I'm just curious because of how intense the reaction to the new songs are, if anyone can remember how they felt when the first songs since There Is A Hell came out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 20:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a depressing notion to think that they forced themselves to write in the style that they found was most popular based on internet views. Not that that is definitely what happened, it's just a sad thing to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 15:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss Jona. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 15:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually yeah, the synths give me a kinda Crossfaith vibe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 14:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was thinking too. It'll just be awkward and weird. I'm guessing Jordan will just hit a sample from the song or it'll be backtracked, and Oli will do his crowd hype thing or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 21:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one thing that I really hope I'm proven wrong on. Maybe the whole album will sound better as a whole listen together, I haven't given up hope yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 21:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, right in between these two styles is the sweet spot. There Is A Hell nailed it imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 21:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that so many people started copying his tattoo designs, and he just wasn't fond of them as he got them when he was very young for the sake of it, so he blacked them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 21:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/4WNQ4ac.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 21:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that chorus melody sounds a lot more like [Crooked Young](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=niGZ1nrVwqE feature=youtu.be t=52) imo, but a lot of it is very familiar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Throw me to the wolves" line was also in the chorus of Hospital For Souls. I'm not suggesting Oli's recycling ideas, but it's just strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This and Crooked Young off Sempiternal have [very similar choruses](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=niGZ1nrVwqE feature=youtu.be t=52). Just thought it was interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may not be a metalcore song, but it's relevant to this sub's interests as Bring Me have released some of the most popular metalcore albums ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely makes sense! Like if it was on in the background I wouldn't turn it off, but it's weird coming from them. Just feels off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely phenomenal! (if you're a Linkin Park fan)

But seriously, it's very bland imo. This will probably sound horribly pretentious or whatever but it just sounds a bit unoriginal. The chord structure is used in *everything* and there's nothing very interesting going on. That video teaser was very misleading, there wasn't a single scream that I heard.

Overall, I'm very disappointed. I really hoped this would be the one to bring people back in, but honestly I prefer Happy Song. And I don't even like Happy Song that much. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring Me The Horizon - Throne (new) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complacency, I guess. Sempiternal did amazingly critically and commercially and they know anything they put out will sell. Like just look at the articles, they literally googled "amazing studios" and chose the first one to make the album in, and they spent half the budget on quad bikes. Also putting Drown on the album, like seriously? All that and Jordan on twitter being aggressively smug just suggests they've gotten cocky and haven't put as much heart into this one, but honestly I'm making a lot of assumptions and maybe it'll turn out good idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 19:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically they wanted a departure from the sound of the "Jimmy era", and wanted to tap into nostalgia and go for a more early 90s Metallica, Iron Maiden, classic metal sort of sound. Because of this, they basically forced Arin to tone it down to the point where he was literally just playing AC/DC and Black Album Lars Ulrich style beats on nearly every song. It was just silly and made for a very bland sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 19:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This can't have been an easy decision for him, he's probably well aware that it's unlikely he'll ever find a job as a musician that would be as steady and pay as well as being the drummer in a stadium band like Avenged. But I think he did the right thing; choosing creative freedom over financial stability. I honestly applaud him. He's a fantastic player and was completely under utilised on HttK for completely idiotic reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 19:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lots and lots of disappointment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 18:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think [this](https://twitter.com/Popvpxnk/status/624250286467629060) tweet just about sums it up. Note Jordan's "lol" reply. They really don't seem to give a shit. Maybe they've just gotten over confident after Sempiternal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 18:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly holding onto hope that they're fucking with us. This can't be real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 18:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't right now, sorry, just search "Memphis May Fire AMA" and set it to show results from the last week and it should show up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bono misinterprets sign with "SF" written on it at 1987 U2 show in San Francisco as standing for Sinn Fin, goes on heated anti-IRA rant (classic Bono) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 00:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 22:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, it made me so mad. Like, of fucking course they would use depression/anxiety as an excuse. These illnesses can do terrible things to a person, but they can't turn you into a slut shamer or an arrogant cock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 22:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly doubt it. In the case of many paranoid schizophrenic episodes, there's a series of coincidences and they occur around someone who's prone to the illness and paranoia, so they manage to delude themselves into believing in some sort of hidden truth or conspiracy. Everything he said is far too unlikely and it doesn't sound credible, but no one can say for sure. It'd make a hell of a story if some of what he said turned out to be true though, you can be sure of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Lowe, guitarist of the progressive metalcore band After The Burial, has been found dead weeks after a public mental breakdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 21:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new New Found Glory video! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hnnnngggh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I wouldn't take it so literally dude. It's just the way it builds really gradually and all, it's really climactic y'know? Obviously it's not "one night stand, in and out" sort of music, it's more serious I suppose. Just thought it'd be nice to post something a bit different! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. They definitely don't seem like the sort of band that has a great sense of humour, they seem to take themselves very seriously, maybe a bit too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's acting like a child. None of this is a race issue. Her video just wasn't up to the standard of the others, in the eyes of those deciding the nominations, and that's perfectly respectable. I mean, come on, Kendrick is nominated once for his own video, and a video from another artist he's in is nominated too. Bruno Mars is mixed race, and Beyonc is African American. 

It is seriously reaching to try to make this about race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This comment on the Memphis May Fire AMA, and knowing they actually read it, made me very happy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/Qi4CYyD.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BASS FACE - ESTE HAIM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Murphy - Sunshine (Adagio In D Minor) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plug it out and put the plug in the shed in your back garden. Or if you don't have a shed, thrown it behind a table, or somewhere where it would take a lot of effort to get it back. I also put a piece of paper on my monitor with one of those signs that basically says "don't use", I'm not sure what the term is, but it has that symbol thing. You can do it, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Found Glory - Vicious Love (feat. Hayley Williams) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 15:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 03:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edgar Wright's Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](http://www.gofundme.com/griffinrocks) the gofundme page. Such a terrible tragedy, R.I.P. Griffin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens all too often. I'll go on the computer to check some information for an essay I'm writing, and then I'll find myself twenty minutes later deep into /r/fantheories telling myself I absolutely *need* to know everything there. The best solution to not getting distracted on the computer is to not go on the computer at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't go near my computer yesterday, and it was my most productive, stress free day in a very long time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 02:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just decided to try it, as I'd had a pretty terrible couple of days before hand, a lot of it to do with being on the computer and what generally goes along with being exposed to the infinite escapism-hole that is the internet. I ended up having a really productive day, doing a lot of chores I wouldn't usually have the energy or will to do, and being more creative than I had in ages, writing a lot of music and being productive in other creative ways. I ate really well too, and didn't fap. But most importantly, I went to bed without a sense of shame or guilt for having wasted the day - I felt refreshed and a bit proud that I managed to pull myself away from the thing that consumes so much of my time and thought. I slept better than I had in ages, because I didn't have all this build up energy from sitting in front of the computer and not being active all day. 

I'm sure I'm not the first one around here to find that going a day (or longer) with no computer/internet is very helpful, but I thought it was worth posting if only just to urge people to just designate one day a week to going completely without your computer or internet, except for the minimum you might need for work or school. It seriously can do wonders. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, their setlist immediately following Sempiternal were about 75% songs off that album, so I'm not too hopeful. But Reading is a bit before the official release, so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very true. Daybreaker and LT/LF together could be considered an absolutely amazing comeback from a bit of a weird point in their career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I find it nearly impossible to write when I'm really up because (not to sound cheesy) it's pretty much a kind of escapism for when I'm down and need to get shit out a lot of the time. Having said that, Oli seems to be a lot happier recently (getting married and in shape and all that), and I had really been hoping he would try to draw on some of that, or at least some of the more specific things surrounding that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 00:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe they said something like "If our younger selves had heard Drown, they'd have been furious! We wrote it because we'll be playing Wembley and wanted something that would really come to life in a stadium, it isn't representative of anything on our next album." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 23:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even a top 30 metalcore band? I disagree. They are one of the most popular bands in the genre by far, I'd argue that they're easily top 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring Me The Horizon's "Happy Song" music video coming this Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 17:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Orlando Bloom in his Legolas days would have been perfect. Has that defined look, with nearly feminine features, but still very handsome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 13:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
