<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7624</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the fountain of youth. Medicine is improving every day, but I doubt I will live to see or use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen one, but I am afraid of getting one. I actually have practiced it in my head, how to turn a poor fellow down without shaming him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of fighting. That is, we went through our ups and downs, and stuck it out. We've seen the best and the worst of each other, and decided that each other is worth it. Now we barely ever fight at all, and have never been happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japanese. I've always liked the sound of it, and it's so deep. As a native English speaker, I'd happily give up being able to speak English if I could speak Japanese at the same level I've mastered English now.     
But I suppose the grass is greener, right? So if I were a Japanese speaker, I'd probably be saying the same thing about English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A purring cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever my tummy starts growling. I usually subside on water and coffee until then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, you chose a picky topic. Well, I'll weigh in. I'm a chick, for the record.     
    
I think that when it's determined the chick is pregnant, the dude should have a say in what happens next. He can cast his ballot to keep the baby. But if they're not married (and therefore have no legal binding to each other as a family unit), then the power to choose goes to the mother. Ultimately, it's her body.     
    
However, if the woman chooses to have the baby but the man doesn't want it, the dude shouldn't be financially obligated to it. He should probably be obligated for half the cost of an abortion, but nothing more. It's not fair for the woman to have a say over 18 years of the dude's life if she chooses to play mom.   
    
But that's just my personal take on it. There are plenty of other issues / situations / opinions out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That if there is a God, He doesn't give a rat's ass about me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-reading their titles to find spelling mistakes before posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toothpicks. Already do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myself get rich enough to pay for the time when we can finally rejuvenate our youth again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Automat removed me again, huh?" or "who did I piss off this time? Better ignore it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe once every two weeks if I have to. Usually for a date or because I need to wear something semi-formal / office attire. I don't have a suit, but for some reason jeans and a collared shirt works as long as I wear heels. I hate heels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being near children. I just don't like them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask a political question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Judge not, lest ye be judged." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised that so few people in the US use the word "fortnight." They still use it in the UK, and I have never heard such a nice, concise way to say "two weeks." I use it despite it being a little odd and fancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely nothing. No one reasonably famous was even born on my birthdate. People who are born on my birthdate inevitably come to nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "adorbz" or any variation of misspelt crappy-ass text talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. It was great up until the "I'm going commando on y'all" sequence. I was going to add it to my collection of DVDs until then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like that film until the ending, actually. It looked so cheap to me, filmed in one location with B or C-level actors and a predictable collection of stereotypical dopes stuck in a predictable location. The end was pretty badass, though. Turned around my perception of it being a cheap movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd pay back all debts, put half into savings, and use the rest to make movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
