<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject72</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is one of the most aggressive Reinhardts I have ever seen in my life. He even left the payload on OT once because he wanted to 'Make a play', the timer burnt out and we lost because of that.                  But thank you for your time. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 12:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this an actual bot?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 12:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is he plays A LOT. And when he isn't, he watches twitch streams (Many pro reins). He is well rounded, but is kinda shit with rein vs rein situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I am so used to not meeting others in team chat and so I do not switch from group. Apart from mid masters up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 09:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ThisServerWillSurvive2017*
2016 was a crazy year, and hopefully this server will survive whatever 2017 throws at it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expect a lot of puns out of this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 06:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get disconnected randomly without being able to REJOIN. I even got kicked out of a SERVER to install the Oasis update. It especially frustrates me when I get kicked in the beginning of a match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 06:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really flexible with my hero picks. But mostly supports/tanks. I would really suggest you to play roadhog in silver, because there aren't a lot of reinhardts over there and you can easily land hooks. Good luck tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 06:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your hero picks might be the reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This issue costed me over 500 SR. This is fucking unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother and daughter slaughtering a pig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 06:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know. But Lassiz's view d.va was on point. Although I really think something was wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, many characters have evolved. But going from 'Raiding undiscovered lands and benefitting Kattegat', to 'Raiding lands and become famous/well-known' is kind of an odd way to evolve for a character like Ragnar.

And idk you might be right. But after all he is dead, and we'll never find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's the case...then why was Ragnar talking about how he would be in Valhalla after his execution?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I do agree that the show is sometimes weird with their sequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Seer did warn Bjorn that Ragnars arrival would bring chaos to Kattegat. Plus Ragnar visited Lagertha, talked to her and even kissed her whilst ignoring Aslaug the whole time. This indicates that Ragnar loves Lagertha. (Plus he wanted to see her before he 'dies', because he said that he'll travel to England to die. I also believe that Lagertha wants to kill Aslaug because she saw her performing some ritual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thnx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try, but I don't think they will be able to help. Fuck the points, I just want to bring up this issue to the community/blizzard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 points gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way as you. But I still fucking love the show. In short: The show went from historic accuracy + action to having more freedom with changing historic events and adding a shit ton of drama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
