<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan on killing a week at least out there, any tips for schoomizing it up with the locals and not coming off as an American douche ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've currently traveled from the southern tip of Mexico, California, Oregon, and Washington. I want to tackle the western portions of Canada, with Alaska not far after.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors of western Canada, what areas should I not miss while visiting on vacation ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe in god, but I don't believe in humanities ability to interpret god. Religion has failed is, find god in the earth and the actions you choose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pants off, if my girlfriend is home I chase after her ass and love her to death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blood sir, if things get worst this wont be a question but if we break into civil war between the right and the left this will be the costly mistake that we have made in some time. 

The blood price will be high.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fry's has a staff of cashiers that do not know their products well and a price match policy that is easily exploited. I price match something I don't care about that is marked down at an insane price in cash. Come and return it for store credit without a receipt and they give me full value of the product worth of store credit. I built my pc for pennies because of this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electricity, we have enough nuclear understanding and material to power the worlds electrical needs for thousands of years. But instead we forge nuclear weapons and stock pile them.

Instead of free energy we have enough destruction capabilities to obliterate earth several dozen times over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ? The other day we were walking to our car from a sushi joint and there are two cars in the parking lot. Ours, and a four door with three duds being loud and sketchy. 

I told her to get behind me, I keep a four inch utility knife on me almost everytime I go out. We just got done having a disagreement over whether she should do the same. She made the point she didn't want to learn how to cut someone and she'd probably end up getting her own knife used against her.

We ended up getting out of there without issue but if something had happened it would have been 3v1 instead of 3v2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So.. how exactly does a white man come to the conclusion that he is black from birth without any other source to support that ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me a 28 Days Later rage virus in a vile and buy me a ticket to the super bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 8ish, I took a trip to mexico to visit family and friends. I don't believe in ghosts so I write it off as some jack ass being a freak. But outside on the street around 3am I awoke to to a horse drawn cart slowly clopping by. There wasn't much light but i could tell it was a man and he was old, and pretty tall. He was dragging chains.

I woke up my aunt to ask and get her to see. She told me it was the devil looking for souls, and that I should go to bed. I slept on the carpet in their room after that on top of some of my blankets.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> suicidal thoughts can some times stem from a lack of loved ones. I'd normally agree but I don't know this persons situation. You know ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment some delusional jack ass leaves a fresh steamer on my front lawn they are getting the hose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... even then.. if I have to refer to this individual that is now a woman. Even though they were once a man, if they pursue a relationship with a woman, isn't that gay ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't step into the minds of the persons in question. But it can some times feel a little like playing pretend,  you know ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well by your definition of a transgender that would mean that the white person was never actually black to begin with. They feel black so they adapt to the culture they feel is fit. And I don't mind people pinching from cultures here and there, play ball. 

But when the census statement comes around, and you have no actual lineage saying that your any kind of black. Than there is an issue. Maybe ?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just trying to get little bites about how the general population feels about it. But every time I bring it up it's like I walked into the trigger section of a gun store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I have no Asian lineage than I have no real stake in how that culture actually operates. I'm just imitating what I've seen in media and passerbys. Like a caricature of what the race actually is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I, a male. Decide i want to be female, and then pursue males. That's.. kinda gay. You know ? I get that trans community just wants to assimilate to the gender that they choose but the reality is that it was originally guy looking for guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not pissed, confused is a better word for how I feel about the whole thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I now have to explain to the children that the barely dressed man with muzzle snout being walked buy his SO is not a valid life strategy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's the big issue right now isn't it ? people trying to validate whether or not a homosexual can go so far as to enter the gender they identify most closely with. the area is grey and it needs an eye kept on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay inside, looks like a free for all out there once it gets going.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good thing homeboy is north of the wall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my thoughts exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But see that's the problem, these parasites latch onto the transgender progress to push their delusions. I've got no Icelandic blood in me. I can't just claim viking liniage all of the sudden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ? I am a Mexican American male. If i just decided that I am now an asian woman.. any accent or modification I make to make myself appear asian... is kind of racist, yea ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't just start being fictional beasts. come on now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aptitude test, Basic common sense and at least a proficient knowledge of high school level education. Tacked in with a basic mental wellness test and you've got a fiar chance for all yea ? Coupled with a good educational system of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man into woman, woman into man, play ball. I don't care, live and let live. But I don't want to start refering to people that Identify as dogs as dogs. Or pretending that some asian girl is black when you know for a fact that it's a lie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Are we going to draw the line at Transpecies and Transrace ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually going to go get a copy of fight club signed by chuck this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea.. tabled it a year ago. We tried some plain jane bondage. So I guess we're making baby steps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spot right where the neck ends and the base of the jawline begins is like cat nip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y tho ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once had a girl take one of the filters off of a gas mask and put it on while we had sex. She'd make me place my hand over the hole where it used to be when it got rough and the result was a suction cup effect on her entire face. She'd squeeze my wrist if she liked it and tapped it to ease off.

But alas, I stopped dating crazy and can't get my current gf into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why all of the random Lincoln hate ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Machete fight with gorge bush. I've got some grievances with the W.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7/10. 

Pros - Very ambitious, absolutely amazing assortment of diverse species and climate. perfect placement in the Milkyway. Breath taking a occurrences and views.

Cons - Buggy weather resulting in mass loss of life. Infrastructure designed based on the death of all those that inhabit it. Dominant species (human) deemed unfit to care for the well being of the planet. Main source of water tainted by salt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The furries have jumped on the transgender wagon and are taking advantage. I'm never going to refer to a grown ass human as any other animal other than human, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't know where to start. How do you confront someone on that kind of delusion ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i would if people didn't effect me directly. Some one goes around writing new rules for this whole reality thing, it interests me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've been watching too much dare devil Haha. I sympathize a little bit, I grew up in a rough area, did a little armature boxing when i was younger. My girlfriend now is a dainty little thing, love her to death, but i still wish I could take her to a metal show and not feel that she's a liability. Ya know ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 07:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if a an old man turns into a little girl that's not some form of transgender ? Guess I am Ignorant, I'm going to learn something new today. What is it called then ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's tough, my mom has that issue with the distant family. She'll never get to the places she wants while people leech without giving back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one wants to have this discussion because it's uncomfortable. Progress is made through discomfort. I'm not here to bash on the trans community. I'm here trying to get you guys to shed the parasites that are impeding progress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's exactly my point. asking her to look out for her self and stop drowning her self in other people's problems seems like an easy thing to do for you and me. But I bet she'd see it as being selfish. I'm on your side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh.. so homeboy that has pretty prevalent mental and social ticks doesn't need help until he's already committed an awful act yea ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see a guy on the street pissing into a mail box whilst at the same time trying to flag you down to help him rebuild his time machine. Your personal opinion I guess would be reserved as not to be rude in making the assumption that the guy needs help, right ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that an elderly couple took him in as their daughter and are further enabling his clear cut mental illness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is the line I am talking about. He needs help for that distinction right ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I feel like i'm in the trigger section of a gun shop. but hell, I'm genuinely curious to see where people land on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> acept that he's made the switch to female and tacked on the age bit. that's abuse of the whole system that the transgender community put in place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to be 200 years old and make my claim to the Guinness book of world records.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on.. are you really going to refer to a fifty year old dude as a six year old chick because that's how he identifies ? Guy into girl and girl into guy i have no issues with. But we should draw the line at species race and age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is a tough subject. but species, age, and race should kind of be sacred you know ? if we start letting people assign them selves that it will get ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, people now deciding that they are a different race, species, or age are kind of shitting on the whole transgender progress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, but those seeking transpecies and transrace are kind of pushing it aren't they ? Also choosing a new age with your sex is kind of out of line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Father leaves family of seven to become a six year old girl. 


https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DuaUl4ed_AU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well more or less, a person making the transition does have to go a pretty strenuous mental exam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a thing, people are now transspecies, transrace. Kinda getting crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so fifty year old man deciding he's now a seven year old girl is cool ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so fifty year old man deciding he's now a seven year old girl is cool ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently saw a story about an older 50+ year old gentlemen who decided that he was now a seven year old girl. Due to the recent trends of dragon kin and other new genders, where does it end ?

I respect the guy into girl and girl into guy, but isn't this new grey area just kind of egging on the mentally ill ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At what point do you draw the line between transgender and mental illness ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> smoke em if you got em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they talk about their ex, if it's relevant fine. But when they bring up their ex they're thinking about their ex. Screw that noise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once came up on some money in a lump sum to help the family in a tight spot. I did the math.. if I sold my car and valuables I'd have enough to head two states north and have a deposit on a fully furnished apartment.  Thought about it for a good while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good people suffer from this plight, asking them to be selfish feels wrong and is hard for them. good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, I learned that day that I can be strong for my loved ones. But if I pretend to be their immovable object I'll break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The physical ones are tough. maybe get her on some squats. A petite girl with a tone ass isn't a bad trade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like... physically ? Or does he just avoid confrontation all around ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is one thing you'd change about your SO and why ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 03:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 03:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the issue is that a lot of it was internal. Growing up in a hispanic household gave me a mindset that no one wants to hear your problems and that you're not really a man if you can't handle it your self. She usually pulled me out of that mentality and was there for me. But during her masters program she was preoccupied through no fault of her own. 

Just be there and listen, try and get her professional help if she'll take it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 8ish, I took a trip to mexico to visit family and friends. I don't believe in ghosts so I write it off as some jack ass being a freak. But outside on the street around 3am I awoke to to a horse drawn cart slowly clopping by. There wasn't much light but i could tell it was a man and he was old, and pretty tall. He was dragging chains.

I woke up my aunt to ask and get her to see. She told me it was the devil looking for souls, and that I should go to bed. I slept on the carpet in their room after that on top of some of my blankets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shot down my ex gf's friend. She was way out of my league but I can't stand cheaters, and I wont be a hypocrite. She coaxed a stiff one out of me though and my gf was working late so I cranked one out when i got home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to do this to a tripper at a music festival. Something where finding a dumby on drugs wouldn't be hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently went to my folks place to pick up some mail and things my mom had left me. When I found that my sister was home alone and left the door unlocked. I creaked the door open and let myself in, I began to make an awful growling noise with the help of a Aztec death whistle. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GLo3XoP5SEY

I once I heard her call out and ask who was there I made it screech for a solid minute. By the time I peaked around the corener she had a look in her eye like she'd accepted death and a 360 controller cocked back as her first line of deffense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst you've scared someone for laughs ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hit up the barns and noble. Practice natural small talk with the patrons there about what to read next. Make up something about needing a book for a long trip or something. The bar scene is full of scum with both sexes. Most have a coffee shop attached which makes for easy interactions that don't have to exceed 15 minutes. I loved leaving there with a fresh read and phone number for a book marker. Offer to buy the person's book or coffee depending on your financial situation and the product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, dated some chick without transport and it was awful. I don't know your financial situation but try and remedy that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I realized that I can't get rid of my taste for finding humor at the expense of others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always say I loved you to those I love when we break company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back I had gone through a nasty loss that set me into a depression. I was the oldest of four and was pretty good about maintaining a the rock title in my family so when I moved in with my partner I filled that role.

My partner was going through a masters program and I couldn't bare to add anymore weight to the load. I drove up to a spot I liked in the forest and left a note in my car and almost stepped off of a 3,000 foot drop. I thought about my family and what i'd do to them, what we'd already been through and the life i'd leave behind.
 
That night I approached my partner after what felt like the longest drive of my life and confided everything I held back. But I never shared the story of the cliff, and I burnt the note.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 06:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spooked the hell out of my sister half to death. She left the door unlocked to my mom's house and that bugs me. Made it growl in the hallway and when she asked who was there I made it screech. When i finally peeked the corner to show her it was me. She had a 360 controller cocked back as her line of deffense and a look in her eyes like she'd accepted death. hahahahahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're born neutral, a blank canvas with a blue brush in one hand and a red in the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own this one. This guy sells his stuff on etsy, great products. If you have a love for pranks this is one of my all time favorites.


https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GLo3XoP5SEY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't see an immediate face to face future within the next 365 days. Get out, I was deeply in love with someone long distance and I feel that all we did was keep each other from enjoying the sanity of a face to face relationship. I loved this person but I am currently in a three year long relationship with someone now and it has been so much more fufilling and eventful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently purchased an Aztec death whistle. It kind of sounds like a banshee screaming. I make it growl at the neighbor kids when they're being loud. And if I'm in the mood i'll blow it at 3-4am when I get up for work. No one knows I have it and I complain about it to other neighbors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 06:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a breakup caused by infidelity I may have come across some messages from my ex's social media account and sent them to her mother. Incriminating her in vulgar acts while she was with me. With some one else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
