<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 23:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My LDS Therapy therapist frequently quoted Matt 5:28. 

But Itell you that anyone who looks at a woman lustfully has already committed adultery with her in his heart.

So, that means essentially all men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 23:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 62And if he havetenvirgins given unto him by this law, he cannot commit adultery, for they belong to him, and they are given unto him; therefore is he justified.

Seriously, read your scriptures before defending the indefensible. 

Would you like me to quote the temple ceremony as further evidence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 23:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Mormon theology, women are sub-equal to men. Property, even, in some cases (D C 132).

The gospel is inherently sexist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 17:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We are all equal in the eyes of god.

Except for women, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 17:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is it wrong of me that I never think about America when I read the book?

Not at all, since it is fiction, and didn't really happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 17:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  do you believe all of this was false?

Yes, absolutely. Made up whole-cloth by Joseph Smith. Do you believe the actually happened? I'd love to see your (**not** BoM) evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 17:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you want to have this conversation you're welcome to make another thread about it.

You may have made the thread, but you don't get to decide it's direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 15:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why a female owned sex toy store? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 23:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 583 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what is it? All I see is "*******". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 03:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trolling. /u/morajic is quite TBM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 03:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was illegal to honk your horn, why would they sell cars with horns?

Is that explicitly what the cop said? That under all circumstances, it's illegal to honk your horn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 05:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth a shot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I like that FAQ better than /r/fitness's. I'll look into them, they sound promising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To look good naked. I've just started to get the whole "shoulder/pec" thing, which is nice. I'll look into PHUL, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I'm running an A/B split. A is Bench, Row, Squat, with curls, pullups, and facepulls thrown in. B is Deadlift, OHP, and Chinups with flyes, close row (via cable machine), and volume bench work.

I go M/W/F, but am interested in going M/T H/F, or 4 days a week.

What workout program would you recommend? 

Numbers: Squat 240lb/5x3, Dead 285lb/5x3, Bench 170/5x3, OHP 125/5x3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 00:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was already shot 7 times. It was going to die anyways, the shot you saw on the video was a mercy shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trouble with mods: Can't delete or unsubscribe from them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 00:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

I am subscribed to a number of mods. However, recently, the game has been unexpectedly crashing. I'd like to unsubscribe from a few of the mods, until I find the one that is the problem child.

Unfortunately, if I go to Steam Workshop - Your Files - Subscribed Items and click "unsubscribe," when I hit refresh, the mod is still there. Going to the mods page to unsubscribe is equally unsuccessful. I've attempted this via the Steam program, and the in-browser Steam.

Any tips? Am I doing anything wrong?

Thanks for your help!

Edit:

Attempted to unsubscribe the mods via the in-game mod list. Not initially successful in removing the mods from the steam workshop (via steam program or browser). Cleared steam files via the steam instructions [here](https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=3134-TIAL-4638). The workshop still thinks I'm subscribed to the mods I left, but the in-game mod list thinks I'm subscribed to no mods. The mystery continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider traps? Spider hunting expeditions? What can you do with your legal property? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 23:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 16:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it, I'm sorry. Good luck to you and your jackass LL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 16:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under New York law, a landlord must return the tenant's security deposit within a reasonable time **after the tenant has surrendered the rental property** to the landlord--that is,  returned the keys and vacated the property. What's "reasonable" would ultimately be up to a small claims court judge (should a deposit dispute end up in court), but it typically means a window of **21 to 45 days.**

http://www.nolo.com/legal-encyclopedia/new-york-security-deposits-36183.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is your website relevant at all here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 15:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As far as mind altering substances goes, I would say all of them, extensively, including your psychedelics.

Antidepressants? Anti-anxiety medication? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 14:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You: not polygamists. Reality: Dallin Oaks is a polygamist, as are many other older male members.

You: Entire church is ran by members, clergy unpaid. Reality: MPs, GAs, Q15 are all paid.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 01:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Joe Jr born 1805 this makes him ~~around 14.~~ several months shy of 15

FTFY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 19:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but you immediately follow up with a Christlike example:

Jesus flipped over tables and used a whip - I think I could smack someone and still be cool.

Given your other devout beliefs espoused, I don't think my conclusion was unwarranted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just take a comment I said in a different thread...and try and apply to to this thread?

That's how reddit works, yeah. You gain a reputation from past comments.

which was so blatantly fesicious

Maybe my sarcasm meter is broken, but it didn't seem facetious at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 18:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  because we're not selling anything.

The missionaries are 'selling' salvation.

Why do you think Provo area has so many sales-based businesses? Because Mormon RMs get pretty good at selling shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 20:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To each his own. You seem to be conveniently leaving out his murderous and narcissistic actions in the OT, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 20:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take his actions in the OT and the NT. Now, imagine your next-door neighbor was acting the same way. I think that any reasonable person would brand such a neighbor a lunatic.

Just because we're separated by millennium from the story doesn't mean Jesus is any less mentally ill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 18:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Argumentum_ad_populum

Lunatics can still be a "positive influence," doesn't mean they're not legitimately crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 17:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the fictional character Jesus is a lunatic, by almost any measure. He thinks he has supernatural powers, speaks to things that aren't there, has visions, flies off the handle, etc.

It gets worse if you think that Jehovah of the OT is Jesus. In that case, absolutely a lunatic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 16:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jesus flipped over tables and used a whip

That's because the fictional Jesus in an unhinged, deranged lunatic of a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 16:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If everything in Mormonism is actually true, then God is a narcissistic, sexist bully, and it'd be completely immoral to follow his commandments. Going anywhere other than the Celestial Kingdom would be the best thing someone could ever do.

Come at me, bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 15:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IANAL, but that sounds an awfully lot like passing a known counterfeit, possibly a felony? Terrible idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /4. Give an update to /r/legaladvice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 20:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to upgrade to 10, get the key, *then* fresh install. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 20:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, then there's [this guy](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2015/07/22/chipotle-chipotlelife-andrew-hawryluk/30502991/), who is fit, and ate chipotle for **154** days in a row. If his calories were off by 500 every day, he'd have gained at least 20 pounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 20:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is exactly why I trust the calculator.

Chipotle is a *massive* restaurant chain. Things are streamlined. If they were using double the amount of rice, that would hurt their bottom line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 20:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this is correct. It may be that they're referring to 4 oz of uncooked rice, cooked rice being heavier. I also get confused about liquid or weight ounces, as they are distinctly different.

I feel fairly confident that the chipotle calculator is correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 19:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my CPU fan is running at a constant, ear shattering, 3600 RPM

My MSI motherboard lets me change how quickly the fan goes based on how hot it is. I don't think the fan is supposed to go full-bore the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 16:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about any of your questions, but I completely agree. I'm a big fan of that style of speaking. Brian Keith Dalton has a fantastic voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 15:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, citing the three-four feet of her property that extend into the lane, she's banned anyone from turning in front of the house, except her one or two favorites.

IANAL. Based on your drawing, do any of the other houses property lines technically extend into the lane? Because they could do a massive 'fuck you' to Lisa, and deny her access to her property all together. Then, they could negotiate back to where they were originally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 02:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check OPs history, he resubmitted it to /r/relationships </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do you have remote access tools on your laptop? If not, the only way he would be able to access the cam would be if you activated it.

Unless there is spyware installed on the computer. Sticky tape or disconnecting the webcam are excellent ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 00:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying I'm wrong to trust the church? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 14:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prior statistic given was from 1985-2009. During that time, the LDS church's reported membership was 5,920,000-13,824,854.

Using the previous figure of 5 million (*not four million*) was, in actuality, **strengthening** the figure, not watering it down. Further, the previous stats were in the past tense (*gave* $1bn, not *gives* $40 mil/year).

Since you have shifted tenses, and also have a previously unreported statistic (source? unless your grammar was wrong, and you meant "gave"), I decided to use the most recent 2014 membership statistics, or about 15 million members.

I never used a 4 million figure. Indeed, you've pointed out an error, I should have used a figure between 6 and 14 million. Let's split the difference and call it $1bn, for 10 million members, over 25 years.

So, instead of my previous comment of $8.33/member/year, we're left with a paultry $4.00/member/year.

Thanks, /u/cbfw86! You've successfully pointed out that your church is even **worse** in a humanitarian sense than before!!

Listen.  Any way you cut it, it's well below $10/member/year. Assuming an average salary of $15,000/year (children, 3rd world, stay-at-home moms, etc), given a tithing of $1500, the church gives an incredibly paultry amount.

Yes, "only" $1bn. Yes, "only" $10/member/year. Yes, your church sucks in regards to charitable giving.

Pathetic. Absolutely pathetic. Your church can't even be consistent to it's teachings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 03:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $40 million per 15 million members? $2.66 a member. What a generous and amazing church! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $40 million/year

If they have 5 million members, that's only $8.33/member/year

So 2 cents/member/day

So, yes, *only $1bn*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 18:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't understand people who don't see the problem with only $1bn over 24 years. Talk about being blinded by a vendetta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 18:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civil discussion is encouraged. Please, no personal attacks.

Let me never fall into the vulgar mistake of dreaming that I am persecuted whenever I am contradicted.  Ralph Waldo Emerson
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you reject both the words of the modern prophets (who speak for god) and continuing revelation, something that is deep-baked into Mormonism.

Although, passing off the words of Prophets as just the words of 'men' sure does fit into the current LDS m.o.

http://www.mrm.org/virgin-birth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While brother Joseph was referring to the provinces of God, I was led to reflect that there is no act, no principle, no power belonging to the Deity that is purely philosophical. The birth of the Saviour was as natural as are the births of our children; it was the result of natural action. He partook of flesh and blood  was begotten of his Father, as we were of our fathers.

- Prophet Brigham Young, Journal of Discourses, v. 8, p. 115

... I believe the Father came down from heaven, as the apostles said he did, and begat the Saviour of the world; for he is the ONLY-begotten of the Father, which could not be if the Father did not actually beget him in person.... I believe the Father came down in His tabernacle and begat Jesus Christ.

- Prophet Brigham Young, Journal of Discourses, v. 1, p. 238

... In relation to the way in which I look upon the works of God and his creatures, I will say that I was naturally begotten; so was my father, and also my Saviour Jesus Christ. According to the Scriptures, he is the first begotten of his father in the flesh, and there was noting unnatural about it.

- Apostle Heber C. Kimball, Journal of Discourses, v. 8, p. 211

God, the Father of our spirits, became the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ according to the flesh.... The fleshy body of Jesus required a Mother as well as a Father. Therefore, the Father and Mother of Jesus, according to the flesh, must have been associated together in the capacity of Husband and Wife; hence the Virgin Mary must have, for the time being, the lawful wife of God the Father.... He had a lawful right to overshadow the Virgin Mary in the capacity of a husband, and beget a Son, although she was espoused to another; for the law which He gave to govern men and women, was not intended to govern Himself, or to prescribe rules for his own conduct.

- Apostle Orson Pratt, The Seer, p. 158

Now, we are told in scriptures that Jesus Christ is the only begotten Son of God in the flesh. Well, now for the benefit of the older ones, how are children begotten? I answer just as Jesus Christ was begotten of the flesh... Jesus is the only person who had our Heavenly Father as the father of his body.

- Prophet Joseph F. Smith, Family Home Evening Manual, pp. 125, 126, 1972

Christ was Begotten by an immortal Father in the same way that mortal men are begotten by mortal fathers.

- Apostle Bruce R. McConkie, Mormon Doctrine, p. 547, 1966

And Christ was born into the world as the literal Son of this Holy Being; he was born in the same personal, real, and literal sense that any mortal son is born to a mortal father. There is nothing figurative about his paternity; he was begotten, conceived and born in the normal and natural course of events, for he is the Son of God, and that designation means what it says.

- Apostle Bruce R. McConkie, Mormon Doctrine, p. 792, 1966

As far as this life is concerned, [Jesus] was born of Mary and of Elohim; he came here as an offspring of that Holy Man who is literally our Father in heaven. He was born in mortality in the literal and full sense as the Son of God. He is the Son of his father in the same sense that all morals are the sons and daughters of their fathers.

- Apostle Bruce R. McConkie, Mortal Messiah, v. 1, p. 330

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints proclaims that Jesus Christ is the Son of God in the most literal sense. The body in which He performed His mission in the flesh was sired by that some Holy Being we worship as God, our Eternal Father. Jesus was not the son of Joseph, nor was He begotten by the Holy Ghost.

- Prophet Ezra Taft Benson, The Teachings of Ezra Taft Benson, p. 7

Thus, God the Father became the literal father of Jesus Christ. Jesus was born of a mortal mother and an immortal father.

- Gospel Principles, p. 57, 1988

[Jesus Christ] was willing to make payment because of his great love for mankind, and he was able to make payment because he lived a sinless life and because he was actually, literally, biologically the Son of God in the flesh.

- Messages for Exaltation, For the Sunday Schools of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, Gospel Doctrine Class, pp. 378-379, 1967

**God had sex with Mary.** To not believe this and to call yourself mormon is an oxymoron of the highest degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not attempting to prove anything, neither am I attempting to be sarcastic.

Listen, I'm sorry that you have a huge chip on your shoulder regarding exmormons, as given from your comment history. I hope you find the peace and harmony that you seek. Maybe your interactions with exmormons would go smoother if you weren't needlessly antagonistic first thing out of the gate.

That said, reviewing your recent transactions with the members of this and other forums, I'm extracting myself from this conversation. It won't be productive for either of us, unfortunately.

Again, good luck finding peace and joy in your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Neither do contemporary Mormons believe that Jesus was conceived through physical sex

Maybe the mormons you interact with don't, or they just don't want to talk about it with you.

However, let me assure you, there's a whole bunch of Mormons in Utah who fully believe that Jesus was conceived physically. I know a few bishops, a stake president, and at least two patriarchs who ascribe to the idea. Moreover, they have multiple statements from Prophets and Apostles to back them up.

Your belief that Jesus wasn't conceived through physical sex is a nonsensical misnomer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Elohim may well include God the Father and his wife/wives, given that it's a plural. God the Father + God the Mother = Elohim. Not hard to work out.

This kind of feels like you're painting the target after you've fired. 

God may be polygamous. He may monogamous. We don't even know.

Wait, the prophet speaks with god and we don't even know his living arrangements? The LDS church pushes "Family" and we don't even know the Divine's family? Polygamy was a necessary and concrete doctrine, necessary for salvation, and we don't even know if God is polygamous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 19:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly *is* unemployment? How do you file for it? Does it vary by state?

Googling "what is unemployment" was not directly helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 22:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird as hell. 

Also, should have guessed, since in /r/Mormon I just found out DH means dear husband.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DW? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 19:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You say that you were drunk that night and have no recollection as to where you were.

And, since he's **19**, he gets hit with underage drinking.

Great idea.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
