<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7495</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has using the word "fascist" become some kind of hipster fad like the latest fashion or music cd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A generation of Germans with a EU mindset make that thinking much tougher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is part of the problem. In the world of globalization other countries ARE affected by what goes on else where. And that includes the US, being a larger country doesn't make the US or any other country immune to the pitfalls of globization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One must wonder about the views and parenting of the dad. Lighting a fire in a crowd is bad enough but when an 11 year old does it(where did he obtain that skill by the way) this won't end well.

Drew Carey endorsed Gary Johnson I think so he doubt he's bitter Hillary lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So people have enough time to get through to gamblers anonymous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drew Carey's Son Was That Mini-Bonfire Kid at Trump Protest (VIDEOS + PHOTO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they are one of the two establishment parties. Like the other establishment party doesn't know about or how to do this stuff. And this is why this will go away or never get the attention it deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A politician was arrested regarding this incident. An Alejandro Espin Sogo of the United Left Party. If this is political I'd throw in treason or sedition charges along with the assault charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ignoring or denying the existence of voter fraud and/or irregularities is done to protect the establishment in both parties because both probably know and participate in these irregularities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "the bias has been toward the establishment candidates over tea partiers" , key words='establishment candidates'.

 This is why many love to deny so much as the existence of voter fraud or irregularities because they know it goes on and they would be implicated themselves. Once the tricks are exposed people know exactly what to look for-can't have that can we. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious  as to the date Soros took out his short positions on ING. ING paid a record fine in 2012 for violating US Iranian sanctions.

http://www.nytimes.com/2012/06/13/business/ing-bank-to-pay-619-million-over-sanctions-violations.html

Did a regulator with political ties leak word of this fine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were short positions on some banks in 2012. Occupy Wall Street protests which many think Soros funded peaked out in the fall of 2011. The occupy movement's primary targets were the big banks.

http://www.thenewamerican.com/usnews/politics/item/9735-big-soros-money-linked-to-occupy-wall-street

Wonder what his short positions on big banks were in 2011? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes the land of single party rule, the status quo and agenda to push. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are probably working; for a protest organization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spain: Girl Viciously Assaulted by Antifa Radicals for Wearing Spanish Flag, Leftists Justify Attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several of these dead people have voted in multiple elections. In the California report one dead person voted from 2004 to 2010. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be living life vicariously through their favorite video game or dystopian Hollywood movie. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did dead people wind up voting in several states.

Dead people voting California 

http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2016/05/23/cbs2-investigation-uncovers-votes-being-cast-from-grave-year-after-year/

Dead people voting Colorado

http://gazette.com/dead-people-voting-in-colorado/article/1586300

Dead people voting Philadelphia

http://6abc.com/politics/action-news-investigation-voting-from-the-grave/1575596/

These investigations are concentrated in and a sampling of one county or city because they are time consuming. If one would apply similar percentages nationwide dead people voting itself is/would be probably be a much bigger issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audit the fed audit the dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an example that voting irregularities including fraud. It exists, maybe not on a huge scale but it exists, has taken place can take place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why bother with discipline, diet, exercise, daily schedule etc when big health care can sell you a pill or procedure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are "working" for a protest group like any other job why would one use their personal equipment for business. 

These are federal felony charges although yes without proper cause or procedure why should law enforcement have access to a private or business phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's seemed that the DNC let the European and some Asian press including down under do stories on or take the heat for positions the US msm would not report on. The US msm touched the TPP but wouldn't go to deep or long. Now the Europeans are openly twisting the narrative to the US won't be able to trade and it will crash the global economy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there is fraud when it comes to voting. Mail in ballot fraud is also an issue. I think there poorly labeling and categorizing voting fraud. 

https://www.texastribune.org/2016/08/22/texas-prosecuted-15-illegal-voting-cases-none-invo/

And this ineligible women voted 5 times in Texas. Registering   voting Republican since 2004

http://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Woman-Jailed-on-Charge-of-Illegal-Voting-342158051.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might even be the same guy but in the 90s it was theorized that the reason AIDs spread fast and/or seem to have stayed with in certain communities is that it was frequently accompanied by hard core drug use/abuse which weakens the immune system. I think there was something in there about a mutated virus as well. I just remember harping on iv drug abusers.

 I don't necessarily agree but I wouldn't discount any drug let alone AZT either weakening the immune system and/or creating or allowing for a mutation of the virus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought her dad was 'murdered' by negligent homicide by the doctor already in jail.

I guess taken out or 'murdered' sounds better than my dad od'd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to worry about those pesky political ramifications with the exit sign in sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it with all these jewelry store robberies. And the New Years Eve heist in NYC.

 Are jewels and diamonds a fad on the black market now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Fly List in Madonna's future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insurance coverage is different that actual care. Using the word "just" makes it seem like it's effective immediately. Also fails to include the probable replacement programs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madonna Secret Service Investigation: Singer Says She Was Taken Out Of Context At Womens March, Doubts Cast On Purported Probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be so sure. Some countries had to be nudged to participate. This treaty was well past a target date of 2013 already. Even farmers in Australia and Canada were not that thrilled. It took a few extra negotiations with Japan to get them in. And Vietnam was taking their good old time ratifying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet many individuals would've been forced to use an arbitration committee set up by treaty companies instead of their own country's civil court system-mandatory arbitration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently nothing other than the writer cancelling their twitter account.

 I guess she didn't expect people disagreeing with her or not finding her funny so for a comedy show writer that was probably a traumatic event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many have gone beyond violence. They want civil war. 

The questions area do they simply want 'a' change and do they realize the implications and/or consequences of a civil war. It simply won't be a change in leadership especially if one with actual fighting starts. 

Peace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. When there's a messenger to shoot why bother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The son will be a school shooter tweet by a SNL writer basically sums up their politics. 

This does nothing but reinforce any indoctrination these viewers already had. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why it should be ALL lives matter. It should be about educating students on basic civil rights. Specifying a particular group sends the wrong message including an assumption that only one group needs help or one group at a time. It would be quicker, to the point and easier to remember-ALL Lives Matter. 

Although it's good that many employers/businesses give eeo or employment rights   anti discrimination training too many look at it as goof off time not paying attention to hours of lectures when a 1/2 hour meeting reading the rules, laws and penalties would do the trick. Many students will also look at these sessions as goof off time-no math, science or grammar. Probably little or no homework. Should have substitute teachers that week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was social media and msm playing the same clips in over and over and over again. BLM has "a" place in some but absolutely not all discussion about police brutality. It is not worthy of it's own week.

 Police brutality and/or corruption should be a session in a civil rights or criminal justice chapter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, remove AN infected nerve is 'not tooth removal techinicaly'. Which is a technicality lawyers will pounce on along with the word 'an' which could mean one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw 'removal of AN infected nerve' but not extraction or entire tooth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use it but I'd say you could cut out a brushing or wash a day. Throw in some floss and tooth picks used at or near the gum line would probably do just as much.

Eh, like most other things-moderation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful not to dry out the mouth. I used to do the same routine and that's what happened. Mouth produces a lot of good bacteria to dissolve a lot of food residue in the mouth. The mouth washes in particular can kill too much. A dry mouth it much better for bacteria because without moisture it has time to grow without moisture that carries good bacteria or washes it away no matter how slow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfamiliar with the politics but the witness in the video saying allu akbhar caught my attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the parents aren't there and in a school setting it's production line medicine no better than a doctor trying to see 10-20 patients an hour for profit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this was a dental school it might have been a student or intern trying to rack up procedure or practice time as well. 

I don't recall friends or family saying they had tooth extractions as a kid. I remember hearing the stories of getting a filling done without novicane but many old school dentists dislike extractions because they feel it could lead to shifting of the teeth issues which could lead to bite problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sugar is an issue but I've been told by dentists that food pieces stuck to or between the teeth are just as bad as sugar because they take longer to dissolve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the sugars. For an adult a dentist once told me it's the stuff that sticks to or gets caught in between a tooth is more of a problem than a lot of the sugars. A lot simple sugar dissolve but not stuck food.

 Also a dry mouth is just as risky for tooth decay or gum issues.  Kids need to be taught drink water several times a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until the emphasis is on specific groups are lowered there will be issues with relations. ALL lives matter is what needs to be taught. And discrimination by race and religion is wrong rather than using quota systems. The time needs to be spent on general discrimination issues and it's actually a pretty short lesson. Businesses do it all the time with eeo/hr programs. Get right to the point.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the video I briefly saw a flash of the permission slip with "additional consent" maybe required. 

When it comes to any medical care the parent should be consulted. There should be a meeting or conference with the school, actual provider and parents before these programs are implemented. And a list of things including tooth extractions should be on a list or on a list of procedures requiring additional consent.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much better than the 200 plus arrests the day before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic Terrorist Attack Cover Up in Melbourne, Australia - Live Trading News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's how Soros helped fund   fuel the Ferguson riots.

http://www.newsmax.com/Newsfront/george-soros-funded-ferguson-protests/2015/01/15/id/618934/

He used groups and organizations like a business uses contractors and sub contractors. Organizations supply bodies to others. Some groups even complained they were not paid as promised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many Soros offices in Europe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repetition and saturation. And like many students once they get out in reality they won't be able to handle something different let alone wrong. But it won't be a different opinion or way of doing things. It will by THE wrong way.

I wonder if the 'voter suppression' lesson will include examples of voter fraud. Oh that's right no such thing as voter fraud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Madonna said was more dangerous than this because she gave specifics including method   location and said " I thought". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think some want to be part of a political event or espouse a political opinion much like a person wants the latest clothing fashion or music cd. They wear that opinion or mindset like a badge of honor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that on the same day anti Trump marchers show up in Paris and London and yet LePen can still draw 'a' crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the saying. "Must maintain appearances" in this case the appearance that the entire country or world hates Trump.

Even the msm are asking high profile individuals where was this turnout at election time. And what are you protesting.

And with companies that provide crowds along with big money/Soros one has to wonder not only was their transportation taken care of but were the numbers supplemented. I know when I was union we sent members to numerous protests and/or events. Unions have been using informational picketing for decades. 

http://theantimedia.org/rent-a-crowd-company-admits-politicians-are-using-their-service/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 21:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the msm is showing multiple protests on a split screen there's a real good chance it's Soros. And most arrests will be out of towners/non resident who don't care if it takes someone 3 hours for a 20 minute drive.

Social media might help with dates and times but not transportation and permits which are money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an observation but Pizzagate and associated crimes seem to keep on getting dismissed by the left yet to today at a speech leftists are again accusing Trump of incest referring to his daughter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  About time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replacing, new etc accompanies most highway bills federal or local. So does 'extending' or 'widening'. Invested or spending money usually involves capital projects-new or replace. Federal and state highway departments already have maintenance budgets for repairs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And endorsed by domestic socialist organizations called unions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opposition followers didn't facilitate, agitate or perpetuate an outrage machine. 

The people protesting that peaceful transition of power or one individual don't realize that the emphasis on one individual is not what the three branch system of government is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left, not the Democrats are waking up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they call that back door socialism. Also known as free stuff to some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is also a difference between repairing a road and repaving  entire stretches. Too many want new or assume new will be 'the' solution. Replacing is not repairing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throwing money at any issue or project goal doesn't always solve it or wind up being practical. Hence under utilized if not abandoned newly constructed cities in China where this billionaire is from and/or influenced by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prostester is too kind. Professional and facilitated anarchist is a more accurate description. Completely covering one's face is something a bank robber or gangster does. Not a snowflake chanting for change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, but when one is new to the workforce and job application process the focus is on getting the job. Online or computerized applications make skipping questions tough. 



    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rent or own question has been there for years although a lot of time employers even large companies use old or generic applications. The house or apartment question is bogus but the theory is one will be more invested in the job if they have something else at stake. There is a line of thought in management that they should be able to hold the job over your head even if it's only hiring someone that really really needs the money. Doesn't always work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are protests then are ignorant disruptions that won't change the public's mind. 

The problem now a days it's about tv coverage. The people that are actually affected most protestors don't care about it's about tv coverage to make it seem everyone is for their cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen apartment rents tick off some let alone salary. The new employee or tenant frequently feels entitled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had jobs in different industries and it's come up and caused problems. Had one job where a recently hired college graduate found out a newly hired technician was making more than him. He hit the roof. He wouldn't train him even on company procedure, his attitude was you apparently know it all.  Also have seen posted overtime and/or sales commission list cause issues because an employee could figure out what the person was making.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the rent or own question either. I've also heard that a lot of businesses only want to hire someone living in a house rather than an apartment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got to pay off those political favors. I lived in a town where to get a government job if you didn't know the right person you were told off the record go volunteer for a local politician as a gofer then about a year later ask them for a reference when applying for a government job. It's pretty standard fare even in large cities with a lot of employees/jobs to fill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh, spend and build like the Chinese winding up with ghost cities.

http://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2015/07/20/what-will-become-of-chinas-ghost-cities/#479da8c2751b

"infrastructure" is an over used term as well. New doesn't necessarily make it better either. Massive construction also causes traffic problems and pollution for decades for which China is/has experienced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ends justify the means especially when the means are THE end.

Today it's radical Islam. Tomorrow it's... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RT and Al Jazeraa covered more progressive/occupy issues in depth than the so called msm. When likes of Ed Schultz are working for RT that's not exactly putting a flag up for right wing conservatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When RT first came on I thought it was tolerated because contrary to popular believe they actually did stories on a lot of progressive issues. I thought the left was using them for the occupy crowd.  Their agenda/direction and/is still towards leftist socialist.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same ethics laws that didn't stop the top recipients of big pharma money from voting against lowering drug prices through imports. No conflict of interest there..... 

It needs consistent enforcement to be effective and have credibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another rich guy who has to talk for himself without a lawyer or consult first. I've seen it first hand. A lot of those in management get used to having people to delegate to or consult. For the first time in a while many of these nominees are on their own in front of those committees. 

Doesn't make their policy or idea that bad but it does bring into question their attention to detail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favors to pay. Network cultivated for future employment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checking the air and getting fresh air into the hole. Here is an example. The ventilator hose is in the hole as the worker in going in or out of the hole. 

http://www.bing.com/images/search?q=men+working+manhole+ view=detailv2  id=B4DAD53EB12EE03F5489D63F6D3E01F20971165A selectedIndex=7 ccid=WhTjZmNe simid=608039633812064585 thid=OIP.M5a14e366635e4fd495f00c59442c5796o0 ajaxhist=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should've dropped a ventilator hose into the hole first then once down at the bottom pointed towards a corner to help displace some of those gases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As necessary as hazardous gas meters should be that hole should've been ventilated with fresh air for about 15-20 minutes minimum to displace and lower the concentrations of gases. And the ventilator hose should've been kept in the hole while they were going in and working. Heck one can buy the blower and hose at places like Grainger over the counter.

The problem with air packs or any equipment tool is that theoretically the metal could rub, cause a spark and poof. Confined spaces should be ventilated prior to and doing the work. 

Yes dangerous but miners, tunnelers and other utilities such as phone and electric go into manholes everyday and one of the things they do/emphasize is fresh air. It's not just about air packs which are important but not 'the' whole solution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's got to be all sorts of electronic testers along with manual squeeze/bladder operated, probably methane and natural gas most common. But just as important as testing is getting fresh air/ventilator hose down in the hole or confined space to displace the gases that have built up.  If it's a street manhole it's subject to run off on the street so that could petroleum products, food/grease etc. Also Florida being at sea level the moisture   soil content of a hole probably allows for different gases to build. 

They kept talking about air packs but the rescuers could've ventilated the hole with that big yellow hose bringing  fresh air in behind them. 

Also any confined space work areas require safety training. A pit might not be considered a confined since it has a large opening. Hole over 3 ft deep I think it is have to have the sides reinforced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tragic. Something is missing here.

 They were cited. One was for not performing test on the air before entering.  A near by resident complained about a smell for months. They should've let that hole air out for a while along with forcing fresh air into the hole before entering. 

Air packs were not the solution. With that much gas a metal tank might banged/rubbed on something and created a spark. 

RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One by one, 3 utility workers descended into a manhole. One by one, they died. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont even like cigar or cigarette smoke smell around food. If it's a restaurant I want to smell food or beer only. No other odors, vapors or smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't by some chance wearing a Hawaiin shirt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TMZ releases disturbing video of dog forced into water on 'A Dog's Purpose' set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 03:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think health will be an issue. Between his ego which is subject to disappointment/stress from the press and his schedule of apparently little sleep I don't know if he will last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The murderer was offered clemency in the 1990s but refused to renounce his actions and group that included bomb making/planting that killed innocent civilians.  What a pos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Pardons Communist Terrorist Lopez-Rivera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indoctrination at an early age works best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not saying it was Russian but if he is extradited there are enough powerful Democrats left to have the screws put to him. If Assange were to publicly admit the Russians were his source that would validate the DNC Russian hacking theory and help delegitimize Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a given. But in the  attempt to down play terrorism and perpetuate lone wolf with a gun this is months late. But better late than never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CIA document dump is a distraction since the intelligence community is in the headlines under fire. Timing is not a coincidence. 

Good news in their zeal to distract maybe some unplanned redactable information slipped through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another down played act of terrorism seems to be moving along as planned. Even if it's eventually classified as terror after the administration changes Obama leaves with one less act of terror under his watch using his criteria.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commutation doesn't exonerate a person of the crime. Just reduces the sentence. I doubt Assange is looking for a reduced sentence. 

It was a win no matter you look at it. Obama and Democrats curryfavor with the LGBT community. And if Assange did allow extradition he probably would forced to admit his source was Russian. Nothing to lose in Obama's eyes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, The CIA, the organization in the news right now all of the sudden declassifies millions of files on mostly old news. Distraction? All the "good" they did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Trump is against black people and sometimes a high profile successful individual can have as much effect as a professional politician. 

Hill seemed to be more interested in name dropping. Name droppers want you to associate them with the names they speak of. It's not just about policy as it is self promotion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The silly part is that I would've moved them and given an EXtremely detailed bill after.

Boycott bring publicity for a while but not results.

And burning Chargers jerseys? Or those over priced shirts which those same customers paid too much money for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airport shooter allegedly logged into Jihadi chat rooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> St Louis or most cities don't build or refurbish stadiums without somekind of preliminary agreement. Few to zero projects municipal or private get started without at least a verbal agreement of some kind.  Once full fledged contracts are signed with these teams they are loaded with clauses(Which St Louis did sign) that include calling for upgrades every time a new stadium is built elsewhere. Most cities can't keep up. 

http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sports-nfl-stadiums-insight-idUSKCN0VC0EP

Point is cities lose out building and maintaining millionaire playgrounds. No matter what's promised up front becomes more meaningless as the years go by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 08:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The initial deal and numbers had the builders/owners getting over 100 million in the form of tax breaks and I think LA has to provide security for events.

Tax breaks can bounce back. St Louis has to pick up what the Rams promised years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal tax payers will be paying over a billion dollars for LA's railine extension. The administration just awarded LA over a BILLION dollars. If LA had funded all or more on their own I doubt they would be that eager to award tax breaks for that new stadium.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been complaints in the past from cities that have been told by the NFL to waive their city hotel taxes during the Super Bowl build up for 2 weeks. This is one reason many cities "lose".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still hear things like 16 agencies concluded... But the Russian "hack" story keeps changing.

First it was the Russians, then 16 agencies 'concluded'-or gave their "opinion", the it was the 13 page report with maybe one page of possible evidence, the another 33 page report short on evidence but again loaded 'conclusions' then Trump was briefed and someone asked about the Russian Hack and Trump gave a thought among many others. 

To top it off "hack" is over used, maybe scammed or trapped since the likes of Podesta answered a virus loaded email/message not a "hack" per say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most regardless of profession don't like rude treatment and no matter how professional they claim to be a doctor can be affected. Most people take things personally and will "screw you" verbally and action wise. Those who tend not to let themselves get distracted and stay focused on the task/s at hand are the ones that will succeed or excel in life in general. 

ANYONE who deals with the public, customers etc has to expect 'rude' treatment. It would be nice if everyone could just get along but that is not reality. Doctors and others should know   expect it.

 I've always found the bouncer training scene in the movie Roadhouse to be most effective in real life as well in which Patrick Swayze tells them "Be nice" no matter what the patron does. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumer Privacy Alert: Family tree website reveals personal address, family information </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genealogy website ignites privacy concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Head of DC National Guard ordered to step down after inauguration starts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Really, REALLY Hate Philadelphias New Soda Tax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ft. Lauderdale airport shooter had converted to Islam before joining the Army </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fort Lauderdale airport shooting: Do Esteban Santiago's mental issues explain attack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE: Nobody Melinda Byerley issues half-assed apology after trashing middle America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evil Trolls Tell Jennifer Hudson to Kill Herself After She Appears in Music Video Promoting Clean Energy for Shell | BCNN1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IGNORANT MASSES SHOCKED BY PHILLY BEVERAGE TAX IMPACT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia's new soda tax causing sticker shock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julian Assange, WikiLeaks To Release Documents That Prove Moon Landing Never Happened? [Rumor] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 17:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HGTV beats CNN in ratings during an election year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HGTV's Non-Political Appeal Beats CNN In Election Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College Student Driven Out Of School For Backing Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
