<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden Tried to Tell NSA About Surveillance Concerns, New Documents Reveal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 23:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TorBlog statement on former Tor Project employee Jacob Appelbaum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 23:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden Tried to Tell NSA About Surveillance Concerns, New Documents Reveal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 22:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The impossible task of creating a Best VPNs list today. Our writer set out to make a list of reliable VPNs; turns out the task is complicated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 20:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tor Browser 6.0 is released (Tor Blog w/ links) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 19:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals Court Delivers Devastating Blow to Cellphone-Privacy Advocates. Strengthens 3rd Party Doctrine, allows cellphone location data demands given w/o warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 01:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Knows Too Much About You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 00:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Knows Too Much About You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 00:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dropbox Wants More Access To Your Computer, and People Are Freaking Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 03:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google aims to kill passwords by the end of this year. Android users will be able to log in to services using a combination of their face, typing patterns, and how they move. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 23:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco retracts program to pay to reserve park's lawn areas amid outrage; reservation bidding of Dolores Park picnic grassy areas  as high as $260  nixed after locals decry invasion of the techies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 23:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brands Want To Predict Your Behavior By Mining Your Face From YouTube, Vine Videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden calls for whistleblower shield after claims by new Pentagon source. Accusations that Pentagon retaliated against a whistleblower undermine argument that there were options for Snowden other than leaking to the media. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 20:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Long Read: How the Pentagon punished NSA whistleblowers. Long before Edward Snowden went public, John Crane was a top Pentagon official fighting to protect NSA whistleblowers. Instead their lives were ruined  and so was his. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 20:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corrupt in its roots: as Oakland police scandals pile up, residents not surprised. Donald Trump may have called the city one of the most dangerous in the world but community members say the real danger is its police officers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 19:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RoboCop is real  and could be patrolling a mall near you with high-def infra-red cameras; can process 300 license plates a minute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 19:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RoboCop is real  and could be patrolling a mall near you with high-def infra-red cameras; can process 300 license plates a minute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 19:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If You Care At All About Privacy, Dont Use Googles Allo. It is the first major messaging App to have the express purpose of learning everything about you, further fleshing out Googles already comprehensive profile of you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 22:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rochester Police Used A $200,000 Stingray To Track Gang Members. Police have used the once-secret counterterrorism tools for pretty much everything except terrorism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rochester Police Used A $200,000 Stingray To Track Gang Members. Police have used the once-secret counterterrorism tools for pretty much everything except terrorism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cell Phone Network Flaws Can Help Spies Get Around Encryption Apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cell Phone Network Flaws Can Help Spies Get Around Encryption Apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even basic phone logs can reveal deeply personal information, researchers find. Stanford study shows how details gleaned from telephone metadata by NSA pose a threat to privacy of ordinary citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social Media Fame Shields Dissidents, Until It Doesnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social Media Fame Shields Dissidents, Until It Doesnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Its Like to Read the NSAs Newspaper for Spies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Intriguing Spy Stories From 166 Internal NSA Reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Closely Involved in Guantnamo Interrogations, Documents Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The SIDtoday  the internal newsletter for the NSAs most important division, the Signals Intelligence Directorate  Files. 9 Years of issues, released in batches starting from 2003 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Intercept Is Broadening Access to the Snowden Archive. Heres Why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is the news  but only if Facebook thinks you need to know. News publishers signing up to Facebooks Instant Articles system are feeding the beast with no guarantee their words will ever be seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 22:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is the news  but only if Facebook thinks you need to know. News publishers signing up to Facebooks Instant Articles system are feeding the beast with no guarantee their words will ever be seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 22:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under the Hood Security Features That Protect Your Mac: Discover the Less Visible Protections in OS X </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds probe mobile phone industry over the sad state of security updates. FCC and FTC coordinate probe of OS developers, hardware makers, and carriers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds probe mobile phone industry over the sad state of security updates. FCC and FTC coordinate probe of OS developers, hardware makers, and carriers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Told Cops to Recreate Evidence From Secret Cell-Phone Trackers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critical Qualcomm security bug leaves many Android phones  Texts, call histories   other sensitive data  open to attack. Fix still isn't available for most users, and many will probably never get it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Euro Parliament's Trade Committee Chairman, Bernd Lange: TTIP expected to fail after US demands revealed in unprecedented leak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edward Snowden: Governments can reduce our dignity to that of tagged animals. Foreword from The Assassination Complex, a new book about drone warfare, he explains why leaking information about wrongdoing is a vital act of resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US foreign intelligence court did not deny any of 1,457 FBI/NSA surveillance requests last year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Uber to Eric Schmidt, tech is closer to the US government than you'd think. Twitter was scrabbling to defend the appointment of a Chinese head with government ties, yet US tech has a busy revolving door with its own government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Uber to Eric Schmidt, tech is closer to the US government than you'd think. Twitter was scrabbling to defend the appointment of a Chinese head with government ties, yet US tech has a busy revolving door with its own government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook corporate network hack discovered by security researcher. Backdoor installed on Facebooks company servers had been logging employee credentials and exposing security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook corporate network hack discovered by security researcher. Backdoor installed on Facebooks company servers had been logging employee credentials and exposing security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SF wants to collect over $3.3M each year from Uber, Lyft drivers. If drivers are independent contractors, they should pay registration fees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MP3s being phased out in favor of MKVs on The Torrents. Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 04:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may be anecdotal, but I've noticed many of the torrent sites that previously used .mp**4**s have switched over to .mkv. Really annoying since all iDevices handle MP3s much better. It also seems a better (or at least, perfectly adequate) file format.

And, yes, I realize converters exist. But it's an extra step, annoying and the ratios aren't on point so now I have annoying black bars where before I didn't. To say nothing of the generational loss.

Is it more a FLOSS preference thing, QT Player for Windows being phased out, or something else? Is it a blip, anecdotal or a trend? Thanks! 

PS: thanks to /u/anu539, /u/asstalos   /u/TomLube for very kindly correcting my mental typo. I will write "MP4" 3,000 times on the chalkboard. Well, actually, I'll write a macro to blast it out via 3D projector, like searing Words of Gods blazing thru my consciousness. But you get the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Which is better for environment: Amazon Prime for (mainly) single items or buying locally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh.

My gut and rough numbers in my head suggest that my (adorable!) roommate has gone daffy but I can't convince them.

S/He claims that, rather than, say, getting a box of cat food at the local store, it's of equal environmental impact to order it thru Amazon Prime.

I think the 

(mfr  distribution centers  local store  my car  home)

 is better than 

(mfr  Amazon distribution centers  FedEx driver  home), 

particularly b/c when we go to the pet store, we tend to get multiple items, versus when s/he orders from Amazon, it's a single item, or Amazon ships multiple items individually anyway.

Plus the extra packaging and whatever nominal electricity is used for the device (but probably TMI for The Maths).

Further, the local route is happening anyway, so by my going to the pet store, it's "free" as far as carbon footprints go. Plus one large truck delivering a pallet load of tasty cat treats is better than 200 individual trips. Plus my car uses less carbon than that FedEx truck.

Thoughts? Anything beyond this line of thought you might think would work better?

Besides the whole, Buy Local thing, which has economic benefits over Amazon (again, TMI).

Thanks!

PS: S/He's very nice to cats, so it's probably not worth smothering him/her will a pillow while s/he sleeps to settle the argument. **Yet.** Thought reaching out to you might be a better approach. For **now.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mortality rate for homeless youth in San Francisco is 10 times higher than peers. A study by UC Berkeley researchers tracked 218 homeless young people over six years; in that time 11 died largely due to suicide or substance abuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft sues for right to tell customers when US government requests emails. Lawsuit argues that the government is violating the constitution by preventing Microsoft from notifying customers about agencies looking at their emails. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 19:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft sues for right to tell customers when US government requests emails. Lawsuit argues that the government is violating the constitution by preventing Microsoft from notifying customers about agencies looking at their emails. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 19:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft sues for right to tell customers when US government requests emails. Lawsuit argues that the government is violating the constitution by preventing Microsoft from notifying customers about agencies looking at their emails. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 19:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court rules warrantless collection of cellphone location data constitutional. Federal 6th Court of Appeals rejected a constitutional challenge, making it more likely that the US Supreme Court will consider the issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 19:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which is better for environment: Amazon Prime for (mainly) single items or buying locally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 08:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh.

My gut and rough numbers in my head suggest that my (adorable!) roommate has gone daffy but I can't convince them.

S/He claims that, rather than, say, getting a box of cat food at the local store, it's of equal environmental impact to order it thru Amazon Prime.

I think the (mfr  distribution centers  local store  my car  home) is better than (mfr  Amazon distribution centers  FedEx driver  home), particularly b/c when we go to the pet store, we tend to get multiple items, versus when s/he orders from Amazon, it's a single item, or Amazon ships multiple items individually anyway.

Plus the extra packaging and whatever nominal electricity is used for the device.

Further, the local route is happening anyway, so by my going to the pet store, it's "free" as far as carbon footprints go. Plus one large truck delivering a pallet load of tasty cat treats is better than 200 individual trips. Plus my car uses less carbon than that FedEx truck.

Thoughts? Anything beyond this line of thought you might think would work better?

Besides the whole, Buy Local thing, which has economic benefits over Amazon.

Thanks!

(S/He's very nice to cats, so it's probably not worth smothering him/her will a pillow while s/he sleeps to settle the argument. *Yet.* Thought reaching out to you might be a better approach. For *now*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber lawsuits timeline: company ordered to pay out $61.9m so far. Batting away lawsuits since 2009  heres a comprehensive roundup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medium and Twitter founder: We put junk food in front of them and they eat it. Ev Williams on feedback loops, giving a home to publishers, and finding critical mass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UC Berkeley students to file state sexual harassment complaint against professor. Allegations against Blake Wentworth, who was not terminated last year despite misconduct findings, renewed in significant development in scandal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UC Berkeley students to file state sexual harassment complaint against professor. Allegations against Blake Wentworth, who was not terminated last year despite misconduct findings, renewed in significant development in scandal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ta-Nehisi Coates's Black Panther review  a promising, subversive start. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Bernardino iPhone hack wont work on newer models, says FBI. Comey says US government in discussions over whether to reveal details of purchased hack that only works on 5C and older devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 02:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spies In The Skies: Govt surveillance planes routinely circle over most major cities  but usually take the weekends off. Heres Where FBI Planes Are Circling US Cities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spies In The Skies: Govt surveillance planes routinely circle over most major cities  but usually take the weekends off. Heres Where FBI Planes Are Circling US Cities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco becomes first US city to mandate fully paid parental leave. Activists hope new law will pave way for more progressive policies in the US, the only developed country that doesnt guarantee paid maternal or paternal leave. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco becomes first US city to mandate fully paid parental leave. Activists hope new law will pave way for more progressive policies in the US, the only developed country that doesnt guarantee paid maternal or paternal leave. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIFA president Gianni Infantino pulled into corruption scandal by Panama Papers, contradicting prior FIFA claims Infantino had no dealings with any of the corruption-tainted officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 20:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/IAmA: We are ACLU lawyers and Nick Merrill of Calyx Institute. Were here to talk about National Security Letters   warrant canaries, because Reddit cant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/IAmA: We are ACLU lawyers and Nick Merrill of Calyx Institute. Were here to talk about National Security Letters   warrant canaries, because Reddit cant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yishans (former CEO, not bound by NSL) take on Transparency Reports and Subpoenas, ELI5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Post an announcement in /r/Privacy for your new Sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 21:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool that you're doing this. Let us know how we can help.

 The /r/Privacy Mods

I see you already have @canarywatch. Perhaps build on that, too? And more generally, focus on other canaries to push forward the whole concept.

Really awesome. Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit removes warrant canary from its latest transparency report. CEO is staying mum: I've been advised not to say anything one way or the other. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit removes warrant canary from its latest transparency report. CEO is staying mum: I've been advised not to say anything one way or the other. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CloudFlare: 94 percent of the Tor traffic we see is per se malicious. Legitimate users suffer as Tor becomes favored tool of spammers and fraudsters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 00:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US says it would use court system again to defeat encryption. Feds say they can force entire tech sector, not just Apple, to disable security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US says it would use court system again to defeat encryption. Feds say they can force entire tech sector, not just Apple, to disable security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US says it would use court system again to defeat encryption. Feds say they can force entire tech sector, not just Apple, to disable security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iMac   External USB 3TB Seagate Drive, bought 2yrs ago. Should I update drivers? Whose, Apple Disk Util or Seagate's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 22:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, all -

Problem solved. It turns out - yay! - OS X is clever enough to not require HDD driver updates for external drives.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple designing its own servers to avoid spying; suspects that servers are intercepted and modified during shipping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple designing its own servers to avoid spying; suspects that servers are intercepted and modified during shipping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI may have found way to unlock San Bernardino iPhone without Apple. Federal authorities have cancelled Tuesdays court hearing with Apple, saying an outside party has shown a potential way to crack Syed Farooks phone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 02:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI may have found way to unlock San Bernardino iPhone without Apple. Federal authorities have cancelled Tuesdays court hearing with Apple, saying an outside party has shown a potential way to crack Syed Farooks phone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 02:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Americans and encryption: the stakes are higher than Apple v FBI. Malkia Cyril grew up under the threat of surveillance and says encryption is critical for human rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Americans and encryption: the stakes are higher than Apple v FBI. Malkia Cyril grew up under the threat of surveillance and says encryption is critical for human rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond surveillance: what could happen if Apple loses to the FBI. An Apple loss in the San Bernardino encryption case risks creating a world in which we can no longer trust the gadgets that track how we drive, when were home and whether the door is locked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond surveillance: what could happen if Apple loses to the FBI. An Apple loss in the San Bernardino encryption case risks creating a world in which we can no longer trust the gadgets that track how we drive, when were home and whether the door is locked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond surveillance: what could happen if Apple loses to the FBI. An Apple loss in the San Bernardino encryption case risks creating a world in which we can no longer trust the gadgets that track how we drive, when were home and whether the door is locked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paris attacker Salah Abdeslam 'backed out of blowing himself up', changed his mind at the last minute. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 22:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazil judge strips Lula of office amid mounting political crisis. Supreme court justice Gilmar Mendes says Lulas appointment appeared designed to prevent him being charged with corruption. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Government Error Just Revealed Snowden Was the Target in the Lavabit Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 06:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ProtonMail, the Easy-to-Use Encrypted Email Service, Opens Up to the Public. Includes beta iOS   Android Apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 00:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ProtonMail, the Easy-to-Use Encrypted Email Service, Opens Up to the Public. Includes beta iOS   Android Apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 00:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ProtonMail, the Easy-to-Use Encrypted Email Service, Opens Up to the Public. Includes beta iOS   Android Apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 00:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adblocking: advertising accounts for half of data used to read articles. Publisher pages are bloated, says Enders Analysis: 18% to 79% of data downloaded on mobiles is from ads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 19:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adblocking: advertising accounts for half of data used to read articles. Publisher pages are bloated, says Enders Analysis: 18% to 79% of data downloaded on mobiles is from ads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 19:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former cyber czar says NSA could crack the San Bernadino shooters phone. Richard Clarke tells NPR that the FBI just wants precedent and could have data already. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former cyber czar says NSA could crack the San Bernadino shooters phone. Richard Clarke tells NPR that the FBI just wants precedent and could have data already. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook, Google and WhatsApp plan to increase encryption of user data. Spurred on by Apples battles against the FBI, some of techs biggest names are to expand encryption of user data in their services, the Guardian can reveal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korean submarine missing and presumed sunk, say reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 08:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A City Mayor Asked the Pentagon to Use Military Drones to Look for Potholes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A City Mayor Asked the Pentagon to Use Military Drones to Look for Potholes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds fire back on San Bernardino iPhone, noting that Apple has accommodated China. Also, DOJ says failed iCloud backup irrelevant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds fire back on San Bernardino iPhone, noting that Apple has accommodated China. Also, DOJ says failed iCloud backup irrelevant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds fire back on San Bernardino iPhone, noting that Apple has accommodated China. Also, DOJ says failed iCloud backup irrelevant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI could force us to turn on iPhone cameras and microphones, says Apple. Eddy Cue warns precedent set by San Bernardino case could lead to company being forced to turn users smartphones into surveillance devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 20:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest policing tool to monitor rowdy spring breakers: Drones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon report admits it has deployed military drones over U.S. territory to spy for non-military missions over past decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Software VP Federighi: The FBI wants to roll back safeguards that keep us a step ahead of criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, any reports of KeRanger Transmission malware affecting any OS X computers? I can't find any online but thought I'd check with you brainy folks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that's all.

Did all the usual searches via the engines, Twitter, tech press and here.

Zero. (Yay, so far!!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intelligence Whistle-Blowers Fear Government Won't Protect Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why your phones security is unlike any other (Or, Everything I learned about digital security started with Whats your favorite color?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 02:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google as a Fortune Teller: The Secrets of Surveillance Capitalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you (yes  YOU!) like to see /r/Privacy handle the FBIvsApple topic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 23:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, all 

So, it looks like Apple being served ~~one~~ 10-20 Writs to ~~create a backdoor~~ gimp passcode security to the point where an asthmatic six-year-old wearing a straight jacket could brute-force ~~one~~ all of their devices is A Thing.

A thing covered by a number of reputable papers, general and tech. A thing covered by numerous digital privacy groups. A thing most of the tech sector is lining up to support Apple's fighting this novel interpretation of using the Writ act.

It'll go to the Supreme Court. Fo sure. There will be many stories on it. It is **Important**.

Yet at the same time, we're conscious that some may want to visit /r/privacy to read about something besides FBIvsApple.

We have our notions (I think we're leaning towards creating a FBIvsApple flair, then a script that lets you hide/find posts on this topic, but we're still discussing it in Mod Mail).

We want to solicit your opinion. So, post questions/comments here and we'll try to figure out the best way to handle it.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drown attack: how weakened encryption jeopardizes 'secure' sites. Researchers warn sites such as Yahoo, BuzzFeed and Flickr would be susceptible to attack, and credit card info, passwords and other data could be compromised. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 21:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman Suggests FBI Is Taking Advantage of San Bernardino Tragedy to Push Agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman Suggests FBI Is Taking Advantage of San Bernardino Tragedy to Push Agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman Suggests FBI Is Taking Advantage of San Bernardino Tragedy to Push Agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Wins Major Court Victory Against FBI in a Federal Writ Case in NY, Similar to San Bernardino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 01:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summoned to Capitol Hill Tuesday, Apple Comes Armed With 4 Key Questions Today Via Written Statement to Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summoned to Capitol Hill Tuesday, Apple Comes Armed With 4 Key Questions Today Via Written Statement to Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summoned to Capitol Hill Tuesday, Apple Comes Armed With 4 Key Questions Today Via Written Statement to Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple tells court it would have to create GovtOS to comply with ruling, claims in 65-page motion to vacate that it would have to build on-site FBI forensic lab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 18:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple v the FBI: why the 1789 All Writs Act is the wrong tool. Law requires a balance between flexibility and tyranny, and was never intended to allow the govt to dictate software design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple v the FBI: why the 1789 All Writs Act is the wrong tool. Law requires a balance between flexibility and tyranny, and was never intended to allow the govt to dictate software design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple CEO Tim Cook: FBI asked us to make software 'equivalent of cancer'; the debate needs to be conducted openly and fairly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple CEO Tim Cook: FBI asked us to make software 'equivalent of cancer'; the debate needs to be conducted openly and fairly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple CEO Tim Cook: FBI asked us to make software 'equivalent of cancer'; the debate needs to be conducted openly and fairly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 05:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FFTF.org: Rallies against FBI demand for iPhone backdoor planned at Apple stores in more than 30 cities this Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FFTF.org: Rallies against FBI demand for iPhone backdoor planned at Apple stores in more than 30 cities this Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carole Adams, mom who lost son in San Bernardino shooting, sides with Apple: Privacy is what makes America great to begin with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 20:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspect in Kalamazoo shootings that killed six was Uber driver, firm says. Police say driver picked up fare between first and second shootings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 20:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Encryption is not the enemy (US Senator Ron Wyden) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 23:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Encryption is not the enemy (US Senator Ron Wyden) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 23:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Memo Details USs Broader Strategy to Crack Phones. Agencies Conspired To Find Ways To Counter Encryption, Gain Access To Secure Consumer Devices, Including iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Memo Details USs Broader Strategy to Crack Phones. Agencies Conspired To Find Ways To Counter Encryption, Gain Access To Secure Consumer Devices, Including iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Wants You to Think Its Supporting Apple in Its Fight Against the FBI. It Isnt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 07:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the FBI's encryption battle with Apple. For months, the FBI searched for a compelling case that would force Apple to weaken iPhone security  and then the San Bernardino shooting happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 08:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the FBI's encryption battle with Apple. For months, the FBI searched for a compelling case that would force Apple to weaken iPhone security  and then the San Bernardino shooting happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 08:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple encryption case risks influencing Russia and China, privacy experts say. Analysts and lawmakers warn, ramifications could snowball around the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple encryption case risks influencing Russia and China, privacy experts say. Analysts and lawmakers warn, ramifications could snowball around the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Cooks letter to public stating why Apple opposes Judicial Writ to create new version of iOS bypassing passphrase delay/wipe protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Slams Order To Hack a Killers iPhone, Inflaming Encryption Debate. Judicial Writ Would Compel Apple To Write Custom OS Bypassing Passcode Delays, 10x Attempt Then Wipe Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Slams Order To Hack a Killers iPhone, Inflaming Encryption Debate. Judicial Writ Would Compel Apple To Write Custom OS Bypassing Passcode Delays, 10x Attempt Then Wipe Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EFF to Support Apple in Encryption Battle (Note this is in regards the Writ to bypass the Wipe Feature, not breaking encryption) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 08:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EFF to Support Apple in Encryption Battle (Note this is in regards the Writ to bypass the Wipe Feature, not breaking encryption) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 08:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NSAs SKYNET program may be killing thousands of innocent people. "Ridiculously optimistic" machine learning algorithm is "completely bullshit," says expert. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 07:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How this company tracked 16,000 Iowa caucus-goers via their phoneswhen you download an app to your phone and it says, Hey, can I use your location?, this is what can happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 20:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How this company tracked 16,000 Iowa caucus-goers via their phoneswhen you download an app to your phone and it says, Hey, can I use your location?, this is what can happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 20:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenage Crackas With Attitude Hackers Promise More Government Hacks After Alleged 16yo Leaders Arrest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 20:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sixteen-Year-Old Allegedly Behind CIA, FBI Breaches, Charged in UK: They're Trying to Ruin My Life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 20:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Is Trying to Scrub Its Employees Hacked Data Off the Web </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 21:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Police Have Used Stingrays Widely, New Documents Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Police Have Used Stingrays Widely, New Documents Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 21:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google to ban Adobe Flash-based advertising. 2016 will be the last year of abundant display-marketing based on the maligned plugin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 21:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US intelligence chief: we might use the internet of things to spy on you. James Clapper did not name specific agency as being involved in surveillance via smart-home devices but said in congressional testimony it is a distinct possibility. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 23:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assume Youre Being Monitored, Because You Probably Are  the Future of Workplace Surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 11:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How activists got a Black Lives Matter sign into the hands of Beyonc's dancers. In a now viral video the dancers hold a sign calling for justice for Mario Woods, an African American man who was shot and killed by San Francisco police. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 06:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyonc unleashes Black Panthers homage at Super Bowl 50  Star makes political statement with dancers posing with raised fists  la Tommie Smith and John Carlos at 1968 Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 15:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyonc unleashes Black Panthers homage at Super Bowl 50  Star makes political statement with dancers posing with raised fists  la Tommie Smith and John Carlos at 1968 Olympics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 15:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Bowl City is utterly, completely, lame. The city is paying $5 million for this sterile corporate theme park? Even the tourists are getting ripped off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 08:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI and NYPD Interrogated Me for Simply Reading an Article About ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 00:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scarlet Mimic: Years-Long Espionage Campaign Targets Minority Activists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden intelligence docs reveal UK spooks malware checklist, in connection with Sherlock Holmes and the Adventure of the Extraordinary Rendition, Poitras Whitney show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 20:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden intelligence docs reveal UK spooks malware checklist, in connection with Sherlock Holmes and the Adventure of the Extraordinary Rendition, Poitras Whitney show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 20:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University of Californias Office of the President Ordered Spyware Surreptitiously Installed on UC Data Networks, Including Web   Email </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 20:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap cab ride? You must have missed Ubers true cost. When tech giants such as Google and Uber hide their wealth from taxation, they make it harder for us to use technology to improve services or for innovative startups like Kutsuplus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 06:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollywood beckons for whistleblower who risked jail over Iraq dirty tricks. Katharine Gun lost her GCHQ job after telling the Observer how the US tried to spy on UN delegates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 06:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An inconvenient truth: Protesting for change disrupts lives. Politely asking for change has never worked, and never will. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 22:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An inconvenient truth: Protesting for change disrupts lives. Politely asking for change has never worked, and never will. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 22:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EFFs Year-End 2015 Who Has Your Back? Government Data Requests Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 Civil Liberties Organizations Call for Open Hearings on Section 702 Surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Cost License Plate Readers Are Turning Texas Police into Mobile Debt Collectors   Data Miners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kickstarter Page for Nothing To Hide. The Documentary by Marc Meillassoux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 22:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do We Expose Ourselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 19:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do We Expose Ourselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News goes all out to save Michael Bays Benghazi flop 13 Hours from its own lies and awfulness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 04:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb refuses to support simple measures that would enforce the citys laws. We now know why: Airbnb makes half its SF money with illegal listings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 04:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb refuses to support simple measures that would enforce the citys laws? We now know why: Airbnb makes half its SF money with illegal listings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 03:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Airbnb landlords rent out properties full time; local Airbnb landlords making millions by essentially turning their properties into illegal hotels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 02:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Airbnb landlords rent out properties full time; local Airbnb landlords making millions by essentially turning their properties into illegal hotels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 02:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Airbnb landlords rent out properties full time; local Airbnb landlords making millions by essentially turning their properties into illegal hotels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 02:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian view on the David Miranda verdict: a counterpunch for freedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 00:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrorism Act incompatible with human rights, court rules in David Miranda case. Appeal court says detention of Miranda was lawful but clause under which he was held is incompatible with European human rights convention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 20:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Lives Matter protesters block San Francisco's Bay Bridge. Five-lanes halted westbound as cars slow in unison and passengers pass chains through windows as part of protests for Martin Luther King Jr Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hypothetical: Sweden drops charges. Assange free to leave embassy. Likelihood of his being seized extra-judiciously, either in UK or Ecuador? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the movement (apparently) with Julian's legal case, assuming Sweden backs down, is he too high profile for someone *cough* us (or at least the US) simply seizing him?

I'd like to think the US is above that, and that would rend to shreds any legitimate court proceeding resulting after he's kidnapped. Then again, the US gov't does a lot of stupid things.

What are the odds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples Tim Cook Lashes Out at White House Officials for Being Wishy-Washy on Encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 21:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Redaction Re-Visited: NSA Targeted The Two Leading Encryption Chips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 21:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assassins Were Paid Less Than $30,000 to Kill Mexican Mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 21:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Do Not Track Ended Up Going Nowhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 00:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luke Tsais Best Bites of 2015 | EBX What the Fork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 21:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech companies face criminal charges if they notify users of UK government spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 01:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Helped British Spies Find Security Holes In Juniper Firewalls. Possibly a situation involving a third party hijacking a NSA-created backdoor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 04:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California approves TaxiOS as old school rivals take on Uber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California approves TaxiOS as old school rivals take on Uber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 20:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police waited two weeks to arrest man over alleged pipe bomb and anti-Muslim threats. William Celli, who has declared support for Donald Trump, was arrested in California on Sunday  despite warnings to authorities as early as 4 December. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 21:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple criticises Investigatory Powers Bill: Theresa Mays spying law could endanger privacy   security, company says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple criticises Investigatory Powers Bill: Theresa Mays spying law could endanger privacy   security, company says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Suspected Of Making Bombs In Richmond Home To Harm Muslims. His Facebook page said he would follow Trump to the end of the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Secret Catalogue of Government Gear for Spying on Your Cellphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Panopticlick 2.0 Tests Browser Fingerprint Uniqueness AND Tracker Blocking Plug-In Effectiveness! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Panopticlick 2.0 Tests Browser Fingerprint Uniqueness AND Tracker Blocking Plug-In Effectiveness! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any experiences w/ CS5   CS6 on El Capitan? Finally making the plunge from Yosemite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 02:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, all you wonderful people -

I have two iMacs that I want to move to El Capitan. I have Adobe CS5 on one that I'll be installing the backwards-compatible version of Java Script on from [here](https://support.apple.com/kb/DL1572?locale=en_US). I have Adobe CS6 on the other that it's critical that it works fine with.

a) Are reports consistent for the CS5 fix? Primarily PhS, Ill   Acrobat Pro. Any drawbacks on having this version of JS on it? Any increased vulnerabilities from those nastier JS-based trojans/ads? 

b) What's the status of CS6 behaving well with El Capitan? Fine out of the box?

It's super-annoying the pain that Adobe makes folks trying to use their software legitimately jump thru so many hoops. I'm hopeful, especially with CS6, it'll be painless.

Thanks!

After doing some research,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter warns users they may have been hacked by 'state-sponsored actors'. Social media company emails more than 20 users, warning them they may have been targeted by hackers possibly associated with a government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
