<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2522</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 16:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly that sounds more communist lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 16:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you get fluoride treatments. As a kid on well water in the US, I had tablets I chewed up then swished around in my mouth with water. You can also find fluoridated bottled water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 02:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for pointing out a coup and democracy don't jive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any concept of the democratic institutions in this country? Bernie Sanders candidacy is dead in the water. Just because you are angry and this is what you want doesn't mean the majority of this country does. The United States has historically been much more conservative than our Western counterparts. A large part of this stems from the Cold War where the US fought local communist influence with hate and discrimination while Europe adopted many socialist policies to reduce the sway of Communism. What do you mean by deposed? A  president of the United States has never and will never be deposed. If he does something illegal he can be impeached and then removed from office, but there would never be a snap election. No such institution exists in the US. If he is removed then his VP would move to the presidency. If both are removed, then it is the Speaker of the House who would take the office, which would be Paul Ryan. There is literally no scenario where a far left progressive wins, it just doesn't match up with the US electorate. If you are really angry become a political activist, reach out to the community. The US government is very much a bottom-up structure. Rally progressives to run for state legislative primaries, build-up progressivism in state governments and take back the country in 2020 through redistricting after the census. That is the only path for progressives.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 12:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you do not deserve to live in a democracy if you just seriously suggested a coup. People like you are the worst elements of the American electorate. Ill-informed and angry without purpose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost so many lunchboxes at school that my mom gave up and just used the standard brown paper bag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know, he is having trouble appealing to people that are not young, white males.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 15:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you are really saying is that they are whiter States.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans, Brace Yourselves for the Bunga Bunga </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 04:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 04:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would get the same thing Italy got with Berlusconi 
http://foreignpolicy.com/2016/03/02/americans-brace-yourselves-for-the-bunga-bunga-berlusconi-donald-trump/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 05:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called policy when everyone does it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make it seem like Hillary is the only one to make those decisions which couldn't be farther from the truth. The entirety of the NSC has to agree to thesr things and finally be approved by the president. With how confrontational the NSC has been under Obama I really highly doubt she could do this against anyone's disagreement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 19:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me this says "I fired some people and had everyone else do more work so there is more profit for the company." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 01:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Hillary I see a leader that knows how to put a good team together. She has the connections to build a strong cabinet and the management skills to make it work. She is a pragmatist that is willing to give a little to move forward on the liberal agenda. She is the politician we need, but not the one we deserve. 

Sanders is inspiring, he can rally the Democratic electorate much like Obama. That is the fear though. Populism is great for the polls but bad for running a country. He doesn't have the greatest success in Congress, he does not have the network to build a strong cabinet, and I don't see him being a great manager. Sanders is the politician we deserve but would only serve to increase the gridlock in Washington. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 23:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he's anything like me it is probably from falling asleep on the couch after eating it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go into polymers it is great, otherwise the competition is much more cuthroat because there are so many chemists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 15:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means it has both positive and negative charge, kinda the action verb of zwitterionic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 22:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't eat red meat because it fucks up my GI tract. Don't get me wrong, I love the taste of red meat and when I get a chance at a really high quality steak it is worth the pain later. Also, my skin hasn't been nicer since I stopped.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow Mr. Angry, let's all jump on the hyperbole bandwagon. Your comment belongs in /r/politics not /r/geopolitics. This is a civil space for open and honest discussion. Not your hate mongering and emotional blathering. I said it is more difficult because they are farther apart. I did not say they do not have any Western values. So, next time either add to the discussion positively or do not comment at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 13:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selection bias man. Those who come to the US generally want to be here and accept our values. The average non-urban Ukrainian is going to be much like the average religious conservative Midwesterner in the States. Either group has difficulty accepting the liberal values that represent the West.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 21:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this is the right path to a more sustainable peace, but it is much more complicated than just giving the Sunnis in eastern Syria and western Iraq their own country. 


In the end it will boil down to three new countries. Syria will keep the coastal provinces like Latakia and the areas surrounding Damascus. These areas are much more loyal to Assad since it has the highest Alawite population. This will also appease Russia since it will easily be able to keep its Mediterranean naval base plus the other bases in Syria which all are within this territory. 

The next country would be a Kurdistan. To make this viable however would require Kurdish land from within Turkey. The only possible way to convince Turkey to give up the oil producing Kurdish lands within its territory would be to swap some of the Sunni oil producing regions of central Syria (the land immediately adjacent to the new, smaller Syria). Without this type of land swap Turkey would never allow an independent Kurdish state for fear of invigorating internal separatist movements. Kurdistan would also take northern Iraq which would form the heart and capital of the future Kurdish state. 

The remaining land in Iraq, being predominantly Shia by this point, would be its own country and almost inevitably fall under the influence of Iran. 

After all is said and done the region will have been split into two Shia nations and two Sunni nations. Two would fall under the influence of Iran and Russia, while the other two would be US allies. This would create a balance in the region that is the best possible chance for a sustainable peace. The details will be messy, but it is the only real option left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 21:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah probably the water they pull out of drought stricken areas like California.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 18:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the hyperbole is strong with this one!

Hillary's stunts are tame compared to past scandals. It's more like she has constantly changed and adapted since she has been shit on her whole professional career for being a woman. 

 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_federal_political_scandals_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 22:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Populism is dangerous much like nationalism. They are both very powerful tools for political change, but can easily run out of control. When this happens the politicians that stoked the nationalist or populist sentiment become beholden to it. The recent [unrest in China](http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/jan/11/japan-china-islands-dispute) when Tokyo bought the Senkaku Islands is an example of politicians losing control over the dialogue. Really, both are tools for reaching and unifying an uneducated or apathetic electorate/population. That in my opinion is what makes both 'bad'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 23:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should contact the Irish embassy first and foremost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 00:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not necessarily a moral issue but a public health issue. Tobacco products, alcohol, and weed all affect development, which ends when the brain finishes maturing in the early- to mid-20s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is all about the passion. I love being a scientist, I love learning new things and teaching others to spread that knowledge. I love being my own boss. Grants are stressful, but every job has a stressful part when you are trying to be really successful. But if you don't have the passion to sustain yourself, it can kinda be soul draining. Definitely don't do it for the money it's not worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sud Sound System - Beddha Carusa [Italian ragga] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 02:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 20:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a serious mistake to call the past irrelevant. The present is a direct descendant of the past. All the shared memories and lives of a culture form its history and shapes modern thought. To call the past, to call history, irrelevant is asking for the hatred to keep growing. Why do you think the Europeans messed up the region so much? It was their total disregard for cultural, historical understanding. The Ottomans managed the region reasonably well because they knew the history and they were the culture. Never disregard the past because you will never find your way to a more successful future. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely laughable! Like literally I was just laughing to myself right now. This deal is far more complex than just supporting big business so much more, but your base hatred for the nation, the only nation, that protects and nurtures the liberal order, is completely unfounded. Would Europe be better off if the US stopped subsidizing their defense budgets? How would they defend against Russian aggression? How would they defend against North African instability? How would the freedom of passage be maintained in the South China Sea? Who would monitor and help train the forces around the Horn of Africa to reduce piracy risks? Who would check the insane blind ambitions of North Korea? Who would keep Taiwan safe from China? Who would keep South Korea and Japan from going at each other? Who would keep Pakistan from becoming a failed state? Who would keep Israel in check? Who could keep China from bullying its neighbors into economic submission? Europe has already shown its disdain for global leadership and spreading the principles of liberal economic freedom. 

So get off of your fucking high horse and learn something about the world around. Learn the challenges that the world faces. The dangers to your lifestyle which is only support by the liberal world order. Do you want regressive policies? Fine, vote in your left-wing populist nationalists. Or hate immigrants? The policies of the far right are pretty much the same. Dismantle liberal markets and centralize state control. That can only help people! Let's make business decisions a political game! That will certainly improve efficiency, stability, and provide more jobs. Well it doesn't that's why Greece is a shit hole right now. No, its not because German is pushing austerity on Greece. Its because Greece fucking lied to the EU about its debts and spending levels and the cronyism that supported the bloated and wasteful bureaucracy that drove the Greek economy. 

I'm pretty sure you don't even know what freedom means, sitting there comfortably munching away on your snacks while smugly commenting on the evilness of the US and its destruction of Western values. Check yourself you fat twat, realize what real oppression is: losing your job because you voted for the wrong person, having your ballot pre-filled, not being able to travel to the next city without having to bribe at least one cop on the way, have to bribe bureaucrats to get even the most mundane things done. So next time you call the US the pest of the West look at the weakness and cowardice of the rest. UK is just a lap dog to money. German will continue to refuse the mantle of strong leadership, France's politicians can't stop fighting with eachother and their restrictive regulations to project any significant leadership. Who does that leave? Absolutely no one you fucking twat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 18:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a result of market volatility due to poor economic management by the respective finance ministers and governments of those nations. Commodity production is inherently volatile and not good for basing an entire economy on. Just look at all the troubles OPEC countries plus Russia are having with the drop in oil prices. Commodity production should be used to support growth in other industries to improve a nation's base skill level in other industries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off that is not a necessary factor for food security, if anything that makes the food supply less secure. Variety and supply stability is more important than location. Singapore has one of the most secure food supplies of any nation and they barely grow anything on their own. Self-sufficiency is not a good policy to support this populist notion you are spouting. It is just pandering to specific industries and using populist messages to get the general population to swallow the overt protectionism. 

http://thediplomat.com/2015/09/singapores-impressive-food-security/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 16:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to get phase separation anytime you freeze a complex fluid. G=H-TS, when the temperature drops the different substances will eventually prefer to order into enthalpically favorable regions instead of the entropically favored disordered mixture at higher temperatures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what Verizon did with the net neutrality rules and look where it got them: even stronger regulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would. Precedence only matters within the jurisdiction of the court. While opinions and decisions can be referenced outside of that jurisdiction, it does not carry the same weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 22:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3r72yz/who_had_the_biggest_fall_from_grace/cwm3aqx

Thought you might be interested in my comment a little farther down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 22:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, it supports his claim that Bush was looking for a reason to go into Iraq.

pg. 31

"We had a ready-made portfolio of theories and plans about the threat Iraq represented. Such well-worn theories and plans concerning Iraq were more conveniently available than were any new conceptions the administration would have needed to create in order to respond against the actual source of the World Trade Center and Pentagon attacks. As Bob Woodward notes in *Bush at War*, before 9/11 "the Pentagon had been working for moths on developing a military option for Iraq. Everyone...believed Iraq President Saddam Hussein was a menace, a leader bent on acquiring and perhaps using weapons of mass destruction. Any serious, full-scale war against terrorism would have to make Iraq a target--eventually.""

"Although Iraq was seen as a potential threat to its neighbors, no study conducted by any reputable organization has ever suggested that it posed any direct threat to the United States. The United States had constrained Iraqi air strength by creating and maintaining no-fly zones since the First Gulf War. According to a 2001 assessment conducted by the Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) regional and military expert Anthony Cordesman, "Iraq's Gross Domestic Product (GDP) has been cut sharply since before the Iraqi invasion of Kuwait with per capita income (around $587 in 1999) and living standards far below pre-war levels.... In 1999, inflation was estimated at 135% and unemployment was high as well." In other words, in the moment before we attacked, Iraq was an impoverished country, and not one that could project any protracted threat to anyone." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 19:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out this book. It might help calm your tits. Great insight and a very fair analysis of the national security decisions of both Bush and Obama. 

https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/book-review-national-insecurity-a-look-at-american-leadership-by-david-j-rothkopf/2014/12/05/8dbfc71c-5ee9-11e4-91f7-5d89b5e8c251_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 21:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How am I supposed to debate a subject of which the other person has almost no knowledge? I might as well just hold my breath until I pass out. Of course there are experiments. Have you actually looked at the literature?!? That was rhetorical, obviously you have not. What do you define as an experiment? Simulations are in fact experiments very effective ones in fact. Does this count as science to you? http://www.sciencemag.org/content/348/6239/1132.short </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not all scientists have equal funding or credibility. Just because you have a PhD doesn't make you a great scientist, it doesn't even make you a good scientist. I know plenty of PhDs that can't design a good experiment to save their lives. You have a huge misconception of what it takes to become a good scientist. Just because someone has a PhD doesn't make them an absolute authority. Scientist are people too. They can lie, mislead, or be terrible at what they do. Why the fuck should they get an equal voice? Seeing this shit all the time is a huge pet peeve of mine. Quality is the most important thing in science, not quantity. People so often mistake the two it is extremely frustrating. Just because a paper is published doens't necessarily mean it is correct either. I just wrote a manuscript lambasting a study published in a great journal by a well respected scientist in my field because of his faulty assumptions and poor experimental procedure. 

If a scientist has a rigorous and quality critique then it will stand on its own upon review and will actually gain widespread support. If you look into the so-called deniers you'll find their methodology was shredded by subsequent studies from other scientists. That is how the field works. You can't make shit up and expect it to last very long in the scientific community. The general populace is another story, just look at how many people think vaccines cause autism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It most certainly is science, which is defined by the scientific method. Just because the tools aren't yet refined does not belittle the scientific rigor. Models will certainly become more accurate with better data, but they are working with what good data is out this points that we should at least be doing something that limits pollution and emissions. If not for limiting climate change, at least improving public health.

The main argument is not consensus. That means you haven't even read the papers or any details on the experiments or results. The consensus argument is used against the variety of politicians and pundits somehow claiming they know best without any sort of scientific expertise. Please learn how to comment on science. Maybe start by actually learning the scientific method and what science means. Then read the reports, find primary sources. The media is absolutely terrible at accurately reporting science. Find out for yourself. Don't be lazy and take others for their word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you know what you are talking about? Dark matter is just a place holder in the standard model, much like how the Aether was for the propagation of light waves. However, [Michelson and Morley](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michelson%E2%80%93Morley_experiment) attempted to prove the Aether's existence, but instead proved it didn't exist and laid the groundwork for Einstein's theory of relativity. The point is eventually experimental capabilities get to the point of being able to test theories, which always come first, and can either prove or disprove them. There was huge backlash at first, but the two went on to be the first Americans to win a Nobel prize. 

Onto the second point, salt? Do you even know what salt is? It is a generic term and a variety of electrolytes are unequivocally necessary for the basic functioning of life. Good luck having a working nervous system or muscles without salt.

Electricity is very well understood. Do you know the Maxwell equations? The more I read your comment the more I am sure you science literacy is....well....sub-par. 

Onto your final point, they are trying to predict trends not the weather in Detroit in 2687 will be exactly x. Please, educate yourself, go to the library, take some MOOCs, just do something to improve your knowledge base.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 19:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing about science though, it's not a belief. Honestly, I don't trust a journalist to determine whether a scientist is 'eminent' in their field. The reputation of individual scientists is determined by their colleagues in the field. Their papers and methodology should stand on their own, offering both criticisms to perceived insufficiencies and corrections to those points. When you make claims against the consensus of a specific field, it requires extreme rigor and patience. The founder of my field of study, [Herman Staudinger](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hermann_Staudinger), faced many difficulties in convincing the scientific community that macromolecules exist. The absoluteness of science will always prevail regardless of opinions and politics, that is what makes it so powerful. The problem is the general population has very limited scientific literacy and relies on the media and politicians to explain it to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 16:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, they can no longer make claims "in accordance with international law." Which would be a significant diplomatic blow. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ousted president Yanukovych sues Ukraine in European court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 14:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 05:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably from a stage fan. If she was speeding like the blur suggests, her ponytail would be moving, her sweater would too. And the wind shield wouldn't protect the side of her skirt, not with her legs that widely spread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 20:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look at the job market on the macroeconomic scale there was minimal job loss, but looking at specific sectors there definitely was lost jobs. However, that's the point. Let each nation do what they are comparatively best at. This will drive prices down for everyone and ideally increase market efficiency and productivity. The US stands to benefit the most from a free an open global economy and the TPP is a way to set up a rules based system that lives up to the higher standards of the US.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 20:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the problem in the US is from Medicare and Medicaid being unable to negotiate prices. This is then compounded by the long patent periods. If the negotiation powers change, I would expect to see a drop in US pharmaceutical prices, but perhaps a compensating increase in other markets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, pretty much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 00:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are not times you can really compare to the present day. There were huge external unifying forces that necessitated compromise between the two parties or resulted in overwhelming majorities. That timeline goes from Great Depression to WWII to the start of the Cold War then to the first two large scale military deployments of containment policy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 21:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One major thing to correct. 

 the substance can be heated so it becomes more runny/elastic, and then cooled back into a solid form

This is literally the opposite of elastic. Elasticity is the ability to reversibly deform. "Melted" glass is viscous not elastic. Also, only melting is only occurs with crystalline materials. The details are more suited for /r/askscience however. 


The most basic difference between glass (amorphous is another term to describe this) and crystal structures is the predictability of atomic placement. In a perfect single crystal, if you know the location of one atom, you know the location of all atoms in that crystal. In a glass, knowing the position of one atom does not give you any information on the position of other atoms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you anecdotally that it marijuana does inhibit driving skills similar to alcohol. The problem is it is harder to tell you are impaired due to THC versus alcohol. Driving impairment seems to last an hour or two longer than the high. Keep in mind this is my experience and others will surely differ depending on how they metabolize cannibinoids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 17:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice that you think decades makes for long-term economic policy...add to that your apparent ignorance to the WTO and literally everything you say is American nationalism with a dash of exceptionalism.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 02:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was explicit in not directly mentioning it because as a direct comparison it is mostly untrue, but that is due to the different cultural context of the same political ideology. The race superiority only came about as political expediency of achieving those goals (along with the humiliation Germans faced in Europe), the Weimar Republic failed utterly at this point of controlling inflation even though the economic fundamentals of production were returning. 

Protectionism is 100% wrong. The best way to approach these problems is through the existing international institutions such as the WTO, much has the Obama administration has. The idea is that all the global economies follow a predictable set of rules to discourage direct state involvement. Protectionist policies only serve to legitimize the behavior of the other party, the whole stooping down to their level idea. We simply cannot do that if we want to make progress in securing a prosperous and safe future. Free trade discourages open conflict, particular between major powers. If China has truly wanted to damage our economy they had the perfect opportunity to when Russia approached them during the height of the financial crisis to dump shares of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, which would have had a disastrous ripple effect through the US economy. Most of the problems now seem more related to an incompetent transition in economic production. The Chinese are pretty good at manage an economy focused around production, but are rather inept in the more complex, but more productive, services (e.g. engineering, finance, etc.). As for the currency manipulation, so what? Everyone nation does it: the US, China, Japan, the EU, you name it, they all do it. It is just a short-term macroeconomic tool. Long-term market pressure will force change that can either lead to reform or economic downturn (severity depending on the competency of those managing it).

Basically, protectionism would trigger a trade war. Tit for tat, until trust in the process starts to break down and the prospect of using force becomes more appealing. At this point, economic warfare could be just as, if not more, devastating than traditional warfare, thereby making it seem more appealing.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 22:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And the people supporting her really showcase how stupid our country is becoming.

Populations have always and will always have large segments of ignorant people. This is nothing new, this behavior is nothing new, it will happen 5 years from now, and it will happen 500 years from now. Strong institutions are what have enabled the progress of man from this callous idiocy that fueled much of human existence. Speaking purely from a ruling perspective, they are the group to be used and controlled by the elite, but thankfully this group has shrunk with massive public education and a secular liberal principles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 21:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie Sanders is unequivocally a nationalist socialist. There are no two ways about it. Many of his policy points on [trade](https://berniesanders.com/issues/creating-decent-paying-jobs/), would be economically devastating and quite possible lead to war. He stands against the liberal order that has overseen the most peaceful and prosperous era of human existence, which only prospers and grows through ever increasing globalization protected under the aegis of free trade. A Sanders presidency, expecting it would bring a favorable legislature, would drastically upset the global order. Fortunately, I believe US institutions are strong enough to stand up to him and his ideals even if he were elected. I doubt the Senate would ever be on his side. This would hobble much of his radical foreign trade policy, hopefully. 

If you really want to compare with past National Socialist parties, I would recommend this Foreign Affairs [essay](https://www.foreignaffairs.com/articles/germany/1935-07-01/national-socialism-theory-and-practice) from 1935. Don't get me wrong I'm not pulling that card, but his core views are very toxic and potentially harmful (way too similar to the [25 points](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Socialist_Program)), but so is any political capital cultivated with nationalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was espionage not war. If the US went to war every time we lost huge amounts of intelligence, we would already have gone through a nuclear WWIII.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What really needs to happen is to break down the obstacles in the labor market that lead to inefficiencies. I call this liberalizing the labor market. What prevents workers from moving with the demand of the market? Mainly skills and geography. The government has made some efforts in reducing barriers to moving through various tax incentives. I don't think much more can be done beyond that because then you start running into people wanting to stay for personal rather than financial reasons. There isn't any government policy that could overcome personal desires. The other more severely lacking one is skills. This requires a long-term cultural shift to significantly improve efficiency in the labor market. Education is the foundation of the labor market and that should start with a free education from pre-school through university and including trade schools. More emphasis needs placed on lifelong learning and developing flexible skill sets. This does not address the inefficiencies that tend to accumulate with age, however. Addressing this would require another tax similar to social security as a way to fund a comfortable stipend that depends on the size of the family while training full time for another field at an accredited school. This would be prohibitively expensive and risky to initially implement and would require a high productivity in the economy as a result of continuing automation. However far down the line this situation is, I still see this as an optimal intermediate on the path to a universal income. Which itself should only come after the rate of job automation levels off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So toss the baby out with the bathwater?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely. My ideal balance of the branches is a progressive judicial branch, a liberal legislature, and a conservative executive. I can't imagine it ever happening unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my thought exactly. The best economists and market strategists have to get the experience somewhere and the best places to work will obviously be the ones best at it which is evidenced by their profits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 00:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should just go the easy route and start taxing the shit out of it. That's what happens in the US. They're called "sin taxes" and are on things like cigarettes too. The view is to slowly price consumers out of the market while collecting gobs of money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How were you in 4th grade in 2001 and only 21 now? That doesn't add up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 01:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look closely you can see the brick lines too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 23:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the wall in the back looks like it matches between the pictures. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was young I dreamed of being rich, like Bill Gates rich. Now, I don't really care about money. I'm working on a PhD in a subset of physics and working with human rights NGOs on my spare time. My dream now is to make this world a better and more tolerant place. 

I stopped caring about money the more I learned what dickheads people in industry can be. I just like learning new stuff and teaching it to others, so now my bath is towards intellectual freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 17:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got all the hype. Sure it is an interesting universe, but I always thought her writing wasn't very good. Even 10 year old me thought she was a bad writer. I never read anything after the first book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are other ways to buy things. Might even be cheaper than what you get. You can get regular modafinil in the range of $1.04-$2 a pill depending on quantity. Armodafinil ranges from $1.21-$2.33. Just ask /u/ModaCat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 15:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also used as an alternative to Ritalin or Adderall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 16:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The third amendment claims were thrown out, but the rest are still going forward. 

https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/volokh-conspiracy/wp/2015/03/23/federal-court-rejects-third-amendment-claim-against-police-officers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 16:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on a declaration of war from Congress. Otherwise, the US is legally in peacetime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 21:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reza Shah was forced to abdicate during WWII because of his perceived sympathies for the Axis powers and to ensure Soviet access to Iranian oil. The Revolution happened almost four decades later under the rule of his son. Iran under Mohammad Reza Shah Pahlavi, the last Shah of Iran, was extremely secular, but that was not the root cause of the Revolution. Discontent was born from the greed and corruption of the Shah as he colluded with the AIOC and pilfered his countries oil wealth for personal gain. At this time, there were two main competing forms of government capitalist democracy (the West) and communism (the Soviets). The country and its people were repulsed by Western governance as it was seen being complicit with the plundering of their country, so that was not an option. Though secular, religion was still quite powerful, think of the US and Christianity during this time. This caused the religious establishment to be fearful of communism, officially atheistic, as they saw what the Soviets were doing to the Muslim countries around them. This really left only one powerful alternative, theocracy. People turned to their faith to relieve the burden of oppression. It is much like Ho Chi Minh reluctantly choosing communism as it was the only real alternative for fighting Western (French) colonialism. He was actually liked the US prior to our involvement in Vietnam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what stage of your education you are in. If you are in high school look for material science programs or mechanical or chemical engineering departments with a nanofabrication component. If you are already an undergrad try to find a professor on campus that does similar work and offer to volunteer in the lab or for class credit if possible. You will also want to look for REU programs during the summer. These are usually 8-10 week NSF funded research internships that are incredible, where you go to the whatever school and learn what it is like to be a grad student.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How else would ACS cover the cost of curating such a large database? Abstracts are free and in the case of older articles the first page is. Then if the author is still around you can contact them otherwise you can go to your local university library.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inorganics are more dangerous than the organics that he works with. I'm not sure risks have been investigated to the same degree as inorganic nanoparticles like gold NPs and silica NPs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first and oldest is tires. They use carbon black (nanoparticles) as a filler in the rubber for abrasion resistance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 15:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You start with the needed properties for a given application and through understanding how structure relates to those properties it is possible to create something that fulfills that need. That's how you form the hypothesis and then experiments tell you if it actually works or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BP and the Brits dragged us into that one :/
One of the biggest tragedies of US foreign policy in my opinion. A secular Iran would have been a very stabilizing force in the region.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 19:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for doing this AMA! 

My question regards the Israel nuclear program. This is one of the worst kept secrets in IR and a major sticking point in Middle East diplomacy. Recently, Javad Zarif published in [op-ed](http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2015/jul/31/iran-nuclear-deal-israel-vienna-treaty-middle-east-wmd) in the Guardian calling out Israel to disarm.  I understand Israel's desire for deterrence in a region surround by state enemies, but that threat has waned in recent decades with the rise of transnational terrorism. Deterrence simply doesn't work on non-state actors. It is also possible that political issues surrounding clandestine US involvement in the late '60s before the NPT could be holding this up. 

With this in mind, what do you think the ramifications would be if Israel declared its nuclear arsenal? Do you think it would be possible to convince Israel to disarm? How would this all intertwine with the ongoing Isreal-Palestinian peace process? 

Thank you again for taking your time to do this AMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 14:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is quite the bold statement, but you seriously aren't worth my time , so whatever.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 00:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, most of the Republican outrage is ramping up the rhetoric for campaign season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 23:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have to be ardently GOP to dislike the president? I can't dislike him for his poor management skills in the White House? Or is ineffectual policies? Or his lack of political will? Or his egotism?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 23:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of something called election season? Fury is what motivates the Republican base.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 23:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering how far center he is (he is *much* farther right than Hillary), I think we all know the real answer to you question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 23:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, unless he unleashes a flurry of orders in the next 1.5 years he is set to have the fewest of any 2 term president since Ulysses Grant who had 217 over 8 years. Obama currently has 213 and I project it rising to around 270. 

http://www.presidency.ucsb.edu/data/orders.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 23:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Iran deal is interesting, but he made far too many geopolitical sacrifices for it in my opinion. Like the removal of the missile defense programs in Eastern Europe. Other areas of inaction and inability: His pathetic response to Crimea and Ukraine in general, his absolute failure with Syria, the Libya debacle, the cooling of relations with Brazil, the shitty relationship with both Israel *and* Palestine, his Egyptian response, his response to Chinese expansionism, his poor record with the AfPak problem and India, his Iraq strategy, the whole "reset" bullshit, intelligence reform, backing away from the Monroe doctrine, the list goes on. He pretty much has the whole world trembling scared because of his weakness on the global stage. 

The Cuban detente is awesome, but progress will stop for a while after his presidency regardless of the next president due to Cuban demands over reparations and Guantanamo. 

Gay marriage was all SCOTUS, the president had no say in the matter, though some executive action inched things forward a tad.

Saying he is doing a TON is bullshit. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 19:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because he often mistakes rhetoric for action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The answer being America couldn't afford too. It could barely ready the second bomb fast enough. No way could it afford to waste one as a show of power, it had to actually destroy something. If a show of power would have worked, there wouldn't have been a second bombing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 04:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't want to rip his pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 04:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still plastic in there bud...epoxy lining on the inside. Same with canned food. Literally everything you have ever consumed from a store has come into contact with plastic at some point for a significant amount of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 18:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they have the same health benefits as Gatorade. If you are dehydrated, it is good, otherwise it is just bunk and about taste.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might be confused here. I was not talking about bis phenol S. I was talking about 1,4-cyclohexanedimethanol and 2,2,4,4-tetramethyl-1,3-cyclobutanediol. Two of the comonomers used along side terephthalic acid. Try to actually read next time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not heavy metals like iron or zinc. The ions that are put into water are various salts to give it a more 'natural flavor' like potassium, sodium, magnesium, calcium, and the like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 17:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope the exact opposite in fact...http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0278691512000865

The abstract is free and if anyone is interest in the full body of the text pm me and I can try to find a way to get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ion leaching is much worse than the even smaller ppm to pop  levels of monomer and additive leaching in plastic. Most metal water bottles you find will typically have a plastic liner anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, first off the trade name is Tritan not Triton, which makes a huge difference. Triton is a surfactant. Though, you obviously don't seem to care. Secondly, you  have a tenuous grasp at best of the science here. Polyesters have a much better track record in terms of biocompatibility than polycarbonates produced via bis phenol A. Are you disgusted by the leaching in your disposable plastic bottles? No? That's because there isn't any and Tritan has even better chemical resistivity than PET. The only difference between the material in new 'indestructible' water bottles and the material in a soda bottle is a flexible cyclic monomer (not aromatic, which pretty obviously needs emphasized for you). This addition adds another mode of energy dissipation that drastically improves impact resistance, which is one of the hallmarks of PC. Why don't you actually educate yourself instead of regurgitating the idiotic leftist bullshit that is on the same level as climate change denial and anti-GMO 'pseudo "science"'. The extra quotation marks are to point out the idiocy of both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 16:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to read this essay again after some more editing. Currently, it self-references far too much. It reads like a college essay and that takes away from its important underlying message. I also find it rather repetitive overall which contributes to it reading like a space filling essay assignment. If this can be distilled into a more concise argument, it would be much more beneficial for highlighting abject poverty as a human rights violation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 15:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't agree with the tone of this article or some of the assertions in it, I do agree with one of its core assumptions. "...economic sanctions forced Iran to choose between political stability at home and hegemony over the region." Sanctions alone, however, we're not the main culprit. It was Saudi Arabia refusing to lower oil output amid the free fall in oil prices. 

Iran to me seems to realize the benefit of becoming a mature and predictable member of the global community. Russia's economic problems really helped put this into focus. If a country as large and powerful as Russia can hurt so much from a combination of sanctions and low oil prices, what hope does Iran possibly have? Iran has a very vibrant culture and a younger generation yearning for the economic benefits they see around the world. It would be unwise for any government to sacrifice domestic stability over regional hegemony.  Without which the latter is doomed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they are both just as likely to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 05:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ground is an interesting story of corporate greed. Just as a disclaimer that I heard this from my parent who was a manager of one. The executives of the corporate headquarters were pretty greedy and funnelled a bit too much of the profit out of the company.  When shit started to hit the fan they all cut and ran, dissolving corporate and leaving all the franchisers SOL. After a few years a bunch of the remaining franchisees are getting together again as a corporate structure for more menu homogeneity and purchasing power. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 22:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The availability of information is no longer a limitation for direct democracy, but the capacity of the people still is and always will be. It is a full time job for our elected officials to run the government and create laws. It would be impossible for everyone to be fully informed of every relevant issue while maintaining any kind of expertise or productivity in an unrelated field. Parties exist to make choosing representatives easier as you generally know their policy leanings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say anything of the sort. There will always be elite simply because some people are more skilled in areas than others. What I am saying is that some child born to a poor family should have access to the same opportunities as someone from a wealthy family. The problem is most acute in education, more specifically pre-school, but continues on through higher education.  Why should the income levels of a child's parents determine their access to a high quality education, which very directly correlates to lifetime success?

https://www.law.umaryland.edu/marshall/usccr/documents/cr12nj12010.pdf

http://www.unesco.org/education/gmr_download/chapter1.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 01:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying there hasn't been progress thanks to all of those. But just because we are better now doesn't mean we can sit idly. Things can always be better. Progress demands action and change.  Saying things are good enough and patting yourself on the back is what leads to the downfall of a civilization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 16:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the goal is to keep heavily polluting and hope someone comes along with a magical device? Without investments at each rung, how is there motivation to research and develop the next one? As far as the anti-dumping tariffs go, they were completely justified. The whole point of dumping is to destroy the competition. Since the Chinese state owned firms were selling their panels in the US and EU at a loss there is no way a domestic company could match the prices. There is a reason dumping goes against the international laws and norms of the WTO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
