<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4091</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 16:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't just walk normally tho. You spin or idk try to cast some spell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm naked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  most expensive free thing

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alona is that you? That bitch took my pencil in first grade and denied it despite having my name written on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 23:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? 'cause that's written all over your name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all of them! i'm that greedy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Def! I actually asked because 3 people who I consider to be very pretty complimented me on my eyes. It was a weird nice thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say look into bitcoins. I personally wouldn't convert all my assets to bitcoins but it's by far the best when it comes to evading tax. You'll have access to it anywhere(realistically, all major cities) and conversion(and remittance) cost isn't as expensive as converting say, php to usd. Plus there's a high chance for its value to go up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend was an extra on one of Coco Martin's projects. He's already mainstream at the time. After one of the sets he went to approach my friend, ask her in a nice way, "Hello, kilala mo ba ako?"
My friend responded with, "Huh? Hu u?"

It was really awkward but we laugh about it every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do these patterns in my head. the idea originated from childhood but i only started doing them in my head a few years back. The idea is to do a pattern, figure; house, flower, etc., without lifting your pen nor repeating a line.

[these are the simple ones.](http://imgur.com/a/6Vep2) Sometimes it gets really complex and huge, sometimes i'm able to solve it, sometimes not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. I'm looking to have my tonsils removed as well. Just wanted to hear from people who've went through it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww man. did they stop hating after tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 10:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "deeper part of me" ***wink wink*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 10:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! and you look lovely, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you only have one contact saved :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did too! Wont start till next month tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend's friend tried to open a bag of henna ink using his mouth. It spattered over his face and mouth which stayed for a few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I still don't know how I landed a job 2 days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where in romania were you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to get a new dad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 10:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TRIGGERED!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 10:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the first time I played CS. Didn't know how to buy guns but I was headshotting everyone. EVERYONE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be able to get there as soon as you obtain HM02 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long time poe player. Hello </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nice! In that case just save the caps and only build supply rooms as needed. You might need them for certain objectives such as upgrade X rooms.

If you're planning to build a straight elevator shaft like me, you can maybe add a floor or two from time to time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure when exactly but I've only got back to playing fos when they released 1.6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just work on getting more dwellers. Build a medbay so you can start saving stimpaks early. Once you get enough people you can build the overseer's office for quest. I would build this right away at 18 dwellers but I make sure I have a few stimpaks before I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 20:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> box wont be there unless you have a mr. handy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.7.1 now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're similar in many aspects. However I have a defense mechanism for this sort of situation.

Anyway, to share an example.
Taong bahay din ako. People in our barangay are familiar with my face tho I only talk to a handful of my neighbours and some occasional vendors.

I often walk by this street, calmly, and just like you, I don't really expect anything to happen. Then these two teenagers started teasing me, "Ooh pogi daw siya oh. Pogi daw oh" in an irritating manner. Yung alam mong nang-aasar.

Initially I tried to ignore it but since they kept on going, I paced slower--waited for them to pass by and once they were in front of me, I asked them, "Anong sabi nyo?" "Trip nyo ko?" I must have said it in a really scary way cause that shut em up good(Both of them were bigger than me).

I kept walking and I wanted to keep walking but at that point I was thinking, they prolly do that to anyone smaller than them. So I turned back I realised they weren't moving. Apparently they were in front of their house already but was hesitant to enter. I waited anyway and just as they entered, I voiced the house number, "949, tatandaan ko yan." then left.

Admittedly, I was already pretty pissed before that incident.

Anyway man, You have to confront him if ignoring doesnt work. Else, tambay ka lang sa tindahan, food trip hanggang matapos sila, saka mo sundan! joookes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I WANT THE VIIIVE!! I've been into the VR scene since oculus DK1 altho I haven't really owned one. I've been active on (local and online)communities discussions/events. I love VR and would be a really huge upgrade to my then sony hmz-t1 and cardboard. This is too nice. Thank you and good luck everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 14:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my dad and his siblings were having a dispute about inheritance. One of them was a greedy fuck, thought his share wasn't big enough so he wanted to get more from dad's.

Dad was willing to give his land but grandma said, if he allowed it to happen, my uncle will just do it again on the other lands.

My uncle then decided to berate my father. He said terrible things despite knowing that dad couldn't take intense emotions due to illness. The one thing that really made me wanna do it tho was when he said, "Fine, I'll leave just enough way for your hearse to get through"

If I was at home that time. I swear.
Typing this is making my blood boil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leatherworking, fashion illustration, theory crafting/item crafting for games--prior to this I just wore every unique/legendary item I can find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A drug dealer and/or a stock trader. I'm really good at trading/buying and selling things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
