<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7498</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gave me a good chuckle. I hope not. I've been enjoying it so far so I guess I will go knock on some wood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestions! After this list is finished I plan on reading whatever I feel like but intend on continuing with more classics. I actually just finished In Cold Blood right before I started this list! For whatever reason I left it out, i guess I felt like I was starting to ramble on about my story. This was the only book I left out of my intro. Now I kind of regret it. Incredible book. It really sent chivers down my spine because of the detail Capote put into the murderers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saved this one. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy. I actually enjoyed the simplicity of the Man and the Sea. Plus it is very short. I'm sure the next one will be in a whole other ballpark, although I do like good war stories. We will see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After rediscovering my love for reading I will be attempting to conquer a list of 40 classic books. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been over 6 years since I graduated high school, and I'm still in school studying boring old textbooks to earn my second college degree. During that span of time, I thought that someone would have to pay me to get me to read outside of my schoolwork. I suppose I was too tired of staring at all these words for class, not to mention staring at a computer screen all day at work, and it was easier to lay down afterward and turn on the latest hit Netflix series. 

That was until recently.. For a couple of months during the summer I had no classes, freeing up a lot of time during my weekends. I was playing with my phone one morning and found a free trial of Amazon Unlimited-- so I decided to download the ebook of *1984* by George Orwell (Can't remember what made me pick that one but I knew it was considered a classic). The book completely sucked me in. I don't want to put out any spoilers, so lets just say that some of the story scared the shit out of me. After that, my college buddy mentioned he watched a cool tv series called *11.22.63*. I looked it up and found out it was also a Stephen King novel about JFK, time-travel, and altering history..woah..sounds like I could get into this. "Oh shit, the book is over 800 pages, I will never be able to get through this." Well, I checked this one out from a nearby library and decided to give it a shot. I couldn't believe how quickly I got engrossed in the story and didn't want to put it down. The storytelling by King made me feel like I was actually in the main characters shoes. Loving every minute of it, I finished that behemoth in only 2 weeks. I knew I needed to find another read fast to fill the void inside me that *11.22.63* left behind. Then, my best friend from my hometown suggested I read *Ready Player One* by Ernest Cline as it's one of his favorites (We're gamers at heart). This one..well this one was just flat out fun. I finished this one in another week's time. 

After telling my friend about how much I've enjoyed reading lately, he told me he was also looking to read more. We both wished we read more of those so-called classics back in high school and so on. So I suggested we do a reading challenge of some sort. Well, we decided to come up with our own list. He would pick 20 from a few online lists of highly regarded books and I would pick another 20. We both picked some of the same books, leading to us just filling out the list with a couple of our own choices. We picked our books from the following lists:

[Reddit's Favorite Books](https://www.reddit.com/r/raerth/comments/cpxkq/reddits_favourite_books/)

[Guardian's 1000 Books](http://www.listchallenges.com/guardians-1000-novels-everyone-must-read)

[and also here](http://www.loved.la/books/genre/Collections/1001_Books)

Once we had our 40, we shuffled the list and agreed to read them in the order they fall. So here is the final list. *drumroll*


**Book List**


* Cats Cradle by Kurt Vonnegut

* The Old Man and the Sea by Ernest Hemingway

* Brave New World by Aldous Huxley

* All Quiet on the Western Front by Erich Maria Remarque

* American Psycho Bret Easton Ellis

* The Perks of Being a Wallflower by Stephen Chbosky

* Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury

* Man's Search for Meaning by Viktor Frankl

* And Then There Were None by Agatha Christie

* The Call of the Wild by Jack London

* Sirens of Titan by Kurt Vonnegut

* The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams

* Any Human Heart by William Boyd

* Cosmos by Carl Sagan

* Animal Farm by George Orwell

* One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest by Ken Kesey

* A Farewell to Arms by Ernest Hemingway 

* Watership Down by Richard Adams

* Walden by Henry David Thoreau

* East of Eden by John Steinbeck

* A Clockwork Orange by Anthony Burgess

* The Giver by Lois Lowry

* Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck

* The Last of the Mohicans by James Fenimore Cooper

* A Wrinkle in Time by Madeleine Lengle

* Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas by Hunter S. Thompson

* The Things They Carried by Tim OBrien

* The Great Gatsby by F. Scott Fitzgerald

* The Handmaids Tale by Margaret Atwood

* The Long Walk by Stephen King

* The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night Time by Mark Haddon

* The Stranger by Albert Camus

* To Kill A Mockingbird by Harper Lee

* Wuthering Heights by Emily Bronte

* Crime and Punishment by Fyodor Dostoyevsky

* The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger

* Catch-22 by Joseph

* Lord of the Flies by William Golding

* Slaughterhouse-five by Kurt Vonnegut

* Post Office by Charles Bukowski



Our final list is interesting because he picked a lot of the ones you think of when you think about high school required reading and I picked more of the hidden gems that I first saw suggested here on Reddit. He also picked a few that I definitely read in high school; such as To Kill a Mockingbird, Lord of the Flies, Animal Farm, etc. However, I barely remember reading them and I sure as hell didn't appreciate them back then, so I look forward to reading them again. 

I thought I would share my story and post my list here to open a discussion about what everyone's thoughts are on the titles. Let me know some of your favorites you see listed, as well as ones you didn't care for. Please refrain from spoilers. 


**Final Notes**


It has been 2 weeks since we began the reading list and I am already on book number 4 -- *All Quiet on the Western Front* by Erich Maria Remarque. I am having a blast and learning so much already! Feel free to join in on our reading list and we can follow each other's progress! Can't wait to see what's to come on our list. 

**UPDATE 10/9/16** 

I have finished 5 more books since my initial post:

* All Quiet on the Western Front by Erich Maria Remarque

* American Psycho Bret Easton Ellis

* The Perks of Being a Wallflower by Stephen Chbosky

* Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury

* Man's Search for Meaning by Viktor Frankl

My favorites out of the bunch so far have probably been All Quiet on the Western Front, Perks of Being a Wallflower, and Man's Search for Meaning. But honestly, I have enjoyed them all so far, none that I would say I hated. 

**UPDATE 12/5/16** 

Checked off the following from my list

* And Then There Were None by Agatha Christie

* The Call of the Wild by Jack London

* Sirens of Titan by Kurt Vonnegut

* The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams

* Any Human Heart by William Boyd

My favorites from this group were And Then There Were None, Sirens of Titan, and Any Human Heart

AND as I waited for my friend to catch up I read some other great books:

* The Journey to the East by Herman Hesse (actually read this for school, but was pleasantly suprised) 

* Cannery Row by John Steinbeck 

* Lolita by Vladimir Nabokov

* Flowers for Algernon by Daniel Keyes

* The Most Dangerous Game by Richard Connell. 

I convinced my buddy to start East of Eden next on our list even though its out of order.


I have been slacking on the written reviews but intend on doing more soon as well as upon finishing each book. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 08:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though we have a guy who has a history of punching people...hmmm...i'll go with Nerlens. He tends to get fired up from time to time. He did nearly kinda sorta but not really take a swing at Jason Smith this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 23:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just added you. I have myself and 1 other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for 1-3 players for Pro-Am (Xbox One) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 23:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for at least 1 player to start a Pro-Am squad. I'm an 89 center and my boy is a 90 SG/PG. We both move the ball well and play unselfishly. 

Add bambaLans on xbl if interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're gonna get more clicks with Okafor in the title..well played.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 03:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Jahlil just got taken out of the game for the night. Finished with 25 points 10 rebounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 02:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me sad because Okafor is having a great night but chances are people will only talk about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is absolutely feeling it tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ish Smith behind the back pass to Nerlens Noel who dishes it to Jahlil Okafor for the easy slam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 02:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 07:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the OP should read: 

Sixers defeat the Kings to earn their 3rd win of the season. More importantly, Sixers avoid sparking a popular debate-- who will hit number 3 first.. Sixers (3-31) or Warriors (2-29)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerami Grant swats away Boogie Cousins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 05:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Omri! Omri Casspi..lets get the name right please." *cuts off* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 06:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those teams rebuilding in less time? Probably. But are they rebuilding more effectively? That has yet to be seen. Only time will tell who is competing deep into the playoffs years from now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 21:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nik Stauskas aka Sauce Castillo](http://ftw.usatoday.com/2015/03/closed-captioning-error-gives-nik-stauskas-the-nickname-he-deserves-sauce-castillo)

I don't know why, but it just fits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 02:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the interview](http://youtu.be/crJr5aOJv5Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [THIS] (https://twitter.com/sandrogasparro/status/677304128792616962) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see that you followed and I can't find your gamertag for some reason. I'll try again later tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 21:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah add bambaLans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for at least 1 Pro-Am player to team up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and a friend need at least one more player to team up with in order to play pro-am together. We are both trying to develop our new myplayers. We both play smart and move the ball well, but just aren't rated that high yet. I just created a new center 60 overall and he is an 80 SG. Let me know if your up for it! 

EDIT: On Xbox One </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 02:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was scared his foot shattered when he kicked the ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joel Embiid spotted shooting free throws without walking boot at Barclays Center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 02:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 05:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you upload these so fast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 05:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The controller at the edge of his bed says he's a PS4 guy.. [Jah's Instagram](https://instagram.com/p/9HnkQVgdaZ/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 03:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philadelphia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A playlist I shared a while back and got a lot of great feedback. I have since added a lot to it. Mostly consists of Rock/alternative favorites, but also includes a little Hip-hop as well. I left out a ton of Pop songs for now. Let me know what you think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30+ hours of nostalgia for those who grew up somewhere around 1990-2005. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 23:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X-post from r/spotify yesterday. 40 of my favorite tunes that either don't show up on an artist's top songs or just often get overlooked. Features mostly alternative, rock, and indie along with some Hip-Hop. More playlists to come. Hope you discover something new. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 01:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Hope there were some unfamiliar ones as well. It was hard to gauge the popularity of some songs if they were by a popular artist so I just referred to the internet.. youtube views, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 00:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha some of my favorites. Gotta love variety! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 20:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40 of my favorite tunes that either don't show up on an artist's top songs or just often get overlooked. Features mostly alternative, rock, and indie along with some Hip-Hop. More playlists to come. Hope you discover something new. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40 Songs That Demand More Plays (Part One) - 40 different artists. Discover some new tunes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 20:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 21:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, i'm positive. I've been testing it with only 3 songs as well using the similar artist search and sometimes the search button won't work. I managed to get it go through a couple times but it only pops up as those three songs on Spotify. Strange. I've tried resetting the cookies on my browser but no luck yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotlistr sounds like just the thing i'm looking for. However, when I input tracks into the last.fm similar track search my playlist comes out as those same tracks I entered into the text box. Can anyone help me with this? I don't have adblocker on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A low-key playlist I made a while back with a relaxing vibe. Features plenty of acoustic sounds from different generations. (Includes Bob Dylan, Simon   Garfunkel, Ben Howard, Modest Mouse, The Shins, and more) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 02:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10+ hours of upbeat alternative, indie, rock, and more. Would love to hear your suggestions for more upbeat music. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Put a little pep in your step with this upbeat playlist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 21:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 16:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we carrying this thread onto this week? Might as well. Heres my discover weekly for the 26th of October. Love these things. Haven't even gotten through mine yet. 

https://open.spotify.com/user/spotifydiscover/playlist/4jDIPuR7vUjRAJuXuUlzpp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 03:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call. I'm actually surprised I missed that one. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 02:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will have premium for 1 month after your last payment went through. Since you must have already payed within the last month you have that whole month after of premium. So you should be fine. If you go to your account settings it should tell you the date your premium expires.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 00:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
