<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4125</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plant hormones called jasmonates protect against herbivores, but evidence that they help plants in the wild was lacking. New findings show that jasmonates benefit coyote tobacco in its natural habitat against a subset of its herbivores (i.e. mammals but not insects). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plant hormones called jasmonates protect against herbivores, but evidence that they help plants in the wild was lacking. New findings show that jasmonates benefit coyote tobacco in its natural habitat against a subset of its herbivores (i.e. mammals but not insects). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 13:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lay summary/digest from Research article:
Our genomes contain a record of historical events. This is because when groups of people are separated for generations, the DNA sequence in the two groups genomes will change in different ways. Looking at the differences in the genomes of people from the same population can help researchers to understand and reconstruct the historical interactions that brought their ancestors together. The mixing of two populations that were previously separate is known as admixture.

Africa as a continent has few written records of its history. This means that it is somewhat unknown which important movements of people in the past generated the populations found in modern-day Africa. Busby et al. have now attempted to use DNA to look into this and reconstruct the last 4000 years of genetic history in African populations.

As has been shown in other regions of the world, the new analysis showed that all African populations are the result of historical admixture events. However, Busby et al. could characterize these events to unprecedented level of detail. For example, multiple ethnic groups from The Gambia and Mali all show signs of sharing the same set of ancestors from West Africa, Europe and Asia who mixed around 2000 years ago. Evidence of a migration of people from Central West Africa, known as the Bantu expansion, could also be detected, and was shown to carry genes to the south and east. An important next step will be to now look at the consequences of the observed gene-flow, and ask if it has contributed to spreading beneficial, or detrimental, mutations around Africa.

Abstract from Research article:
Similarity between two individuals in the combination of genetic markers along their chromosomes indicates shared ancestry and can be used to identify historical connections between different population groups due to admixture. We use a genome-wide, haplotype-based, analysis to characterise the structure of genetic diversity and gene-flow in a collection of 48 sub-Saharan African groups. We show that coastal populations experienced an influx of Eurasian haplotypes over the last 7000 years, and that Eastern and Southern Niger-Congo speaking groups share ancestry with Central West Africans as a result of recent population expansions. In fact, most sub-Saharan populations share ancestry with groups from outside of their current geographic region as a result of gene-flow within the last 4000 years. Our in-depth analysis provides insight into haplotype sharing across different ethno-linguistic groups and the recent movement of alleles into new environments, both of which are relevant to studies of genetic epidemiology.

Link to press release (including title) https://elifesciences.org/elife-news/press-package-scientists-reveal-sub-saharan-africas-legacy-of-past-migrations-over-last-4000-years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists reveal sub-Saharan Africas legacy of past migrations over last 4,000 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For title and more details see press release: https://elifesciences.org/elife-news/press-package-flatworms-left-in-sunlight-spur-investigations-into-rare-metabolic-disorders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flatworms left in sunlight spur investigations into porphyrias, rare metabolic disorders that can cause extreme sensitivity to light, facial hair growth, and hallucinations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study with rats shows that the synthesis of estrogens in the brain contributes to the escalation of seizures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 16:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
