<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8940</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ocean at the End of the Lane by Neil Gaiman.

I'd also recommend Odd Thomas.  He's a 20-ish character but pretty much everyone is oblivious to the boogeymen he sees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Parasol Protectorate by Gail Carringer. - Werewolves, vampires, ghosts and the soulless.

The Sookie Stackhouse books by Charlene Harris (The books True Blood is based on) have quite a lot of were side characters along with the vampires.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Old Kingdom series by Garth Nix (I'd start with Sabriel)

His Dark Materials by Philip Pullman - I recommend because you like HP, they are written for a somewhat younger crowd but they're still engaging.

Odd Thomas by Dean Koontz - often classified as horror but they're really much more fantasy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that so many of the classics deal with the human condition, at least as it was in the their time period.  Often references classics that I would recommend:

Jane Austen - Pride and Prejudice; Sense and Sensibility; Mansfield Park; Emma; Persuasion - All dealing with various aspects of the human condition - usually family relationships, constraints of society - Mansfield Park addresses a fair amount of morality and views on slavery.

The Bronte sisters - Wuthering Heights as someone else recommended, Jane Eyre

To Kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee - life in a small southern town and how being different impacts one's life, how the lottery of birth can dictate your circumstances

I, Robot by Issac Asimov - Fantasy/AI/the morality and ethics of creating AI and how "laws" can be bent or broken based on perspective

The Giver by Lois Lowry 

Brave New World by Aldous Huxley - Both this and the Giver are dystopian society books with very interesting perspectives on what affects human behavior and thought and how it can be controlled.

Not so much classics exactly as those I've found interesting...

In the Garden of Beasts by Erik Larson - historical about the US ambassador that was posted to Hitler's Berlin with his family - I would also recommend his others - The Devil in the White City, Thunderstruck, etc - they're histories that are just extremely interesting.

Gun, germs and Steel by Jared Diamond - a fascinating look at the development of the modern world

The Abhoreson Series by Garth Nix - fantasy series

Ender's Game by Orson Scott Card - debatable that this is a classic in sci-fi but certainly addresses what it means to be human


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaving the Saints by Martha Beck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
