<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy! Be careful, however, it is *powerful* stuff! Make sure you enjoy the stair climb in the belfort, and perhaps a scenic river cruise. I can also recommend the beer at De Halve Maan brewery, though I was to hungover to take the tour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 14:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A recommendation, from one beer lover touring Belgium to another, for Bruges: you must go to De Garre for a glass or two of their house Tripel. A little hard to find, down an alley between two chocolate shops, just off the centre of town. Their house brew is only available on the premises, so please do yourself this favour!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 23:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon to be torn down for more condos, alas.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 23:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is beautiful, inside and out. The grounds are used primarily by people in the neighbourhood walking their dogs, but the building, since its restoration, looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's low-relevance, and then there is this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 07:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you just, y'know, tell us what is in it, rather than try and bait people in? This isn't facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 05:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back the Sargon. Good lord, let me have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 21:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article. I moved here shortly after it came out, and this gives me a new persepctive on why things may be the way they are.

From personal experience, the neighbourhood has been trying to tidy itself up, but the "element" is still there. In addition to the blood and guts that actually make the news, several stores have been reporting break-ins and personally, my bbq was half-stolen (just the lid and the pipes, ffs) a few weeks ago. All in all, it is a fairly decent neighbourhood, with a lot of good people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn tootin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been living in the Monarch Park area for 5 years now. Since I moved in, there are all kinds of new bars, restaurants and shops from Greenwood to Woodbine (my stretch). I have noticed a steady march towards "nice" from "sketchy" in this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  its middle class procreationville

Same goes a few blocks east. Check out East Lynn Park on a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be many comments from friends this week about my "living conditions". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starbucks was fine when it was at Coxwell   O'Connor. Is this my first feeling of NIMBY-ism?! Although to be fair, it *is* a long walk to Red Rocket. But Circus does fill the void when a good cup is necessary... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sell $3 bottles of 50 faster than the Beer Store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, and they charge nicer too. Can't I have a happy medium between Broken-White-People-Bar and "That will be $25 for your fancy pizza?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Big Nickel](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Big_Nickel), of course! 

If you are in Quebec City, you should make time to wander Vieux Quebec, and the Plains of Abraham. Beautiful neighbourhood and park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 13:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably will grab a couple bottles. One of my favourites from them. But $8? Blargh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 07:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are accurate pictures of my childhood throughout this gallery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's file this under "Things I hope my girlfriend doesn't read before we go camping this weekend". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duly noted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 11:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea this was a thing. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which LCBO locations are best for craft beer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 07:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in the east end. Just wondering if there are good, reliable locations in the city for all the awesome brews I keep hearing about. If anyone feels like divulging their secrets, that is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 05:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might give it a whirl this weekend. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 04:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have only made hollandaise the traditional way and it is truly not a thing to prepare when already hungover. However, I recently watched [this video](http://www.seriouseats.com/2013/04/video-foolproof-hollandaise-in-2-minutes.html), which may change all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 04:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and asparagus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I draw our attention to the CIBC Pan Am stage?

Everyone should be at Charles Bradley's show. Just amazing performer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 08:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made in America was the first time I caught her act, as well! High energy, and a successful Hendrix cover? Blew me away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 17:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at 6am, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 10:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who uses the east end of the Gardiner frequently, I agree. We already have few enough arteries in and out of the city. I would love to not take it, but if I am working in Burlington or Mississauga, what alternative is there? 

Curious: Would knocking it down past Jarvis disconnect it from the DVP?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did that bottle come from? Haven't seen it before.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way he says it: "You've never *beeen*?" is so perfect. Utterly quotable episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I think my respect level for the Archer crew is maxxed out, here comes another bit of trivia out of left field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. I've never seen the Fracture anywhere, but do enjoy a double IPA. Keeping an eye out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 06:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not clear from the emails obtained by MobileSyrup when Uber plans to launch the service in Toronto

Title: They're doing it! 

Body: We're not sure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 04:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The Boneshaker is the only one I really connected with. The 416 is alright, but my appreciation drops off dramatically after that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 04:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I am around the corner from the newly-minted [Left Field Brewery](http://www.leftfieldbrewery.ca/), I have had their Eephus Oatmeal Brown Ale and Maris* Pale Ale in the fridge the last few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 02:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not spicy. A little spice, but nothing overpowering. I might toss in a couple more next time. Use your discretion, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 17:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made [this recipe](http://www.reddit.com/r/slowcooking/comments/32ny1q/the_best_thing_ive_ever_done_with_my_slow_cooker/) on friday. Just awesome. Obviously culled from /r/slowcooking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 03:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaat? When was this? I'm right around the corner, but haven't been in the area today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 11:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a beer! Have a nap! Get sexy spots for the Superjam! Ride the ferris wheel!

...actually, you could probably do all these things in two hours. Make me proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....does this apply only to garlic? Or fresh garlic? We received some ultra-fancy infused oil as a gift. Not sure if garlic is involved, but I surely will be checking the label when I get home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grocery stores would sell only six packs or less, and have limited sale hours. 

You still won't. Do you think the grocery stores will be allowed to sell later than the LCBO or Beer Store? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 21:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I think he knows that.](http://i.imgur.com/UpzfJKc.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drove to the amphitheater once. ONCE. Getting there was the usual hassle, parking wasn't cheap. Leaving was ridiculously busy and slow. I just suck up the ttc + walk now, but the GO to exhibition might be a viable option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remembering parts of that movie gives me shudders.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 15:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That is the axe that killed me"

Hooked me right at the start, but I am probably misquoting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't dive in Canada, or rather I haven't, other than my checkout. And if I did, a dry suit would be mandatory, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 21:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are near Toronto, I can recommend [Aquarius Scuba](http://www.aquariusscuba.com/), where I did my checkout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did my open water course last year, ran about $500 (in Ontario). Done over two weekends. 

The equipment can get pricey, if you want it to. I bought fins and a mask/snorkel, because who wants to share those with strangers! I was told that if I intended to carry on with it long term, a dive computer would be the ideal next investment, since it keeps records of your dives, tracking your nitrogen and such over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 12:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palms immediately sweaty, gag reflex triggered for some reason. Thanks for tonight's nightmare, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to agree as well. We stayed at a hotel in Poperinge, rented bicycles and rode up to In de Vrede. Lovely ride (bit rainy that day), and we got to do all the sampling we could handle. Bought a couple of six-packs of 12, and wobbled back. Still have some left, aging nicely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see an LCBO worker do an LCBO worker's job. I mean, no offense to those who work there, but their methods for solving my problems are no better than my own. Staring blankly at shelves, checking the same areas like I haven't been in the store for twenty minutes doing the same thing. There never seems to be anyone with a knowledge of what is in stock. And god forbid I ask them to call another store. "Just look online," they say, like I asked them to blend a puppy, "It should tell you." 

(I eagerly await options on where to buy my alcohol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think Bonnaroo is suffereing? Simply from the increasing number of options? I personally think they are moving more towards the 'profitability' aspect over putting on the best possible festival. Blatant sponsorship is one of the more annoying aspects. Cramped set times get annoying too (unavoidable, I know, and part of the fun).

We've got a few new ones blooming up her in Southern Ontario, but we'll see which ones survive. They seem like half-festivals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 03:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I exaggerate, of course. Proper sweet tea is like proper homemade lemonade. Delicious, but you shouldn't drink it all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good lord, the autocorrect whargarrbl is strong in this thread. Take a minute before you hit send, people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 20:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno. Proper sweet tea is more like brewed tea, served ice cold, with a 1:1 water:sugar ratio.

Proper sweet tea is amazing. The stuff that comes in a jug is "just" iced tea, indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 04:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is specifically for scuba divers. Just simplified signs and gestures that get the point across quickly and, hopefully, universally.

That being said, dive buddies who know sign language can communicate even more effectively underwater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planning a Trans-Canada road trip. Does anyone have experience travelling/camping along the Mackenzie Highway? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vague plan is to go north from Edmonton to Yellowknife or Whitehorse, but no solid plans yet.

Looking for some advice on where to stop, camp, etc., from anyone who has travelled the region. It's the only part of the trip that seems a little daunting to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BlogTo "reporters" can't even make it to the east end, let alone Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 17:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things have really started changing in the last few years. Although there certainly still is an element of "charm" the further east you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 06:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Penny Arcade](http://art.penny-arcade.com/photos/221858835_PP6z6/0/1050x10000/221858835_PP6z6-1050x10000.jpg) has you covered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 00:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We head down with a big group (6-14 in the past) so we always meet up at the tents at the back of the What before headliners/pre-headliners. Whoever wants to bury themselves in the crowd sharpens their elbows and makes a run for it, those who just want to chill with a hacky-sack or whatever relax. It's a good system, give it a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 05:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Off the Hook](http://www.offthehookfishandchips.com/) @ Broadview and Danforth has a halfway decent poutine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 05:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot that all their reviews are from 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 05:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought some pre-made pizza dough, 700g worth. Any thoughts on how I should divide it for the skillet recipe? Been meaning to try it for a while.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely one of my favourites. One of my prized books is a complete Holmes set that I browse through at irregular intervals. Such great stories.

Out of curiosity, have you read Neil Gaiman's ["A Study in Emerald"](http://www.neilgaiman.com/mediafiles/exclusive/shortstories/emerald.pdf)? He wrote it for some anthology/tribute to Holmes, as I recall, and was later collected in one of his own anthologies. Might be an interesting read, with you having so recently finished the source material.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 04:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When an author changes their style, or maybe repeats themes, etc. from previous books, it frustrates me. It's hard to explain properly. 

Some examples, perhaps: 

China Mievielle had me hooked with Kraken and Perdido Street Station, but when I tried reading The City and The City? Nothing clicked. Still unfinished. 

The first two books of Philip Jose Farmer's Riverworld had me interested, but His Dark Design felt like it was just re-hashing old ground. Plus the extensive autobiography of the character with the same initials as the author...ugh.

I haven't enjoyed anything by Chuck Palahniuk since Rant. I feel like he lost something, maybe it's just me. And I loved most of what came before.


As for sci-fi/fantasy recommendations? China Mieville's Perdido Street Station and The Scar, John Scalzi's Old Man's War (haven't read the sequels yet), Warren Ellis' Transmetropolitan, if you are a graphic novel person.

Don't get discouraged! What I have learned is to just read what you like. Branching out can be fun and interesting, but you should still enjoy reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 15:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, why would a translation not be in the public domain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 05:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a person who once rode that very bus: You are drastically overstating the comfort level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 02:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try and get a couple glasses in you at De Garre, in Bruges. Great place, excellent beer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 04:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo... May sometime?

Source: have subcontracted with PCL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 03:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just stewing beef. I have never had a problem with toughness. That 2 hour cookdown could soften a rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 18:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds very similar to my beef goulash recipe. I use Hungarian sweet paprika, which gives it a really nice flavour without being too smokey/spicy. Also serve with kajmak cheese (doesn't last long). I need to try making spatzle though...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 03:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say Jones is my favorite member of Zep, now. It is easy to love Bonham for the representation of reckless abandon and innate skill. And Page and Plant are household names. But JPJ, imho, is the coolest musician in the bunch. I've seen him twice with Steve (Roo and Glasto) and I know he will play with just about anyone he finds interesting. What a chill guy. What an embodiment of the spirit any music festival should strive for. Especially Bonnaroo, built on the back of the Jam Sesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 00:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always heard Aussies paid more for games, but I never thought it could happen to me. Oh well, Summer Sale, here I come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 07:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed the mobile app is giving me prices in USD...dunno what that means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Currently vacationing in Australia. Am I missing out on the sale prices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 07:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I am getting the $AUS price, despite being Canadian, due to my location. Is this correct? I mean, missi g the sale for a month-long vacation is totally a first world problem, I was just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant XKCD](http://xkcd.com/277/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got dinged in a "just-a-minute" coffee stop at the mcdonald's on bloor, near sherbourne. Parked just behind (in front? it's been a while) of the legitimate parking spots, and had a ticket on my windshield before my hash brown got cold and greasy.

Moral: I doesn't do that anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 23:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be in the Mayan Riviera/Cozumel in March. I eagerly await the update to this thread. I have heard Chichen Itza is nice, but touristy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 20:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a question: We have a dozen Westvleteren 12 that we brought back last year. Currently a) standing up b) in a dark cupboard. We crack a couple about every 6 months. Is this wrong? I thought for some beers bottle conditioning was good. I see so many strong opinions on aging v. just-drink-it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bugs Bunny would be so proud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Bring Me the Disco King* is one of my favourite Bowie tracks altogether. And yes, it had my friends who are "huge fans" saying things like "What album is this from?", and "(after checking phone) Oh, it *is* Bowie!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 13:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am lucky in that I leave for work around 5am most days. No traffic to speak of. My Golden Rule For Driving In Toronto: "Stay off all highways while the sun is up".

I agree with what /u/crankybadger said, however. You get a feel for the flow of traffic, if it is your regular commute. I could predict the QEW's ebb and flow like a mariner when I was driving to Burlington every day. And my choices in the "Lake Shore or stay on Gardiner?" riddle almost always led to victory.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are starting to refer to anything near streetcar tracks "core" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets not pretend mine has been 'recently renovated'. No balcony either. We got real lucky. I need to coerce the landlord into fixing some shit though. Problem is, we have too much furniture now to downsize :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 16:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are definitely trying tonget someone who will pay the same for a shitbox cityplace condo. All things aside, 7.5' ceiling in a basement is awesome, and most rentals I've been in don't boast new appliances. 

Do you think there is a market for places like this? I know the area is meant to be 'up and coming' but... 

For reference on prices, I have a two bedroom near Danforth and Woodbine, paying $1250. Before that, one bedroom basement near Greenwood and Danforth for $725. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 13:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I like it. Although I would prefer better grammar. Maybe a comma in there and the standard "..." instead of looking like you own stock in the company that makes the "." key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 12:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doublespeak, more like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 18:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, at the City Parks Office:

"Someone just blogged about how to easily book our parks."

"Shit. Well, I guess we have time to change it before summer comes. Maybe we can make them mail a cheque?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being from Oshawa, I would need to be paid just to show my face inside the Five Points Mall for any reason. Unless something has drastically changed in the last couple years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Humble Bundle](https://www.humblebundle.com/) currently has some interesting titles up for grabs. 

I can personally attest to the wonderful time-sink of FTL, and the insane frustration of Super Hexagon. Looking forward to trying Democracy 3. 8$ for 7+ games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested in Hellmouth, mostly because of Stephen McHattie. The one I really wanted to see was The Babadook, which according to many is scary movie #1 this year. Unfortunately sold out already though.

Unless someone has extra tiiiickets.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 22:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used chorizo, but hot italian was our fallback. I'm sure it will be great. As mentioned in the video, if you switch from lamb, the mint isn't really necessary, and you can use something that jives better with pork.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 14:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe is [here](http://foodwishes.blogspot.ca/2011/12/merguez-sausage-rice-stuffed-acorn.html). Love Food Wishes.

I used chorizo instead of merguez, since my butcher didn't have any made. Also, I found any rice in the mixture near the top of the filling got kind of crunchy. Next time, will leave some unmixed meat for a thin layer on top, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who needs turkey? Acorn squash stuffed with sausage and rice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 14:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 14:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coconut milk in butter chicken is not the norm. When I see 'slow cooked curry' posts, many use it, but in my mind coconut milk is best left to thai curries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 00:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The resolution is horrendous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I thought I was the only one who couldn't work a reddit search. So this is what it's like...when doves cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the past, I have seen Julia Roberts' accent in Michael Collins held up as the Golden Turd for Bad Accents. But I haven't seen the movie in a decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 04:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically the same thing that happens on r/ArcherFX. Relevance? Low, so extremely low. Upvotes? Through the roof! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 01:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just about any game appeals to me. I imagine with my restrictions, sidescrollers and top-down thingys might be the order of the day.

I don't have an external. I know it doesn't sound like much of an expenditure, but I am on a strict (food+gas, basically) budget. Trying to justify anything takes a lot of work :-p
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 01:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the links, and the advice! Just broke as a joke (means no new laptop), and just looking for some stuff to fill the void. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't tried it. Fairly unfamiliar with the OS, just haven't delved into the finer points. Are there any good tutorials on how to get Boot Camp up and running? I'm on a MBP, late 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laptop down. Stuck on a Mac. Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 21:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since my old laptop crapped out, I am "gaming" on a mac laptop. Trying to make the best of a bad situation. Anyone have some suggestions for keyboard (minus the mouse, if possible) based games, preferably on Steam? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 14:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is basically r/hereisapictureofathingthatsaysarcher. Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
