<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6666</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nitrogen ROM 7.1.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been hearing a lot of positivity about it lately, I'm running Cortex 7.1.1 with ElementalX and I have insane battery issues here. An hour of SOT and my battery is at 65%. My screen only having took 6% of my battery.

I've been looking to switch to Nitrogen and I've been wondering what you guys' experiences are? What's your battery life like? SoT? Usage? What kernel are you using and what's scrolling performance like?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's your battery life on Nitrogen like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 08:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> y tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about linking /r/Madlads shows you're being sarcastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ez pz and if you don't want to put in the effort to do it yourself, nexus root toolkit will do it without any effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Nitrogen on 7.1.1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use reddit is fun but thank you so much for the support you are giving this community, it's rare to see a dev so consumed in helping his userbase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My email is written clearly there but it rejects it and doesn't let me sign up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tumblr's register </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Scribblenauts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Einstalin* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I flashed the boot image, then the recovery, and it didn't do anything. did i do it wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted to do F2FS but every time I flash the modded TWRP and then I boot into TWRP I get asked for a password, so I might have to skip the F2FS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current ROM came preinstalled with substratum so I had no idea it was simply a root app, i thought you had to flash it. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you don't have to flash Substratum?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Substratum included with the rom or must I flash it separately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two variants of the 821, and the only difference is the clock speed. It is exactly what I said, an underclocked 821. Even if Google isn't the one who underclocked it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pixel has the underclocked 821 instead of the 820 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone plays on console </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Division worth $25? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.dictionary.com/browse/irrelevance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked conspiritard for the first time in ages and Jesus christ are they full of themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See, now this is an opportunity for me to simply reply </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, now this is an opportunity for me to simply reply "No its not." and follow the context of the posted image. I could easily expect a few upvotes for this, as it is simple ironic humor. But I will not suffer such temptation. Though you may offer me a beginning with your "me", allowing to follow through and perhaps a third member to finish our trifecta of bland, internet comedy with an "it is" comment, I will resist. I am greater than this and will not give in to losing myself in the sea of insignificant thoughts in hopes of inspiring a flash of joy in some other who may reply to the most minor surges of endorphins with a click and an increase in pointless comment karma.

I wonder what the follow up to my revelation here will be? Will my monologue be lost forever in obscurity, never to be read by more than the one I am replying to, or will the oddity of my rant bring more eyes to it? I do not relish in the thought of either event, though I am fearful of the absence of both. Perhaps someone will reply to my statement here. In my heart, I would hope for some deeper comment, but I know my place and those who surround me. A basic "me too thanks" will further fuel the pyre of ironic humor established here, rendering my words insignificant and setting them on the path of annihilation. 

This world is both beautiful and terrible. I wonder which way this road will go today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait

u/spez: ok downvotes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a Firefox extension?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They still haven't responded rawrgh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> official app is ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> about r/whatnextcd, I just found it like half hour ago, but my mobile app doesnt find the sub so I'm going to have to wait till I get home in order to message them. I do have the sufficient proof, luckily enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me as well. All my effort went into What, and when it shut down, I don't have a way to get in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alien is gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Mr. M.P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Mr. M.P

My story begins from when I was a little girl. An innocent child at the hands of a cruel grandfather. About twice a year my family would fly out to where my grandparents lived. Thats how my young life started, being violently raped and abused over and over again. And thats how the sexual abuse continued throughout my entire childhood. Also, you're gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nova gestures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch has kill streaks in the form of ultimates. You will barely get a fully charged ult without getting a couple kills. 

Also Titanfall 2 is just straight up a fucking great and fun game. 

It's $30, give it a try. If you don't like it, origin support will be happy to refund you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modern EA is far from a joke. 2016 was a fucking great year for EA. Titanfall 2 is absolutely fucking GREAT. Battlefield 1 is fucking GREAT. Tbh I'm not sure what else they released this year but I'm liking it so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Optimizing DDR4 timings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Corsair Vengeance LPX. Came stock at 2666MHz and I have it running at 3000MHz stable. I never bothered or touched anything about the ram timings, and I have XMP enabled. How do I get the best timings for the RAM to decrease latency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lauren is dank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Prime Minister of Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 01:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we try reaching The Rubin Report? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't have millions of subscribers, but I have noticed, that like r/The_Donald, his fans are extremely dedicated. I think that would be a good opportunity to reach more people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mystery by Lacey Sturm eBook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 00:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> faggot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to check if EVGA 1070 SC has thermal pads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that the new ones come with the new pads. I got this gpu on Monday. I've never opened a gpu before so how can I tell if the VRM is being properly cooled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I monitor the VRM temps on the GTX 1070 SC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gpu z doesn't show vrm temps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IFTTT Alternative? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One that actually works. A lot of them are ones like "if I get an email do this" but I need more "at x time put phone on vibrate and enable airplane mode" or something like that. IFTTT is extremely unreliable. it works like 80% if the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVGA GTX 1070 SC Micron Artifacting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens with or without the overclock. It's most noticeable in DOOM. The card is cool (62-65C while gaming). The card is quiet. I have downloaded the BIOS update for the card and it didn't fix it. My current afterburner settings will be [here](https://i.gyazo.com/959a642110b249576c3bcad7c3b6ee9f.png).

Gears of War 4 is also extremely blurry. I'm not sure if it's a game issue or a card issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cf lumen quick settings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on my old phone my quick settings had an option to enable the light filter. opening the cf lumen app to turn it on or off is inefficient any suggestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amoled vibes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 03:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> generic "I have good battery" post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subatratum themes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently switched from a LG G3 to the 6P. On my G3 I had the CM13 theme called dark red/pitch black. I'm running pure nexus which uses the Substratum theme engine. It looked like CommuteUI had a nice black theme embedded, however it costs money and I don't have enough play credit. I opted for InversionUI but some notification text isn't legible, the color is green and I would have preferred red, and it isn't pure black, more a dark gray. As well as it didn't theme my Instagram like Dark red did. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What y'all listening to rn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sum41 - Screaming bloody murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> erik and danny sittin in a tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At dan's house Erik would be standing there watching him playing games while repeating "your internet is shit". Dan had enough of it so he did the usual and tells him to kill himself but this day the air feels more....thick...dan does not know why but as this thought came to mind, there is a warmth on his chest suddenly and the hand runs up and down his white chest slowing. When dan turned around to try and punch and break his nose like when he was younger...the man was met with a rough,lust filled kiss and as it went on...dan fell for it and kissed the man (man) back. Erik pulls him up and throws him onto the bed and rips dans pants off and his own to ram into dan....time skip to after....they both laid panting and dan was filled like a donut and just as he was going to say something....Erik pants out"no homo" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Webcam sticker on this laptop came tilted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switching to the 6P, adis! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was at the Costco Rogers station and they were having a sale on the 6P, $75 CAD without a contract!?!? No shit I went for it! Just got to wait a little because it's being transferred and goodbye on Wednesday! This phone was a champ while it lasted, but I'm jumping ship on this sale. You guys are great, I'm out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch_Dogs 2 Pineapple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you connect to a Pineapple on accident in public, will using a VPN mean your safe(r)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> does this gta screenshot have a mod installed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can anyone find this boot animation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got this as a spam text </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could not sleep in last 4 nights since noticing  u have sold the house while I was trying to find the money. to keep it My wish is to have a bird nest where u and Andrew can live whenever needed and ur mom could stay. But u chose to sell it ignoring my plead to ask u to wait for me for 2 Wks. U rush into selling while similar house on Cook in a bad shape were sold when asking $900,000 After ur mom' s death I were thinking of moving in to cover all expenses so u and Andrew can live without worrying but ur attitude had put me back . In order to be able to stay with u and Andrew I had been living unhappy life for 24 yrs and U can't just wait for me for 2 wks .I love u two quietly unlike others who likes to speak out. Even though I live apart fr u two for the last 7 yrs I am working hard to try to save something for u and Andrew but U and Andrew now think of being matured enough to be on ur own,u may think my advice is nonsense but just wait until u need to support a family of 4 . Life is not easy , making money is tough saving money is even tougher . I hope u would use the money to invest instead of spending it unwisely or u will be regret , remember only money can make money , don't rely on ur working income to live comfortably, I used to make average of $180,000 /year but after taxes and all expenses, I could only saved $160,000 ,without any vacation ,for the down payment toward buying that house, 8 yrs ago ur mom secretly took out $50,000 loan because it was under her name and now u sold the house without consulting me.With proof of down payment and all monthly expenses,I thought of court action against her when I were lock out of the house but then I promised to myself not to take action as long as u two stay in that housebut then to make $100,000 is not hard but to save that much money it may require u to work for ur whole life,I wonder what I have done wrong . During the 2 wks in and out of hospital for treatment of a scar in my lung ,I worried  of what u guys had for meals, how u cope with life without ur mom ,but I was in big shock to be told that u were in Europe, Andrew was in Kingston ,ignoring my calls ,the house was put up for sale, it really hurts me.I never expect to have such ending in my life sometimes people just simply speak to gain love without predicting the consequences. 
God knows!!! U may not hear me lecturing again.
All my hope is to see u and live a happy and prosperous life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This kids professor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTX 480 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 23:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Brian Peppers, and this is my nursing home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Brian Peppers, and this is my nursing home. I work here with the old man and my daughter, "Juliana Wetmore." Everything in here has a story and a price. One thing I've learned after 43 years - you never know what is gonna reach the County. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 04:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit has truly become quite lazy in nature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit has truly become quite lazy in nature. One worded posts are truly quite a disgrace. I'm sure for you, you just see it as easy karma - you come on every week or so and just think about how to contribute in the laziest way possible. I hate how in reddit it seems that some of the laziest, shortest comments seem to get upvoted and I truly believe it is a disgrace and shows that we are in darker days as a website. We almost lost ourself during the Pao debacle, we almost lost ourselves before that but Reddit just continues to grow stronger. I'm starting to believe it's just similar to facebook - too big to fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abraham Lincoln: "Hillary Clinton is my Father" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, I'm shaking. I'm fucking shaking. I never wanted to breed with anyone more than I want to with Halloween Mercy. That perfect, curvy body. Those bountiful breasts. The child bearing hips of a literal goddess. It honestly fucking hurts knowing that I'll never mate with her, pass my genes through her, and have her birth a set of perfect offspring. I'd do fucking ANYTHING for the chance to get Halloween Mercy pregnant. A N Y T H I N G. And the fact that I can't is quite honestly too much to fucking bear. Why would Blizzard create something so perfect? To fucking tantalize us? Fucking laugh in our faces?! Honestly guys, I just fucking can't anymore. Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I took a break from 100% material </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIREFOX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(

You mentioned resubmitting it a year ago, where is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> average onision viewer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grayed out OC settings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My motherboard is a Gigabyte Z170M-D3H. Latest BIOS. 

I can't overclock anything, I can't change frequency values or voltage values. It's all grayed out. I don't understand? Can someone help me out here? My CPU is an i7 6700k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Managers of Reddit, what's the most unprofessional interview you have had to go through? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was never molested by my uncle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 06:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was never molested by my uncle, which kind of bums me out. Was I too ugly for him? He had no problems molesting the other nephews, but never me. Selfish prick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this sub is extremely depressing to look at </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> reinstall audiofx? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 06:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I deleted it in attempt to install viper, but that didn't work out, so how do I reinstall audio fx? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WELCOME TO YOUTUBE JUSTICE WARRIORS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 23:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone actually thinks this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 16:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The way this book conveys teenage texting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only thing preventing me from academic success is my sleep pattern. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a terrible kid academically, my marks are usually in the higher 70s right now. I'm a sophomore in high school, and I usually head to bed at like 11, but I usually browse reddit on my phone, and by the time I decide to go to actually sleep it's usually 1-3AM. 

I frequently lose focus in my first three periods because I'm tired. I also find myself struggling to understand things that I know my brain is perfectly capable of understanding thoroughly. I guess my brain is using the excuse that Grade 10 marks don't matter, and that would be right. Grade 11 and Grade 12 are what's important, but if I keep the sleep pattern as it is now, it won't be easy to switch. 

Theres no reasoning with me when I'm tired, so help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the way this book conveys teenager texting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've found the subreddit's secret </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DO UR HOMEWORK ON WHEEL MUSIC AND THEN TALK TO ME </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kidding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 06:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, then I was just kidding. I hate thick, pulsing cocks wedged between my crapflaps. you're a girl, huh? I bet you're hot. I love girls. I love to do kissing and stuff with them too. are you married? i'm interested in you because you don't have a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HATE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 01:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If u don't like Onision don't post and share hate about him U CAN SIMPLY UNSUBSCRIBE !!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I Can Never Have - Nine Inch Nails [Flyleaf] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Social] Something idk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bored what up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mobile Render Resolution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 03:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game renders at 1440p on my LG G3, and so it runs like shit. I'm running RR (CM13 based ROM) how can I change the game specific render resolution to fix games performance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flyleaf - Something I Can Never Have [Hard Rock] [4:58] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aggressive doze vs Shallow Hibernation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is the better option for Greenify on a G3 running RR Marshmallow with Xposed.

I have the donation package.

Also, what are some system apps worth greenifying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys do when you can't find a high enough quality source for a song/album you love? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite song that you discovered in the past week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fEVOVN24R08 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why are the edges switched like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why is the edge switched here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/RyqSHvj.jpg

amd r9 380

fx 8350 @4.2ghz

1024x768 stretched

latest 16.9.1 drivers

**its only in CS not in other games or desktop** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why is the edge switched like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/RyqSHvj.jpg

amd r9 380

fx 8350 @4.2ghz

1024x768 stretched

latest 16.9.1 drivers 

*****its only in CS not in other games or desktop***** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the edge switched like this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 02:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHEEL MUSIC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> None of my friends share my lunch period </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been walking around aimlessly all week, fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG V20 Hands On: The Phone For A/V Geeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Material Design Attempt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/__buzzbuzz__ deleted his account again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Generic Homescreen Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 06:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/YYaJTOz.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 02:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sickest music video moments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iWIADZKU9dw) first 30 seconds (that scream tho) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit image hosting still not working (same window)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 06:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very strange, is it just me or common problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> any idea why Google services is eating so much power? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> has anyone seen clockwork 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackintosh Laptop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 22:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't relevant for me just yet... I've still got about three years till I head off to college. BUT, I've been wondering about a certain thing. Is it possible to get a laptop that can dual boot windows and OSX without spending a fortune on an actual Mac? 

It would be nice, in class OSX would seemingly be more useful, since I don't have anything to distract me and a clean sleek work efficient process. Once I'm done studying I could boot into windows and do whatever I would like to there. How realistic is this? Can it be done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTubes new ToS bans Swearing, Aggressive speech, and Political Talk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking crazy. If YouTube doesn't revert this policy then YouTube will become the next MySpace. 

The Young Turks news channel already had 500 videos removed. Watch the drama at r/YouTube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jishnu camera port having flipped selfies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any fix? Kind of annoying to have to edit each photo afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meme] This sub in a nutshell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some general questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now first off, I'm not diagnosed with ADHD. However getting diagnosed would be too expensive where I live. I've just been wondering if this one specific trait I have could be related to it, and some other questions. 

a) I'm addicted to my phones battery life. Every time I use my phone my eyes just stay on the battery percentage and just stare. If I'm browsing reddit I end up looking at my battery every ten seconds, and I constantly worry about it. If my phones at 99% I will work my ass off to make it 100%. Constant pinging in my mind of what could be wrong and how to improve it. Could this be related to an ADD/ADHD? 

b) What is the difference between ADD and ADHD? 

c) I can't watch movies or shows. I lose focus way too fast and struggle to stay in my seat without occupying myself with something else. Is this a trait? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> G502 500Hz vs 1000Hz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cab anyone guess my favorite band? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA Request: Generic Porn Star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is this battery usage normal? it can't be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once again Canada Post is unable to knock or ring a doorbell and just leave with a notice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly fucking pissed, this seems to happen nearly every time and there isn't anything I can do about it. I've tried leaving a note on my door to leave the package at my front steps. NOPE DIDN'T LISTEN. I've tried sitting on the couch right next to the door all fucking day, they don't even try to get your attention, they just leave the notice and leave. And guess what now? I have to wait until tomorrow for the order that I needed to have for work related reasons TODAY. 

Tl;dr Delivery dudes don't know how to ring a fucking doorbell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korn - Insane VIDEO [Metal] [2016] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Flyleaf Special Edition DVD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Flyleaf Special Edition DVD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android 7.0? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't use stock, I use AOSP Roms, so this doesn't really affect me. But I'm still curious, do you know anything about whether the G3 will get an official Nougat update? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Around 300,000 People die every year in hospitals around the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 300,000 People die every year in hospitals around the world. To avoid more casualities, hospitals should be abolished. Please spread the message, together we can save millions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Music] Flyleaf - Red Sam acoustic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 19:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHat's the difference between a .png and a 100% quality .jpg? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 01:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google won't give me an answer, so which one is better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
