<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 01:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wisconsin has hills.


Good guy glaciers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 03:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a high res version you can use because rule IV for size requirements.


http://i.imgur.com/VZCIjBy.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 00:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starts at 8:25 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 23:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat meat but I also eat a lot of vegan/veggie meals because it's good to try new things. 


I find it weird that people can talk for days about how to grill steak or make a roast but if you start talking about chickpeas or lentils people look at you like you just fucked their mother in the bathroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 21:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Grace of Monaco Premiere - 14 pics](http://imgur.com/a/aRNzh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 04:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1

Spends 90 bucks on locks to protect a 300 dollar bike. He is stupid but he's also an asshole.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 21:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 07:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we as a society are distracting our hate away from Creed. 


Honestly Nickleback is your every small town garage band but Creed is a different beast that should be stomped out and ridiculed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 06:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should be teaching gun safety in public schools. 


Unpopular but accidents would go down and people would be less fearful of the unknown that is guns because a lot of people have no real experience.







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What plot there is, is pretty good.


http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LtE6kxgV3XE


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 20:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.xvideos.com/video6559911/cute_ariel_rebel_blowjob

Enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 20:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've ordered them from amazon a few times and I end up eating the entire bag the same day they're delivered. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 07:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That right there is a work of love and art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 04:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can make some money at farmer's markets with that much. Up to 5 bucks a pound some places.


With 20 plants they could make a nice chunk of money if they live near a farmer's market in an urban area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 03:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Micah Moore. Full vid here: http://www.xvideos.com/video1578658/micah_moore_teeny_hardcore


That is an ugly couch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 16:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More from the MET Gala in New York](http://imgur.com/a/vTaCk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More from the Met Gala](http://imgur.com/a/9ZlhH) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 23:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=im9XuJJXylw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 14:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great picture but that's Emma Stone.


Edit: You don't have to downvote them, it's still a great pic and they made a honest mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 17:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a loofah, soap it up and exfoliate the area in warm water.


Use stupid amounts of shaving cream to rub into the hairs and let it sit on your skin for 30 seconds at least and keep an even pressure while moving the blade.


Then smear your junk with a bottle of good moisturizing lotion and you'll have little problem the day after.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just the angle of the shot along with her pose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 05:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her sister, Emily Deschanel, is on the tv show Bones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 01:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More + article for her: 

http://nypost.com/2014/04/29/24-star-yvonne-strahovski-is-a-jeans-kind-of-girl/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 06:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you restrict in-app purchases then in her phone so she doesn't get charged a million dollars for coins, gems or boosts. 


[Restricting In-App Purchases](http://support.apple.com/kb/ht6088) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 06:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 days before her bday last year JustJaredJr said she was 17 so she's been 18 for 5 months.

http://www.justjaredjr.com/2013/11/21/katherine-mcnamara-bailee-madison-is-one-of-my-favorite-people/


Nice of her not to list her bday on her tumblr, imdb, twitter, official page, whosay or youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 05:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMC knows this that's why they split up the last season of Mad Men in half like they did with Breaking Bad to milk it for viewers and awards like the whores they are.


I think they'll rely on milking Hell on Wheels next which is popular to.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 05:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birthday: November 23, 1995 - Age 18

http://www.famousbirthdays.com/people/katherine-mcnamara.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 01:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Graham_Vest#Old_Drum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 00:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're from Nordstrom the shoot page says. 

http://www.bellusmagazine.com/katherine-mcnamara/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 20:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birthday: November 23, 1995 - Age 18

http://www.famousbirthdays.com/people/katherine-mcnamara.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 03:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpopular but I think you should do what makes you happy. You only do have one life to live so why stay miserable for the sake of others?


I can't possibly imagine forcing someone to stay unhappily married for another 50-60 years just for the sake of appearances.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 19:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn your router around or make a tinfoil radar to direct it towards your place.



I'm fairly impressed it'll even reach down the street. Mine is on full power and doesn't even go 25 yards.



If that doesn't work because of your walls being too thick or something, you can always buy wifi range extender that's just another device that'll link to your router and broadcast the same signal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 18:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *It's a funny thing; people worry so much about their throats that they forget about what's down low. Now, I sharpened this blade before* *breakfast. I could shave a spider's arse if I wanted to, or I could nick this artery in your leg. And once it's nicked,* *there's no one around here who knows how to unnick it.* -Yoren, GoT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 11:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Susann from Femjoy

http://susann-femjoy.bravoerotica.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For 8 grand that better be at least Egyptian cotton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 19:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More from the Boulevard Premiere at Tribeca Film Festival](http://imgur.com/a/GoatU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More from the Boulevard Premiere at Tribeca Film Festival](http://imgur.com/a/GoatU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 03:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot porn so you don't waste your morning wood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 18:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torrent it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 21:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imgur has been having a lot of issues lately and that's why people are probably using minus.





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 21:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normal users can't see removed posts in the search so I couldn't have known. I know it was posted in /r/EmiliaClarke that's why I searched here before posting.


Alright, thanks for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 21:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't think there was anything wrong with a shoulder sweater and dress.

Don't see much photoshopping either. But ok... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 18:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been duped for years! I found out about these when Rome was still on the air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 17:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This picture is new and hasn't been posted in this sub before. I double checked in the search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 17:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Emilia Clarke, Marie Claire Magazine, May 2014 Issue - 5 pics](http://imgur.com/a/K1Z2Y) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 22:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same problem here. Imgur has just been a hassle lately with uploads from the hard drive. But if you right click and go to "view image" for Firefox or "copy image URL" for Chrome, you'll get a direct link you can upload via imgur and that'll work fine.


Minus or not, who could downvote that smile? =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exercise more. A good cardio burn makes everything better.



Buy off label benadryl (diphenhydramine, becauase it's a thousand times cheaper) and split two pills in half a hour or so before bedtime and take them.



Since you'll build up a tolerance you can't do this every night so also buy melatonin pills. I use 5mg but 3mg is more than enough if you're female/small build. And take those on alternating nights during periods of sleeplessness.



Also I found that doing a full body stretch before going to sleep is amazing for relaxing your body and mind.



I wear a sleep mask as well just to keep all light sources out (alarm clock, tablet, street lights, etc) so my body knows it's time to sleep.



Umm... And try not to eat 4-5 hours before bed so your stomach isn't digesting food that will keep you awake. Breakfast is suppose to be your biggest meal of the day, not dinner, so if you can make that change it's worth it in the long run.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 07:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why even have a loud bike in the first place? 


It's not a safety issue because they can't hear police sirens, other cars or yelling from pedestrians because their pipes are so loud.


It's no different then bicycling with headphones on being dangerous. 


Only self centered assholes think everybody else in the world is going to just get out of their way or watch for them instead of taking responsibility for their own actions on the road. Then blame everybody else for accidents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 07:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Biggest version I could find](http://i.imgur.com/bYgO9wN.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 03:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Law firm, bodyguards, and a hotel.

Need to manage that money, keep the leeches off me and a new place to lie low till I've got my winnings transferred and organized. Then I'm off into the sunset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 02:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She searchers herself and puts out dcma take down requests so vids are hard to find.

More pics: http://teenbay.org/vsexie/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 02:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why people order boneless. Wings with bones taste better because of the flavoring from the bone/marrow when cooked.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 23:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eleonora B from MetArt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 23:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanessa Rand or V_Sexie a Canadian former camgirl. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 22:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgia from x-art.

More here: http://hosted.x-art.com/galleries/gorgeous/index.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 22:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a link to the surveillance video. [Link](http://www.jsonline.com/news/milwaukee/medical-examiner-rules-corey-stingley-death-homicide-b99185586z1-240532271.html)


I don't think it was racially motivated, I think the guys restraining him just went over board with their force while he was fighting them to get away with the stolen goods. 


It doesn't take much to cut someone's air supply off and when that happens it doesn't take very long for brain damage to occur.

A tragic accident that the guys will have to live with now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 21:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cosmopolitan.co.uk/celebs/entertainment/hayden-panettiere-april-2014-cover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 22:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Emma Stone - Amazing Spiderman 2 Premiere in London - 21 pics](http://imgur.com/a/rbycO) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 17:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's 23 and this picture was taken just a few days ago.

http://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-beauty/news/sarah-hyland-summery-ombre-hair-201494 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 22:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/Av11Hug.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 03:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People ask questions and use scientific method to try and answer them.


Just because something comes up wrong only adds to the knowledge base and helps us get closer to finding truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 02:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't argue that basic fact. Life is suffering. It's one of the things from Buddhism that's changed my world view.


It's not even a different approach, it's literally a thousand different faiths making up their own version of the truth to gain power, money, followers or really whatever else they're trying to achieve.


Even the Buddhist who wishes to give a robber the moon is trying to achieve his own goals with him and others by devoting himself to an idea.


Where science asks questions to even the most basic of truths to find what really is truth and what is false. If it's false, it can be tested again and reviewed to know for sure. The entire process of science is to disprove it's self to know what's really fact. Something no religion can withstand.


I don't dehumanize anybody just for following a religion but when challenged, when they try to impose their faith onto others in some form, then they must be discredited. Just like any idea out would go through the same process to see if it's truth.


There are always those that ignore this and keep fueling the cycle to their own ideas no matter the evidence or answers they really want to seek. It's a driven delusion and that's what's dangerous because it never stays benign. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 02:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddhism discusses an afterlife and different ways of being a higher being.


Christianity isn't about the natural world but about a world they think is real. Assuming you are talking about mainly Genesis.


Every religion out there has some form of belief that they make up to feel special and safe. It helps a lot of people cope in their life but you can't simply ignore the harsh realities of what pretending does to the world outside that belief and even in cases to the person that's believing.


People do strange things when they feel they're somehow protected and safe from an imaginary being(s).


To break religion down to a single follower, say instead of praising Muhammad or Shiva they worship something they made up after taking lsd last night. Are they right and is it a healthy world view to see shared and followed by others? 


Or is it just a made up reality they made up to help them understand feelings and their limited experiences.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 01:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion isn't just poison because it promotes violence but because it promotes willful ignorance of the natural world around us by saying some form of higher being did it instead of being the result of nature. By saying you know what it is, it doesn't really encourage curiosity and the spark of strive in our humanity.


It's a way of thinking that challenges facts and realities is what is wrong to people not thinking the same things they are.


This translates into the world we live in now where women have to fight for basic rights to their own bodies, people in love have to live in fear and inequality and schools are constantly under attack for teaching children about basic facts of nature for a few examples.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 01:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a ruse!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 03:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And one more:

http://i.imgur.com/R3wFq8P.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 02:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn to make your own pizza. It's really easy.

It's healthier and tastes a lot better than from any company, local or global, using cheap products to boost their bottom line.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 02:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Children of Bodom (metal group) doing a cover of Britney Spears' "Opps! I Did it Again..."](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lZK-P5d-cVg)


Makes me laugh every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 01:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can save comments now. Between permalink and report button under their comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 21:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how he can put up with that much sodium in a single "meal". Even more so with his heart issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 21:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dethklok reminds you to neuter your pets! NSFW](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pz7Q8lP239A) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 17:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name is Camilla Luddington.


Everybody should watch Californication. Laughs and boobs in practically every episode. 



I pray to Satan that Marcy gets naked in the last season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 17:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I am a generous god.](http://i.imgur.com/xyN5nua.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 03:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/morbidreality would be better for you then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 03:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*Why you gotta be so mean?*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jYa1eI1hpDE feature=kp)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 10:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what he and his friends used to attack innocents. That's what he passed down through the ages because that's all he's remembered for.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 09:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you even know who that is? Ali did terrible things in his life including helping attack a caravan of innocent people just to provoke all out war with the Meccans.



http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ali


Using religious ideology to justify behavior isn't teaching your children to be better, it's teaching them to fall in line. Just like he helped preach in his life.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 04:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the person who's posting a shamelessly naked bear.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 05:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't meet the size guidelines but here's an [HD copy of the same image.](http://i.imgur.com/4pUPpt9.jpg) Post that instead if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 04:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Wisconsin, we'd just keep on drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 22:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/TEJjD4B.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're thinking of her in Mission: Impossible - Ghost Protocol. Where this still is from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 18:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you uploaded the wrong image because that's Billie Piper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd hold off on Out of the Furnace then, it's a pretty dark drama.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 05:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is amazing in "Out of the Furnace" which got snubbed at the Oscars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 23:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a few months till season 2 of Masters of Sex. Not only is there lots of plot but also a pretty good show.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 21:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you got me curious so I checked and yes, she does have red lipstick on in the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 18:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/WhiYmke.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 04:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you on mobile? The image you posted is heavily pixelated.


Here's the same image that meets the guidelines that isn't over stretched: http://i.imgur.com/jpSM0aC.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 20:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Global warming, pollution on a whole new scale destroying natural habitats, new diseases, drug resistance viruses, ever growing inequality, droughts, population over growth, over fishing depleting our oceans and a polar shift under way yet letting more radiation hit our planet, and all of that leading up to a collapse of our civilization possibly in our life time but in all that you care about me wearing pj's and slippers/sandals to walmart?



http://i.imgur.com/BpXuaFx.gif


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 18:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should I get dressed to go to the store? I'm not there to impress strangers that I'll likely never see again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 18:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source with more pictures](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2589986/He-look-unusual-dont-worry-hes-white-Albino-monkey-wrestles-friends.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 06:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't either. She's really cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 05:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to admit it but she's growing on me for the new vocals for Arch Enemy after hearing her in War Eternal.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 04:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do because I like the scene/it's my fetish, want it in HD and in 6 months to years later I'll suddenly remember a good scene and spent a few hours going through old hard drives and back up discs to find it to jerk off a few times to put it back into the vault for next time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 05:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should talk to him and use safe words/gestures. A bit of communication never hurt in the bedroom.






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 18:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is. She was there promoting Spider Man 2.


http://nymag.com/thecut/2014/03/emma-stone-wore-sheer-lacy-stripes-in-sydney.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 06:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've already posted his words as of a few week ago on the matter that says otherwise.



The vactican doesn't change much but only to serve it's self. It's blind ways will and have come back to bite it's self in the future. More and more people are learning more about the world that isn't black and white as the vatican puts it. 



In time we will see that basic human rights apply to everybody and not just somebodies in times. At least that's what I hope.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Vatican has a long history of tolerance and peace. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That just means they don't like it. 


I don't like black licorice but you don't see me raising a global campaign with millions of dollars and millions of people to outlaw/ban/speak out against it.


Just because I don't like something doesn't mean consenting adults won't like it and I have no problem with people eating black licorice. I let them do their own thing and make no effort to ban or outlaw their black licorice while I eat red licorice.


Some people are just born with taste buds different than my own. Doesn't make them better or worse than I but just another person trying to make their way in this crazy world.


I believe in a world that doesn't judge a man/woman by the color licorice that they eat or don't eat but by their actions that they commit in this life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His words echo from the bible that help discriminate against against homosexuals in marriage, equal rights and employment. He is a relic in a modern world preaching hate and calling it a religion.


As I linked to above, the pope's own words said he's for marriage as long as it's a man and woman which is against our own human nature.


Hate hiding behind religion is still hate no matter how you want to dress it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he does. Just because you don't consider his words intolerant or hateful doesn't mean that they are.



His beliefs in a book from thousands of years ago doesn't give him the excuse or right to help deny people basic human rights with his words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"In his response to the interviewer, he emphasized the natural characteristic of marriage between one man and one woman, and on the other hand, he also spoke about the obligation of the state to fulfill its responsibilities towards its citizens."*


*"We should not try to read more into the Popes words than what has been stated in very general terms," Rosica added.*
http://religion.blogs.cnn.com/2014/03/05/pope-francis-church-could-support-civil-unions/


Romans isn't just part of the Bible and New Testament but a major part of it from Paul that denounces homosexuality and that god would punish the behavior. Unless of course you are arguing against Paul being a major player of the bible.


[Romans 1: Starts at verse 24](http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=romans+1 version=NIV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is an asshole though because his words echo down the ranks of millions of people to justify their behavior against human nature and the rights of others.


WBC isn't a cult but rather a church focused mainly on a few issues that they're loud about. WBC is as christian as any other mainstream church out there that believes in the word of the bible that denounces homosexuality in the old testament and new testament. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 04:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pope says homosexuality is a sin and he's on reddit every other day.


Fred Phelps says homosexuality is a sin and everybody on reddit loses their minds denouncing Phelps as the world's biggest asshole since the dawn of our species. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 02:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that looks like an outtake of the shoot before magazines go nuts with photoshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 01:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who enjoys /r/gentlemanboners , I could tell to that this is [Candice Swanepoel.](http://i.imgur.com/o6ZyppG.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 18:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am probably the only person on reddit that doesn't watch that show.


Out of curiosity, what's their beef with these beautiful women? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 18:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know but they buy the rights to photos for their magazine.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 05:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romans 1:

*26 Because of this, God gave them over to shameful lusts. Even their women exchanged natural sexual relations for unnatural ones. 27 In the same way the men also abandoned natural relations with women and were inflamed with lust for one another. Men committed shameful acts with other men, and received in themselves the due penalty for their error.*

http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=romans+1 version=NIV


That's from the New Testament.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 22:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like they buy the rights to a lot of photos for their magazine. I didn't know that before hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 20:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Scarlett Johansson  California Style Magazine - April 2014 - 14 pics](http://imgur.com/a/UeMaJ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 18:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging from the vhs tapes, nos, and cd this picture was probably taken in the early 2000's after the fast and the furious came out.


I'd bet good money her boyfriend had a honda civic with a body kit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 18:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/48mZBDn.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 00:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *This was necessary because breeding stocks of the leonberger were seriously affected by the two world wars. During World War I most Leonbergers were left to fend for themselves as breeders fled or were killed. Only five Leonbergers survived World War I and were bred until World War II when, again, almost all Leonbergers were lost. During the two world wars, Leonbergers were used to pull the ammunition carts, a service to the breed's country that resulted in the Leonbergers' near-destruction.*
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leonberger


Not a very fun fact at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 21:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He basically did by picking Sarah Palin as his running mate.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 14:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full dress/body shot](http://i.imgur.com/BL7j5rF.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 20:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She should always wear red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 20:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did he pervert the religion? All he did was focus on one issue and stuck with it while being very loud about it.



Even the current pope says homosexuality is a sin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 16:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [January Jones in Violet Grey](http://www.violetgrey.com/violet-files/cover-story/january-jones) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/WhiYmke.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 21:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of last month. Feb. 21st is her b-day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 19:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck carries around a pink pen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 16:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 15:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If any are Zippo, you can send it in and they'll repair it for free.


http://www.zippo.com/customercare/repairs.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 14:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much everybody on reddit thinks Lars from Metallica can be a douche yet I can confidently say that a large percentage of people here listen to Metallica.



Kayne only gets so much attention because he relies on his talent to even out what a giant fishstick he is.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 05:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/8ANlN6t.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 05:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the stars have aligned for you to try out anal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 03:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey did you know that "Blue the Warmest Color" is on netflix now? It's an amazing French film about life and love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone hasn't heard of tumblr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're posting outdated information.


http://thechart.blogs.cnn.com/2013/12/03/study-theres-no-such-thing-as-healthy-obesity/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 20:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/oWOHyZ9.gif

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 19:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angela is a liberal vegan that influenced Arch Enemy's work.


[Cruelty without Beauty - NSFW](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eTUTs_UzmzA)





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 03:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And pepsi max has ginseng in it to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 19:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [She cleans up nice.](http://i.imgur.com/0tsMvSH.jpg)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 03:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No where in your article does it say they're Muslim.






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 15:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It helps a lot of people get to sleep. 


Also socks have been linked to better sex and orgasms.

When they gave the couples socks to wear, about 80% of the couples were able to achieve orgasm compared with 50% previously in this staged environment. 
http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/4111360.stm



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 02:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/3lcCdo5.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 00:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A large study of more then 60,000 people came out a few months ago that debunked that myth.



http://thechart.blogs.cnn.com/2013/12/03/study-theres-no-such-thing-as-healthy-obesity/



If you are overweight, you will have health problems sooner and you will die sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 18:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video of the shoot with the puppies and Zlata Ognevich.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J3cpt3MH74U) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 17:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  wondering how I had gotten something so wrong. 


It's not your fault he's an asshole through and through. 


Didn't notice the vomit is bullshit. To be graphic for a moment, the guy can feel her gag and the vomit has a much different feel and texture than saliva does.


Communication and reading your partner is hugely important in rough scenarios. Even then you should have safe words/gestures to be in a safe and fun environment.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 17:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more umbrellas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 20:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [$33 bucks for 4 cork coasters? ](http://www.reactiongifs.us/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/youre_serious_futurama.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 18:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hannibal on NBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 18:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't always drink to get drunk. It's relaxing to have a nice drink with dinner.


If I want to get drunk, I'm not going to spend 15 bucks on a 6 pack that I'm going use to wash down cheetos and jalapeno poppers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 18:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mostly make up and lightning from how the killer prepared the bodies to set them like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week's episode was really obvious with this.


[NSFW + Last week episode spoilers](http://i.imgur.com/AvzcE0P.jpg)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 17:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're often paying for them to rip you off with cheap oil, cheap air/oil filters and a quick "good enough" drain. Which will cost you more down the road if you plan on keeping your vehicle.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 16:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That comforter looks amazing and soft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 16:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Sweden also has bands other than death metal.


Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 03:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what do you call attacking civilian caravans to provoke all out war with Mecca?


My copy is the Muhammad Asad translation which I'm told is one of the best out there. Plus it gives footnotes and background.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 02:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mecca wasn't always a muslim holy city. Muhammad conquered it and turned it into a muslim city.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Badr


You should pick up a quran and read through it. It's interesting to see their point of views and it's full of history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 22:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully his children and so on learned from his mistakes then...


Ali was a terrorist who helped attack innocent civilians in the beginning muslim war against Mecca.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ali_ibn_Abi_Talib#In_battles

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 21:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience hippies have the best coffee. Go for it!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 02:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the video that was made during the shoot.](http://vimeo.com/49882824)



And [the more pictures from the shoot here.](http://www.mendaily.com/christina-hendricks-kurt-iswarienko-photoshoot-for-blackbook-photos/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a good rain fall everything smells ridiculously good.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh gods, they somehow baked a crust on those cupcakes. Do want.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 20:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the internet is a safe place to vent frustrations from your daily life?


Religious people effect our daily lives, some more than others, so it can't be ignored. 


I find it funny that christians can talk about lent all day long and shove it in our faces but the second anybody says differently, they're ridiculed.


How dare people living in a secular country have a different opinion from your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 21:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was her and I had no idea that was her real name. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 21:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I wanna taste you, but your lips are venomous poison...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 21:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not suppose to be an action show, it's a drama in a post-apocalyptic zombie world. If you read the comics, they make it more clear about that.


It's like when people would complain about Battlestar Galactica for not being more action packed for taking place mostly on a warship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should watch the director's cut of Daredevil if you haven't already, it adds more story and is a lot better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce Willis in "A Good Day to Die Hard". Not a dead career but slowed down. 


I really liked RED 2 and am looking forward to Sin City but A Good Day to Die Hard was painful to watch.


And yet they're supposedly making another Die Hard movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hayden Panettiere - Brides Magazine April-May 2014 - 6 pics](http://imgur.com/a/Jwf3N) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 02:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's dark red, peasants!](http://i.imgur.com/ugh5PTQ.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 18:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue is the Warmest Color is on Netflix if you wanted to see more and watch a great movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 17:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully he wasn't an altar boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 00:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? He is amazing.

The only movie he's directed that's perceived as "bad" is Sucker Punch and that's only because a bunch of the story was cut from the theatrical release but was released later on dvd as an extended version.


I'm most impressed with his work with Watchmen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 19:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 18:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really good but only got two seasons and is now a comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Emily Ratajkowski - S Moda Magazine, March 2014 Issue - 8 pics](http://imgur.com/a/wP5Rk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 18:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pose from another angle.](http://i.imgur.com/flcAqsH.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 18:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alexa Vega - Bello Magazine, March 2014 Issue - 6 pics](http://imgur.com/a/iMOaB) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 16:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hayden Panettiere - Sonya Jasinski Photoshoot - 8 pics](http://imgur.com/a/AbDNE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 06:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the nude gifs of Nadine Velazquez (Catalina) that were posted a while back: [NSFW - 8 gifs](http://imgur.com/a/TqCFa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 20:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *11 This is what the Lord says: Out of your own household I am going to bring calamity on you. Before your very eyes I will take your wives and give them to one who is close to you, and he will sleep with your wives in broad daylight. 12 You did it in secret, but I will do this thing in broad daylight before all Israel.*


--


Seems pretty extreme for a supposedly loving god with the killing an innocent baby and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The days when 4.39gb rips were a massive pain to download. I'm glad those days are gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 20:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part is when god tortures a new born baby to death and orders it's mother raped in the street because god is throwing a tantrum.

http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2+samuel+12 version=NIV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 17:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The glorious Pancake of course! 


Sadly there would be many wars and deaths in disputes over what kind of pancake a certain people think is the one true recipe but in the end it would all be worth it for the love and warmth of each bite we get from our beloved Pancake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 07:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reference for those that don't know. Well worth the long read.](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/fn5gr/reddit_what_is_your_silent_unseen_act_of_personal/c1hdgwv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 03:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see it. She was at QVC 5th Annual Red Carpet Style Event yesterday where this picture is from. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 02:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kristen Bell - 2014 Film Independent Spirit Awards](http://imgur.com/a/sY4N6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 01:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw her again on Hannibal while watching the new episode. She is still hot as ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 01:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accidentally mistyped her name the first time. Sorry about that people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 22:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care much about reposts but I do get irked when someone claims it as their own as they are in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 17:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is more your thing then.](http://i.imgur.com/IHE1pzs.gif)

Enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 17:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? She did a hot scene in The to do List.

NSFW: http://minus.com/lQ6JuVj19bhNt


Here's the video: [NSFW](http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x12ajlj_the-to-do-list-cunnilingus-clip_videogames) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 16:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We"? Why lie?


Anyone seeking more info might also check here:

title | points | age | /r/ | comnts
:--|:--|:--|:--|:--
[I heard this is what's happening behind the scenes when your mining program is waiting for work](http://www.reddit.com/r/dogecoin/comments/1xqoq4/i_heard_this_is_whats_happening_behind_the_scenes/) | 76 | 16^dys | dogecoin | 12
["Ok, we can play this, I am patient..."](http://www.reddit.com/r/GifSound/comments/1l9dqi/ok_we_can_play_this_i_am_patient/) | 61 | 6^mos | GifSound | 4
[Boss!](http://www.reddit.com/r/gif/comments/1ehdnp/boss/) | 543 | 9^mos | gif | 8
[Doggie see, doggie do!](http://www.reddit.com/r/gifs/comments/14tgsw/doggie_see_doggie_do/) | 1635 | 1^yr | gifs | 36
[Doggie see, doggie do](http://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/10ed1g/doggie_see_doggie_do/) | 24 | 1^yr | aww | 1
[Like human. So criss-cross. Wow.](http://www.reddit.com/r/SuperShibe/comments/1rqhpl/like_human_so_crisscross_wow/) | 31 | 3^mos | SuperShibe | 1
[wow such polite, much manners. miss lady doge](http://www.reddit.com/r/SuperShibe/comments/1qovlh/wow_such_polite_much_manners_miss_lady_doge/) | 2317 | 3^mos | SuperShibe | 19
[Cute Dog Copies Owner](http://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/1c6d0d/cute_dog_copies_owner/) | 84 | 10^mos | aww | 1
[Cute dog copies owner.](http://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/10ph4q/cute_dog_copies_owner/) | 2458 | 1^yr | aww | 253

*[Source: karmadecay](http://karmadecay.com/r/gifs/comments/1z9j14/we_can_do_this_all_day/)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 03:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunday nights are the best nights because near everybody is sleeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 17:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the video of her performance: [YouTube](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A7EmK68h0qw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.gotceleb.com/victoria-justice-xex-magazine-april-2012-issue-2012-05-07.html

Victoria's b-day: February 19, 1993 - April 2012 = 19

So even if she did the shoot before her birthday she would have still been 18.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how people pick and choose from their holy books to justify their hate while forgetting to read the entire thing.

Romans 2:1 *You, therefore, have no excuse, you who pass judgment on someone else, for at whatever point you judge another, you are condemning yourself, because you who pass judgment do the same things. *
http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=Romans+2


"He who is without sin among you, let him be the first to throw a stone at her." ~Just some random dude who was in the same book she's quoting.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 03:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wisconsin here and see them all the time from bait to fresh honey. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 20:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hammerfall agrees.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vkmlujV-TvU)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 19:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More [Scarlett Johansson in Dazed and Confused Magazine Spring 2014 - 10 pics](http://imgur.com/a/pgevR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 19:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Scarlett Johansson in Dazed and Confused Magazine Spring 2014 - 10 pics](http://imgur.com/a/pgevR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 01:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wookiee*


You damn nerf herder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone put her pics up on 4chan and I saved them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 19:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/c7NJRa2.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
