<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7316</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - Agronomic practices certainly can have a big effect but are not sufficient to eradicate the problem completely once it is established.  For example, in Australia the pathogen has been introduced a couple of times and as soon as it was noticed they immediately destroyed all bananas within a few miles of the outbreak and supposedly eradicated it.  This may be possible but difficult if you don't catch it early.  In Ecuador, they cut off infected leaves and put them on the ground with the upper surface down, since the spores are supposed to be produced only on the upper surface.  This can slow it down but it is still very difficult to produce bananas.  Agronomic effects are probably not large enough for effective disease management, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Hi. There is plenty of variation available. Productivity ad getting that into your stores that is the problem. Therefore, we believe that breeding can fix it. Eventually delivering a suite of banana varieties with enough variation to choose from, taste, size etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  system

Igor: You are right, genomes are just a starting point and we are moving toward functional genomics to bridge the gap between the enormous number of sequenced genes and still relatively small number of genes with known function. JGI works with other DOE User Facilities like the Environmental Molecular Sciences Laboratory ( http://bit.ly/User-Facility-JGI) to produce various omics types of data (genomics, transcriptomics, proteomics, epigenomics, metabolomics, etc ) and analyze them.  The recent Facilities Integrating Collaborations for User Science (FICUS) initiative was established for this purpose. (More: http://bit.ly/JGI-FICUS). FICUS is all about expanding the diversity of datasets and connecting systems; for example, we worked with Michelle O'Malley at UCSB on sourcing cellulolytic fungal enzymes from zoo animal feces capable of degrading biomass more efficiently for fuel, generating metabolomic datasets (http://jgi.doe.gov/biofuel-tech-fungi-straight-from-the-farm/).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Hi, there. There are excellent groups in banana R D that support the Australian industry. They even managed - in a public private partnership - to eradicate black Sigatoka, miraculously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - No, see breeding posts above.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - I think so, see above posts. Gene editing is surely not the only option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - This is an interesting idea but I think the chances of something being developed are low.  There certainly are fungi that are parasitic on other fungi but I don't know of any that attack the black Sigatoka pathogen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Not very big, I'm afraid. Biocontrol will contribute to disease management though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - I think there is no way to predict for certain regarding extinction events, but certainly higher genetic variation gives you more phenotypic variation and that should increase your chances of survival.  The same rules of evolution that apply to humans also apply to plants.  Asexually reproducing organisms with low genetic variability are usually much more vulnerable to extinction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - There is a lot to say about sub-optimal doses of fungicides. Some claim that this improves control, others claim that is contributes to resistance development/selection. In principle, I tend to follow the recommendations of the industry to guarantee the lifetime of fungicides. We cannot spoil these worthwhile active ingredients. It has taken years of development to come up with these products. Without them we could presently not grow bananas. Whether we like it or not, these are the facts. So also from that perspective, more diversity in banana varieties is necessary to reduce the chemical load in banana production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  psyllium

Igor: You can check it in JGI Mycocosm portal (http://jgi.doe.gov/fungi) searching by name among ~700 annotated genomes and hundreds project in progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - This is an interesting question.  In my lab we actually have looked at the effect of sublethal doses of fungicide in a different fungus (a wheat pathogen) and found that they increase the rate of loss of dispensable chromosomes.  The stress caused by sublethal doses of fungicides could increase the mutation rate which certainly could affect virulence, but that has never been studies as far as I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - organic and conventional bananas ar both Cavendish. So they are both prone to the mentioned diseases. We can fix the fungal problems, see the above discussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fundi

Igor: The genomics work was done by JGI, which is supported by the Office of Science of the U.S. Department of Energy. JGI is a DOE Office of Science User Facility which produces genomics resources (sequencing, synthesis, and analysis) to enable researchers around the world do their great science via our Community Science Program calls for proposals (http://jgi.doe.gov/user-program-info/community-science-program/). The JGI Fungal Program aims at exploring the diversity of fungi important for energy and the environment (https://www.youtube.com/user/JointGenomeInstitute); we contribute to nearly half of all fungal genomics projects worldwide through large-scale projects like 1000 fungal genomes, fungal mini-ENCODE and others (e.g., http://jgi.doe.gov/our-science/science-programs/fungal-genomics/1000-fungal-genomes/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - There is no exclusive strategy. We should do one as well as the other. GM is a great way to "repair" Cavendish deficiencies. Breeding is the way to go for the ultimately required diversity. I will not comment on individual breeding programs, but the facts are that thus far none has been successful in marketing viable replacements for Cavendish. Fungicide resistance is also an issue in Yellow Sigatoka. However, black Sigatoka is much more aggressive and has replaced YS populations in most countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - It is a problem for both organic and conventional growers.  Probably worse for organic growers since they have no available controls.  There is no solution right now other than lots of sprays with fungicides, but even that is not sufficient as fungicide resistance evolves very rapidly.  Unfortunately, a time machine wouldn't solve the problem - we would just get to see it happen again - although it would allow you to taste Gros Michel bananas again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Yeah, what to say. There is always something, and unexpected things we're not prepared for can show up. Currently, the treats are these two fungi and, yes, we need to invest in strategic R D to topple them down. Of course the beauty of breeding is versatility, we always can change focus, improve another character etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - Yes, I think both approaches are needed.  The FHIA program has produced bananas with increased resistance so we know it works.  Genetic engineering will work in the future but getting around barriers to public acceptance will be the difficulty.  For example, for Panama disease, there is a report that Host-Induced Gene Silencing can control the disease, although it has not been tested in the field to my knowledge.  It also may be possible to use non-host resistance.  One result from the black Sigatoka genome sequence is that it contained effectors (proteins that facilitate disease) that could interact with tomato resistance genes.  Possibly genes from other edible crops that recognize the banana pathogen could be put into banana to increase its resistance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Fusarium, decades. P. fijiensis not so long as it depends on the host for its survival. Your question refers mostly to Fusarium, right? Cleaning land from the persistent spores that survive for decades is not easy, but we're testing (biological) methods to do so. I'm sure that we will have many more tools to reduce Fusarium in soil over the next few years. We can use genes from other plants in disease control strategies. The paper gives one example: use a gene from tomato, or use it as a probe to find/clone/use the banana homologue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - OK, that is several questions.  We often have collaborators in industry to work on basic science, including on our genome paper.  Industry sequenced the second genome.  Agrochemical companies are definitely interested in the genome sequence, for example to help design compounds that could target the pathogen specifically with fewer negative environmental effects.  Of course, our long-term goal would be to make chemicals unnecessary, but that is a long way off and many chemical companies also are into producing resistant plants.  Hopefully we can work together to reduce the amount of chemicals applied.

I have not heard of Jason Glaser - maybe Gert knows of him.

You can grow bananas in greenhouses now - production out of tropical areas is possible but yields are probably too low to make them commercially viable.  I have a dwarf banana I grow as a houseplant that has fruited several times so it is definitely possible to grow them outside of the tropics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert -Correct. You are referring to co-evolution. That's why in the center of origin, SE Asia, there is plenty of diversity. However, thus far this remains largely untapped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Well, there are vast areas of crops, but mostly these are divided over a range of genetically different cultivars. This is where bananas are truly the exception. There it is mostly one and the same cultivar, thus genetically uniform. As these are natural clones, they have never been bred for such a vast acreage and that makes them prone to diseases </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - In banana this is the norm. Retail, industry kind of "suffocate" the potential, already for years. We need to kind of circumvent, convince, break this armor. The best way forward is an innovative, professional, commercially driven and highly technologically driven breeding program meeting consumer preferences. Take consumers serious, they don't want to be told that they really need Cavendish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - Unfortunately, you are right that another disease is likely to show up, particularly with a long-lived, clonal crop.  I think the only long-term solution will be genetic engineering of better resistance, but that will take time.  Our sequencing the genome of the banana pathogen is only the first step in a long process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Frankly, we're always on the watch for new funding. There is never enough to meet our ambitions for safeguarding bananas. As mentioned earlier, banana funding is negligible compared to the major staple crops (wheat, rice, maize, potato and others). We have to come from far, but we're slowly getting there. More funds would help us to train many more students (capacity building is very important) and to come up with more innovative solutions and new varieties. Funding presently is mostly in public private partnerships, thus governments (Netherlands), companies (global, not the "big guys" though), universities (Wageningen and others), institutions (JGI did a great job to support this work), private foundations/charity (Dioraphte in The Netherlands). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - Rotating when a crop can be planted can work with some crops (e.g., sugarbeet) but would be hard with banana which takes more than a year to produce fruit and is widely planted in suitable climates.  You would also have to eliminate any susceptible plant nearby - possible in theory but very difficult in practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve - No, the spores are only on the leaves and external parts of the plant, certainly not on a peeled banana.  Even if you did ingest spores, they have no effect on humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Many. Preferred are the local bananas in SE Asia. Got in touch with banana 12 yrs ago through the link with my R D in wheat and a related fungus, Zymoseptoria tritici. Steve, Igor and me work on that pathogen already for decades. Hence, banana was a fantastic opportunity to use the gained know-how to boost R D in banana. Much needed as it is generally considered an orphan crop, respite the fact that it is a staple for millions of people. It is a shame that R D in banana is so limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dumb question

Igor - There are no dumb questions! Sequencing just by itself does not do it. We would like to understand what triggers it, how this happens, and how we potentially avoid it. With a genome in hands you can compare it to the genomes of other pathogens, find conserved genes and similarities to those already known genes, develop hypothesis and design experiment to study mechanism of action. We used the collection of ~700 annotated fungal genomes that we built at JGI Mycocosm (jgi.doe.gov/fungi), a web-based fungal genomics resource, which integrates fungal genomes with other omics data and provides interactive analytical tools to explore them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Difficult to say. There are projections and yes, environmental changes will affect the distribution/epidemiology of fungi. No question. However, to precisely answer your question for banana pathogens is difficult, if not impossible, yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Likely not. The fungus is a foliar pathogen that does not infect the fruit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  skills

Igor: I suggest to look at molecular biology and bioinformatics. While genomics data become readily available from core lab facilities or commercial entities, bioinformatics skills remain critical for data analysis. In fact it requires more resources to assemble, annotate, and analyze genomics data computationally than sequence it. Frequently you are on your own facing tons of raw genomics data shipped to you. At JGI  we perform these computational tasks for every genome we sequence (jgi.doe.gov/fungi) but you still need to understand how the data were processed, to which extent you can trust the data, and what else you can do with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Yes, they can, but they cannot replace them. At most they're part of the overall package </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Possible. Requires old style explorations. Fact is that we are largely natural clones that may have developed thousands years ago in tropical forest. Both Gros Michel and Cavendish are no breeding products, but naturally formed triploids. We can repeat the process though and work from smart diploid breeding to new triploids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get- Yes, with sufficient budget we'll be albe to target those genes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - The progress comes from multidisciplinarity. Breeders need a lot of pathological input, similar to what is common practice in other crops. Think about wheat and the global networks for disease surveillance and understanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Boy we have the same ideas. However, more genetic diversity is necessary. In principle, though, we should be able to revive Gros Michel. Next question is, does the industry/logistical chain/retail like it. They are very influential and powerful to either slow down or embrace innovation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - For sure. Genetic modification, either through GM technologies or breeding is definitely possible. However, the facts are that the major genetic basic work on the plant side is still fairly limited. Not a single R gene has been mapped and for genome editing we have no clue yet on the targets. But, we'll get there, for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - There is indeed a plethora of Fusarium genotypes threatening bananas, but the strains killing Cavendish are essentially one and the same clone (thus far; VCG01213, Tropical Race 4; see the PLoS Pathogen Pearls paper). However, you are right Panama disease or Fusarium wilt can be caused by a range of different genotypes of the fungus in other banana varieties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get - As a kid I think you were eating Gros Michel, which has a better taste than Cavendish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - It is not that easy, but yes smart genome management will result in new edible varieties with increased levels of resistance. However, I think it is better to start breeding at the diploid level to introduce much more diversity (taste, shelf life, productivity, disease resistance). The "addiction" to Cavendish is kind of worrisome. Consumers should have more options. That's where commercial breeding is all about. What does the consumer prefer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - Per is definitely an environment where black Sigatoka does not thrive (yet). It may expand in the future, but still represent a minor percentage in global production. For now, this is an environment for organic production, which is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gert - I don't think bananas will be extinct. Journalists like asking these questions, but the situation is of course very serious. Agronomically growing a suite of essentially identical clones around the world is asking for problems as banana history has shown already once before (Panama disease epidemic previous century). History repeats it self and hence we need to come up with solid strategic solutions. Prime target is to introduce genetic diversity - new varieties - to slow prevent and manage epidemics. This takes many yeas of R D and meanwhile we need to implement other management options. 50-70 fungicide applications to manage black Sigatoka is very unsustainable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Igor, Steve and Gert and we sequenced fungus DNA and found banana crops are highly susceptible to the fungal pathogen and resistant to fungicides, creating unsustainable growing practices -- Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 13:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


We're Igor Grigoriev, Steve Goodwin and Gert HJ KEMA, and we recently published an article titled [Combating a Global Threat to a Clonal Crop: Banana Black Sigatoka Pathogen Pseudocercospora fijiensis (Synonym Mycosphaerella fijiensis) Genomes Reveal Clues for Disease Control](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=info:doi/10.1371/journal.pgen.1005876) in [PLOS Genetics](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics).


[Gert HJ Kema](https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Gert_Kema), Professor of Tropical Phytopathology at Wageningen University, The Netherlands, researches fungal diseases in banana and wheat, with a focus on genetic diversity and mechanisms of pathogenicity of the causal agents.


[Igor Grigoriev](http://jgi.doe.gov/about-us/organization/eukaryote-super-program/igor-grigoriev/), Head of Fungal Genomics program at the U.S. Department of Energy Joint Genome Institute and [Adjunct Professor of Plant and Microbial Biology](http://plantandmicrobiology.berkeley.edu/profile/igrigoriev) at University of California Berkeley, employs genomics tools to explore fungal diversity for energy and environment science and applications.


[Steve Goodwin](https://www.ars.usda.gov/people-locations/person?person-id=2061), Research Plant Pathologist with the Agricultural Research Service of the U.S. Department of Agriculture and [Adjunct Professor of Plant Pathology](https://ag.purdue.edu/btny/pages/profile.aspx?strAlias=sgoodwin) at Purdue University, uses genetics, genomics and bioinformatics approaches to analyze host-pathogen interactions between wheat and fungal pathogens and to utilize genetic diversity in hosts and pathogens.


The [PLOS Genetics article](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1005876) focused on determining the DNA sequence of the fungus and applies it by focusing on two major aspects of current banana production: overall susceptibility of the crop and reduced efficacy of disease control agents (fungicides). The overall susceptibility of the major export Cavendish banana varieties - that essentially form one huge monoculture around the globe - is the underlying problem of the unsustainable banana production. Hence, the only way to manage black Sigatoka is the use of fungicides. However, due to the high application frequencies (between 50-70 times per year) their efficacy continually decreases, which in turn requires more/different control strategies. Our paper unveils the unsustainable status quo by showing the need and possibility for developing new and better varieties with improved disease resistance. This helps growers in the developing world and meets consumer demands for a caring society.


To learn more about the featured study, read Gert's PLOS Blogs post on [Biologue](http://blogs.plos.org/biologue/2016/08/12/one-super-susceptible-clone-a-versatile-fungus-and-failing-fungicides-black-sigatoka-and-banana/). See for another effect of the global banana monoculture the PLOS Pathogens study [Worse Comes to Worst: Bananas and Panama DiseaseWhen Plant and Pathogen Clones Meet](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1005197).


Also, dont forget to follow us on Twitter: [DOE Joint Genome Institute](https://twitter.com/doe_jgi) and [USDA](https://twitter.com/USDA) and [Wageningen University](https://twitter.com/UniWageningen).


Visit us at [www.panamadisease.org](http://www.panamadisease.orghttp://www.panamadisease.org) and/or subscribe to the newsletter.


**Well be back at 1 pm EST (10 am PST, 5 pm UTC) to answer your questions, ask us anything!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's much easier to have the math and learn the biology than to have the biology and try to learn the math. A decent modeler like you can go into any field and basically say "what are the differential equations?". We're now teaching an undergrad course in modeling at UCLA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good to hear from you, and thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's funny. I'd have given it to her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> genetic problems exist, but in the adult population, lifestyle issues are the dominant cause of heart disease! You are doing the right thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan:  somebody desperately needs to do the UQ you are asking for, in relation to inducibility of VF. the best group looking at patient-to-patient variability and its implications is Blanca Rodriguez at Oxford. Much more needs to be done here

2. So we've published lots of papers showing how fibroblasts coupled to myocytes cause arrhythmias in various cultures and other reduced preparations. The big issue, as you obviously know, is whether this plays any role in the whole in vivo heart. I saw a screaming match at a conference over this particular issue. My money is on "yes"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> about 1 hour on a CPU cluster. Human is 500 X the rabbit, but that can be greatly improved. we can already do a human in about 8 hrs. biggest challenges: computational and getting the physics of contraction right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no contraction is the worst. we're working on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the remodeling in hypertrophy has got to contribute somehow to the higher probability of arrhythmias in this pop. We would love to get a really good DT MRI image of this hypertrophy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. I personally think the concept of synchrony is probably the most important single concept in dynamics, that is, everything. The synchrony is achieved in the heart through gap junctions, which are the connections from one cell to its neighbors. These then support a wave conduction that passes through the tissue like a stadium wave. In VF, this wave becomes unstable and fragments itself. See our paper
Preventing ventricular fibrillation by flattening cardiac restitution. Proc Natl Acad Sci U S A 97, 6061-6066. (2000)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks so much! makes my day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yes, the risk is real. those folks really do have disproportionate VT/VF. One issue that I should mention is that the cellular EP changes that accompany HF also create an arrhythmia that is driven by delayed afterdepolarizations (DADs), which is something that is happening in the cell EP  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: mouse is a bad model for arrhythmia research (heart is too small). Stick with LS30 and you'll be doing this sort of modeling yourself pretty soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: this is a very intelligent and knowledgeable response from "eagle". (S)he is right in #3: The PhD is not an absolute requirement: our chief of cardiology and chair of medicine are both superb researchers with large funded programs, and neither has a PhD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: yes, there is an "association" but it's statistical not causal. Those folks really do need ICDs, but that's because we don't have anything better. You are obviously knowledgeable, and you are right in saying "there is something inherent" but we have no idea what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: This is a REALLY good question. VVUQ is becoming a major issue in lots of sciences from cardiology to nuclear engineering, fluid dynamics, etc. Our PLoS one paper concerns the second "V" (validation) but we do not address the hugely important question of UQ.  Groups at Mt Sinai (Eric Sobie) Cornell Med (David Christini) and Oxford (Blanca Rodriguez, Gary Mirams, etc.) are beginning to address this, and we will too in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: if it's just a "predisposition" then those are the best. You might want to see a cardiologist if it's more than just family history. But (s)he won;t have anything better than those 3!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: mostly drugs. we can test all kinds of drugs in the model first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: sorry, site prohibits medical advice. everyone has PVCs, but you might want to see a Cardiac Electrophysiologist ("EP") about the bigeminy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: look at the paper. No 2D here, this is a 3D whole heart simulation, it's many many cells 'deep' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: yep, that's right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, that was a typo. I meant it the other way around, of course. and I should have said "GPU has been awesome". I will edit the original </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: yes, see answer to "tiredgirl". For example, we think we can detect using characteristics of the QRS complex (eg. QRS alternans), as well as how the T-wave looks in the 12 leads of the full EKG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: hey, thanks! Yes, we hope to use our physiologically-correct EKG  in a study like you suggest. There have been some prior attempts by other, for example looking at micro-volt T0-wave alternans on EKG, which has had a mixed success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: yes, we are looking at those SERCA therapies that we discuss in the PLoS CB in this light. Any advance in therapy would be a big one, since HF is a gigantic health burden in the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: Definitely sex differences in cardiac EP. women have more Ica,L (calcium current) and hence longer QT intervals. Lots of lit on this. see for example
Molecular and cellular basis of cardiovascular gender differences
ME Mendelsohn, RH Karas - Science, 2005 - </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: cardiac electrophysiology is VERY mathematical. I was a math guy who didn't want to do research math. The problem of VF, the leading cause of sudden cardiac death, can be put totally mathematically: there is this Partial Differential Equation, which is known, governing cardiac conduction. If that PDE in your heart currently has a rectilinear solution, you are healthy; if it has a periodic solution, you are very sick, and if it has a chaotic solution, you are about to die! I thought "well, this is something that could yield to mathematical analysis and modeling" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: echo shows motion, which is mechanics. You can see all sorts of problems in contractility, EF, etc. EKG shows electrical activity, which is another dimension: arrhythmias. They are very independent and complementary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: why do you say "besides"? Those three are very powerful!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: no. SVT is easily diagnosed on 12-lead EKG
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: As a professor of Medicine, I'm a big believer in Academic Medicine. The kings and queens here are the MD/PhDs. However, I have to tell you that the grant-writing-and-rejection process is soul-destroying. With the current NIH policy of funding ~15% of submissions, there is terrible competition.One of my postdocs showed me an article that said that only 1 in 6 PhDs ends up with a faculty position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: we would be VERY interested in looking at cardiac microstructure changes in HF. We already have one paper on it. I'm going to get in touch with Dr. Li at your suggestion and compare notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: this is a growing field. Other areas where there is already excellent work include immunology, epidemiology, development and its pathologies, circadian rhythms, molecular biology (feedback control of gene regulation). I tell my students to search "differential equations" + your favorite topic. you will probably get some hits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: huge. imbalances in Mg, K, Fe etc. are major causes of cardiac arrhythmias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: the biggest impact on morbidity and QoL that I see is the possibility of avoiding ICD implantation, which is a) expensive, b)highly invasive and c) requires pre-identifiaxtion of the at-risk pop. ICD is so bad that several papers have appeared using ICD patients as a model for Post Traumatic Stress syndrome, that's how bad the shock is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: Diagnosis of cardiac arrhythmia is already pretty straightforward. 90% of the time a 12-lead EKG (completely non-invasive) will do the trick, while the remaining 10% might need a cath exam. That's easy. what's hard is understanding the mechanics of the arrhythmia, and (related) design therapies. We do hope our model can help design therapies and understand mechanisms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: yes! we have a protocol in place to obtain some human hearts and image them in DT-MRI. This is clearly the way to go and is absolutely the necessary next step, since we aren't here to treat rabbits!
and also, although the rabbit heart is qualitatively similar to the human, we can't just extrapolate trivially to the human. You have do the model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: (1) Writing the FiniteElement Code and getting it into computable form. Ponnaluri and Perotti did a fantastic job on this, working under the direction of the late Prof. Klug, who is much missed
(2) finding the right combinations of parameters to make the model work. Lots of trial and error
(3) finding the data on rabbit cell physiology, since the literature is, like, Old MacDonalds farm, here a pig, there a rabbit, here a rat, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: What you say is true: current standards for implanting an ICD place importance on the EF. But there is absolutely no mechanistic connection, to my knowledge, between "low EF" and "arrhythmia". "low EF" is a marker for advanced disease, and then you are also at risk for arrhythmias, but I don't know the connection. Of course, as you well know, ACE targeting is supposed to address contractility, and BB is supposed to be anti-arrythmic. One very interesting recent development is the role of autonomic (parasym and sympathetc) innervation of the heart as a cause of arrhythmia. See my colleagues work, for example 
The role of the autonomic nervous system in sudden cardiac death
M Vaseghi, K Shivkumar - Progress in cardiovascular diseases, 2008 
This actually provides a mechanism whereby BB could act as an anti-arrhythmic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan:overall, there is nothing wrong with Matlab or Mathematica FOR VERY SIMPLE problems, often called "toy problems" in differential equations. Great for playing around with simple systems. except it's very expensive. R and Python will do the same things open source and free. And then if you get into big-time computation, see above. None of these will work even remotely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: this reply is from a "bioinformatics" leaning grad student, and is appropriate for bioinformatics and statistics, which is now, as (s)he says, largely done in Python or R. 
However, we are doing "computational biology" in the other sense of that word, which is large scale simulation of Ordinary and, mostly, Partial Differential Equations. These are huge computations, and Python and R are completely inadequate to handle this and way way too slow. We are doing Finite Element Method calculations with millions of elements. We use hand written C++ for CPUs and CUDA for GPUs. GPU computation is awesome and is very valuable to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan: 1) current situation for HF is based largely on hemodynamic measures like Ejection Fraction and treated with drugs to improve that situation. Our focus was on electrical arrhythmias in this population, which is a known problem but whose mechanism are unclear. 
2) your question about types of HF is a good one. There are definitely distinct types of HF: HFpEF, hypertrophic cardiomyopathy, and a few others. We are focussing on HFrEF (r = reduced), and we really have no idea whether this would also hold true of entities like hypertrophic CM. 3) see Cardiac inotropes: current agents and future directions.
Hasenfuss G, Teerlink JR. Eur Heart J. 2011 for a good discussion of research-level drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Alan Garfinkel and I developed an electrophysiology model of heart failure that shows certain cellular conditions in the heart may be predispose people to cardiac death  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Alan Garfinkel](https://www.ibp.ucla.edu/physcifacultyindiv.php?FacultyKey=965) and I am Professor of Medicine (Cardiology) at UCLA. My research focuses on the use of mathematical models of cellular and tissue electrophysiology of the heat, especially on the causes of cardiac arrhythmias.


I recently published an article [Electrophysiology of Heart Failure Using a Rabbit Model: From the Failing Myocyte to Ventricular Fibrillation](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/article?id=10.1371/journal.pcbi.1004968) in [PLOS Computational Biology](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/). Previously, I had published an article [Simulation methods and validation criteria for modeling cardiac ventricular electrophysiology](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0114494).


Both papers use a large-scale model of electrical conduction in the heart. The PLOS ONE [paper](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0114494) addresses the question of verification of a whole heart electrophysiology model: what reality criteria does a model have to meet? We propose a series of these, and describe a model that satisfies them.


The PLOS Computational Biology [paper](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0114494) develops this model, and creates a version modeling the electrophysiology of heart failure. We show that the altered cellular conditions known to be present in heart failure predispose the heart to a greater risk of ventricular fibrillation, the leading cause of sudden cardiac death.


See also Xie, F., Qu, Z., Yang, J., Baher, A., Weiss, J. N.,   Garfinkel, A. (2004). [A simulation study of the effects of cardiac anatomy in ventricular fibrillation](  https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC351312/). The Journal of Clinical Investigation.


**I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did examine sex as one of more than 700 potential predictors of progression from MCI to AD. However, our analysis was not designed to identify every possible predictor of MCI-to-AD progression but rather to identify a small number of predictors that, when used together, maximized the accuracy of the prediction. The best performing model incorporated scores from cognitive/functional assessments and structural MRI measures and predicted progression with 80% accuracy. Although sex may have an effect on the rates of cognitive and functional decline, as suggested by Lin et al. (2015), our analyses did not identify sex as a unique predictor that added significant predictive information over and above the other included predictors. It's possible that the effects of sex are already in part reflected in the cognitive / functional assessments and brain MRI measures that were selected as predictors in our model (i.e. predictive information provided by sex may be redundant). Alternatively, it's possible that sex was not identified as a reliable predictor of progression in our study because we used a different dependent variable than Lin et al. Because we used a binary outcome variable (clinical diagnosis of progression or no progression from MCI to AD dementia), as opposed to a more fine-grained outcome variable such as scores on a specific cognitive or functional assessment (e.g. ADAS-Cog, CDR) as used by Lin et al., our approach may not have been sensitive enough to identify sex as a predictor of progression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your comments/question.

Several research studies have examined the utility of cognitive tests, brain imaging, and blood and cerebrospinal fluid biomarkers for predicting the progression from mild cognitive impairment (MCI) to dementia. No single test or biomarker has been shown to have very high predictive accuracy, and it is likely that a combination of different types of tests/biomarkers will be necessary for accurate prognosis. When we wrote the article, other researchers who analyzed the ADNI-1 dataset reported models with prediction accuracies of 65-80%, depending on what biomarkers were analyzed, how long the time frame for prediction was, and the analysis methods used. MCI has been viewed as a transitional "at-risk" stage in clinical practice, but just using the diagnosis of MCI to predict the development of future dementia or AD is not a reliable approach. To my knowledge, no test for predicting progression to dementia has been widely used clinically. Accurate early diagnostic (or prognostic) approaches are critical in the fight against Alzheimer's disease (AD). The research community has shown convincing evidence that AD likely begins at least a decade (and likely longer) before the onset of symptoms. By the time a person with AD starts to show symptoms, there are significant, irreversible brain changes. Therapies for preventing and/or slowing down the degeneration caused by AD are likely to work best when initiated early in the disease course. Certainly, the tests must be reliable enough to identify with high accuracy people who will likely develop AD or dementia (so that they can be treated early). However, ideally, the tests should also not falsely identify healthy people as having AD or an increased risk of developing dementia. AD therapies, as most treatments, may have side effects and should probably be limited to people at high risk for developing AD based on accurate prognostic / diagnostic tests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your question. Regardless of age, all of us experience moments of forgetfulness at times (e.g. misplacing the keys or forgetting a person's name). However, if the episodes of "forgetfulness" are becoming more frequent and bothersome, and in particular, if a person's function is affected by the forgetfulness (activities of daily living such as doing finances, remembering appointments, driving, shopping etc.), an evaluation by a doctor may be necessary. Neuropsychological or cognitive tests can be used to formally assess a person's cognitive function in various areas (memory, attention, language, visuospatial function), as compared to healthy people of similar age and educational level in order to determine whether there is cognitive impairment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your excellent questions!

1. The progression rate from mild cognitive impairment (MCI) to Alzheimer's disease (AD) varies with the type of MCI. Specifically, people with amnestic MCI who have memory loss develop AD at a greater rate than those who have non-amnestic MCI (where the predominant cognitive deficits are of the non-memory type, e.g. attention, language, visuospatial function, etc). In our study we analyzed data from the Alzheimer's Disease Neuroimaging Initiative (ADNI), which recruited people with amnestic MCI within a research setting and generally from specialty memory disorder clinics. People with MCI in research- or specialty clinic-based settings tend to have a greater rate of progression (7-15% per year) as compared people with MCI living in the community (3-8% per year in some studies). Thus, the group of people recruited in the ADNI and other similar studies tends to be enriched with people at greater risk of developing AD. Thus, there is a limitation in generalizing the results from our study and other work based on ADNI data to the larger population. For various reasons described in our paper, we also did not include every person with MCI from the ADNI dataset in our analyses. Thus, the overall progression rate from MCI to AD cannot be estimated based on the data we used in the paper.

2. Our model for predicting which MCI patients will progress to AD dementia was most accurate when using cognitive and functional assessments (i.e. paper-and-pencil tests) and a brain MRI scan. In the clinical setting, AD and MCI are diagnosed using a medical history, physical and neurological examinations, and neuropsychological testing. Some version of cognitive/functional assessments and a brain MRI scan are generally already obtained by a neurologist or psychiatrist as part of the evaluation of cognitive impairment, so there should be limited additional cost associated with obtaining the data. There may be costs associated with the software to analyze the MRI scan or administration and scoring of the cognitive/functional assessments. However, our model and similar published models still need to be validated and translated into clinical practice -- they are not yet ready for prime time!

3. At this moment, the only FDA approved treatments for Alzheimer's disease are for symptomatic relief only. There are no approved treatments available that prevent or slow the progression of AD, but there are several ongoing clinical trials testing these new "disease-modifying" AD therapies. The use of the prognostic model would be to identify patients who are at greatest risk of progression to AD for participation in clinical trials. This type of prognostic tool is not quite ready for clinical practice yet. As far as informing patients and their families of the future risk of Alzheimer's disease, without the current availability of disease-modifying therapies, that's a highly controversial issue from an ethical standpoint. In some cases, knowing this information may help patients and their families plan for the future, but this issue must be considered on case-by-case basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your question, and I'm sorry to hear about your grandmother. Generally, research on the biomarkers of Alzheimer's disease (AD) has focused on older adults who are 60-90 years old, as is the case of the Alzheimer's Disease Neuroimaging Initiative, which collected the data we used in our work. The most common form of AD, known as sporadic AD (as opposed to familial AD), occurs rarely prior to age 65, and its risk grows with increasing age. Thus, research studies attempting to identify biomarkers and develop new diagnostic methods have focused on this age group. However, there is a growing recognition that AD may begin a decade or more before the symptoms begin. Thus, there are increasing efforts to develop new diagnostic methods and to conduct preventative clinical trials in people who show no symptoms of cognitive decline but may be at risk for developing AD (e.g. genetic risk factors or based on early changes seen on brain scans or laboratory tests). This is a very exciting, rapidly developing but challenging area, and much work remains to be done on both the research and the clinical sides. One such clinical trial is the A4 study (http://a4study.org). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Igor and I developed a prognostic model that predicts the progression of mild cognitive impairment to dementia due to Alzheimer's disease over a three-year period  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 12:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Igor Korolev, and I am a resident physician in psychiatry at the [University of Miami/Jackson Memorial Hospital](http://uhealthsystem.com/locations/jackson) (previously a D.O./Ph.D. candidate at Michigan State University). My research focuses on using various methods such as neuroimaging and cognitive tests to develop novel approaches for the early detection of Alzheimer's disease (or alternatively for identification of people at risk for developing dementia due to Alzheimer's disease).

I am the lead author of a research article titled, ["Predicting Progression from Mild Cognitive Impairment to Alzheimer's Dementia Using Clinical, MRI, and Plasma Biomarkers via Probabilistic Pattern Classification"]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0138866), published in the journal [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/). This work was co-authored with my mentors, Andrea Bozoki, an academic neurologist, and Laura Symonds, a neuroscientist, at Michigan State University.

Mild cognitive impairment (MCI) is considered to be a transitional phase between normal cognitive aging and dementia. We used data from the Alzheimer's Disease Neuroimaging Initiative and computer algorithms (referred to as machine learning) to design a model for predicting whether a person with MCI will develop dementia due to Alzheimer's disease over a three-year period. Our model was able to predict future progression from MCI to Alzheimer's-type dementia with 80% accuracy using information from cognitive and functional assessments and brain magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) scans. The model utilizes widely available, cost-effective, non-invasive methods and can be used to improve patient selection in clinical trials of Alzheimer's disease therapies as well as to identify high-risk MCI patients for early treatment.

**I'll be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that we know of.  It appears to be perfectly fit for purpose!  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know from stomach content analyses that thresher sharks like prey items that aggregate in shoals (sardines and squids for example).  Since we have no evidence that the unique tail design has any other function than to hunt and locomote with, my suspicion is that tails and tail-slapping coevolved in response to the defensive schooling behaviour of their available/preferred prey. In this context we might consider tail-slapping to be an efficient strategy since thresher sharks are able to debilitate and consume more than one  prey item at a time (we observed up to seven).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weve been studying these sharks in their natural environment since 2005.  From our 2000 or so hours of video observations, we have no evidence to suggest that they use their tails for anything but hunting and locomoting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tail-slapping of course!  In sharks, this behaviour is unique to the alopiids (thresher sharks) and might be considered interesting for a variety of reasons.  For instance, while we were analysing our video data, we noticed plumes of bubbles being released into the water column at the apex of the arc that formed the travel path of the tip of the tail for many of the tail-slaps that we observed.  Tail-slaps appear to occur with such force that they cause dissolved gas to diffuse out of the water column in a fluid dynamics process known as cavitation.  Unfortunately we were unable to report the intricacies of this process due to very valid points raised by our reviewers.  However, I remain convinced that localised explosions caused by cavitation play a part in the relative efficiency of this unusual hunting strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly.  It has indeed long been speculated that thresher sharks hunt with their tails.  In fact the first description of thresher shark hunting behaviour dates back to 1923 when Allen published surface observations that he made from a pier of what he thought was a common thresher coach whipping a California smelt in Science.  Decades later Aalbers et al. (2010) showed that under controlled conditions common thresher sharks were able to make contact with tethered bait using their caudal fins. While it has been suggested that bigeye and pelagic thresher sharks employ similar methods of hunting to those described for common thresher sharks, the kinematics that structure alopiid predatory behaviours in the wild have not been previously documented. The novelty of our paper stems from the analyses that we undertook of thresher sharks interacting with natural prey in the wild.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Simon and I discovered that thresher sharks use their tails to hunt prey and published the results of the study in PLOS ONE  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 12:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Simon Oliver](https://www.chester.ac.uk/departments/biological-sciences/staff/dr-s-oliver) and I am a marine ecologist at the University of Chester. My research focuses on using integrated approaches to understanding animal behaviour in the context of their use of habitats, ecological services, cooperation, and predator-prey interactions. I am particularly interested in the behavioural ecology of oceanic sharks in response to their cleaning, hunting, and migration strategies, and applying associated behavioural knowledge to address conservation issues.

I am the lead author of a 2013 paper in PLOS ONE titled [Thresher Sharks Use Tail-Slaps as a Hunting Strategy](http://dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0067380). Unique to their taxa it has long been suspected that thresher sharks use their tails to corral and stun their prey. Although some empirical evidence for this unusual hunting strategy has been quantified from controlled experiments, descriptions of the behaviour and its association with the capture of live prey have remained vague. While we were studying the cleaning ecology of pelagic thresher sharks in the Philippines, my co-authors and I came across a site where they could be regularly observed hunting sardines. Knowing that we had stumbled upon the Holy Grail of thresher shark behavior, we designed a simple set of experiments show beyond doubt that thresher sharks really do hunt with their tails.

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything!

Dont forget to follow the [Thresher Shark Project](http://www.threshersharkproject.org/TSRCP/Home.html) on Twitter [@s_tsrcp](https://twitter.com/s_tsrcp).

Watch a video of thresher shark hunting strategies in action: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OA98bN7mxjw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> crickets... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used to get free coffee at Wistar but they even took that away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very good question.  Most of the OAS Abs in the PLOS Pathogens papers inhibit virus replication in vitro (in cell culture) which indicates that they act independently of ADCC.  But ADCC might play a role in vivo, and this could be experimentally addressed with Fc receptor knockout mice, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your username--catchy.  Most people are infected with influenza viruses ~ 3 years of age, and these early infections shape the way our immune systems respond to other influenza virus strains for the rest of our life.  Since you are in your 20's, your first flu encounter was like in the late 90s/early 00s.  It is likely that B cells primed 20 years ago will be recruited against new influenza virus strains that you are exposed to today, even though these new strains are quite different from the strains you were first exposed to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CYD-TDV vaccine appears to have different effects in different aged individuals, and this likely is due to differences in past flavivirus exposures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See answer above. You would need a really big 'at home booster kit'...probably not practical... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think genetic vaccines show a lot of promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically, it would probably be a good thing to include more viral strains in flu vaccines.  But it is impractical to include more than 3-4 viral strains.  It takes a long time to prepare each vaccine strain, and it is not possible to vaccinate with too many strains.  For example, imagine each vaccine strain is delivered in 1 teaspoon.  Now, multiply that by 1000.  That is a lot of teaspoons!  We can't vaccinate people with 1000s of teaspoons.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good question--a question that people ask me a lot.  There is a finite amount of antigen that can be included in annual flu vaccines.  If we put every viral strain in the vaccine, then each antigen would essentially be diluted to accommodate all of the strains.  These diluted antigens would likely not elicit a good immune response.  If we increased antigens amounts x1000 fold in flu vaccines, there would likely be increased inflammation, etc.  So, the best option is to include a decent amount of antigen from a few strains, rather than a little bit of antigen from many strains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flu vaccines usually provide some protection even in years where there is an antigenic mismatch between the vaccine strains and circulating strains.  Mismatched vaccines might not fully prevent infection, but they usually limit viral replication and prevent severe disease.  I receive my flu vaccine every year, even in years where the vaccine strain is not completely 'matched' to circulating strains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Scott Hensley and I recently published a study showing that antibodies with the original antigenic sin phenotype are an important component of immune responses against influenza  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Scott Hensley and I am an Associate Professor at the University of Pennsylvania. My research focuses on how our immune systems try to stop pathogens and how pathogens fight back. At our [lab]( https://www.wistar.org/our-science/scientists/scott-e-hensley-phd), we are particularly interested in figuring out how viruses evade antibody responses.

We recently published a study titled [Antibodies with Original Antigenic Sin Properties Are Valuable Components of Secondary Immune Responses to Influenza Viruses](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1005806) in [PLOS Pathogens](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens). In this study, we used a mouse model to show that antibodies stimulated by past influenza virus infections can help fight against new antigenically distinct influenza viruses, despite binding poorly to these new viruses. We propose that these antibodies, classically termed original antigenic sin antibodies, are an important component of secondary immune responses against influenza viruses.

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Me Anything!

Dont forget to follow our lab on Twitter [@SCOTTeHENSLEY](https://twitter.com/SCOTTeHENSLEY). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] That sounds like an interesting problem. Do the bats interfere with your lectures? I can imagine they would be distracting. I don't know of strategies to drive bats away -- could you close off the lecture theatre when the bats are out feeding at night, so they have to find alternative roosting habitat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
