<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5890</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookies: http://sallysbakingaddiction.com/2014/08/03/classic-peanut-butter-cookies/

The ganache was just 1/2 cup of heavy cream and 1 cup of semi-sweet chocolate chips. Place the chocolate chips in a bowl. Heat the cream in the microwave for 30-60 seconds until hot, and pour over the chocolate chips. Wait a minute and then stir together until smooth and silky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pasta especially stuff like lasagna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Pratt, Jennifer Lawrence, or Anna Kendrick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the general consensus on buying makeup on eBay? Bad idea?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I know I have a bottle of tea tree oil that I stopped using for some reason but I can't remember why. I'll still look into it though because I really like ELF products! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! I hadn't heard of using that as a primer before. I'll definitely read more about it. Thanks! 

The trick is simply to use a light dusting of loose powder all over after you prime, and then apply your foundation as normal. It helps keep you matte for a lot longer. You can also use a bit of powder to set afterwards too. I usually just do a bit on my t-zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'll definitely read about that one. I haven't heard of it before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'll look into it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Peanut butter cookies with chocolate ganache filling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's a good boy?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firefly!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drugstore pore filling primer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a drugstore pore filling primer. It doesn't have to be mattefying as the Wayne Goss powder before foundation trick is working wonders. I just have large pores and also some cracks/lines on my chin that I think are caused by past acne.

I have sensitive, combo, acne-prone skin and I think I read that pore fillers tend to lead to breakouts? 

The only "primer" I have used in the past is the Monistat gel which made my t-zone very shiny in just an hour or two. I am much more matte without it.

Hoping someone has a suggestion for me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't You Forget About Me - Breakfast Club </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I never even considered that. I get into "must cover EVERYTHING" mode and didn't think to just not put makeup there. That should work! I'm very blind without my glasses so I never take them off and no one should be able to see a discrepancy. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damp sponge/BB. I used to get so frustrated when my makeup would highlight my dry patches and flakes when I used my fingers to apply. The day I finally learned about using a damp applicator made me so freaking happy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear glasses and the spots where the nosepads touch my face get red and irritated when I'm wearing makeup (IT Cosmetics CC cream) but it's fine on a non-makeup day. What can I do or use to help with this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely use a waterproof mascara. My lashes go limp the second regular mascara touches them. Try jojoba oil for removing waterproof makeup. I have sensitive skin and eyes and the oil works great for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have combo skin and this makes me T-zone super, super shiny in just a couple of hours. I was constantly blotting throughout the day! I was really bummed it didn't work for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love watching the lava ooze!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was delicious leakage!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Chocolate molten lava cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you find Mini Eggs in that colour combo? I've only ever seen bags with blue, white, yellow, and pink ones.

Edit: I googled and these are the UK version. Never knew there were regional differences in colour!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
