<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're probably planning some type of cartel purge... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due process sure sucks in America...especially when clogging the courts to create an exponentially long backlog may not matter if Trump starts his roundup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Espero sinceramente que Mxico se fortalezca como pas, y el mundo se fortalezca ms para el futuro de nuestros hijos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct, but they can be issued directly to the immigrant via consulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole shit storm is nothing more than rhetoric banter. Some dipshit somewhere in office isn't getting laid enough, or has mommy issues, and wants to cry...plain and simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a last-ditch effort to keep the peace between immigrants who want to stay, and the new regime who wants them out. I presume, yes, that this new center will act as an intermediary between government agencies and the immigrants, helping to establish residency and get official documentation. 

Or, hell, maybe it'll be a place where people can vent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-technical glitches (those that are self-induced) are harder to fix.

As the saying goes, *stupid is as stupid does*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're really hellbent on keeping their problems on our soil.

Keep the ones who are making something of themselves, deport the felons and drug kingpins, problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico opens migrant defense centers at U.S. consulates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we actually have alternatives? Or is the press/political agenda tag team locking down the world as they see fit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada: No plans to clamp down at border to deter migrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm telling ya, we're going to be involved with some Cold War shit if we don't leave well enough alone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin: US uproar over Russia ties 'a witch hunt' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think the figures are a bit off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, remember that 50% of every move he makes has business implications. The other 50% is a conglomeration of guesswork and irrelevancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 220 civilians killed by strikes in Iraq, Syria since 2014: U.S. military </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought about renting a condo in Mexico City or further down into the Yucatan to use as a vacation home...I don't imagine it would be higher than $500 a month... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His entire 3 years and 9 months left in office will be one giant scrutiny wrapped in a conundrum underneath a giant shit tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Country is too broke to back him on any wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ingenious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denial - it's not just a river in Egypt anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox is the only mouthpiece he has left, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Le Pen mightier than the sword here? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northern Ireland talks to begin after transformative election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explosive articles (or those with strong opinions rather than actual facts) are commonplace at The Atlantic. NYT and WaPo are two sites who pay their 'journalists' to attempt to persuade public opinion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer's definitely one of history's more 'colorful' frontmen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether or not we like it, Trump will eviscerate humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia expels North Korean ambassador after Kim Jong Nam murder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incompetency, given our country's current state, is actually good...never thought of it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean *Mein Kampf*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nervous? It'll get buried, unsubstantiated, or slid to the side by another scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, albeit dry and somewhat lacking rationale, have to give him props for trying to take the heat off Sessions   co. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, when you use spray-on tanning lotion and talk out your ass, public perception isn't going to be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's his own personal horse and pony show. I mean, I get that he loves media attention but despises what media stands for. What I don't get is why he's concerned about public opinion when he never really established a firm political position from the start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if there isn't some silent party out there intentionally trying to get him impeached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump, who we all know is politically inept, will be his own undoing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No chatter on RedState yet...plenty of brouhaha surrounding Sessions and the b.s. in Mexico, but haven't uttered a word over tapping allegations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Trump Tower is home to many other people. I imagine whatever sections of the building were tapped received some very unsettling conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's definitely adopted some 'interesting' political tactics thus far in office. I know his administration is crumbling before him, so why not concentrate on damage control? This sideways deflection crap isn't helping make America great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does he even care? That's like telling a ref he made a bad call two months after a playoff game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump alleges wire tapping by Obama during campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you are a Mexican native, right?

If so, you being in the U.S. means YOU favor U.S. over Mexico - or else you wouldn't have come.  :)

js... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian government says agenda agreed, seeks united opposition at next Geneva talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think most under 30 just want unity. Those of us over 40 just want to work, eat, sleep and die while having some semblance of fun between the chaos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if we did matter, don't you think the playing field would be a little more level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then again, who are we? Oh, I forgot, we're part of the 99% that doesn't matter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is my sentiment. 

Create a means to monitor those who come across, or attempt to, instead of creating an uncomfortable situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to clarify, I'm anti-illegal without a wall. I believe everyone deserves to bask in the American dream, provided they go through the same process Americans go through when leaving for another country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...then this conversation would never take place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, that's why I believe (just like Americans) that when you want to enter a country and live there permanently, a visa or something should be required. If seeking asylum, head to the embassy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 11:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...just not a good one in America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for you guys succeeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I think there needs to be some type of happy medium between America and Mexico, I do not think a wall is the long-term solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'd prefer a wall just never get built. There's always another way to skin a cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, knifegash, I believe anything is possible. Circumstances have dealt us all a giant shit sandwich we're all about to take a nice bite out of. Not just Mexico. Not just America. 

This whole fucking planet - from North Korea's bipolar leader to the mayor of Nome, Alaska - feel the pain of those who needlessly suffer, and it will take a synergetic effort to pull us out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Trump isn't exactly known for his political power. Give the man a few months, let's see how he adjusts and fixes the numerous fuckups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or they could simply band together and yank the wall down. I'd say 30-40 Dodge Rams with chains could easily yank a few sections down an hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree that drug kingpins (and their prized merchandise) will probably keep their stronghold on Mexico for years to come. I agree that it's government will continually be padded with endless money to keep military from storming strongholds more frequently. And I agree that your media will continually be bullied into printing whatever the fuck Los Zetas and Sinaloa members (et al) say to print.

However, maybe it's time the good people in Mexico grab bats, knives, guns, rocks or whatever they have and take their country back. A good 'ol purging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. But any gain is better than no gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what a wall is going to do besides cost taxpayer money.

Will it keep individuals from coming into America? For awhile, until Trump figures out he's pretty fucking lame for forgetting the fact people can take a boat and either enter through California, Florida, Mississippi, Louisiana, Alabama or wherever there's no wall.

Then you'll get *Berlin Wall: Part 2*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't care. I feel for the Mexican people. Do I think there should be a process everyone follows to get to live in America? Sure - it's how every country works. That process, however, shouldn't involve a wall.

Do I believe the undocumented workers trying to better themselves should be banished? No, I do believe they should be given 'x' amount of time to take a citizenship test and obtain papers, however...that's fair.

Do I believe undocumented residents who are committing felonies and flooding our jails/communities with drugs should be banished? Absolutely - they are not contributing anything to our society.

Trump doesn't know politics, but knows business. He will eventually meld the two together and make his four-year term work for everyone involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not defending anything the cartels do - I think they're the scum of society.

However, as stated, they do give their blood money to communities, a widely known fact that I simply highlighted.

Trump hasn't done anything yet, but trust this: he will. And Mexico will become a stronger nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sorry - Cialis didn't start working until well after I posted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it you know something relevant to this conversation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they'll go batshit crazy boycotting stuff.

What you're seeing now is an inexperienced politician who wants to make one country better at several dozen others' expense. His head will get screwed on straight, hopefully sooner than later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but since they stand to lose many of them, I'd venture to guess their only recourse would be to rally around their peso. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence? No. I'd take my chances with Tillerson before Pence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The peso has been down low enough to dissuade me from investing. Nothing I'm stating is baseless, and I'd never attempt investing. Common sense applies here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a stronger currency can only help an economy. Call this a rally or a prelude to a better future, Mexico is done fucking around with bullshit - they're about to make things happen down there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And could be talking his way out in two more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back Vincente!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slim's a telecom guy. Diversified or not, telecommunications investments aren't that stable outside the US. Sure, he's probably got his hands in many other ventures, but his bread and butter is telecom.

The Mexican stock market will probably hit some lows before rallying, my friend. Consider everything going on right now:

--threats regarding trade
--a fictitious wall
--immigration (which could flood Mexico with more mouths to feed than jobs to feed them)
--cartels (who, although are roughnecks, do take care of their communities) getting broken up

These all add both mitigating and aggravating factors to the peso's stability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That clickbait CNBC bullshit is unsubstantiated information. The reality is this: every baseless move Trump makes moving forward will simply strengthen the economy. 

The FED strengthening peso? Maybe giving it a little kick in the ass, but not the sole perpetrator behind it's rally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, however you look at it, the markets apparently believe the Mexican people will hold on strong despite Trump pulling jobs back into America, and trying to do whatever crazy shit he calls 'making us great again'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on who you're asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give it to August, it'll get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, true, but a strong indicator that Mexico's economy can sustain despite whatever agenda Trump may have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this countereffect was planned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they deserve to have a good life like everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live mas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico peso surges to strongest level since Trump election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree. A fucking joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela's epileptic patients struggle with seizures amid drug shortage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiting for my accepted ad to be reviewed, have changed start date 3 times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, it's agenda. Someone's agenda isn't being pushed across. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taxi app Uber loses UK court battle which could cost it London drivers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a greater agenda the world is unaware of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free speech, in any form of government, has it's limitations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more an ethics question than criminal matter. Which, indeed, lends itself to the question of why she's being ran through the cleaners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot say I blame them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why the UK would want to disband. Think the IRA is quiet these days, the Scots keep to themselves... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is no economic case for breaking up the United Kingdom, says PM May </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I feel for the EU people. I'd fight to get something like that put in your country's constitution, or at least lessen the impact of how free speech gets people jailed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey accuses Germany of providing succour to its enemies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le Pen is mightier than the sword... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit like this should be shared betwixt those who need the information, not on a social platform designed for those 13-25. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should probably start preparing for more outside interference, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revolt? Pfft.

People have a hard enough time staying out of bars and brothels to actually give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the children cry, let them know we tried...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's about the best summary I've heard yet.

It is really fucked up, but unless the entire European leg of the Reddit community plans on marching for her, there's not a fucking thing we can do but watch her ankles get grabbed and the proverbial cock of the law get shoved in raw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better question: who'll stop it from happening? Not a fucking soul. It's how the world is these days - change shit as you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the franc and lira are slightly outdated, so my best guess would be 10 pence per pound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For starters, France was always great. Then, the women started shaving their armpits and legs (finally). Of course, you have the Tour de France, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speech policing is exactly what Spicer has been trained to avoid. But seems to run head-first into every time he speaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EU is, indeed, a dirty player in the French election - Merkel being a huge part of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been following this whole Jeff Sessions thing? Trump's world is about to unravel - quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not always. Immunity is usually granted to those from another country acting as intermediaries (diplomats) between their home country and the country they currently reside in. Immunity is granted to ward off petty bullshit, generally. When it comes to genocide, murder, posting fucked up pics on Twitter, I guess that's where the line is drawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A-fucking-men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone sees a problem with this. We are part of the 1% that doesn't matter, apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. They need to ban Sharia-based grocery stores then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most laws are dumb, except for those designed to shield us from physical harm or loss of liberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems a pretty accurate subtitle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I presume you have a better one?

Didn't think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once her immunity was cancelled, her entire life (and any ensuing investigations) is open to scrutiny/investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le Pen may not need to do anything. I think she stirred up quite the shit storm without the need to go nuclear.

And Merkel? Her days are numbered. Germany will find a way to oust her and go back to the Hitler days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! Tea Party at my place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I figured. People don't want the truth, because they can't handle the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you conjure that? 

Fucktard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this is my take: don't shoot me, I'm just the messenger. The photographer should be the one to pay (if anyone). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a roundabout way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immunity is like a natural rite of passage for individuals. In some cases, you get immunity in exchange for testimony which implicates someone else. Or you get immunity for being a brown noser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Donald will more than likely plan a French tour based off the Brexit/Le Pen bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...with a Sinaloa cartel member who loves French ladies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing sits well with the French, hell, I don't think French people sit well with French people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desperate but effective enough to raise doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about that dude in Iceland bitching about pineapple on pizza? Surely that's worthy of impeachment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily happening to those of any particular color - we're being verbally reprimanded for existing. If anything, call it 'cultural genocide'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like they somewhat have in parts of North Carolina? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Censorship blinds those who need to know the truth from actually knowing it. By censoring a promising candidate and threatening legal action, they'll 'purportedly' put fear in the eyes of public interest groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See also Clinton's 'email scandal' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody wins when corruption runs rampant. Certainly not the citizens, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When gerrymandering meets reality...this is what you get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. But this is politics, a completely different ballgame altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting pictures of terrorism in action makes her seem like she's advertising (or lightweight recruiting) for the very terrorists she's determined to exterminate. Very, very fishy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They care about as much as Hitler did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independents will rise again. Hopefully, sooner than later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a completely different note, she looks like a closet porn star... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 yard penalty, election to restart at the spot of the foul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think we're more than likely looking at ethics violations here. 

But to answer your question, Tweet images of an American military member's splattered remains on foreign soil, and see what happens... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS killing people for no reason IS a big deal. They have no premise for their killings. They're simply murdering people because they think they'll push their retarded Allah propaganda down our throats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the holier than thou in our society need a means to shield themselves from the very laws they help lobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. It's really just a big fancy horse and pony show, IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd make Twitter culpable, too, in this scenario. And Daily Mail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le Pen doesn't favor blonde hair blue eyed individuals. She doesn't favor gassing the innocent.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then if this is the case, I presume Le Pen is being (or could be) indicted amiss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Islamic-induced tortures are now scientific/artistic depictions?

Man, that's pretty fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the world actually knows the true face of ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweeting news is one thing. Not sure if this situation encompasses proper ethos in media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's ideology is quickly spreading across oceans and borders. So yea, when some cock juggling thundercunt decides to tweet sketchy pictures, it does affect us all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent movie, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay a fine for tweeting pictures of real-world struggles? Oh she'll pay a fine alright - it's called Bertha, who'll be waiting for her to drop her knickers then pounce on her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In America, tweeting pictures of kids not fully clothed makes you a pedophile for a reason - it's sick, twisted and outside any realm of sanity. It's a justified reason to charge someone criminally.

With that in mind, Marine decided to Tweet pictures of horrific acts related to a very real worldwide struggle. Do I think she should be charged criminally? Abso-fucking-lutely. That's like giving a ISIS car bomber the keys to a fucking Ferrari and begging them to blow up an embassy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People never were in control of the government. Voting is a technicality... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a certain Russian president hellbent on disrupting the Democratic fabric, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Control to a point. Can't mute everyone because the upper echelon is constantly embroiled in scandal.

In terms of the Catholic church and whatever archdiocese chooses to speak on its behalf, fuck them. Fuck their skanky priests who fondled little boys and girls all these years. May they rot in the deepest, darkest pits of hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is the very subject I was referring to - FWIW, I wasn't trying to divert this conversation *completely* towards America's deep rooted political struggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like American politics is starting to circle the drain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't even think Trump would stoop that low.

Being radical is one thing, using social media as your platform of choice for spreading imagery is just plain retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have it good so long as outside influences stop padding the pockets of those in power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never old news to see another country's political system fall to scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a government purging will help matters here. I think, however, a better selection of candidates needs to surface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diplomats to 'x' countries do. Absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the entire country is being held down by the notion some fucktard who looks like Mr. Mayagi swallowed Psy is really that intimidating... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it was an insider pulling her immunity for her benefit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which tends to happen when the natural order of selection is disrupted. 

But then again, what do I know? I'm a fucking deplorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She COULD still win, if vindicated, but I cannot conceivably see anyone who's after her let her name make it to polls, let alone win outright. Someone (maybe even a constituent) has a boner for her, and won't stop until they've rammed the proverbial cock of the law straight up her brown backroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, shit. Just cut down the fucking Eiffel Tower and ship it to Greece while you're at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS is a well-funded band of psychopathic twat waffles. They have no idea what they're fighting for, they just know anyone west of them must die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even dictators can fall, lest we forget the Hitler regime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are free in the sense that we can enterprise, work, and pay taxes - as with any written doctrine, there's a limit on how free we are.

You can, in fact, be prosecuted for posting offensively online, albeit civilly. 

You can own a gun provided you have no violent crimes, (even if those crimes aren't gun-related) and are deemed mentally sound enough to use it responsibly.

Freedom of speech? To a point. Telling cops 'fuck you' was only recently decriminalized.

We DON'T import 'migrants'? They're killing infrastructure by taking over grocery, gas and hotel chains then dropping prices low enough to choke out the good 'ol ma and pa store.

Norway is actually sounding kinda nice right now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting how people (not necessarily anyone in this conversation) believe a president / PM / chancellor or leader in general actually run a fucking country. Their job is simple: smile for camera, read scripts or prompts, shake hands with similarly uninteresting ass clowns - basically they're like wingmen for their country's inhabitants without the work that wingmen actually do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there something different about Algerian cock? Why not French cock or (better yet) Lichtenstein cock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's this easy to strip immunity and prosecute the ignorant, why hasn't North Korea tried to oust Kim Jong Un? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but still not as bad as North Korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America. Hell, you couldn't remove a politician's immunity unless a major felony was committed. Le Pen just had her immunity stripped just so she could be questioned and (possibly) charged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 43, and haven't figured out the 'inner workings' of American politics. Between palms being greased and opposing parties crying 'foul', it's hard to judge what the end goal of any politician is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems a much easier process to remove immunity in EU countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. election this year is a prelude to what global politics will turn into: a giant pissing match that ends in someone being investigated for some non-existent scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm American. My European political insight ends at the Atlantic Ocean. I love to learn, however. I will then speak off what I've found.

Appreciate your insight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care about the very laws they intend to uphold? Theoretically, nobody cares about laws. Ethically speaking, at least someone should *pretend* to care if they wish to win an election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proof positive that honesty can work for you IF you let it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Sucks that she's another victim of twisted politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driver stops bus to prevent woman from jumping off bridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marine Le Pen loses EU parliament immunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PR. That's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thrill of being chased by guerilla fighters who think you're federal agents snooping around their territory is too much fun... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you've never seen the sequel...

Stay tuned. It gets interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American man claims hes the rightful king of England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada, U.S. join forces on tackling border asylum-seekers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tell myself that every time I fire up my Amazon TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an unfortunately reality, but yes, I (for one) pay Comcast (heftily). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we *do* fund immigration, loosely... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isil 'regrouping in southern Libya with support of al-Qaeda and preparing for further attacks' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could YouTube TV Mean the End of Cable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New justice plan: Flee into exile, lose appeal rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uber isn't uber cool anymore. Hate seeing the old school cabbies fading away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm....now that's an interesting angle. "Desperate Bing ad executive hires sniper to send warning to Google". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
