<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6464</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just asking her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting a New Printer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the 2020 election and olympics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Butthurt Alt-Right and Breitbart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately, Trump announced that he "will not prosecute Hillary" and "disavow and condemn" the alt-right. This has caused his supporters, Breitbart, and the alt-right feeling butthurt.

To understand why he doesn't want to prosecute Hillary, read the post "The Real Reason Trump Won't Prosecute Hillary." During the RNC convention and the nomination speeches, he announced that he will "lock Hillary up." He flip-flopped the prosecution due to the hardships Hillary faced in the race.

Recently, we see a video of a neo-Nazi group making a Hitler salute. On Monday, his team made a statement of disavowment and today, he made such a statement with his own words. I see that his rhetoric sparked a rise in alt-right but with this statement, many will split away from him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the PATH is Better Than MTA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to the Same Restaurant 3 Weeks in a Row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past three Mondays, I started to go to this Japanese buffet restaurant called Ichiumi at 32st in Koreatown.

The first time I went to Ichiumi was in mid-September, the restaurant only had cooked food. The place is large and have lots of food to choose from. It was $18.95, which I though was cheap as they have more than 50 items to choose from compared to only 10 item for $9.99 around Baruch.

On the first Monday of this month, I went there for lunch. Shabu-shabu is included in the lunch buffet. While I was getting food, my uncle approached me. My aunt, my uncle and aunt-in-law also came. They asked me if I come here every day, to which I said no.

The shabu-shabu includes seafood, noodles, vegetables, pork, and beef. It was fun to have this type of winter dish as part of the buffet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Reason Trump Will Not Pursue Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that, I meant psychic predictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Believing in Psychics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past year, I have been visiting websites from psychics. I believe that psychics can be accurate of what the future have in store.

Since Trump announced his run last year, I relied on psychics to see if he can win. Many of their fingers were pointing to Hillary.

One of the most reliable psychics was by the name of Jeanne Mayell. I like her website as she explained her predictions and her monthly readings. 

Recently, I am seeing a new update where we see what republicans are doing in 2017, i.e. scandal with Russia; a scene still grey snow, looking out the window, a phone call, talk with Russia at the White house; the White House talking, making deals with Russia in Feb. 2017, a donkey walking away lonely and defeated (democratic party) in Mar. 2017, Republicans trying to amend the Constitution, take away rights in Apr. 2017, hard times, fear, depression in May 2017, an important international, probably U.N. council takes place in Jun. 2017, vacations are down  people are too poor in Jul. 2017, tax issues  Trump making tax policy to lower taxes on the ultra rich, formalized in Aug. 2017, kids going back to school with the weight of the world on their shoulders in Sep. 2017, the prison system expanding and the latino illegal immigrants being pursued in Oct. 2017, new tax law created, not passed in Nov. 2017, and Capitol building glowing red hot with conflict, rage, asserting itself in Dec. 2017.

Stay tuned 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021 updates as they are vague.










 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Fire Drill at Baruch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiting For 10+ Minutes For a Train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday, I left college at 6:20pm and went to the train station to get home. While I was in there, I waited for 10+ minutes for a 6 train.

The first train skipped the station. When the next train arrived, I was so crowded that I had to take a seat to avoid the crowding. When I went to the 42nd St-Grand Central station, it took a while to get off the train.

Speaking of such situation, last Monday, I took the M train to Lexington Ave-52nd St station and transferred to the 6 train. The next train dispatcher said that the next train will arrive in 10 minutes. When the train arrived, it was crowded.

Sometimes, the 6 trains skip all the way to 14th St-Union Square. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Years Since The Closing of Handlebar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handlebar, a restaurant from Mount Sinai, NY, was owned by a formal construction worker by Billy. Malissa didn't want to be a chef, but she was offered the job.

On the day of the reopening, Billy walked out of the restaurant before coming back to finish the day.

In the revisit, we see that the restaurant is doing well. Shortly after the restaurant closed and became Skybox Restaurant and Sports Bar, which closed in 2011, before becoming Benchwarmers Tavern and Grill.

The owner Billy succumbed to cancer last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using #Notmypresident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Staying Loyal to The democrat party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I immigrated to the US in 2000, my family have been supporting the Democrat Party. I myself consider myself center-left to left wing.

When I came, President Bush was in office. I felt that he is not as radical as Trump. He did a shit job during his tenure.

From 2008, I became more interested in politics as America is having the first black president. In the 7th grade in intermediate school that I attended that was a few blocks from where I live, we were given a mock ballot. I myself voted for Obama. When the results were announced, the vice-principal announced that 95% voted for Obama, while 5% voted for McCain.

In school, we watched Obama's inauguration. I felt that the inauguration shows that the government is on the right track.

My parents voted for Sanders in the primary elections. I myself supported for Hillary.

Now that Trump will become the next president, I have been signing petition after petition to overturn Trump's policies. Tomorrow, I will call Senator Schumer directly to voice my concerns directly.

I hope the senate Democrats and senate Republicans can work to oppose Trump. I will always vote for Democrats no matter what is going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vowing to Vote in Future Elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why 2016 Was a Mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dislocated Shoulder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started swimming at 11:30am on Aug 10. When I started diving, I felt a twisting sensation and then pain in my right arm.

My dad and a guard pulled me up. I was laying on my belly for 20 minutes. My dad wanted to call an ambulance but I was reluctant to let him. When I was walking to the bench, I was screaming in agony from the pain. At 12:25pm, I got transferred to the ambulance by the medical team via a wheelchair. Getting on the ambulance was a hard thing az I felt the pain from my arm.
 
The ride was rocky. The arm hurts when the ambulance goes through an uneven section. We eventually arrived at the Presbyterian Hospital at 1pm.

While I was there, I got transferred to a hospital bed in the ER. I was given a shot of saline solution and then a shot of morphine. The morphine didn't make me drowsy and didn't cut the pain. 
 
At 3pm, I got transferred to the X-ray room. They took two scans. Later a doctor determined that it was a dislocated shoulder. Four doctors and nurses moved me to the right place so that another nurse can move the shoulder to the right place.

After relocating the shoulder, I got transferred to the X-ray room the second time. They took three scans before sending me back.

I received an evaluation. The nurse who fixed my shoulder told me that she prescribed me some painkillers. She also asked me if I have a job or school. I told her that I start classes by the end of the month. I was also instructed to call a number to schedule a follow-up. She gave me a cloth slung to replace the paper slung. When I change my clothes, I heard a popping noise from my shoulders, meaning that the shoulder fell back into place.

Ever since the shoulder injury, I started to drink notoginseng broth, which help with blood circulation. The first few days since the injury, lifting my arm hurts. One week since the injury, I can lift my arm halfway. Towards the weekend, the arm didn't hurt much when raising it, but the muscles close to the shoulder was stiff. Now, I can fully raise my arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will America ever have a female president? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing Hillary losing 2016, I have been wondering to myself, "Will America ever have a female president?" The answer is yes and no.

In the post "Why Hillary Lost," I have listed the reasons why she lost. It's not that America doesn't want a female president, but rather based on  policies and the past. In this case, Hillary doesn't have good policies and she is corrupt, i.e. Clinton kill count, where people who worked for Clinton die untimely attempting to expose the Clintons, collecting money for speeches, and bribes that go to the Clinton Foundation.

In another post "Who are the Likely 2020 Election Candidates," Elizabeth Warren is on the list. She is better than Hillary and currently in the senate to work with Sanders and Schumer likely to work with Trump. 

In the world, there are female leaders, i.e. Merkel, Indira, and Park. America is behind by not following this trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One-Term Presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I am an idiot, supporters of Clinton are idiot, and Trump is an idiot, does that mean that we are all idiots? The election was unpopular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. Sanders, according to GradeAUnderA, is like "a time-traveller from the future," i.e. back in 2002, where he criticized the Iraq War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: I found new videos supporting Clinton's hypocrisy and corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [fanart] [OC] Anpanman and Niyandar Kamen in GMod Style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 06:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://fav.me/dao4gie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: Trump is a secret democrat. Several news rise support this claim, i.e. only deporting criminal illegals, keeping and redesigning Obamacare, and giving funds to prominent Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the recent news, I can say that by 2020, the democrats can have a chance to reclaim the white house, congress, senate, and the house of representatives. Trump's policies would fail and alienate the working class and the middle class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the Likely 2020 Election Candidates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats:
Cory Booker,
Sherrod Brown,
Julian Castro,
Hillary Clinton,
Bill de Blasio,
Tammy Duckworth,
John Bel Edwards,
Al Franken,
Tulsi Gabbard,
Kirsten Gillibrand,
Kamala Harris,
John Hickenlooper,
Amy Klobuchar,
Chris Murphy,
Martin O'Malley,
Deval Patrick,
Bernie Sanders,
Elizabeth Warren

Republicans:
Ted Cruz,
Nikki Haley,
Dwayne Johnson,
John Kasich,
Tim Scott

Libertarian Party:
Adam Kokesh
Austin Petersen,
Jesse Ventura

Independent or unaffiliated:
Dan Rattiner,
Kanye West,
Evan McMullin

In this names, I see the mayor and governor of New York. If they become the last-standing nominees, I want Cuomo instead of de Blasio because de Blasio did a shit job as a mayor.

Kayne West will have no chance of winning after all. Michelle Obama is not included in the list as she dropped out early.

Elizabeth Warren is better than Hillary. She is a down-to-earth politician that we can depend on.

By the time 2020 comes, both Hillary and Trump would be too told to run.

Update: Data based on Wikipedia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. According to a psychic, in 2020 there will be another recession. According to Mother Jones, Elizabeth Warren, Tim Kaine, Amy Klobuchar, Kirsten Gillibrand, Kamala Harris, Tammy Duckworth, Cory Booker, Martin O'Malley, Chris Murphy, John Hickenlooper, and Michelle Obama is the candidates likely to defeat Trump in 2020.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Hillary Lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several reasons why Hillary lost.

One reason is the Emailgate. James Comey had affected Hillary significantly. The end was too late.

Another reason is her lies. She lies during her campaigns. Trump, however, speaks the truth, which nobody wants.

The third reason is the social dystopia. The Democratic Party caused all this recent dystopia, I.e. Black Lives Matter, Syrian War, ISIS, and South China Sea conflicts. During Benghazi, Hillary causes the deaths of four soldiers and the ambassador. The ambassador made several calls to her, which she ignores, to the point that he dies. 

The fourth reason is that she is not a strong political candidate. She dropped in 2008. She failed the bar exam. She was rejected from NASA.

The fifth reason is that she is corrupt. She received payments for making speeches. Various corporations have funded the Clinton Foundation. I made some small donations to her campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were right. Looks like a war is unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt excited. The supermarket trip was unexpected as we were picking up the food. It's was a good time because I can meet my new relatives-in-law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
