<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1334</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 00:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have more young players than we know what to do with. Adams is major league ready, we don't have a spot for him, and we won't for a while. But we need a SS. And Drew is not worth that much money. A trade is honestly the only thing that makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 23:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paying 10-14 mil/year for Drew would be one of the stupidest decisions the Cardinals have ever made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 23:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't God have stopped the people from persecuting them, so they wouldn't have to leave in the first place? God's a dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 15:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have. Pretty much everyone I've talked to thinks TSCC is bat-shit crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 06:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just frustrating because the characteristics of a cult list had nothing to do with Mormonism. I came to the conclusion that it fit Mormonism after looking at the characteristics. But then they say that "I need to look up what a cult is, because Mormonism isn't a cult and it's intellectual dishonesty to say that it is." I DID look up what a cult was and concluded that Mormonism was one. Apparently, it would only be acceptable if I read a Church sponsored article on how they weren't a cult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 04:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a chosen generation. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 04:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Except I'm not 18 yet, that's just what it's going to be in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 03:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. They CAN do much better. That doesn't change the fact that Stephen Drew is a significant upgrade over Kozma. Stephen Drew is not that great. There are better, but Drew is still lifetimes ahead of Kozma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 02:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So pissed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 02:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think the Rockies are not completely opposed to trading him like they say, but I do think they would like him to stay. And thus would take a lot to get him. More than I think we should give up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 19:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it is up to opinion. I think we both agree that Stephen Drew isn't great and Pete Kozma isn't great. It is up to the individual on whether Drew would be a significant upgrade. It depends on whether you want a worse (but still good defender) for better (but still not good offense.) I will say again I DO NOT want Stephen Drew and frankly, I would rather have Kozma for cheap than Drew for 10-14 million per year. There's no obvious answer to whether Drew provides a significant upgrade. As I said before, it's opinion and really is up to the individual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 17:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His stats, which weren't great to begin with, I agree, will most likely go down before they go up. I do not think, however, they will ever dip to Kozma's level in the near future, if ever. Signing Drew at all would be a mistake, but especially for long term. Whoever signs him will definitely significantly over pay. (Due to hype and lack of good SS both as FA's and on the trade market.) He is worse defensively than Kozma, but he is still a stellar defender and has a bat lifetimes ahead of Kozma's. Do I want him? No. 10mil (he will probably even get more than that) is WAY too much for a guy like Stephen Drew. My point is not in support of Drew, or the cardinals signing him. I don't think he's a great player and I hope to God that the Cardinals don't overpay to sign him. All I'm saying is he would be a significant upgrade over Kozma.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drew-
501 PA, 112 hits, 57 runs, .253 BA, 13 HR, 67 RBI, 29 doubles, 8 triples, 57 walks, 124 SO, .333 OBP, .443 SLG, .777 OPS, 196 TB, 6/6 SB 3.1 WAR 

176 PO, 332A, 516 CH, 8E, 82 DP, .984 FLD%, -2 DRS

Kozma-
448 PA, 89 Hits, 49 runs, .217 BA, 1 HR, 35 RBI, 20 doubles, 0 triples, 34 walks, 91 SO, .275 OBP, .273 SLG, .548 OPS, 112 TB, 3/4 SB, -0.2 WAR 

155 PO, 397A, 561 CH, 9E, 98 DP, .984 FLD%, 8 DRS 

Analysis- While Pete Kozma's defense does appear to be ahead of Stephen Drew's (especially in DRS), Stephen Drew's defense is still remarkable (although that -2 DRS is concerning), and he did have less errors in more innings played at shortstop. While Kozma has slightly more assists, he also has more chances, and Stephen Drew has more put outs on less chances, Still, I agree Stephen Drew has a worse glove, but he is still a stellar defender. Based solely on defense, Pete Kozma has a SLIGHT edge. On offense, Stephen Drew blows Kozma out of the water. It's not even close. The only offensive category Pete Kozma beats Stephen Drew in is strike outs, however Kozma had less plate appearances, averaging about 1 SO per .203 PA, whereas Stephen Drew averaged 1 SO per .247 PA. While Kozma still has the edge there, it's a lot closer than what it looks like at first glance. Based solely on offense, Stephen Drew had a SIGNIFICANT edge. 

Final thought- Stephen Drew is not an offensive machine. His numbers weren't that great (and they will probably go down before going up), and I don't consider him that great of an offensive player, and I DO NOT, I repeat I DO NOT WANT THE CARDINALS TO SIGN STEPHEN DREW, whatever team signs him will definitely overpay significantly for a player that is not that magnificent. However, he would be a HUGE upgrade offensively at shortstop without losing too much defensively. He is still a stellar defender with a bat lifetimes ahead of Kozma's. Do I want him? No. Do I think he's an incredible player? No. Is he better than Kozma? HELL YES. Would he be an upgrade for the cardinals at SS? A significant one. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would absolutely LOVE Jed Lowrie. I just don't know if the A's will be willing to trade him seeing as he's a central part of their team, and, if they are willing to trade him, because he is a central part of their team, they might over demand for him. But I have confidence Mo will find the RIGHT SS for the RIGHT price (Illustrated when he turned down the JJ Hardy for Shelby Miller swap. I would LOVE JJ Hardy. He's towards the top of my list. But Shelby Miller is too much. Right player, not the right price. I have all the confidence in the world in Mo.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would significantly. I just have a hard time seeing the Rockies not demanding too much for him. The Cardinals definitely have enough to get him, but I can't see Mo giving up as much as I envision the Rockies wanting for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could draft a shortstop, but we need a SS NOW. Not in a couple years. I'm confident Mo will find the right SS at the RIGHT price. He WILL NOT overpay (Stephen Drew) and he WILL NOT over trade (as he illustrated when he declined the JJ Hardy for Shelby Miller swap). I have all the confidence in the world in Mo. #Moforpresident  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, hope they don't sign him, but I disagree on your second point. He is a significant upgrade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. While he is good, whoever signs him will be overpaying and the Cardinals have the pieces necessary to trade for an even better shortstop. The trade market is definitely the way to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why I find this so funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 04:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Bautista would add to the team, he's a bit unnecessary. Especially for Miller and Wong. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 21:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lance Lynn for JJ Hardy- Yes 
Shelby Miller for JJ Hardy - No

IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 21:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did. So I guess their freak out wasn't completely unwarranted. However, shouldn't I be allowed to think for myself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually believed it when they told me that "polygamy was the hardest commandment Joseph Smith ever had to follow. He really didn't want to and it was really difficult for him."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My patriarchal blessing told me I was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine also said that "I would one day be in a position of great power and authority in the church and that I would need to stay humble during this time." Again, obviously that isn't happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine said "learning a second language is necessary for you while you prepare for mission" (or something to that effect.) obviously that isn't happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All it was was a screenshot of the list of characteristics of a cult. No subreddit, nothing but the list of cult characteristics. I had sent it to a friend saying "it's interesting how well Mormonism fits."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TBM parents freak out and say the church is NOT a cult. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 06:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing I had screenshot the article posted here earlier about signs you're in a cult and how well Mormonism fits, my parents freaked out. Claiming that I needed to look into what a cult is (what?) and that it's "intellectual indecency" (or something like that) because we both know Mormonism isn't a cult. (By this point I'm confused because I thought what I had been looking at was characteristics of a cult and no specific connection to mormonism; I just made the connection myself based on the characteristics. So was I not looking up what a cult actually was? Getting mad at me, but then telling me to do what I was doing?) anyways, they then Proceeded to claim that "cults have to shelter their members from the world to get them to follow" (Be in the world not of the world comes to mind). And that "cults don't have people working for Walmart and cults don't send the kids to public school"(again I say "what?") the whole time all I could think about was the characteristic of a cult on this list that said "they stop you from reading negative things about themselves." I just needed to vent. This sucks. Hold me r/exmormon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what happened to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 19:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Adams, Shelby Miller, and Kevin Seigrest (or Rosie), plus the possibility of another, is, IMO, too much to give up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 19:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lynn was always a plan to start. Wacha was in triple AAA when he wasn't starting because there was more room in the bullpen. Martinez was in the bullpen last year and he will be there again if he doesn't start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 17:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But as the Cardinals have shown over the last couple years if there's room in the bullpen they fill spots with potential starters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 01:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way Martinez will be in Memphis to start the season. If he doesn't win a starting spot he will be in the bullpen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for the memories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 01:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Chris Carpenter leaving has hit me harder than anybody else that has ever left the Cardinals. 2011 would not have happened without him and game 5 of the 2011 NLDS is still one of the greatest pitching duels I have ever seen. He remains one of the greatest pitchers to ever where a Cardinals uniform. He will be beyond missed. Thanks for the memories; there sure are a lot of them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 00:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if the Dodgers would pay enough of his salary (which they might to get rid of his contract) I think he could make a good fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 00:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they would need to pay half, but they would definitely need to pay some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 22:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would actually have to agree. The money he makes is a shit-load higher than what his production deserves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any chance the cardinals make the trade for Kemp or Ethier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 21:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 16:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Salt Lake City is Zion. He's trying to tell you that that's where you need to be. Don't you feel the burning in your bosom anytime anyone ever mentions Salt Lake City? It's the Lord's city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 09:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there is a good chance that this "unidentified source" is a mormon. However, there's probably just as good of a chance that it was a non-mormon acting irrationally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 09:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can say is try your hardest to get her the fuck away from TSCC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 08:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if Joe Nathan wasn't a free agent, this would be a terrible move by the Cardinals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 07:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this post on r/latterdaysaints and the comments were so fucked. It made me want to vomit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
