<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2846</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 01:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are one or two moves away from being serious championship contenders, and we are already in the WC semi finals. You could almost call this a practice run for next year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 18:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did she expect? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 turnovers between Aminu and Plumlee. Smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnovers. That's what killed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnovers killed us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hug accepted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, where are the fouls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some soulless warriors fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hurts to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No foul? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 07:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You poor soul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go to bed. Or whatever you are gonna do. When you look back you can either be happy, or look at it like, we'll it was a close one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offensive foul? Seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ye of little faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 fouls for GS in the paint but none for Aminu?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha true true. They have been getting some good calls in the paint tho. I think the officials like to keep that tempo up and won't call some resulting fouls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the Kings imploded like 5 years ago I stopped watching basketball, came back and decided Portland was my team. I'm rooting for the Kings tho, they are my second favorite and my first love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next season, I'm feeling it. Kings will make some good moves this off-season, 6th seed next year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you watching the same game? All I see is blue and yellow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Lillard gets going like this. Scary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you know how the rest of the league felt all season! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time playing, I am a GM for the first couple games. Do these story arcs work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am writing outlines for two campaigns, one in Edge of the Empire, one in Age of Rebellion.

EotE-

Episode 1. Hired by a crime lord to find a crashed ship and bring it back, and can either steal the lucrative freight outright or plan to grab a ship a little later. you will have to deal with local looters and scavengers and possibly the npc part of the crew you came to do the job with.

Episode 2: Depending on which way it goes, you either need to smuggle the cargo to multiple space ports and sell it or take it up with the planetary governer and persuade him to pay you in return for destroying the illicit cargo instead of selling it and creating a problem on his planet. Destroy it, or try to sell it and collect the money from the governer. 

Episode 3: the entire arc ends in a big chase through space and planetary systems, and finally finishes with an attempted evasion using the kessel run.

AoR-

Episode 1: Rebel base on {planet} is being attacked. Launch counteroffensive and fight the imperials off the planet/moon. destroy or loot as much as you want.(I'm trying to keep this morally ambiguous to let the players decide.)

Episode 2: Directly after, sabotage a Tie manufacturing plant on some planet. This is kind of a stealth mission, but you can go in loud as well. Ultimately we will need to steal an imperial transport to escape.

Episode 3: Lastly, using this transport and some stolen storm trooper garb, enter a star destroyer, shut down the shields, and try to blow it up from the inside.

This is my first time playing and i volunteered as GM. Having read through most of the books, these missions don't seem impossible, but i will have to scale the difficulty down on some of this stuff to work with my players. If these sound like they wouldnt work, let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am writing outlines for two campaigns, one in Edge of the Empire, one in Age of Rebellion.

EotE- 

Episode 1. Hired by a crime lord to find a crashed ship and bring it back, and can either steal the lucrative freight outright or plan to grab a ship a little later. you will have to deal with local looters and scavengers and possibly the npc part of the crew you came to do the job with.

Episode 2: Depending on which way it goes, you either need to smuggle the cargo to multiple space ports and sell it or take it up with the planetary governer and persuade him to pay you in return for destroying the illicit cargo instead of selling it and creating a problem on his planet. Destroy it, or try to sell it and collect the money from the governer. the entire arc ends in a big chase through space and planetary systems, and finally finishes with an attempted evasion using the kessel run.

AoR- 

Episode 1: Rebel base on {planet} is being attacked. Launch counteroffensive and fight the imperials off the planet/moon. destroy or loot as much as you want.(I'm trying to keep this morally ambiguous to let the players decide.)

Episode 2: Directly after, sabotage a Tie manufacturing plant on some planet. This is kind of a stealth mission, but you can go in loud as well. Ultimately we will need to steal an imperial transport to escape.


Episode 3: Lastly, using this transport and some stolen storm trooper garb, enter a star destroyer, shut down the shields, and try to blow it up from the inside.

This is my first time playing and i volunteered as GM. Having read through most of the books, these missions don't seem impossible, but i will have to scale the difficulty down on some of this stuff to work with my players. If these sound like they wouldnt work, let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 11:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, some of the refs coming out and saying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 11:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, and I picked a different team coming back. I was dating a girl from Portland and it stuck, forgive me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 11:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why an entire generation of Sactown kids hate Kobe. I watched that series when I was 9 years old.  Ripped my heart out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 11:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so true! The CPU becomes amazing regardless of how good you play. It makes no sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 08:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhhh. Yeah, he is. He is like 300 votes away from the nomination, she needs like over 600. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 07:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all started playing by street rules on that last play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plumlee has been decent though, give him a stronger wing player and he could really lock down the middl, especially if you made him put on like 15 lbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear out room for KD??? Who would have to be made into a power forward, but I mean is that a stretch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are young though. Also, Bronnie has a fat contract that he is going to sign and yall need to free up some space. In all reality though, yeah, that trade would suck ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but there have been plenty of volume shooters who have paired up before with a lot of success </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way. KD to Portland. He is the missing piece! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take Crabbe, Aminu and a first round pick next year. We fill in the open 3 spot in free agency and the draft for our backup 3/4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of finesse required for those trades doesn't exist in Sactown. I grew up with the Kings, I wish We could get Paul George and Boogie on the same team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, between Bledsoe and knight I kinda figured it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jefferson looks like he is going to stick around though, he said he would sign for less like Lin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either way, take Rondo and you guys become at least a contender for the 8 spot, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A solid 1 and 2. Fill in the gaps along the way! The for sure need at least a 2 with Kobe gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horford is unrestricted this year, he is smaller but might be a good fit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would actually be a good move. Who is the Knicks 2 though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DeMar comes this year, westbrook next year? Who do the Lakers even have any more? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your "realistic" dream team going into next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am hoping we might be able to move some players around and get KLove in Portland. Or maybe Durant, but I just don't see that happening realistically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 07:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every game, regardless of how much better you are, ends up coming down to the last 2 minutes. Up 18 at the end of the first quarter? Doesn't matter, you will shoot 15% through the second and be downice by 2 at halftime. Build up an incredible lead? Your opponent will suddenly go on an 11-2 run that puts it within reach at the start of the fourth quarter. It doesn't matter how open you are, you will always miss that wide open 3 to go to double digits if you are under 2 minutes. Hell, you could take 10 wide open 3'source and you would still only make 1 or 2.

If my team is dominant, the worst team in the league should not be able to keep up with me, especially without a star player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 09:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but they are sold out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 09:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Idk, feels less illegal I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you can't find a copy of the Core Rulebooks ANYWHERE... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 08:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 04:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it tastes anything like ch mate? Also, ever tried Guaran Jesus? That pink stuff is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta problem with my subpar internet?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lag tho..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 09:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/LdP0Oew.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 07:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really though. Major respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 07:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clippers played tough as nails, but how about them Blazers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 04:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kings way. Geez, get rid of any talent we have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I know that, but can I get a source, because when I looked all I found was state laws that decide. And I was threatened with immediate termination if I discussed my salary with other employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in all states though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 07:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys were the favorite in both games though! Last night's Portland was under 3.5 too, so you have been pretty close all series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 06:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good man. Honestly it's a bummer that CP and Griffin both got hurt, this series was going to go 7! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 06:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one more day and you can bandwagon for them too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If success is a broken hand, then you chose right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the teams to bandwagon, you chose the Clippers?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is! He just has a sense of humor about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 09:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God is a blazers fan, simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 09:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 09:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a kid in Sacramento when that team played. The only thing worse than watching the kings implode after that season was watching the Lakers win the Western Conference Finals after paying off the flippin refs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 09:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sudden moment of realization.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 08:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but they were Blazers fans so.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 06:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they don't. He said on a blog that they were making a movie and video game out of it, but I just don't think it would transfer mediums very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a sexy ass cow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are always welcome here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could let submissions happen every day, but make them for an entire week, and you will always be writing about the week before. You could do voting for the weekend, like pick top three from the week that got the most up votes, and then have them choose which one they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 17:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are good, it was more of a joke haha. For real though, I might be able to hook you up with some goodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 09:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can send you some fry sauce from utah?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Back in my day, our favorite musicians had an unpronouncible symbol instead of a name, and we liked it that way!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when was the last time these people listened to Kanye or Bieber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 09:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we judge them by today's standards, then yeah, it's messed up. But back then it wasnt viewed as it is today. It was manifest destiny, and America was going to possess the land, come hell or high water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 06:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And even had a hit with Paul McCartney! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 06:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you actually did tour with them, that would be real cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel on reddit most days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Here I come!" *slips* "rawwwww........ meh" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true. I
However, if Dame and CJ hit their shots, it would have been a lot closer, or even a victory but they couldn't get hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents live in Rocklin now anyways and claim it is a nicer place. I feel like Roseville us just a little scrappier from the low key hood around the high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO GOOD CLIPPER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate watching this series just because of this. DJ is a monster at the rim and it's driving me nuts how he is just swatting everything! We have no offense right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have two at home. No way we don't win those! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 08:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty relevant to the Blazers game as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 22:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always make fun of me for drinking diet soda, but if we are already eating a burger or a giant fatty ribeye, i don't want an extra 400+ calories in liquid sugar on top of that huge caloric hit I'm about to take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 08:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read it in a Mr.Burns voice haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that, a tower for ants?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 07:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a great coach. Seriously, can't they just make an award for this guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to restart the app at every break. I wish they would just make a chrome app or fire TV app go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between foul shots and time outs I watched like 40 min of commercials on the TNT app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he air balled like twice? other times he was close-ish. I mean at least he was consistently close. He just had an off night I think, I bet they come back next game and he is a little closer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the teams are a lot closer than it seems. The double team on Dame shut down the perimeter offense, and DeAndre in the paint shut down the drives in the paint. Blazers did well midrange, Harkless and Henderson played well. If Aminu can shoot from the 3 more consistently or if they can get Crabbe open on the 3 line, the offense opens up and this series goes 7 with a toss up.

If every game goes like last night, it will be a long (albeit short) series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't get ugly until the third quarter though, so we have that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was 2 for 10. Just about as bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 07:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their roads suck but there is a toll booth every 15 miles! It makes no sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 07:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing with that real conservative bunch is that they want medicaid and Social Security and school districts but they don't want to put up the cash for it. They argue about social programs but refuse to fork over the money to house the homeless vets and fix the VA. 


*Disclaimer* Not all conservatives are this way, just those real fickle ones who seem to be running the GOP right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 05:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 21:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your are either mauled then torn apart piece by piece while clinging onto life until your skull is crushed, or thrown into a pit of tigers. I'd take the tigers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 21:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roll towards the attacker, 2 hits and pow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 21:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I didn't like was that they could have climbed a fence and gotten out of there. I would take a pitbull over a bunch of angry Mexican gangsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 20:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That game got so much easier when I discovered quen. The only thing I don't like about it is the roll. You roll too far away and can't really counter attack really quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 20:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 percent yes. Although it will be subtitled, it is great and worth the watch. Definitely a different pace and story than narcos though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
