<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8219</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CEO import and export vehicle. Its good. Costs $1.5 million for the garage but ive made that back already ! Get top end cars its  $100k a time for about fifteen minutes grind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in 1980 and remember seeing thalidomide victims around, what a truly horrific medical catastrophe to prescribe it to pregnant women. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And can you choose to play as her ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which games have the best female protagonist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since early gaming i have always chosen to be the female characters. As far back as Streets of Rage and Golden Axe. Right up until GTA Online now.

What other games have fantastic female characters ?

(Tomb Raider is obvious) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1408 is a brilliant head twisting film.

Don't know if anyone else could relate,  but sometimes on higher doses of LSD (I took it quite a lot in the 90s), you would get locked into thought and hallucination loops where you would feel like you were experiencing the same thoughts and visions over and over again. 1408 gave me that same feeling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's the snuff movies that make it head fucking. Sinister 2 was utter shit though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favourite films. Both versions. But yeah it is weird as fuck ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A journalist and his attorney attend conventions in Las Vegas. They take some drugs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love old boy one of my favourites ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredibly misogynistic. "I couldn't have her so nobody else should" is every wife beater and woman killers justification and motive.

 The story did have the inconsistency mentioned above!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Lancashire was going to say that's a pasty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like playing public sessions too....just for CEO work its better alone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in a very modern apartment. Hated the community. Full of douchebags. Ended up the only positive was the place was very modern and decorated well.

Moved to a more dated property (textured wallpaper in every room). 

The lesson I learned was apartment living is not for me. And that the best most modern decor means nothing if you are surrounded by imbeciles that like to cram as many people into their small property to blast out club music, completely disrespecting the 40 other apartments that want peace 

Tl;dr - go for a less stylish house in a better area than a more stylish house in a worse are.

Yes it's true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One little squeaker to me "i banged your mom"
i replied "i better tell my dad then he won't be happy"
He then replied "sorry that was my cousin messing about"


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think i wasnt replying to myself. Split personality disorder is a thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i can totally relate. Nothing worse than driving the full length of the map with a slow weed truck just to have it blown up by some douchebag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It annoys me you can't take weapons in...then get stabbed or pool cued to death.

For what it's worth i solo it every time and still do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally stocked up my vehicle import garage with top end cars, without the constant gauntlet of trolls in hydras and general douchebags blowing up your hard earned cars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes an empty lobby is just perfect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rockstar is a business.

$700,000,000 a year from online alone. That is good business.

Why would they want to end that ? The only time they will is when they are in a position to increase profit with GTA6. 

That is me being optimistic though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quite liked resurrection and made a million and a half in cash, levelled up 12 times and generally enjoyed it. 

This new one is meh. Didnt even bother finishing the three rounds it was so boring. No skill or strategy involved. It was like those pointless park our death matches but even less exciting. 

I do love the game and love that they still add content, but considering they make 700 million dollars a year out of online alone....i think they could do a bit more!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine they just show Team America World Police! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
